<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6780" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-03-06</startdate>
<enddate>2010-06-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Working!!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Работаю!!</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="synonym">Muncind</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Работа`!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">working</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">WORKING!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Wagnaria!!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">迷糊餐厅 WORKING!!</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8364" type="Sequel">Working`!!</anime>
<anime id="12059" type="Same Setting">Www.Working!!</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9798" approval="95" total="101">Servant x Service</anime>
<anime id="7569" approval="39" total="70">Soredemo Machi wa Mawatte Iru</anime>
<anime id="12694" approval="26" total="32">Blend S</anime>
<anime id="2165" approval="15" total="35">School Rumble</anime>
<anime id="5909" approval="9" total="29">Toradora!</anime>
<anime id="9466" approval="8" total="25">Hataraku Maou-sama!</anime>
<anime id="9659" approval="7" total="16">Yuusha ni Narenakatta Ore wa Shibushibu Shuushoku o Ketsui Shimashita.</anime>
<anime id="4777" approval="5" total="19">Lucky Star</anime>
<anime id="5720" approval="5" total="18">Kannagi</anime>
<anime id="10619" approval="2" total="5">Denki-gai no Hon`ya-san</anime>
<anime id="9153" approval="1" total="13">Sakura-sou no Pet na Kanojo</anime>
<anime id="10288" approval="1" total="8">Bokura wa Minna Kawai-sou</anime>
<anime id="6384" approval="1" total="5">Ristorante Paradiso</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="25">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="138173">Good laugh but the end was disappointing and Inami was the most annoying anime char I have ever see in any anime for 20 years now if it was a real person I would beat her till he stop breathing no joking.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="724513">Not very funny but extremely moe.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="393532">I love this anime! I don`t really have much else to say about it, except that I hope a second season will get green-lit.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="103294">Its a normal anime but its a good show..fun and enjoyable to watch. Characters are diverse and entertaining.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="424134">A really funny show, made me smile and laugh quite a lot. I sure hope they make another season. :-)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="264658">sweet, sweet anime... peculiar and funny characters, nice story, and just the right number of episodes.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="106859">This is quite a funny show.  It started of a bits slow for my taste, but it`s the type of show that just gets progressively funnier and funnier as it goes.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="384820">Truely an awesome amv. The plot might seem boring, but in reality it`s both exiting and extremely funny :) Animation and voice acting are great aswell, so don`t hold back on this one ;)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="177341">It`s hilarious, I can watch it many times. Good humour, likable characters, cute art -&amp;gt; my best series of season.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="264691">people said that the plot is too boring and plain but it`s still very interesting, hilarious anime. They build up a good comedy with original characters. Some are not well developing but i am looking for the season 2. Good anime, must see i guess.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="582739">Very funny and cute</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="625155">If you enjoy slice of life with hilarious comedy, then this is the show for you. I was smiling and cracking up every episode, whether it was due to Popura`s cuteness, or just the hilarious antics of all the characters.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="313575">One of the most hilarious anime I ever saw. I laughed from episode one to thirteen. Really worth it. Hope there more coming :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="416687">This show`s a good litmus test for how you view fiction.  People see the plot as anywhere from nonexistent to convoluted.  A lot happens and relationships constantly shift and evolve, but the story threads take relaxed, meandering scenic routes that may not even have a destination.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="373333">If you like comedy, you must see this anime. Hilarous!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="327549">One of the best comedy anime I`ve seen. It`d be better if it didn`t focus around that "ugly, violence, short hair, flat-chest girl " that much. 

 Yamada or Popura is thousand time cuter than her. Damn it T^T</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="417064">Relly good series. all the characters are funny and crazy. you`ll love the small Taneshima Popura.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.wagnaria.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="2149" type="Series Composition">Hiraike Yoshimasa</name>
<name id="1303" type="Work">A-1 Pictures</name>
<name id="2149" type="Direction">Hiraike Yoshimasa</name>
<name id="3020" type="Music">Monaca</name>
<name id="10051" type="Original Work">Takatsu Karino</name>
<name id="8899" type="Character Design">Adachi Shingo</name>
<name id="8899" type="Chief Animation Direction">Adachi Shingo</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr10051 [Takatsu Karino]`s 4-koma seinen manga by the same name, serialised in http://anidb.net/cr23601 [Young Gangan].
In a family restaurant named Wagnaria in the northern Japanese prefecture of Hokkaido, http://anidb.net/ch13559 [Takanashi Souta] works part-time among the restaurant`s high-spirited, mysterious, yet down-to-earth staffers.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="4402">7.04</permanent>
<temporary count="4434">7.66</temporary>
<review count="2">6.08</review>
</ratings>
<picture>32911.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11017</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6956</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4664</identifier>
<identifier>hrsghk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.wagnaria.com/1st/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Working!!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>WORKING!!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1885</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>336375</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12527</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>wagnaria</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="34">
<externalentity>
<url>https://ch.nicovideo.jp/working</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="204" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-06-19">
<name>violent</name>
</tag>
<tag id="235" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-05">
<name>waitress</name>
<description>A female attendant who serves customers in a restaurant, café, or similar.
Source: Wiktionary</description>
<picurl>163704.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="618" parentid="2565" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>trap</name>
<description>A trap is a plot device where a male character is mistaken for a female, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the male (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the male, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the male character as a female; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through his behaviour, and/or language. A male character misinterpreted by others as female, without action from the male (explicitly feminine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t1637 [reverse trap].
Note: the tag image is from http://anidb.net/a10475 [Himegoto].</description>
<picurl>161537.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1283" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-24">
<name>tsukkomi</name>
<description>A tsukkomi is a comedy duo stock character in a traditional Japanese slapstick stand-up comedy style known as manzai. Tsukkomi characters are the smart, reasonable, and down-to-earth half of the unit; their simple-minded counterparts are the http://anidb.net/t1399 [boke] characters. As a result of their boke counterparts` simple mistakes and gross exaggerations, tsukkomi berate and abuse them both verbally and physically; a very common example of tsukkomi physical abuse is a paper fan slap, which is generally accompanied by a sound effect. Their approximate equivalent in Western culture is the comedy role of straight man.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1446" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-15">
<name>energetic</name>
<description>An energetic character, often also called a genki character, shows great, often excessive levels of activity or vitality, and seems to always be doing everything extra fast. Genki characters are often slightly, or sometimes very, eccentric, and are filled with confidence and determination, regardless of whether they are competent or not; in fact, they often have little to no actual competence at whatever they generally do. Although genki characters are usually played exclusively for comedy effect, sometimes they may slow down for a serious or introspective moment. The most common genki character archetype is the genki schoolgirl, who will often be late to school and run with a toast in her mouth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2678" parentid="2672" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Hokkaido</name>
<description>Hokkaido is the second largest island of Japan, and the largest and northernmost prefecture. The Tsugaru Strait separates Hokkaido from Honshu. The two islands are connected by the undersea railway Seikan Tunnel. The largest city on Hokkaido is its capital, Sapporo, which is also its only ordinance-designated city.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214292.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2788" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-21">
<name>confession</name>
<description>Someone confesses his/her love to someone else.</description>
<picurl>160903.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2805" parentid="2798" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>4-koma manga</name>
<description>Yonkoma manga (4コマ漫画, four cell manga, or 4-koma for short), a comic-strip format, generally consists of gag comic strips within four panels of equal size ordered from top to bottom. (They also sometimes run right-to-left horizontally or use a hybrid 2x2 style, depending on the layout requirements of the publication in which they appear.) Though the word yonkoma comes from the Japanese, the style also exists outside of Japan in other Asian countries as well as in the English-speaking market.</description>
<picurl>70558.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2873" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>Valentine`s Day</name>
<description>Valentine`s Day is a festive day celebrated every February 14.
In Japan, South Korea, Taiwan, and China, Valentine`s Day is one month before http://anidb.net/t3147 [White Day], a celebration unique to those countries.
In the rest of the world:
On Valentine`s Day, both males and females will express their feelings of affection towards their loved ones, by exchanging gifts (such as cards, candies, and chocolates), going on dates, and other signs and actions of affection. Some people also take the opportunity to confess and propose for marriage. In Western countries, it is generally expected of the male to offer gifts to the significant other.
In many countries, friends and co-workers also exchange small gifts to show their friendship towards each other.
In Japan, South Korea, Taiwan, and China:
On Valentine`s Day, many women feel obliged to give chocolates to all male co-workers, except when the day falls on a Sunday, a holiday. This is known as giri choco (義理チョコ, "obligation chocolate"), with unpopular co-workers receiving only chougiri choco (超義理チョコ, "ultra-obligatory chocolate") cheap chocolate.
This contrasts with honmei choco (本命チョコ, "love chocolate"), chocolate given to a loved one.
Friends, especially girls, may exchange chocolate referred to as tomo choco (友チョコ, "friend chocolate").
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>160891.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3119" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-24">
<name>restaurant</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3147" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>White Day</name>
<description>White Day is a festive day celebrated every March 14 in Japan, one month after http://anidb.net/t2873 [Valentine`s Day]. People who received honmei choco (本命チョコ, "love chocolate", given as an expression of romantic feelings) or giri choco (義理チョコ, "courtesy chocolate", given as social obligation) on Valentine`s Day are expected to return the favor through gifts.
Traditionally, popular White Day gifts are cookies, jewellery, white chocolate, white lingerie, and marshmallows. Sometimes the term sanbai gaeshi (三倍返し, "triple the return") is used to describe the generally recited rule that the return gift should be two to three times the cost of the original Valentine`s gift.
While typically females give males of their social circles chocolate in Valentine`s Day and receive gifts in White Day, it is common for popular females to receive chocolate from other females and thus also give many gifts on White Day.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>160890.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3444" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>hot springs visit</name>
<description>An onsen is a term for hot springs in the Japanese language, though the term is often used to describe the bathing facilities and inns around the hot springs. Often the cast of a show somehow ends up going to an onsen because of various reasons, such as winning a lottery ticket. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters nude and raise the DVD sales.
Another cheap variant is the http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160784.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4228" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-09">
<name>subtle OP ED sequence change</name>
<description>A (small) part of the opening or ending sequence changes after a certain episode, usually to reflect a plot milestone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5805" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-06-11">
<name>post-credits scene</name>
<description>A little bit of the story is found after the credit titles. A little bonus for those patient enough!
This applies regardless of if the credits play over an ED sequence, or over the "regular episode" that continues to air into the credits.
A sequence at the end of an episode, showing what will happen in the next episode, is NOT a post-credits scene; that is a preview.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6088" parentid="2785" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-01-29">
<name>unrequited shoujo ai</name>
<description>At least one female character has a romantic or sexual interest in another female character, but the feelings are not returned.
This can be because the recipient is oblivious, straight, or simply not interested.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="13559" type="main character in" update="2017-09-13">
<rating votes="118">6.26</rating>
<name>Takanashi Souta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takanashi Souta is a high school student who was pressed into service at Wagnaria by Taneshima Poplar. Poplar keeps mispronouncing his name as `Katanashi`, and can never seem to say it properly. He is a self-described `minicon`, a person with an obsession with small, cute things such as children, kittens, hamsters, and water fleas, and as such is immediately charmed by the diminutive Taneshima.
Since he is the only boy in a family of five, he wound up wearing many of his sisters` old clothes as a child, and as such harbors deep insecurities about his masculinity. He arguably allows Inami Mahiru to keep hitting him as this works as affirmation for his manhood.</description>
<picture>39732.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13560" type="main character in" update="2014-09-30">
<rating votes="188">7.49</rating>
<name>Taneshima Popura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Taneshima Popura is a waitress at Wagnaria, and the first employee of the odd restaurant that Takanashi meets. While she is a year older than Takanashi (who calls her `senpai`, as she is his upperclassman at the same school), she is very small for her age, and is too weak to perform some of the menial tasks at the restaurant. She does not take kindly to remarks about her small size, even when they are meant to be complimentary.</description>
<picture>39733.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13561" type="main character in" update="2010-06-28">
<rating votes="215">6.19</rating>
<name>Inami Mahiru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Inami Mahiru is a waitress at Wagnaria, who harbors a deep fear of men, and will involuntary hit any man who comes too close to her. She is also freakishly strong despite her willowy appearance. Since Takanashi Souta started working at Wagnaria, she has been hitting him more frequently than others, a risk he takes so he can cure her androphobia.
[SPOILER]It turns out that Inami`s father is to blame for her behavior, since he brainwashed her into fearing all men and placed extra weights in her schoolbags which gradually increased her strength.[/SPOILER]</description>
<picture>39734.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1673" picture="41835.jpg">Fujita Saki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13562" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-02">
<rating votes="129">6.53</rating>
<name>Todoroki Yachiyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Todoroki Yachiyo is a waitress at Wagnaria. She has a strange obsession with Kyouko that began when they were children, and will do anything she asks, which usually means making her a parfait or some other food. She will not tolerate anyone who even seems to make advances that may take Kyouko away from her, and will readily threaten someone inopportune enough to do so with her katana, which she carries at all times.
Satou Jun seems to like her, and she seems to like him best among all of her male co-workers, but her obsession with Kyouko makes any progress between them unlikely.</description>
<picture>39735.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13563" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-09-13">
<rating votes="109">5.92</rating>
<name>Shirafuji Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shirafuji Kyouko is the restaurant manager of Wagnaria. She is almost never seen doing any useful work, except to call on some mysterious people to shake down ruffians who foolishly attempt to leave the restaurant without paying. She is a childhood friend of Todoroki, whom she once saved from bullying, but that seems to have mutated into a strange obsession, but Kyouko seems as oblivious to this as with almost everything else, content to receive Todoroki`s service as it is given.</description>
<picture>39736.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3130" picture="186156.jpg">Watanabe Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13564" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-01">
<rating votes="119">8.29</rating>
<name>Satou Jun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Satou Jun is one of the cooks at Wagnaria. He is usually silent but can be very blunt when he is forced to speak. He has an unrequited love for Todoroki Yachiyo, and is frustrated by the fact that she seems to be warming up to him but will not let go of her obsession with Shirafuji Kyouko. He is also a heavy smoker.</description>
<picture>39737.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13565" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-01">
<rating votes="78">4.98</rating>
<name>Souma Hiroomi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Souma Hiroomi works as a cook at Wagnaria. He attempts to find the secrets of everyone he comes into contact with, and does not seem comfortable associating with anyone he cannot dig enough dirt on to blackmail. He has occasionally used his knowledge of many of his co-workers` most intimate secrets to get out of unpleasant chores at the restaurant.</description>
<picture>39738.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15258" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-02">
<rating votes="83">7.35</rating>
<name>Takanashi Nazuna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nazuna is the fifth and youngest of the Takanashi siblings, but despite her youth she is easily the most mature and reliable one in the family. She is tall for her age, nearly as tall as Souta.</description>
<picture>43585.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="476" picture="23579.jpg">Saitou Momoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15259" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-02">
<rating votes="54">5.87</rating>
<name>Takanashi Kazue</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takanashi Kazue is the eldest of the Takanashi siblings, and works as a lawyer. She is a no-nonsense type and is exasperated by the behavior of her siblings, especially of Kozue and Izumi.</description>
<picture>43586.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="208" picture="20458.jpg">Shiraishi Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15260" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-02">
<rating votes="66">4.87</rating>
<name>Takanashi Kozue</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kozue is the third child of the Takanashi family. She is an alcoholic and always seems to be in and out of relationships, but it is unclear whether she drinks because she can`t keep a good relationship, or her boyfriends dump her because she drinks too much.</description>
<picture>44883.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15261" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-02">
<rating votes="71">6.29</rating>
<name>Takanashi Izumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Izumi is the second child of the Takanashi family. She is supposedly a novelist, however, she appears to be suffering from perennial writer`s block and doesn`t seem to have written anything of significance in a very long time. The fact that she doesn`t move, not even to clean her living space of her failed attempts at writing, and even considers standing up straight to be too much of an effort, is a running gag.</description>
<picture>43588.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15957" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-01">
<rating votes="28">2.76</rating>
<name>Otoo Hyougo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Otoo Hyougo is the general manager of Wagnaria. He is frequently absent from the store, always on a trip to supposedly find his lost wife, whose appearance he cannot seem to remember clearly. He picks up various odds and ends that remind him of her on his trips, and always brings Shirafuji Kyouko various presents (usually food) to keep her pacified.</description>
<picture>44880.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15958" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-01">
<rating votes="189">7.87</rating>
<name>Yamada Aoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yamada Aoi is a girl Otoo picked up one day in his travels, and recruited to work at Wagnaria. Not much is known for certain about her, not even that `Yamada Aoi` is actually her real name, which makes Souma nervous. She lives in the attic of the restaurant.</description>
<picture>44881.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="346" picture="17184.jpg">Hirohashi Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15959" type="appears in" update="2010-07-01">
<rating votes="37">5.78</rating>
<name>Matsumoto Maya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Maya Matsumoto is a waitress at Wagnaria. Painfully aware of how all her co-workers are all misfits and weirdos, she attempts to stress that unlike them she is completely normal.</description>
<picture>44882.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3601" picture="38507.jpg">Kawase Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17730" type="appears in" update="2010-05-17">
<rating votes="18">8.62</rating>
<name>Inami Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48093.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="388" picture="17234.jpg">Suzuki Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18333" type="appears in" update="2011-02-24">
<rating votes="28">8.33</rating>
<name>Kotori-chan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>"Kotori-chan" is Takanashi Souta in drag. The name `Kotori` derives from a more straightforward reading of `小鳥`, using the ordinary kun-yomi readings of the kanji rather than the variant nanori reading that becomes `Takanashi`. Despite his distaste for cross-dressing, Takanashi is convinced to do so when Inami`s father visits Wagnaria, and again during his date with her.
Taneshima idolizes Kotori-chan as being the woman she aspires to be.</description>
<picture>66355.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18335" type="appears in" update="2010-06-01">
<rating votes="3">6.15</rating>
<name>Takanashi Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48919.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1630" picture="1887.gif">Tasaka Hideki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18336" type="appears in" update="2010-06-01">
<rating votes="6">1.68</rating>
<name>Inami Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48920.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="297" picture="233915.jpg">Ootsuka Houchuu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="116785" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-03-06</airdate>
<rating votes="18">6.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ワグナリアへようこそ♪小鳥遊, 働く.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to Wagnaria: Takanashi Goes to Work.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wagnaria e Youkoso Takanashi, Hataraku.</title>
<summary>A high school boy that loves small, cute things starts working at the family restaurant, Wagnaria, a nest of abnormal fruitcakes. Just as he is acclimating to his new environment, he meets a young woman who will alter his fate for good.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>585582</identifier>
<identifier>wagnaria</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="116876" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-11</airdate>
<rating votes="16">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">伊波, 男性恐怖症. だって怖いんだもん...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inami, the Androphobic, Because... She`s Scared!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inami, Dansei Kyoufushou. Datte Kowain da mon...</title>
<summary>No sooner had Sota met Inami than she punched him in the face. He soon learns that Inami has a habit of reflexively punching men on sight. Kyoko orders them to break the ice and help each other out with their respective personality flaws.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>585602</identifier>
<identifier>wagnaria</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117613" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">相馬, さわやか すぎる青年</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Soma, the Nice...est Young Man</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Souma, Sawayakasugiru Seinen</title>
<summary>Soma takes care of everyone, and seems to simply be a super nice guy. Intrigued by Soma`s rich personality and knowledge about everyone, Sota soon learns all about his dangerous methods of "negotiation."
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>585606</identifier>
<identifier>wagnaria</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117614" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-02</airdate>
<rating votes="13">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ある風邪の日に..., いつもと違うワグナリア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">One Windy Day, an Unusual Wagnaria.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aru Kaze no Hi ni..., Itsumo to Chigau Wagnaria</title>
<summary>Sota takes a day off work to take care of his younger sister, Nazuna, while she is sick in bed. In order to make up for his absense, everyone else jumps in to juggle Wagnaria`s hectic tasks. And just as the chaos reaches its apex...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>585608</identifier>
<identifier>wagnaria</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117615" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-18</airdate>
<rating votes="16">4.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">八千代と杏子と佐藤... と, 帰ってきた音尾さん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yachiyo and Sato, and Otoo-san Returns</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yachiyo to Kyouko to Satou... to, Kaette Kita Otoo-san</title>
<summary>The Branch Manager, Otoo, returns to Wagnaria for the first time in a while. Everyone rejoices in the wide variety of souvenirs that he brings back—except for one vengeful nemesis.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>585604</identifier>
<identifier>wagnaria</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="118134" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-09</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宗太の憂鬱, 小鳥遊家の女達</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sota`s Melancholy, the Women of the Takanashi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Souta no Yuuutsu, Takanashi-ke no Onna-tachi</title>
<summary>The Takanashis live in a typical home in Hokkaido. But, beneath the shell of a regular household lies a cruel hierarchy of power. Surrounded by predators (his older sisters), Sota lives a day-to-day struggle to survive.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>585610</identifier>
<identifier>wagnaria</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="118184" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-04-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118185" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-04-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118252" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-16</airdate>
<rating votes="14">7.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">久しぶりの音尾と, 新しいバイト=山田(!?)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Long Time No See, Otoo! The New Part-Timer, Yamada!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hisashiburi no Otoo to, Atarashii Baito = Yamada (!?)</title>
<summary>Otoo is scheduled to return to Wagnaria today! Kyoko gets excited about receiving his usual, edible souvenirs and Sota jokes about the possibility that Otoo may bring something different back with him this time. He does. It`s a new employee.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>585612</identifier>
<identifier>wagnaria</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="118548" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-23</airdate>
<rating votes="13">5.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">伊波, はじめて? のお・で・か・け!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inami`s First Execu... Excursion Trip!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inami, Hajimete? No O-de-ka-ke!</title>
<summary>When city maintenance forces the restaurant to close for a day, the staff decides to enjoy their day off by going to the hot springs. But, can Inami handle her androphobia in a popular tourist spot?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>585614</identifier>
<identifier>wagnaria</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="118557" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-30</airdate>
<rating votes="18">8.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ことりちゃん登場!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kotori`s Big Debut!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kotori-chan Toujou!!</title>
<summary>Inami is supposed to have the day off, but she visits the restaurant and confides in her co-workers that she needs their help because she lied to her dad. Surprised by the revelation, Sota goes to extreme lengths to help her out.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>585616</identifier>
<identifier>wagnaria</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="118622" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-05-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118625" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-06</airdate>
<rating votes="13">6.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">疑惑の真相..., なずな働く.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Moment of Truth, Nazuna Dons the Apron!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Giwaku no Shinsou..., Nazuna Hataraku.</title>
<summary>After the incident in the previous episode, Sota and Inami decide to work on curing her androphobia. To do so, they decide to walk home together. Along the way, they run into Sota`s younger sister, Nazuna, who becomes curious about their relationship.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>585584</identifier>
<identifier>wagnaria</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="118907" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-27</airdate>
<rating votes="13">5.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">デートと言う名の"決戦", 小鳥遊と伊波のそれから...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Date, the Final Showdown. Takanashi and Inami Ever After...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Date to Iu Na no "Kessen", Takanashi to Inami no Sore kara...</title>
<summary>At Taneshima`s behest, Sota and Inami go on their first date. Though nervous, Inami arrives dressed to kill, whereas Sota arrives anticipating that he might just get killed. Oh, and meet another member of the staff who has been there all along!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>585590</identifier>
<identifier>wagnaria</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="118908" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-20</airdate>
<rating votes="13">5.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なぜか!? の決戦前夜. 種島[たねしま]の恩返し</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eve of the Duel!? Taneshima`s Reciprocation.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Naze ka!? no Kessen Zenya. Taneshima no Ongaeshi</title>
<summary>Taneshima finds Sota`s student ID that he left at the restaurant. Knowing that he`ll need it the next day, she decides to deliver it to him at his house, not knowing the chaos doing so will bring upon Wagnaria the following day.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>585588</identifier>
<identifier>wagnaria</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="118909" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-13</airdate>
<rating votes="14">8.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あの頃の二人, 八千代と佐藤. と, ようこそ小鳥遊[たかなし]家へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Way They Were... Yachiyo and Sato, Welcome to the Takanashis.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ano Koro no Futari, Yachiyo to Satou. to, Youkoso Takanashi Ke e</title>
<summary>Yachiyo, Sato and Kyoko find photos of themselves from years ago in a photo album that Soma brings to work. Sato and Yachiyo reminisce about how they first met at Wagnaria. Also, due to a ghost story that Yamada tells, an unforeseen incident transpires.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>585586</identifier>
<identifier>wagnaria</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="119639" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-05-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134636" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Cinematic 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134637" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Cinematic 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134638" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T35</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Character PV - Yamada Aoi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134639" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T34</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Character PV - Shirafuji Kyouko</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134640" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T33</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Character PV - Souma Hiroomi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134641" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T32</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Character PV - Satou Jun</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134642" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T31</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Character PV - Todoroki Yachiyo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134643" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T30</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Character PV - Inami Mahiru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134644" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T29</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Character PV - Taneshima Popura</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134645" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T28</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Character PV - Takanashi Souta</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134646" update="2012-01-18">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134647" update="2012-01-18">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134648" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T27</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Vol7 Cinematic 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134649" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T26</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Vol7 Cinematic 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134650" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T25</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Vol7 Cinematic 1 (Short)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134651" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T24</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Vol6 Cinematic 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134652" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T23</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Vol6 Cinematic 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134653" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T22</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Vol6 Cinematic 1 (Short)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134654" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T21</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Vol5 Cinematic 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134655" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T20</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Vol5 Cinematic 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134656" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T19</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Vol5 Cinematic 1 (Short)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134657" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T18</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Vol4 Cinematic 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134658" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T17</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Vol4 Cinematic 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134659" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T16</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Vol4 Cinematic 1 (Short)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134660" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T15</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Vol3 Cinematic 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134661" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T14</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Vol3 Cinematic 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134662" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T13</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Vol3 Cinematic 1 (Short)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134663" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Vol2 Cinematic 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134664" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Vol2 Cinematic 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134665" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Vol2 Cinematic 1 (Short)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134666" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Vol1 Cinematic 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134667" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Vol1 Cinematic 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134668" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Vol1 Cinematic 1 (Short)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134669" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Cinematic 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134670" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Cinematic 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134671" update="2011-12-21">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>115</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ワグナリア~夏の大感謝祭~ 夜の部</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Live Cast Special 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134672" update="2011-12-21">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>110</length>
<rating votes="1">8.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ワグナリア~夏の大感謝祭~ 昼の部</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Live Cast Special 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="141280" update="2012-07-28">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-05-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="141400" update="2012-08-04">
<epno type="4">T37</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Blu-ray Perfect Box Cinematic 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="141401" update="2012-08-04">
<epno type="4">T36</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Blu-ray Perfect Box Cinematic 1 (Short)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
