<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6786" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-10-17</startdate>
<enddate>2009-10-17</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Buddha Saitan: The Rebirth of Buddha</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The Rebirth of Buddha</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Happy Science Movie 5</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">仏陀再誕 The REBIRTH of BUDDHA</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4631" type="Other">Eien no Hou</anime>
<anime id="9081" type="Other">The Mystical Laws</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.buddha-saitan.jp/wb/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="774" type="Animation Work">Group Tac</name>
<name id="6000" type="Original Work">Ookawa Ryuuhou</name>
<name id="5280" type="Direction">Ishiyama Takaaki</name>
<name id="15499" type="Music">Mizusawa Yuuichi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Adaptation of a book by Happy Science founder http://anidb.net/cr6000 [Ookawa Ryuuhou].
17-year-old Amanokawa Sayako aspires to become a journalist, just like Kanemoto, an elite newspaper writer she looks up to. But Kanemoto, ashamed of making an erroneous report about a corruption scandal, jumps in front of a train and commits suicide. Since that incident, Sayako suddenly becomes able to see spirits and almost loses her life. However, from that near-fatal incident she experiences something extraordinary. The journalist inside her stirs, and she sets out to find out the truth. But the forces that stand in her way turn out to be much more formidable than she ever imagined.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="194">3.58</permanent>
<temporary count="197">5.61</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>33173.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11029</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6985</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4659</identifier>
<identifier>eqfwrb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.buddha-saitan.jp/wb/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>334878</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12186</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3137" parentid="4665" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-31">
<name>religious propaganda</name>
<description>Religious propaganda is a form of communication aimed at influencing the attitude of a community toward some religion or cult. As opposed to impartially providing information, religious propaganda in its most basic sense, presents information primarily to influence an audience. Religious propaganda often presents facts selectively (thus possibly lying by omission) to encourage a particular faith or religion, or uses loaded messages to produce an emotional rather than rational response to the information presented.</description>
<picurl>60310.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3596" parentid="2876" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-28">
<name>Happy Science</name>
<description>Happy Science is a new religious and spiritual movement founded in Japan on 6 October 1986 by http://anidb.net/cr6000 [Ookawa Ryuuhou].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4665" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>propaganda</name>
<description>Propaganda is communication aimed at influencing the attitude of a community toward some cause or position. As opposed to impartially providing information, propaganda in its most basic sense, presents information primarily to influence an audience. Propaganda often presents facts selectively (thus lying by omission) to encourage a particular synthesis, or uses loaded messages to produce an emotional rather than rational response to the information presented. The desired result is a change of the attitude toward the subject in the target audience to further a political agenda.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="106482" update="2010-04-16">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>115</length>
<airdate>2009-10-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
