<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6794" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-10-05</startdate>
<enddate>2009-12-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Miracle Train: Ooedo-sen e Youkoso</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Miracle Train: Welcome to Oedo Line</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Miracle Train - Welcome to the Oedo Line</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">奇迹列车~欢迎来到大江户线~</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ミラクル☆トレイン~大江戸線へようこそ~</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Miracle Train</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.miracle-train.tv/</url>
<creators>
<name id="845" type="Animation Work">Yumeta Company</name>
<name id="5802" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tsunaki Aki</name>
<name id="5802" type="Animation Character Design">Tsunaki Aki</name>
<name id="9764" type="Series Composition">Katou Youichi</name>
<name id="654" type="Direction">Kasai Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="10106" type="Music">Katou Tatsuya</name>
</creators>
<description>* Adaptation of the Miracle Train multi-media franchise that depicts stops on Tokyo`s Chou commuter train line as handsome young men.
There is an urban legend in Japan about an underground subway line that moves without limitations. The rumor is only gorgeous men ride a train that is known as the Miracle Train. And if you were to happen upon this line, you would undoubtedly fall into a complete state of happiness. Being touched by a ray of light, granting her access to enter into the Oedo Line platform, where the Miracle Train runs. As the doors open up, the space inside is very different, as six handsome men await you inside. According to the conductor the leadership of these six gentlemen and the female guide, when women have worries or insecurities, the Miracle Train will appear. With names matching the stations along the line, these fabulous gentlemen, whose bonds together are tight, despite their different personalities, will erase all of your worries and fears.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="229">3.14</permanent>
<temporary count="230">5.48</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>33289.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10763</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7103</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4550</identifier>
<identifier>pterzh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.miracle-train.tv/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ミラクル☆トレイン</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1741</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>334969</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11919</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>miracle-train</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2779" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>multiple couples</name>
<description>More than one couple is developed in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2792" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>reverse harem</name>
<description>Reverse harem, or sometimes also male harem, is the common name for the gender-reversed version of the usual http://anidb.net/t2859 [harem genre]. In a reverse harem, instead of the usual situation with several female characters focused on one male character, the viewer sees several male characters surrounding a single female character. Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. The most notable exception is that, due to the most relevant characteristics of the trope`s fan base, reverse harem authors tend to go for http://anidb.net/t1760 [bishounen] looks. Though they are also exceptions to the common harem genre, harems with homosexual relationships are not covered by reverse harem.</description>
<picurl>126787.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="31214" type="main character in" update="2011-04-15">
<rating votes="1">8.85</rating>
<name>Roppongi Fumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4037.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="367" picture="17213.jpg">Kenn</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31215" type="main character in" update="2011-04-15">
<name>Tochou Saki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4038.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31216" type="main character in" update="2011-04-15">
<name>Shinjuku Rintarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4039.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31217" type="main character in" update="2011-04-15">
<name>Tsukishima Izayoi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4040.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31218" type="main character in" update="2011-04-15">
<name>Shiodome Iku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4041.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31219" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-15">
<rating votes="1">8.85</rating>
<name>Shashou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4042.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31220" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-15">
<name>Tokugawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4043.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31221" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-15">
<name>Akari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4044.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="448" picture="158105.jpg">Sakai Kanako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31222" type="main character in" update="2011-04-15">
<name>Ryougoku Itsumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4045.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="138" picture="23200.jpg">Morita Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31223" type="appears in" update="2011-04-15">
<name>Shinjukunishiguchi Hajime</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69917.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31224" type="appears in" update="2011-04-16">
<name>Higashishinjuku Reiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69918.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="612" picture="79531.jpg">Maeno Tomoaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31225" type="appears in" update="2011-04-16">
<name>Nishishinjukugochoume Fuku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69919.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="644" picture="205640.jpg">Suzuki Tatsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31226" type="appears in" update="2011-04-16">
<name>Iidabashi Remu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69922.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31227" type="appears in" update="2011-04-16">
<name>Toshimaen Saburou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69923.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2226" picture="23215.jpg">Suganuma Hisayoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31228" type="appears in" update="2011-04-16">
<name>Daimon Tetsuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69924.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="109022" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラビリンス42.3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Labyrinth 42.3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Labyrinth 42.3</title>
<summary>Crisscrossing deep under Tokyo is the subway system. Among those subway lines is a train filled with handsome young men known as the Miracle Train. Passengers are met by the six human manifestations of Oedo Line stations Roppongi, Tocho-mae, Shinjuku, Tsukishima, Shiodome, and Ryogoku. Finding and resolving the troubles of their passengers is their calling.
Today`s stop is Roppongi station. Who will be their first passenger?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>534920</identifier>
<identifier>miracle-train</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="109099" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">パスポートをあなたに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Passport for You</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Passport o Anata ni</title>
<summary>Looking up at the towering Metropolitan Government Office, businesswoman Mai sighs. With hesitant steps, she enters the building.  Meanwhile, inside the Miracle Train, Tocho is worried about the time, saying their next passenger is late. Leaving Tocho to worry by himself, the other stations find ways to pass the time. Mai finally gets on at the Tocho-mae station, but claims to have solved her problem herself already.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>534922</identifier>
<identifier>miracle-train</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="109328" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">十三万人の旅立ち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">130000 People Start Travelling</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Juusanmannin no Tabidachi</title>
<summary>Unhappy girl Michi makes her way through the crowds of the Oedo Line`s Shinjuku station only to find herself on the Miracle Train. The stations run into trouble when Michi demands to be let off the train after hearing the conductor`s explanation. With her policy of strictly following her life plan, Michi refuses to participate in unexpected activities. When Michi is told her well organized life resembles the accurate subway schedules, she says she hates trains. Shinjuku takes Michi out into the city to find the root of her problem.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>534924</identifier>
<identifier>miracle-train</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="110776" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">未来発 過去行き</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Departing From the Future, Going to the Past</title>
<summary>While watching the crowds come and go at Ryogoku station, a strange young women catches Ryogoku`s eye. She is Mirai, a fortune teller working with her good friend Asuka. The stations try to talk to her, but Mirai insists that a fortune teller listens to other people`s problems and does not discuss her own. When Ryogoku discovers the day`s lucky spot is his very own neighborhood, he hatches a plan.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>534926</identifier>
<identifier>miracle-train</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="110940" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-11-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋の0哩標識(マイル・マーカー・ゼロ)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love`s Mile Marker Zero</title>
<summary>“No way! I`m on the Miracle Train?” Noriko takes the stations by surprise with her excited outburst. Self-proclaimed train fanatic Noriko is overjoyed to find herself on the legendary Miracle Train after getting on at Shiodome station. Closet train maniac Shiodome tries to be helpful by talking to Noriko about trains, but she cannot keep up with him, leading Noriko to reveal her plan to get her revenge on her train fanatic classmate.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>534928</identifier>
<identifier>miracle-train</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="111129" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-11-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">レールウェイ フロム 月島</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Railway from Tsukishima</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Railway from Tsukishima</title>
<summary>A woman dressed in an extravagant gown tries to get through the Tsukishima station ticket gate. Behind her are suspicious men in black. At the last minute, Tsukishima guides the woman to safety on the Miracle Train. The woman turns out to be Himero, daughter of an extremely wealthy family, and she has never ridden the subway before. Suspicious of the motives of the men in black and the not entirely truthful Himero, Tsukishima takes her out to explore the area and find answers to his questions.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>536058</identifier>
<identifier>miracle-train</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="111308" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-11-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大江戸ミステリー☆トレイン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ooedo Mystery Train</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ooedo Mystery Train</title>
<summary>The stations learn they won`t be getting any passengers any time soon. When they try to find out why, the conductor evades their question, and the stations choose to use their unexpected break to relax. Roppongi wanders off on his own to think, but his thoughts are interrupted when the Miracle Train suddenly gains speed and inexplicably enters overdrive. At the end of their ride through space, the stations find themselves in a strange place.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>536060</identifier>
<identifier>miracle-train</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="111395" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-11-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">小さなお客様</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tiny Customer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chiisana Okyakusama</title>
<summary>The stations try to give a warm welcome to their young passenger from Roppongi station, Airi. As the stations try to figure out why she ran away from home, Airi latches on to the late arrival Tocho, calling him "daddy." The surprised Tocho decides to act as her father for the time being.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>536062</identifier>
<identifier>miracle-train</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="111396" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-11-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">男たちのミラクル☆トレイン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Men`s Miracle Train</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otoko-tachi no Miracle Train</title>
<summary>The stations` next passenger turns out to be not a lost lady, but a lost gentleman. By some accident, businessman Sakuraba finds himself on the Miracle Train. Despite the circumstances, the Miracle Train must stick to its promise, and the stations are forced to solve Sakuraba`s problem. At first he insists nothing is wrong, but before long he reveals a secret he has been keeping from everyone.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>536064</identifier>
<identifier>miracle-train</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="111397" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-12-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大江戸線にほえろ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bark at the Oedo Line!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ooedo-sen ni Hoero!</title>
<summary>Tocho`s favorite police drama "Oedo Cops" is being revived 10 years after the original series first aired. Despite his irrepressible excitement, Tocho is paralyzed with shock when he sees the Miracle Train`s next passenger Makoto, the rising actress cast to act in "Oedo Cops Part 2." The stations are filled with excitement in the presence of a rising star, but Makoto is weighed down by her concerns surrounding the filming.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>536066</identifier>
<identifier>miracle-train</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="111698" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-12-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">3年後のプロポーズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Proposal from 3 Years Ago</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sannengo no Propose</title>
<summary>A single girl named Mayu rushes onto the train at Azabu Juban station. As an extremely kindhearted person, she always helps those in need, making her late to all of her appointments. Today, she is determined to meet her boyfriend at Roppongi station on time. Without signs of any other problems, the stations escort her to Roppongi station.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>536728</identifier>
<identifier>miracle-train</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="111699" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-12-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">もうひとりの乗客</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Another Passenger</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mou Hitori no Shoukyaku</title>
<summary>It`s another ordinary day on the Miracle Train. While waiting for the next passenger, Roppongi takes a nap and has a strange dream about the mysterious train station. Roppongi`s toughts are interrupted when the train goes into overdrive again. The problem is quickly resolved, but with the cause still unclear the stations cannot hide their unease when the conductor announces he is putting the Miracle Train out of service.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>537164</identifier>
<identifier>miracle-train</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="111700" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-12-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">聖夜の奇跡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Miracle of the Holy Night</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seiya no Kiseki</title>
<summary>Akari finally regains her memory, but remains unable to remember her all-important problem. The conductor returns to announce the Miracle Train will resume running on its diagram. The Miracle Train resumes regular service with Akari once again working as a guide.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>537166</identifier>
<identifier>miracle-train</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="133041" update="2011-09-14">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode T1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
