<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="68" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>8</episodecount>
<startdate>1987-02-25</startdate>
<enddate>1991-01-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Bubblegum Crisis</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Кризис каждый день</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Bubblegum Crisis 2032</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Bubblegum Crisis 2033</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">BGC</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">バブルガムクライシス</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Bubblegum Crisis</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Bubblegum Crisis</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Bubblegum Crisis</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="535" type="Sequel">Bubblegum Crash!</anime>
<anime id="779" type="Same Setting">Parasite Dolls</anime>
<anime id="345" type="Alternative Setting">Bubblegum Crisis Tokyo 2040</anime>
<anime id="441" type="Character">A.D. Police</anime>
<anime id="2891" type="Character">Scramble Wars: Tsuppashire! Genom Trophy Rally</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="452" approval="11" total="11">A.D. Police (1999)</anime>
<anime id="1536" approval="5" total="6">Bakuretsu Tenshi</anime>
<anime id="28" approval="3" total="8">Akira</anime>
<anime id="619" approval="3" total="4">Kyoushoku Soukou Guyver (1989)</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="371655">A masterpiece of 80`s animation.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="538225">The first cyberpunk anime with a masterful soundtrack. This show spawned a lot spin-offs and derivatives. If you are interested in animes that set the standard, this is a must-see.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>https://web.archive.org/web/20140425222105/http://www.anime-int.com/works/bubblegum/crisis/</url>
<creators>
<name id="781" type="Work">Artmic</name>
<name id="1382" type="Original Work">Suzuki Toshimitsu</name>
<name id="1382" type="Original Plan">Suzuki Toshimitsu</name>
<name id="3652" type="Direction">Gouda Hiroaki</name>
<name id="153" type="Direction">Oobari Masami</name>
<name id="3987" type="Direction">Akiyama Katsuhito</name>
<name id="510" type="Chief Animation Direction">Urushihara Satoshi</name>
<name id="3983" type="Character Design">Sonoda Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="732" type="Work">AIC</name>
<name id="4287" type="Music">Makaino Kouji</name>
</creators>
<description>The year is 2033, and Mega-Tokyo is just beginning to recover from a devastating earthquake that completely rearranged the face of Tokyo. Part of the recovery is due to the recent advancement in Boomer technology. Boomers are androids that look, think, and act almost like human beings. They can be put to work, perform as soldiers in the military, or mysteriously go berserk and terrorise the population.
The corporation responsible for all the major Boomer advancements is a monolithic company called http://anidb.net/ch36334 [GENOM]. But GENOM has a rather underhanded secret agenda — to take over the world. With the world dependent on Boomer technology, there does not seem to be much that can stand in GENOM`s way.
Only a mercenary team of four young women, the http://anidb.net/ch36262 [Knight Sabres], equipped with hardsuits, have the courage and the firepower to stand up to rampaging Boomers and the company behind them.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1437">6.27</permanent>
<temporary count="1442">7.22</temporary>
<review count="2">6.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>224208.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>201</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5043</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>1347</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>5036</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>90</identifier>
<identifier>iwckrc</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://web.archive.org/web/20140425222105/http://www.anime-int.com/works/bubblegum/crisis/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Bubblegum_Crisis</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>バブルガムクライシス</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88743</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1797</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>1798</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>1800</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>1802</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>1087</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>1796</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>1801</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>1799</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="920" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-03-22">
<name>perverted</name>
<description>Is a concept describing those types of human behavior that are excessive or deviated from what is considered to be orthodox or normal.</description>
<picurl>245189.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1221" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-28">
<name>scooter</name>
<description>A scooter is a type of motorcycle with a step-through frame and a platform for the rider`s feet.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>218044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1590" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>biker</name>
<description>A person who is skilled at riding a motorcycle/motorbike and does so on a regular basis.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1773" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-12">
<name>tentacle</name>
<description>A tentacle or bothrium (plural: bothria) is one of usually two or more elongated flexible organs present in animals, especially invertebrates. Usually, Tentacles are used for feeding, feeling and grasping.</description>
<picurl>236087.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1876" parentid="2794" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>musical band</name>
<description>A musical ensemble also known as a music(al) group or music(al) band is a group of people who perform instrumental or vocal music, typically known by a distinct name.</description>
<picurl>10249.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2180" parentid="2636" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-24">
<name>cyborg</name>
<description>A cyborg is a cybernetic organism (i.e. an organism that has both artificial and natural systems). The term was coined in 1960 when Manfred Clynes and Nathan Kline used it in an article about the advantages of self-regulating human-machine systems in outer space. D. S. Halacy`s Cyborg: Evolution of the Superman in 1965 featured an introduction which spoke of a "new frontier" that was "not merely space, but more profoundly the relationship between `inner space` to `outer space` -a bridge...between mind and matter." The cyborg is often seen today merely as an organism that has enhanced abilities due to technology, but this perhaps oversimplifies the category of feedback.
Fictional cyborgs are portrayed as a synthesis of organic and synthetic parts, and frequently pose the question of difference between human and machine as one concerned with morality, free will, and empathy. Fictional cyborgs may be represented as visibly mechanical (e.g. the Cybermen in the Doctor Who franchise or The Borg from Star Trek); or as almost indistinguishable from humans (e.g. the "Human" Cylons from the re-imagining of Battlestar Galactica). The 1970s television series The Six Million Dollar Man featured one of the most famous fictional cyborgs. Cyborgs in fiction often play up a human contempt for over-dependence on technology, particularly when used for war, and when used in ways that seem to threaten free will. Cyborgs are also often portrayed with physical or mental abilities far exceeding a human counterpart (military forms may have inbuilt weapons, among other things).
Real (as opposed to fictional) cyborgs are more frequently people who use cybernetic technology to repair or overcome the physical and mental constraints of their bodies. While cyborgs are commonly thought of as mammals, they can be any kind of organism.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42022.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2345" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-02-06">
<name>zettai ryouiki</name>
<description>"Absolute Territory" (絶対領域, Zettai Ryouiki in Japanese) describes the area of uncovered thigh between the skirt and the knee sock.
As per usual for fandom who obsess about costumes, this can be considered a moe attribute and thus, present prominently in character designs and schoolgirl outfits. The term originates from http://anidb.net/a22 [Neon Genesis Evangelion] to designate an area of Absolute Terror, although it`s had considerable semantic drift. In this case, it may jokingly refer to the fact it emphasizes a shorter skirt without actually becoming creepy and showing the underpants.
As if that wasn`t enough, some even categorize it into five "Grades", from E to A. Only the top two (A and B) are considered true Zettai Ryouiki and they are only usable by female characters. Some researchers additionally introduce Grade S, the highest one which consists of Grade A plus further requirements to personality and hairstyle.
Just to make it clear, Zettai Ryouiki is made up of three components: socks, skin, and skirt. An Action Girl may trade the latter for hotpants but if it doesn`t include knee-highs and thighs, it`s not Zettai Ryouiki. Panty Shot is an entirely different zone.
For more information on sock lengths in general, see also: http://anidb.net/t6419 [hosiery]
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>165582.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2438" parentid="2794" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-16">
<name>idol</name>
<description>In Japanese culture, idols (アイドル) are media personalities in their teens and early twenties who are considered particularly cute and cuddly and who will, for a period ranging from several months to a few years, regularly appear in the mass media, e.g. as singers for J-pop groups, bit-part actors, TV personalities, models in photo spreads published in magazines, advertisements, etc.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>63097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2455" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>tsundere</name>
<description>Tsundere (ツンデレ) (pronounced /(t)sʌnˈdɪə(r)/ in English or /t͡sun.de.ɽe/ in Japanese) is a Japanese concept of a character archetype which describes a person with a conceited, irritable, and/or violent personality that suddenly becomes modest and loving when triggered by some sort of cause (such as being alone with someone). The inverse scenario, where a modest and loving person becomes conceited/irritable/violent, is also a tsundere.
The default state does not matter. The character can default to "tsuntsun" or "deredere"; the key concept is the fact that there`s a (generally very quick) flip from one mode to the other.
It can also describe a contradictory personality which is good-willed on the inside, but with a harsh attitude on the outside. Originally found in Japanese bishoujo games, the word is now part of the otaku moe phenomenon, reaching into other media such as anime, manga, novels, and even mass media.
Tsundere is a portmanteau of the two words tsuntsun (ツンツン), and deredere (デレデレ). Tsuntsun is defined as "aloof, morose, pointed", and deredere is defined as "exhausted, lovestruck". Tsunderekko (ツンデレっ娘) is a related noun, referring to a girl with a tsundere personality. Like nekomimi, tsundere is considered a moe-inspiring character trait. The concept has received increasing attention in Japan, with a tsundere cafe opened in Akihabara and tsundere-themed products released (like Tomy Co.`s portable television set), and the concept increasingly reflected in recent anime, from an extended discussion of the meaning of the concept and its origin on the internet in http://anidb.net/a4777 [Lucky Star]`s Lucky Channel segment to merchandise for http://anidb.net/a3651 [The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya] classifying the characters according to tsundere-ness. Another accepted definition of tsundere is a girl who has a combative attitude toward others but is also kind on the inside. She usually plays out as having an attitude toward the main character, usually a male, and often criticizing him in one way or another, but as the series progresses she eventually warms up to him and sometimes even falls in love with him.</description>
<picurl>30388.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2643" parentid="2638" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>power suit</name>
<description>Power Suits are similar to Piloted Robots which are controlled from inside the robot except that Power Suits tend to be more directly tied to how the character moves and they are usually not as big as Piloted Robots can be. They are still mechanical and shouldn`t be confused with plug suits.</description>
<picurl>222235.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2745" parentid="1773" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>mechanical tentacle</name>
<description>Same as tentacles, but instead of being fleshy-slimy, they`re made of metal or perhaps plastic, doesn`t really matter, as long as they look mechanical.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2840" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>mafia</name>
<description>A mafia is a type of organized crime syndicate whose primary activities are protection racketeering, the arbitration of disputes between criminals, and the organizing and oversight of illegal agreements and transactions. Secondary activities may be practiced such as gambling, drug trafficking, loan sharking, and fraud. The term was originally applied to the Sicilian mafia, but has since expanded to encompass other organizations of similar methods and purpose, such as in "the Russian mafia" or "the Japanese mafia", and is applied informally by the press and public, but the criminal organizations themselves have their own terms; for example, the original Sicilian and Italian-American mafia call themselves "cosa nostra", while the Japanese mafia calls itself "yakuza".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>211289.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2861" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>cyberpunk</name>
<description>Cyberpunk focuses on computers or information technology, usually coupled with some degree of breakdown in social order. The plot often centres on a conflict among hackers, artificial intelligences, and mega corporations, tending to be set within a near-future dystopian Earth.</description>
<picurl>211264.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2875" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>ecology</name>
<description>Nature and ecology are a central theme of this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2877" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>revenge</name>
<description>A primary factor that drives the plot forward, is the almost obsessive desire of one of the characters to get back at someone else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2895" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>dark-skinned girl</name>
<description>The anime features a girl with dark skin. A fetish of sorts, since the other protagonists are usually as white-skinned as porcelain dolls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3167" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-16">
<name>Tokyo destroyed</name>
<description>Tokyo is depicted as being or having been destroyed, either partially or completely, by some sort of disaster, such as a nuclear blast, a very large-scale fire, or rising sea levels. Should the situation be dire enough, Tokyo may be destroyed again after a recovery, or a new Tokyo may be built and subsequently destroyed, by a new disaster.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3489" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>car chases</name>
<description>Car chases occur as part of the action setting in this anime.</description>
<picurl>211263.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4073" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-15">
<name>unusual weapons -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This anime tag is set to be split into multiple character tags. If you are sure of what existing tag to use, please apply it to the relevant characters and remove this one from the anime. On the other hand, if you know why this tag is applied and either expect a new tag will be necessary or don`t know how to handle the retagging, simply remove it from the anime and explain the case to the mod.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4131" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-11">
<name>cultural references</name>
<description>The plot of this anime shows signs of cultural references, these are often jokes that make reference to a certain custom, habit or history that is specifically attributed to that culture. Knowledge of the culture itself is needed in order to properly understand these jokes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4170" parentid="5626" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-08-08">
<name>police are useless</name>
<description>The civilian law enforcement representatives do not seem to be of much use, when trying to take on the usually vastly superior foes.
The "helpless" and often clumsy antics of the police can be used as a comedy element.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4277" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-30">
<name>nuclear weapons</name>
<description>A nuclear weapon is an explosive device that derives its destructive force from nuclear reactions, which release vast quantities of energy from relatively small amounts of matter. Nuclear weapons are considered weapons of mass destruction, and their use and control have been a major focus of international relations policy since their debut.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4538" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>long episodes</name>
<description>Long episodes are regular episodes that are much longer than the standard 25-30 minutes, usually 45-60 minutes. 
Not to be used if a show has occasional 45-60 minute specials. Also not to be confused with an OVA or music video with multiple (otherwise unrelated) full-length http://anidb.net/t7241 [bundled episodes] consolidated into a single episode video track.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4566" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-08">
<name>transforming weapons</name>
<description>This anime features transforming weapons, this can either be cars or household appliances that transform into weapons, such as transformers or weapons that themselves transform into bigger badder shapes to deal more and more damage.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4612" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep?</name>
<description>The title of Philip K. Dick`s SF novel (movie: Blade Runner). 
The phrase implies a set of existential questions: Do artificial beings (e.g. Replicants, Bioroids, or other AI constructs) dream, feel, or have a soul? If memories can be implanted, what makes real memories real? By contrast — what makes humans human? What is reality? 
These are central themes e.g. in all of the Ghost in the Shell and Appleseed series / movies.</description>
<picurl>210067.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5626" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>adults are useless</name>
<description>For when adults can`t do anything right.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5792" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-08">
<name>gangs</name>
<description>A gang is a group of people, through the organization, formation, and establishment of an assemblage, share a common identity. In current usage it typically denotes a criminal organization or else a criminal affiliation. In early usage, the word gang referred to a group of workmen. In the United Kingdom the word is still often used in this sense, but it later underwent pejoration. The word gang often carries a negative connotation; however, within a gang which defines itself in opposition to mainstream norms, members may adopt the phrase as a statement of identity or defiance.
The word "gang" derives from the past participle of Old English gan "to go". It is cognate with Old Norse gangr, meaning "journey."</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5816" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-10-03">
<name>massacre</name>
<description>Mass murder.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5882" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>secret identity</name>
<description>The (usually main) protagonist has a secret identity that he or she desperately tries to keep secret.
This can lead to all sorts of amusing misunderstandings, thus is used as comedy element in some anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5916" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-26">
<name>product placement</name>
<description>Otherwise known as a "plug" or "writing commercials right into a show". The practice of prominently displaying or talking about a recognizable product in a program, in exchange for some consideration from the manufacturer, usually monetary. (Source: TV Tropes)
Particularly notorious example, Pizza Hut for the involvement with Code Geass, Darker than Black and other series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5930" parentid="2785" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-01-29">
<name>unrequited shounen ai</name>
<description>At least one male character has a romantic or sexual interest in another male character, but the feelings are not returned.
This can be because the recipient is oblivious, straight, or simply not interested.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5993" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-28">
<name>black humour</name>
<description>Sure, it`s funny, but you really shouldn`t be laughing...
In other words, it`s a comedy that employs situations that nice people should not be laughing about.</description>
<picurl>222688.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5998" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-08">
<name>spider tank</name>
<description>A spider tank is a tank that uses four or more legs for movement instead of the tracks seen in most real-life tanks.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6010" parentid="1278" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-12-29">
<name>human-replacement robots</name>
<description>In an usually sci-fi setting robots, or quite probably actually androids, take the place of humans.
Examples: Humans have become infertile and androids now take the place of children. Or it may be a more sinister undermining of human society by artificial intelligence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6062" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-05">
<name>heroic sacrifice</name>
<description>"In order to save the many, the few will need to sacrifice their lives..." or so this character may think. 
In a seemingly hopeless situation, against impossible odds, the character does not choose the path of the coward and run, he or she chooses to bravely face the enemy, fully aware that this will mean death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6254" parentid="2872" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-23">
<name>terrorism</name>
<description>Terrorism is, in the broadest sense, the use of intentionally indiscriminate violence as a means to create terror among masses of people; or fear to achieve a religious or political aim. It is used in this regard primarily to refer to violence during peacetime or in war against non-combatants (mostly civilians and neutral military personnel). Some definitions now include acts of unlawful violence and war.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10657.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="8994" type="main character in" update="2009-06-11">
<rating votes="35">8.75</rating>
<name>Priscilla S. Asagiri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Priss lost her parents in the great Kanto earthquake in 2025 and was raised in an orphanage. However, she soon ran away and teamed up with a biker gang. When her boyfriend, the gang leader, was murdered and his death declared an accident by the police, she intended to hunt down the killers by herself, but was discovered and taken in by Sylia as the Knight Saber`s assault specialist.</description>
<picture>28452.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4943" picture="28468.jpg">Oomori Kinuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36205" type="appears in" update="2011-09-02">
<name>ADP Shochou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2279" picture="23207.jpg">Satou Masaharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36206" type="appears in" update="2014-02-04">
<name>F.G. Frederick</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149549.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36207" type="appears in" update="2011-09-02">
<name>J.B. Gibson</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51263.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1819" picture="20694.jpg">Shiozawa Kaneto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36208" type="appears in" update="2011-09-02">
<name>USSD Choukan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3283" picture="24293.jpg">Oomiya Teiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36209" type="appears in" update="2014-02-01">
<name>Irene Chang</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132409.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="229" picture="152363.jpg">Itou Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36210" type="appears in" update="2011-09-04">
<name>Anri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51257.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1870" picture="186893.jpg">Mizutani Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36211" type="appears in" update="2012-04-25">
<name>Kaufman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3096" picture="186182.jpg">Sawaki Ikuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36212" type="appears in" update="2011-09-02">
<name>Callahan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3223" picture="88844.jpg">Ootaki Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36213" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-04">
<rating votes="3">3.54</rating>
<name>Quincy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51250.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="480" picture="232940.jpg">Kawakubo Kiyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36214" type="appears in" update="2011-09-02">
<name>Kate Madigan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51253.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="685" picture="24841.jpg">Takano Urara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36215" type="appears in" update="2011-09-02">
<rating votes="1">8.40</rating>
<name>Koo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51262.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="455" picture="17356.jpg">Matsumoto Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36216" type="appears in" update="2014-04-19">
<name>Shou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154227.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28564" picture="186256.jpg">Hamura Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36217" type="main character in" update="2011-09-03">
<rating votes="20">8.70</rating>
<name>Sylia Stingray</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51240.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="571" picture="172734.jpg">Sakakibara Yoshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36218" type="appears in" update="2011-09-04">
<name>Sylvie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51256.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3890" picture="186170.jpg">Takamori Yoshino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36219" type="appears in" update="2011-09-04">
<name>Cynthia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51891.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="167" picture="16972.jpg">Kasahara Hiroko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36220" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-03">
<rating votes="6">5.87</rating>
<name>Daily Wong</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51345.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36221" type="appears in" update="2011-09-02">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Naomi Anderson</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51267.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3947" picture="25762.jpg">Shou Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36222" type="appears in" update="2014-04-19">
<name>Naoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Naoko is Nene`s colleague (as an ADP Operator) and best friend outside the Knight Sabers; the two share a common interest in popular music and looking for a boyfriend.</description>
<picture>154224.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15085" picture="44410.jpg">Asami Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36223" type="appears in" update="2012-05-19">
<name>Nam</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81981.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36224" type="main character in" update="2011-09-03">
<rating votes="20">8.12</rating>
<name>Nene Romanova</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51234.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="692" picture="188445.jpg">Hiramatsu Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36225" type="appears in" update="2011-09-02">
<name>Fank</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2946" picture="23373.jpg">Gouri Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36226" type="appears in" update="2011-09-04">
<name>Fargo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fargo is an informant, plain and simple. His background is unknown, but his information includes data from the government, Genom, and the various criminal syndicates and underworlds, so he has a lot of connections. He has found the Knight Sabers a few Genom-related contracts, and Sylia trusts him to the point that he knows her true identity. He even has the audacity to ask Sylia into dangerous parts of Megatokyo after dark for meetings, and is constantly pursuing her as a sexual conquest. Sylia, however, does not have any interest in this and makes it very obvious.</description>
<picture>51887.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="380" picture="158572.jpg">Yamadera Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36227" type="appears in" update="2011-09-02">
<name>Flint</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3223" picture="88844.jpg">Ootaki Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36228" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-04">
<rating votes="3">1.85</rating>
<name>Brian J. Mason</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51251.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="413" picture="151647.jpg">Ikeda Shuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36229" type="appears in" update="2011-09-02">
<name>MacLaren</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3096" picture="186182.jpg">Sawaki Ikuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36230" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-04">
<rating votes="12">6.49</rating>
<name>Macky Stingray</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Macky Stingray is Sylia`s younger brother and her only family. He serves as the Knight Sabers` backup and mechanic along with Sylia`s friend, Dr. Raven. Macky is a whiz kid with computers and technology. He has to constantly make repairs to Priss`s bike because of her driving and the situations she gets into. He can pilot an armored suit himself and drives a large truck that delivers the Knight Sabers and their bikes to a situation. Macky`s character is also extremely perverted, trying to catch his sister (as well as the other Knight Sabers) in the nude as much as he can.
In the 2040 storyline Mackie is much more polite. His sister Sylia tries to keep Macky from becoming involved, but he helps the former Genom employee named Nigel at his rundown motorcycle shop and builds and repairs the team`s Hardsuits. It is later revealed that Mackie is actually a prototype Boomer that has a more advanced brain modeled after Sylia`s own brain functions. In both versions, Macky also shows romantic feelings towards Nene Romanova.</description>
<picture>51243.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="270" picture="25681.jpg">Sasaki Nozomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36231" type="appears in" update="2011-09-02">
<name>Miriam Yoshida</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51254.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="281" picture="151723.jpg">Futamata Issei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36232" type="appears in" update="2011-09-02">
<name>Meg</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="9649" picture="77764.jpg">Maruo Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36233" type="appears in" update="2011-09-02">
<name>Largo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51255.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3313" picture="24334.jpg">Sogabe Kazuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36234" type="appears in" update="2012-12-03">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Lisa Vanett</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lisa Vanett is the niece of AD Police Chief Todo and an aspiring photojournalist who sets her sights on exposing the Knight Sabers when she photographs a fight between them and a renegade Boomer and Priss smashes her camera to prevent her from capturing their activities on film. Nene is assigned to accompany Lisa around the city. One night, after a fight between the Knight Sabers and a Boomer, Lisa discovers in one of her photos that Nene is one of them after her helmet is damaged in battle. But after coming to appreciate the work the Knight Sabers do, she eventually turns the photo and its digital negative over to Nene.</description>
<picture>51272.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36235" type="main character in" update="2011-09-03">
<rating votes="26">8.46</rating>
<name>Linna Yamazaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51228.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3374" picture="24704.jpg">Tomizawa Michie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36236" type="appears in" update="2011-09-02">
<name>Luu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="1446" picture="19314.jpg">Touma Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36237" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-03">
<rating votes="25">8.94</rating>
<name>Leon McNichol</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leon McNichol is a frustrated but dedicated cop, with a tendency to rush in without thinking. Having worked his way up from the normal police, Leon sees himself as the protector of the local citizens and initially dislikes the vigilante nature of the Knight Sabers. He meets and becomes a big brother figure for Nene and falls in love with Priss. He is unaware of her being a Knight Saber until later in the series, but when he learns the truth he keeps it to himself. At the end of the series, Priss returns his feelings.</description>
<picture>51246.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2583" picture="23188.jpg">Furukawa Toshio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36238" type="appears in" update="2011-09-02">
<name>Levin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="604" picture="154161.jpg">Ogata Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36239" type="appears in" update="2014-02-04">
<name>Katsuhito Stingray Hakase</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149550.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2729" picture="186723.jpg">Ishimaru Hiroya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36240" type="appears in" update="2011-09-02">
<name>Aikawa Youji</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3249" picture="24746.jpg">Kobayashi Michitaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36252" type="appears in" update="2011-09-04">
<rating votes="2">9.93</rating>
<name>Moto Slave</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>51902.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="36253" type="appears in" update="2011-09-04">
<name>Reika Chang</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51261.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5067">Hashimoto Maiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36261" type="appears in" update="2011-09-03">
<name>AD Police</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="36262" type="appears in" update="2011-09-03">
<name>Knight Sabers</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Knight Sabers are a mercenary team of four young women. To enhance their natural abilities, they each wear a Hard Suit - each of them specialized in its equipment and performance according to the respective wearer`s field combat role. They were recruited by Sylia Stingray to battle the corrupt Genom corporation that dominates their home city of Mega Tokyo and which was responsible for her father`s death. In order to finance their activities, the Knight Sabers also accept paying jobs as bodyguards or mercenaries. Their main activity is fighting out-of-control boomers, half biological/half-mechanical robots built by Genom.</description>
<picture>8198.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="36334" type="appears in" update="2011-09-04">
<name>Genom</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Genom is the primary manufacturer and distributor of the bio-organic constructs known as "Boomers". This makes Genom the primary enemy of the Knight Sabers - led by Sylia Stingray, daughter of the man who created the Boomers. In both versions of the series, Genom is run by a mysterious figure named Quincy, though the depiction of Quincy varies from one continuity to another (in the original series he was a dangerous, hands-on owner, while in Tokyo 2040 he is almost a puppet vegetable of a man, so old and decrepit he needs tubes and wires to keep himself alive while insanely dreaming of a boomer/human paradise). Brian J. Mason also works for Genom, and his schemes are either offshoots of or interference to Quincy`s.</description>
<picture>51899.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="36335" type="appears in" update="2011-09-04">
<name>Moto Slave Typhoon I</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>51905.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="36336" type="appears in" update="2011-09-04">
<name>Moto Slave Typhoon II</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>51906.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="36337" type="appears in" update="2011-09-04">
<name>Mobile Pit</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>51907.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="36339" type="appears in" update="2011-09-04">
<name>K-11</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>51932.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="36340" type="appears in" update="2011-09-04">
<name>K-12S</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>51993.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="36341" type="appears in" update="2011-09-04">
<rating votes="2">8.23</rating>
<name>Fire Bee</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>51997.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="36342" type="appears in" update="2011-09-04">
<name>Gryphon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>51998.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="36343" type="appears in" update="2015-12-07">
<name>Road Chaser</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>52000.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="36344" type="appears in" update="2011-09-04">
<name>D-D</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>52001.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="36367" type="appears in" update="2015-08-07">
<name>Highway Star</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>52157.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="36368" type="appears in" update="2011-09-05">
<name>Boomer BU-55C</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52158.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="36369" type="appears in" update="2011-09-05">
<name>Boomer BU-12B</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52159.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="36370" type="appears in" update="2011-09-05">
<name>Doberman</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52160.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="36371" type="appears in" update="2011-09-05">
<name>Super Boomer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52161.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="36372" type="appears in" update="2011-09-05">
<name>Hyper Boomer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52178.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="36373" type="appears in" update="2011-09-05">
<name>Hyper Boomer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52179.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="36374" type="appears in" update="2011-09-05">
<name>Hyper Boomer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52180.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="36375" type="appears in" update="2011-09-05">
<name>Boomer BU-33C</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52181.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="66832" type="appears in" update="2014-04-19">
<name>Shou no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154228.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4591" picture="77707.jpg">Nakajima Chisato</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="3774" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>1987-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">TINSEL CITY</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tinsel City</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tinsel City</title>
</episode>
<episode id="3775" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1987-09-05</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">BORN TO KILL</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Born to Kill</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Born to Kill</title>
</episode>
<episode id="3776" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1987-12-05</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">BLOW UP</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blow Up</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Blow Up</title>
</episode>
<episode id="3777" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>1988-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">REVENGE ROAD</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Revenge Road</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Revenge Road</title>
</episode>
<episode id="3778" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1988-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">MOONLIGHT RAMBLER</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Moonlight Rambler</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moonlight Rambler</title>
</episode>
<episode id="3779" update="2005-12-31">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>1989-08-30</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">RED EYES</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Red Eyes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Red Eyes</title>
</episode>
<episode id="3780" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>1990-03-14</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">DOUBLE VISION</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Double Vision</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Double Vision</title>
</episode>
<episode id="3781" update="2005-12-31">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>1991-01-30</airdate>
<rating votes="9">9.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">SCOOP CHASE</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scoop Chase</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Scoop Chase</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8743" update="2007-09-11">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1988-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">HURRICANE LIVE 2032</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hurricane Live! 2032</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hurricane Live 2032</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8744" update="2005-05-25">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1990-06-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">HURRICANE LIVE 2033 Tinsel City Rhapsody</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hurricane Live! 2033</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hurricane Live 2033: Tinsel City Rhapsody</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35851" update="2014-02-04">
<epno type="6">O1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>1990-06-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">HURRICANE LIVE 2033 Tinsel City Rhapsody クライシス~怒りをこめて走れ~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hurricane Live! 2033 - Crisis - Run with Anger</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hurricane Live 2033: Tinsel City Rhapsody - Crisis: Ikari o Komete Hashire</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35852" update="2014-02-04">
<epno type="6">O2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>1990-06-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">HURRICANE LIVE 2033 Tinsel City Rhapsody 悪魔と天使のキス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hurricane Live! 2033 - Devil and Angel`s Kiss</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hurricane Live 2033: Tinsel City Rhapsody - Akuma to Tenshi no Kiss</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35853" update="2014-02-02">
<epno type="6">O3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>1988-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">HURRICANE LIVE 2032 MAD MACHINE</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hurricane Live! 2032 - Mad Machine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hurricane Live 2032: Mad Machine</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35854" update="2014-02-02">
<epno type="6">O4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>1990-06-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">HURRICANE LIVE 2033 Tinsel City Rhapsody Rock me</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hurricane Live! 2033 - Rock Me</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hurricane Live 2033: Tinsel City Rhapsody - Rock Me</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35855" update="2014-02-04">
<epno type="6">O5</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>1990-06-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">HURRICANE LIVE 2033 Tinsel City Rhapsody 薔薇の戦士[ソルジャー]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hurricane Live! 2033 - Soldier of Roses</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hurricane Live 2033: Tinsel City Rhapsody - Bara no Soldier</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35856" update="2014-02-02">
<epno type="6">O6</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1988-04-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">HURRICANE LIVE 2032 KONYAWA HURRICANE</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hurricane Live! 2032 - There`s a Hurricane Tonight</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hurricane Live 2032: Kon`ya wa Hurricane</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35857" update="2014-02-04">
<epno type="6">O7</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>1988-04-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">HURRICANE LIVE 2032 ASU E TOUCH DOWN</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hurricane Live! 2032 - Touchdown to Tomorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hurricane Live 2032: Asu e Touchdown</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35858" update="2014-02-04">
<epno type="6">O8</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>1988-04-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">HURRICANE LIVE 2032 VICTORY</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hurricane Live! 2032 - Victory</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hurricane Live 2032: Victory</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35859" update="2014-02-04">
<epno type="6">O9</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>1988-04-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">HURRICANE LIVE 2032 KIZUDARAKE NO WILD</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hurricane Live! 2032 - Wild and Scarred</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hurricane Live 2032: Kizudarake no Wild</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67683" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C14</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Undetermined Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85394" update="2014-02-04">
<epno type="6">O10</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>1990-06-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">HURRICANE LIVE 2033 Tinsel City Rhapsody ジャンピング・ハート</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hurricane Live! 2033 - Jumping Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hurricane Live 2033: Tinsel City Rhapsody - Jumping Heart</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85395" update="2014-02-04">
<epno type="6">O11</epno>
<length>3</length>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Bubblegum Crisis 2033 MV - Revenge road</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85396" update="2014-02-04">
<epno type="6">O12</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>1990-06-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Hurricane Live! 2033 - Say Yes!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121032" update="2014-02-02">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="3">6.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121033" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C13</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="2">5.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121034" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="2">6.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121035" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="2">3.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121036" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="2">5.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121037" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="3">4.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121038" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="3">4.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121039" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="3">6.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121040" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="3">6.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121041" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="2">3.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121042" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="2">2.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121043" update="2014-02-02">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="3">4.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121044" update="2014-02-02">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="3">4.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157810" update="2014-02-02">
<epno type="6">O13</epno>
<length>4</length>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">HURRICANE LIVE 2033 Tinsel City Rhapsody 明日へタッチダウン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hurricane Live! 2033 - Touchdown to Tomorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hurricane Live 2033: Tinsel City Rhapsody - Asu e Touchdown</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157837" update="2014-02-02">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV There`s a Hurricane Tonight</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">PV Kon`ya wa Hurricane</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157851" update="2014-02-04">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>40</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">Bye² Knight Sabers HOLIDAY in BALI</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bye-bye Knight Sabers: Holiday in Bali</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bye-bye Knight Sabers: Holiday in Bali</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157852" update="2014-02-04">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo Moonlight Rambler</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
