<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6804" restricted="false">
<type>Other</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-08-01</startdate>
<enddate>2009-08-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Pikachu no Kirakira Daisousaku!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pikachu`s Great Sparkling Search!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pokemon: Movie 12 Short</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ピカチュウのキラキラだいそうさく!</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4728" type="Parent Story">Pocket Monsters: Diamond and Pearl</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="727" type="Animation Work">OLM</name>
<name id="7914" type="Character Design">Yamada Shun`ya</name>
<name id="2841" type="Work">Shogakukan-Shueisha Productions</name>
<name id="5780" type="Original Plan">Tajiri Satoshi</name>
<name id="10185" type="Original Plan">Masuda Jun`ichi</name>
<name id="10181" type="Original Plan">Sugimori Ken</name>
<name id="4235" type="Direction">Yuyama Kunihiko</name>
<name id="7914" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yamada Shun`ya</name>
<name id="13743" type="Music">Shima Ken</name>
<name id="2822" type="Music">Tada Akifumi</name>
<name id="6897" type="Music">Tanaka Hirokazu</name>
<name id="5660" type="Music">Miyazaki Shinji</name>
<name id="27525" type="Character Design">Matsumiya Toshinobu</name>
<name id="27526" type="Character Design">Matsushima Kenji</name>
<name id="27643" type="Character Design">Nishino Kouji</name>
</creators>
<description>Note: Originally shown on All Nippon Airways (ANA) flights starting from 01.08.2009 to 29.08.2009.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="90">3.06</permanent>
<temporary count="92">4.96</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>143976.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15658</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6555</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>336876</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1846" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>kodomo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word kodomo refers to a children`s audience roughly for the ages 12 and younger. In Japanese, the word means simply "child", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3955" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>DESCRIPTION MISSING</name>
<description>The description for this entry is missing. e.g plot, biography...
Please help by adding it, and remove this tag afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="459" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<name>Kabigon</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Snorlax is a Normal-type Pokémon introduced in Generation I.
It evolves from Munchlax when leveled up with high friendship. It also has a Gigantamax form.
In the Generation I and II games and their remakes, wild Snorlax can be found sleeping in inconvenient locations throughout Kanto. In order to catch one, a Trainer must first awaken it with music from either a Poké Flute or Pokégear set to the Poké Flute channel. A sleeping Snorlax makes a return in Pokémon X and Y, in which it is blocking the player`s way on Route 7.
Snorlax is a huge, bipedal, dark blue-green Pokémon with a cream-colored face, belly, and feet. Its body is composed of mostly its belly, as its limbs are comparatively small. Its head is large with small, pointed ears and two pointed teeth protruding from its lower jaw. It has round feet, which both have three claws and a circular brown paw pad, and short arms with five claws on each hand. Snorlax`s bulk makes it the heaviest Normal type.
Snorlax is often found in mountains and forests. It wakes up only to eat, requiring 900 lbs. (400 kg) of food per day before returning to its slumber. It is not a picky eater, as its strong stomach allows it to eat even moldy food without feeling any ill effects. It can even handle thorny plants or Muk`s poison. It can also eat while it is resting. Snorlax is docile enough to let children and small Pokémon bounce on its large stomach.
Snorlax can show awesome power when prompted. As Gigantamax Snorlax, seeds and small rocks that were tangled in its belly fur goes through immense growth and a tree spouts upon its belly. The tree has three red clouds surrounding it like a circle. It almost never moves; even when in battle it only slightly lifts its body and attacks by flailing with its arms and legs. However, its attacks are very powerful — Gigantamax Snorlax is considered to be the strongest Dynamax Pokémon to have been discovered.
It is the only known Pokémon capable of using the exclusive Z-Move Pulverizing Pancake and G-Max Move G-Max Replenish.</description>
<picture>68376.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="541" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Ordile</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Feraligatr is the final form of the Totodile evolutionary line. Feraligatrs are massive, Godzilla-like crocodiles with long, blue bodies and four legs, although they may also stand upright on land. Their appendages have sharp claws at the ends, and its jaw is lined with teeth. On its head, back, and tail there are red, jagged scales. As stated in the Pokédex in Pokémon Ruby and Sapphire, "Feraligatr intimidates its foes by opening its huge mouth. In battle, it will kick the ground hard with its thick and powerful hind legs to charge at the foe with incredible speed."
Feraligatrs are ferocious and have a tendency to lash out at those that come too close. They eat Magikarp and other fish-like Pokémon, as well as larger prey (such as Stantler and Tauros) when they come close enough to the water.</description>
<picture>243046.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="566" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="15">5.12</rating>
<name>Kireihana</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bellossom is a diurnal plant Pokémon. It evolves from Gloom if exposed to a Sun Stone. Bellossom`s petals can rotate, and they usually do when it is absorbing sunlight. The color of their leaves vary from a sickly brown and gray to a fluorescent yellow and red, depending on how much sunlight it has absorbed in the past few hours. When its petals are moving, either due to rotating or dancing, they rub together to make relaxing, bell-like sounds. The petals on its head also create a sweet scent.
It is also noted that a Bellossom will be even more beautiful if it was an especially rancid Gloom. The worse it smells as a Gloom, the prettier its petals will be as a Bellossom. Although naturally a peaceful and friendly Pokémon, it can be very territorial and violent fights can break out if there is an intruder or a challenger. Despite this, it is very social in areas outside of its self-determined territory, and the most common time to find a group of Bellossom together is when they all meet in one location to dance. It is said that these dances summon the sun.
Its Japanese name, "Kireihana", translates to "Beautiful" (kirei) and "Flower" (hana).</description>
<picture>243066.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="271" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="567" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Maril</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Marill is an aquatic mouse Pokémon. Marill`s tail floats like a buoy because it is filled with oil, which is less dense than water. When fishing at a fast-running stream, Marill wraps its tail around a tree. Since the tail is stretchy and flexible, it allows the Pokémon to get food and still stay safely anchored. Otherwise, when in a lake, it uses the buoy-qualities of its tail to keep itself suspended as the rest of its body dives underwater to feed on aquatic plants. Its fur is impermeable, which keeps it dry, and that allows it to swim through water at high speed without being slowed by the water`s resistance.
In the Pokémon Anime, Tracey, the Pokémon Observer from the Orange Islands, has a Marill which he uses on multiple occasions.</description>
<picture>243067.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="70" picture="171604.jpg">Kanai Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="601" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Upah</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wooper are similar to Axolotl. They are light teal-colored Pokémon with round feet, no arms, and a long tail. Their simplistic face consists of mainly of a large mouth, primarily while open. They have purplish barbed antennae on the sides of their head. Three purple, though sometimes shaded blue or pink, gills are on its stomach. Wooper will usually live in cold water: however, they occasionally come out onto land in search of food. When doing so, they coat their bodies with slimy, poisonous film. Touching the slime with bare hands will cause a shooting pain. Male Wooper have two barbs on their antennae, while female Wooper have one barb. Males also have larger gills.</description>
<picture>243078.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="602" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Nuoh</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Quagsire has an appearance and habitat similar to that of a giant salamander. Quagsire live a carefree life in muddy ponds and rivers. It acts oblivious to its environment, accidentally bumping its head on the hulls of boats and bottoms of whatever body of water it swims in as it swims, but seeming not to care. Quagsire always bear an absent-looking facial expression. This is likely due to Quagsire`s easy-going nature. It hunts by staying still in the water with its mouth open, waiting for small prey to swim into its mouth. It doesn`t move, and therefore, doesn`t get hungry. It`s not uncommon that a fishermen`s hook will get caught in the gaping mouth of a feeding Quagsire. Trying to eat what it has caught, the Quagsire would try to swallow, and end up pulling the fishermen off his boat and into the water. Male Quagsire have larger fins on their backs. They wait at the bottom of lakes waiting for prey to wander into its mouth. It also loves eating cherries.</description>
<picture>243079.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="605" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Yamikarasu</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Murkrow is a small black crow with red eyes. The top of its head is styled as a witch`s hat and its tail bristles out like a broomstick. Murkrow is rather unpopular in the Pokémon world. Its dismal appearance and nocturnal nature have long caused it to be considered an omen of ill fortune to all who see it. If a Murkrow finds itself wounded, it fights back by leading its pursuer to dark mountain trails in an attempt to get him hopelessly lost in the darkness.
Murkrow is also attracted to bright, shiny objects, which it collects to stash in its nest. This, of course, leads to many arguments between Murkrow and Meowth, who both share a common love of stashing things - and taking from each other! It does not hesitate to steal such objects if necessary and has even been known to attempt to snatch rings off their owner`s fingers (and complete strangers too, for that matter). With the addition of Pokémon Diamond and Pearl, it is revealed that some Murkrow are servants to its evolved form, Honchkrow, who spends all of its time preening and ordering the Murkrow around. Also with Diamond and Pearl`s release, Murkrow, like many other Pokémon, have gender differences. In this case, Males have a taller "hat" - technically, the crest that resembles a three-pointed witch hat - than females would. Murkrow can only be found wild in the Pokémon Diamond Version in Eterna Forest, while Misdreavus can only be found in Pokémon Pearl at the same location.</description>
<picture>243082.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="838" type="main character in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Muchul</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Smoochum is a the pre-evolution of Jynx that was introduced a generation after. It is a female-only species that uses its lips, the most sensitive part of its body, to examine new and unfamiliar objects, and remember its likes and dislikes. This sensitivity quickly develops as it grows. It actively runs about, but often falls. When idle, it rocks its head back and forth, as if it were kissing someone. It constantly searches for ways to see its reflection, so it can see if its face is dirty.</description>
<picture>243116.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="551" picture="228658.jpg">Nishimura Chinami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1209" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Fuwante</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Drifloon resembles a toy balloon with two strings and cross-like patch. Drifloon has a wispy cloud on its head, and the ends of its two strings resemble hearts. According to its Pokédex entry, it attempts to abduct children but is so light that it ends up being pulled along instead, much like it was a balloon on a string. Drifloon and its evolution are the only two Pokémon that are ghost- and flying-type. Its classification as the `Balloon` Pokémon is shared with Igglybuff and its evolutions Jigglypuff and Wigglytuff as well as the water/poison Pokémon Qwilfish. The creature appears in Pokémon Diamond and Pearl, and the episode "Drifloon on the Wind" where it belongs to a Nurse Joy and her two daughters, Marnie (Sayaki) and Paige (Mai). Drifloon can only be obtained at the Valley Windworks on Fridays after defeating Commander Mars of Team Galactic for the first time</description>
<picture>243366.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1938" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-13">
<rating votes="420">5.46</rating>
<name>Nyarth (Rocket-dan)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Meowth is a very unique Pokémon as it has many of the characteristics of a human. It walks on two feet, talks and is as smart as any human. Meowth is currently a member of Team Rocket and he travels around with Jessie and James trying to capture Pikachu and other rare Pokémon for Giovanni.
Meowth generally finishes his sentences with "Nyaa (ニャー)" which is the equivalent of "meow" in English. This helps people remember that despite his ability to talk like a human, he still has cat character traits.
Meowth is also known for coming up with his many schemes to try to capture Pikachu. While Jessie and James always agree with Meowth and think his plans are brilliant, they are generally foiled by Ash and his friends.
Long Con to Access Raimon City Pokémon Center
Meowth schemed with Jessie, James and Doctor Zager to figure out a way for them to infiltrate the Raimon City Pokémon Center where high-leveled Pokémon are stored in a vault that is protected by a security machine scan system that would only open if Nurse Joy (Isshu) or Nurse Joy`s Audino were scanned. Meowth pretended to be no longer part of Team Rocket making up a story that his made an error while executing a certain operation and when headquarters hear of his mistake, they told him he was fired.
Ash, Iris and Cilan believed him and allowed Meowth to travel with him. Pikachu though didn`t trust Meowth even though Meowth proved on numerous occasion that it should be trusted. Meowth`s plan was put into action when they arrived at the Raimon City Pokémon Center and as soon as Nurse Joy`s Audino was scanned to open the door, Meowth turned on Pikachu and the other and captured all the Pokémon in the vault. The long con had been a success and Meowth met up with Jessie and James below the Pokémon Center. Unfortunately, they weren`t able to get away as Ash and his friends realized that Meowth had just been conning them and they were able to stop Team Rocket.</description>
<picture>56344.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3832" picture="170554.jpg">Inuyama Inuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8091" type="main character in" update="2017-10-30">
<rating votes="989">3.91</rating>
<name>Pikachu (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Beginning
On the morning that Ash was to start his Pokémon journey, he woke up late and by the time he reached Professor Samual Oak`s laboratory, all of the beginner Pokémon were already taken. However, Professor Samual Oak did have one Pokémon left, a wild Pikachu. At first, Pikachu did not like Ash and would refuse to enter his PokéBall. He would often laugh at Ash`s failures and refused to listen to him. However, after Ash proved his loyalty to Pikachu by protecting him from a flock of Spearow, and thus began to earn Pikachu`s trust and respect. The two have since become best friends and Pikachu never leaves Ash`s side.
Since the day Team Rocket first encountered Pikachu, it has been their sole goal to capture it. Day after day, their plan to capture Pikachu has been thwarted mainly due to Pikachu`s amazingly powerful Thunderbolt that keeps on blasting them off.
On numerous occasions, Pikachu has made it evident that he is happy being a Pikachu and has no desire to evolve into a more powerful Raichu. It has proven time and time again that it is a powerful and worthy opponent to any Pokémon that dares to battle it.
Gym Battle against Burgh`s Leavanny
Pikachu was then sent out to battle Burgh`s Leavanny. Burgh`s Leavanny managed to tie up Pikachu with String Shot but unlike Ash`s Swadloon who was able to break free, Pikachu ended up getting hit with a couple of Leaf Storm attacks and a Hyper Beam before it rolled into another of Burgh`s Leavanny`s Leaf Storm attacks to break the string off its body so it could attack. Freed from the String Shot, Burgh`s Leavanny tried to tie it up again but Pikachu managed to avoid it with its speed and then knocked Burgh`s Leavanny out with a combination of Iron Tail and Electro Ball.
Gym Battle against Elesa
Elesa`s Emolga knocked out Ash`s Snivy and was then matched up with Pikachu. Pikachu made quick work of Elesa`s Emolga and knocked it out with one attack, its Iron Tail.
Elesa`s Tynamo was the last Pokémon that she used in her gym battle against Ash. It was matched up against Pikachu who had just defeated her Emonga. Pikachu had a hard time defending against the fast Tackle attack that Elesa`s Tynamo kept hitting it with but Pikachu used its Thunderbolt to create a large dust cloud leaving only a small corridor for Pikachu to focus on it and so Elesa`s Tynamo couldn`t maneuver out of the way. Pikachu one hit K.O`d Elesa`s Tynamo with a Iron Tail. The loss gave Ash the overall victory.
Battle against Alder`s Bouffalant
Ash challenged Alder to a battle and he accepted though he had been walking all night and was actually quite tired. Alder sent out his Buffron to battle Pikachu but just as the battle started, Alder fell asleep standing up and didn`t give any orders to his Buffron. Alder`s Bouffalant stood still as Pikachu began hitting it with attack after attack until it Alder`s Bouffalant finally got mad at Alder and charged at him and set him flying into a tree. After that, Alder`s Bouffalant no longer wished to battle and Alder conceded the battle.
Gym Battle against Skyla
In Skyla air battle simulation, Ash`s Tranquill was matched up against Skyla`s Unfezant and since her Pokémon was the highest evolved form, she determined that her Pokémon would be the winner in that match-up. In the actual gym battle, Ash`s Tranquill was up against Skyla`s Unfezant which was the match-up just after Ash`s Tranquill had defeated Skyla`s Swoobat. Skyla`s Unfezant proved to be stronger and faster than Ash`s Tranquill, so Ash recalled it and set out Pikachu. Pikachu had a definite advantage over Skyla`s Unfezant with its electric attacks and it quickly knocked it out with its Electro Ball attack.
Ash Just after Pikachu ended up knocking out Skyla`s Unfezant, Skyla`s Swanna was sent out to battle against it. Skyla had been watching her grandpa`s battle videos and noticed that he used the move Aqua Ring to defend against Electric attacks. She used that same defense against Pikachu which nullified its Electric attacks. It`s Iron Tail also couldn`t hit it so high in the air. Ash then noticed the rings in the air and Pikachu jumped up on them and managed to hit Skyla`s Swanna but not directly. Pikachu was now up in the air though and Skyla`s Swanna had the advantage there and it quickly knocked Pikachu out with a powerful Brave Bird attack.
Battle Against Trip`s Serperior at the Isshu League
Pikachu participated in the Isshu League in the preliminary match where it is was matched up against Trip`s Serperior. Cilan noted that Trip`s Serperior speed and its attack power had leveled up quite a bit too since the last time they saw it. The match was pretty one sided for a long time as Pikachu wasn`t able to counter its speed and ended up getting wrapped up. After using Iron Tail on the ground to get loose, Pikachu used a combination attack of Iron Tail and Electro Ball to one hit KO Trip`s Serperior. As a result, Trip was eliminated from the Isshu League and Ash advanced to the next round.</description>
<picture>88041.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7" picture="186500.jpg">Ootani Ikue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8135" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-12">
<rating votes="73">8.01</rating>
<name>Sonans (Musashi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>While Wobbuffet is technically Jessie`s Pokémon, it has been around so long that it has become a main character, appearing in almost every episode of the series since it debut.
Wobbuffet was first seen walking around with Benny, his previous trainer. Jessie traded her Lickitung for Wobbuffet and it has been with her ever since that day.
Wobbuffet rarely battles but when he does, his Counter and Mirror Coat moves have proved to be very effective. Unfortunately, Jessie`s tactics aren`t always sufficient to master Wobbuffet`s superior defensive skills.
Wobbuffet also randomly comes out of his Pokeball, especially during the Team Rocket motto. He is also seen blasting off with Jessie regardless if he was actually part of the action.</description>
<picture>56350.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8150" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-12">
<name>Manene (Kojirou)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mime Jr. previously resided with the old couple who took care of an old vacation castle that James`s family owns.</description>
<picture>56367.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="24143" type="appears in" update="2010-11-10">
<name>Hayashigame (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>During a battle with Paul, Ash`s Turtwig evolved into Grotle.</description>
<picture>59096.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24147" type="appears in" update="2012-10-27">
<name>Buoysel (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>When Ash and co. were traveling towards Daybreak Town for Dawn`s next Pokémon Contest, a mysterious Pokémon Trainer specializing in martial arts, named Clayton, challenged Ash and his Buizel to a battle after seeing how Buizel saved Gible who had fallen into a river. Clayton`s Mr. Mime proved to be a really strong opponent, though, as it managed to dodge Buizel`s Aqua Jet and SonicBoom attacks by skillfully using its Psychic and Double Team moves, eventually knocking Buizel out with a powerful ThunderPunch. Ash and Buizel, determined to make up for the loss by getting stronger, started training with Clayton`s help so that Buizel could learn a new move; Ice Punch. He told them that, in order to master the move, they had to work on improving their speed and concentration.
At first, the progress of Ash`s Buizel`s training seemed to be really slow. However, after training overnight using unstable and light objects as targets for its punches, like floating leaves, Buizel managed to master the move completely. After the completion of Buizel`s training, Ash challenged Clayton to a rematch, and Clayton accepted. Ash`s Buizel proved to be more of a challenge for its opponent, Mr. Mime, this time and after activating its ability, Swift Swim, in the midst of the battle due to a sudden rain, Buizel managed to increase its speed and finish Clayton`s Mr. Mime off with a powerful Ice Punch. Clayton then acknowledged Ash`s Buizel`s improvement and praised its skills, but also put emphasis on the fact that Buizel still had a long way to go and had to keep on training.</description>
<picture>58893.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2364" picture="151724.jpg">Furushima Kiyotaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24148" type="appears in" update="2010-11-10">
<name>Glion (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ash`s Gligar evolved into Gliscor in order to save Ash from a fall. It used the Razor Fang Ash received from Gary to evolve.</description>
<picture>59100.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24149" type="appears in" update="2012-10-27">
<name>Usokkie (Takeshi)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Brock`s Bonsly evolved into Sudowoodo after it escaped from a cage that Team Rocket caught it in.</description>
<picture>58869.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="336" picture="17172.jpg">Sakaguchi Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24150" type="appears in" update="2011-01-15">
<name>Pinpuku (Takeshi)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Brock won Happiny`s egg in a Pokémon cosplay contest by entering his Croagunk dressed up as a Politoed. While traveling on Cycling Road, the egg began to glow. After taking it to a Pokémon Center, the egg hatched into Happiny.</description>
<picture>58870.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6925" picture="201846.jpg">Itou Miyako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24151" type="appears in" update="2011-06-08">
<rating votes="11">9.08</rating>
<name>Gureggru (Takeshi)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Team Rocket recruited Croagunk while they were running their fake Gym in the Sinnoh region.</description>
<picture>58871.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="24156" type="main character in" update="2011-06-08">
<rating votes="12">7.27</rating>
<name>Pochama (Hikari)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dawn`s first Pokémon that she got from Professor Rowan.</description>
<picture>58876.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2046" picture="186581.jpg">Kozakura Etsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24183" type="appears in" update="2011-06-08">
<name>Mimirol (Hikari)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dawn battled many wild Buneary before she captured captured this Buneary.</description>
<picture>58877.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="24198" type="appears in" update="2010-11-08">
<name>Pachirisu (Hikari)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dawn captured Pachirisu which has a very hyperactive and mischievous personality.</description>
<picture>58878.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="24232" type="appears in" update="2010-11-08">
<name>Manmoo (Hikari)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mamoswine evolve after being attacked by Team Rocket.</description>
<picture>58881.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24438" type="appears in" update="2012-10-27">
<name>Mukuhawk (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ash`s Staraptor evolved during the PokéRinger competition held in Wind Town.</description>
<picture>59101.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="24475" type="appears in" update="2010-11-10">
<name>Moukazaru (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ash`s Monferno evolved during a full battle against Paul just after it defeated Paul`s Ursaring. Having grown in strength and power due to its evolution, it quickly showed everyone that it was a very formidable opponent. It learned Mach Punch right after its evolution from a Chimchar.</description>
<picture>59102.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="316" picture="25472.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26843" type="main character in" update="2011-06-06">
<rating votes="3">3.20</rating>
<name>Giza Mimi Pichu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Spiky-eared Pichu was friends with Damos and with the help of Ash`s Pikachu and Dawn`s Piplup, it was able to get the key to the cell where he, Ash, Dawn and Brock had been imprisoned.</description>
<picture>63698.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="453" picture="45925.jpg">Shindou Kei</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="106442" update="2011-06-23">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2009-08-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
