<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6816" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-01-10</startdate>
<enddate>2010-06-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Seikon no Qwaser</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">성흔의 퀘이사</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">圣痕炼金士</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">SnQ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Qwaser</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">聖痕のクェイサー</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The Qwaser of Stigmata</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8154" type="Sequel">Seikon no Qwaser II</anime>
<anime id="7971" type="Side Story">Seikon no Qwaser: Jotei no Shouzou</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8338" approval="17" total="19">Manyuu Hiken-chou</anime>
<anime id="8660" approval="6" total="17">High School DxD</anime>
<anime id="3348" approval="2" total="9">Fate/Stay Night</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="5">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="336778">This show had all the ingrédients to become a really interesting anime,  but they did crap from it.
They had a good background and chara design, the plot seemed interesting at the beginning... but it just turned to be stupid quite porn stuff....
Watch only if you wanna see porn and are underage  :D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="317702">the story is good but it is CEN maybe it is for children??!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="248024">Great character design, but so much fan service it will kill the most dedicated watcher off. Think Juebi-chan without the cute charming characters, but the nice action sequences. Not quite as nice as jubei action wise, but worth a watch if your bored.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="30310">In the opinion of many (including myself) it`s THE ecchi show of all times. Self imposed censorship, stricter laws and a saturation of the borderline hentai category probably ensure that this show will NOT be topped for a long time to come, if ever.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.qwaser.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3333" type="Character Design">Uno Makoto</name>
<name id="1540" type="Series Composition">Uezu Makoto</name>
<name id="4250" type="Original Work">Yoshino Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="3097" type="Direction">Kaneko Hiraku</name>
<name id="10188" type="Original Work">Satou Ken`etsu</name>
<name id="3672" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sugimoto Isao</name>
<name id="1793" type="Chief Animation Direction">Iijima Hiroya</name>
<name id="10106" type="Music">Katou Tatsuya</name>
<name id="11225" type="Animation Work">Hoods Entertainment</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the shounen manga series written by http://anidb.net/cr4250 [Yoshino Hiroyuki] and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr10188 [Satou Ken`etsu], serialised in http://anidb.net/cr32008 [Champion Red].
On the grounds of St. Mihailov Academy, a Japanese Eastern orthodox school, http://anidb.net/ch11293 [Oribe Mafuyu] and http://anidb.net/ch11294 [Yamanobe Tomo] encounter a mysterious, silver-haired, Russian boy named http://anidb.net/ch11297 [Sasha]. This pits them and the whole school in an all-out war between the Church itself and the so-called Adepts, a sect of individuals wielding powers linked to the elements of chemistry.
Source: Wikipedia
Note: Every TV broadcast was heavily censored. All scenes containing nudity and some panty shots were replaced with views of background art, even during action sequences; these cuts were common to a point they may confuse the viewer. An uncut "Director`s Cut" was streamed online, and the DVD/BD versions are also uncut.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2193">3.06</permanent>
<temporary count="2231">5.81</temporary>
<review count="2">8.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>37481.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10873</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8668</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>6500</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4575</identifier>
<identifier>ayykdg</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.qwaser.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>The_Qwaser_of_Stigmata</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>聖痕のクェイサー</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1828</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>336310</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12230</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="301" parentid="2848" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-10">
<name>lactation</name>
<description>Capable of secreting breast milk, sometimes referred to as Mother`s milk.</description>
<picurl>176139.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1894" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-04">
<name>shota</name>
<description>Shotacon, sometimes shortened to shota, is a Japanese slang portmanteau of the phrase Shoutarou complex and describes an attraction to young boys, or an individual with such an attraction. Outside Japan, the term is less common and most often refers to a genre of manga and anime wherein pre-pubescent or pubescent male characters are depicted in a suggestive or erotic manner.
In a general sense, this is the same as http://anidb.net/t2566 [loli], just replace young girls with young boys.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>35399.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2259" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-30">
<name>naked apron</name>
<description>A character wearing nothing but an apron appears in the show.</description>
<picurl>162045.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2455" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>tsundere</name>
<description>Tsundere (ツンデレ) (pronounced /(t)sʌnˈdɪə(r)/ in English or /t͡sun.de.ɽe/ in Japanese) is a Japanese concept of a character archetype which describes a person with a conceited, irritable, and/or violent personality that suddenly becomes modest and loving when triggered by some sort of cause (such as being alone with someone). The inverse scenario, where a modest and loving person becomes conceited/irritable/violent, is also a tsundere.
The default state does not matter. The character can default to "tsuntsun" or "deredere"; the key concept is the fact that there`s a (generally very quick) flip from one mode to the other.
It can also describe a contradictory personality which is good-willed on the inside, but with a harsh attitude on the outside. Originally found in Japanese bishoujo games, the word is now part of the otaku moe phenomenon, reaching into other media such as anime, manga, novels, and even mass media.
Tsundere is a portmanteau of the two words tsuntsun (ツンツン), and deredere (デレデレ). Tsuntsun is defined as "aloof, morose, pointed", and deredere is defined as "exhausted, lovestruck". Tsunderekko (ツンデレっ娘) is a related noun, referring to a girl with a tsundere personality. Like nekomimi, tsundere is considered a moe-inspiring character trait. The concept has received increasing attention in Japan, with a tsundere cafe opened in Akihabara and tsundere-themed products released (like Tomy Co.`s portable television set), and the concept increasingly reflected in recent anime, from an extended discussion of the meaning of the concept and its origin on the internet in http://anidb.net/a4777 [Lucky Star]`s Lucky Channel segment to merchandise for http://anidb.net/a3651 [The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya] classifying the characters according to tsundere-ness. Another accepted definition of tsundere is a girl who has a combative attitude toward others but is also kind on the inside. She usually plays out as having an attitude toward the main character, usually a male, and often criticizing him in one way or another, but as the series progresses she eventually warms up to him and sometimes even falls in love with him.</description>
<picurl>30388.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2566" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-31">
<name>loli</name>
<description>Lolita (often also just abbreviated to loli) refers originally to a novel by Vladimir Nabokov. The book is internationally famous for its controversial subject: the narrator and protagonist, middle aged Humbert Humbert, becomes obsessed and sexually involved with a 12-year-old girl named Dolores Haze.
Nowadays the name "Lolita" describes a sexually precocious young girl.
Related to this is http://anidb.net/t2415 [lolicon], the Japanese abbreviation of the English phrase "Lolita Complex". Sometimes written as "roricon" or "rorikon" due to the inexact mapping between Japanese and English phonemes. This is the term used to describe the fetish/fascination some mature people have for underage girls. There is an entire industry in Japan devoted to providing legal but schoolgirl-themed pornography, taking advantage of the cute childlike appearance some Japanese women maintain well into their twenties.
Because the characters in anime are often young by convention, many fans think that a character can only be Lolicon if she is twelve or younger. Exceptions are granted if the other character in the relationship is a lot older.
One particular device used to skirt the boundaries of taste and legality is the exotic being (alien, creature of magic, robot or the like) which takes the form of an underage human girl, but is in fact for all other practical purposes an adult.
Another reason why lolicon is fetishized by people may be because some of them just view it as a substitute for their fetish for flat-chested, but otherwise well-developed, women.
Source: Wikipedia / TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2675" parentid="2831" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Russia</name>
<description>Russia, officially known as the Russian Federation, is a sovereign country in Eurasia. Russia is the largest country in the world by area, covering more than one-eighth of the Earth`s inhabited land area, and the ninth most populous. The European western part of the country is much more populated and urbanised than the eastern; about 77% of the population live in European Russia. Russia`s capital Moscow is one of the largest cities in the world.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192045.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2713" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>oral</name>
<description>Oral sex is sexual activity involving the stimulation of the genitalia of a sex partner by the use of the mouth, tongue, teeth or throat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2823" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>paper clothes</name>
<description>Worn clothing appears paper-thin and takes little abuse to be shredded or torn from the body. This is common in ecchi anime where the main storyline involves some type of fighting but consists primarily of dialogue and fanservice (Ikkitousen and Platonic Heart). Various girls’ clothing exploding as if made of rice paper is a very enticing prospect.</description>
<picurl>150776.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2828" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-26">
<name>borderline porn</name>
<description>Breaks the bounds of "excessive fanservice".
While the physical interactions and dialogue between characters may be extremely sexual, the most sexual situations do *not* have sex itself take place.
Specifically descriptive of containing all the plentiful features of (excessive) fanservice in addition to the interactions between characters being quite sexual — at most, sexual in NATURE only. This means physical touching such as groping, molesting, or bondage will focus primarily on the revealed (i.e. nude) upper portion of the body or through/over clothing on the lower half of the body. This is all WITHOUT actual sex acts (penetration, etc.) taking place.</description>
<picurl>214855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2843" parentid="7220" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-08">
<name>sexual abuse -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is to be split into the following new tags under the http://anidb.net/t7220 [sexual abuse] category. Afterwards, delete this tag.

* http://anidb.net/t7222 [groping / molestation]
* http://anidb.net/t1306 [chikan]
* http://anidb.net/t7221 [psychological sexual abuse]
* http://anidb.net/t2715 [rape / attempted rape]
</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2895" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>dark-skinned girl</name>
<description>The anime features a girl with dark skin. A fetish of sorts, since the other protagonists are usually as white-skinned as porcelain dolls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2901" parentid="2729" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-09">
<name>bondage</name>
<description>Bondage is the use of restraints for the sexual pleasure of the parties involved. It may be used in its own right, as in the case of rope bondage and breast bondage, or as part of sexual activity or BDSM activity. When a person is sexually aroused by bondage, it may be considered a paraphilia, known as vincilagnia (from Latin vincio, to bind or fetter with chains, and lagneia, lust).
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42021.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2918" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>cunnilingus</name>
<description>Cunnilingus is an oral sex act performed on a female. It involves the use by a sex partner of the mouth, lips and tongue to stimulate the female`s clitoris and vulva. A female may receive cunnilingus as part of foreplay before sexual intercourse, or the sex partner may proceed until the female reaches orgasm.
The term is derived from the Latin words for the vulva (cunnus) and tongue (lingua).</description>
<picurl>161636.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3575" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-13">
<name>damsel in distress</name>
<description>The damsel in distress is usually a young, nubile woman placed in a dire predicament by a villain or a monster and requires a hero to dash to her rescue. Often used to unite the cast of a show for this one goal, to make them put differences aside and become a band of nakama. 
Examples: Sakoshita Yanagi from Rekka no Honoo, Yuuki Miaka from Fushigi Yuugi or Higurashi Kagome from Inuyasha.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3854" parentid="2891" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-03-13">
<name>breast expansion</name>
<description>When the breasts grow in size, right before the viewers eyes!
The breasts will slowly grow larger, either stretching clothing to its limit or bursting free completely!</description>
<picurl>184159.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3909" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>talking is a free action</name>
<description>Time in comics is flexible. Each panel shows a single event, which is usually accompanied by a length of dialog, which must take some time to say. This disparity is usually accepted if it isn`t taken to extremes.
But often, characters will exposit when it`s most needed: at the story`s climax, when both the intricacies of the plot and the intensity of action hit their highest.
While the Heroes Outrun the Fireball, Mr. Exposition might explain why the Evil Overlord`s death caused the explosion. The Action Girl can deliver impressive lectures on why the monster`s Achilles` Heel will work, while still engaging in Waif-Fu. The Superhero can quip to his heart`s content and explain his abilities while dueling one insignificant mobster, or deliver a Kirk Summation during the course of a single Finishing Move. Sometimes even apparent mere mortals can give a lecture on what is happening when it would be a much better idea to simply run like hell.
Without stopping to breathe, apparently.
Source: TvTrope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4112" parentid="3842" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-14">
<name>excessive censoring</name>
<description>There are basically two cases to which this term can be applied to:
1) creative censorship
The TV station airing the anime does its best to remove most ecchi parts from the show, using various and original methods. Usually, an uncensored BD/DVD is released later. Apart from the publisher`s greed - sometimes the censorship is used intentionally to make a scene look more obscene than it actually is.
2) convenient censorship
Another case of it - more often known under the term of "convenient censoring/ship" - is a blatant substitute for mosaic/steam/etc. over nether regions. This applies both to normal shows with occasional nudity as a normal part of human life (or just occasional flash of fanservice), as well as to heavy ecchi / borderline hentai shows where /literally/ everything is a fair (and far more "obscene" no matter how to look at it) game, except that misinterpreted taboo nonsense coming from §175 of JPC.</description>
<picurl>169459.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4302" parentid="2876" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-11-24">
<name>Christianity</name>
<description>Christianity is a monotheistic religion based on the life and teachings of Jesus of Nazareth as presented in the New Testament. http://anidb.net/t524 [Christians] believe Jesus is the son of God, God having become man and the saviour of humanity. Christians, therefore, commonly refer to Jesus as Christ or Messiah.
Source: EN Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4386" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-19">
<name>eating Pocky</name>
<description>Pocky (ポッキー) is a Japanese snack food produced by the Ezaki Glico Company of Japan. Pocky was first sold in 1966, and consists of a biscuit stick coated with chocolate. It was named after the Japanese onomatopoetic word for the sound Pocky makes when bitten, pokkin (ポッキン). The original was followed by "Almond Pocky" in 1971, with an almond coating, and "Strawberry Pocky" in 1977. Today, the product line includes such variations as milk, mousse, green tea, honey, banana and coconut flavored coatings, and themed products such as "Decorer Pocky," with colourful decorative stripes in the coating, and "Men`s Pocky," a dark (bittersweet) chocolate and "mature" version.
Source: Wikipedia
It`s marketed in Germany under the name Mikado (Note: NOT the game, the snack).</description>
<picurl>73630.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4947" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-23">
<name>oppai pillow</name>
<description>Japanese for "breast" pillow.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5455" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>creepy laugh</name>
<description>At least one character in the show inexplicably and repetitively seems to have the urgent need to laugh in a creepy, loud and usually very annoying way.
For male bad guys this seems to be a must, but some of the uppity (rich) female characters use the laugh as part of their condescending attitude as well.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5705" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-08-18">
<name>butchered foreign languages</name>
<description>In this anime, some characters "speak" foreign languages, successfully making the audience`s ears bleed. That is especially true if the viewer is a native speaker of or otherwise proficient in the languages in question.
The foreigners in the show do not seem to take much notice of the fact that their supposed native languages are being massacred. In fact, oftentimes they also actively participate in the butchering of said languages. That happens, of course, because they, too, are voiced by Japanese people without knowledge of the language they`re supposed to speak, or to pretend to speak at any rate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5859" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-30">
<name>monster of the week</name>
<description>On a pretty much regular basis — weekly or episodic — the protagonists engage in some kind of conflict. This can be an actual showdown between mecha, or the all-out fight against an enemy, or a (car) race that needs to be won.
This can make the anime quite repetitive.</description>
<picurl>60013.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5915" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>French kiss</name>
<description>A kiss in which the tongue enters the partner`s mouth.</description>
<picurl>238326.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6083" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>master-servant relationship</name>
<description>To some genres, this would suggest a genuine pairing where one person exists to serve another person, such as in some action/dramas where the pair becomes united by destiny as partners — fighting or battles between different pairs/partners will usually be a dominant part of the story.
In other genres, this suggests a relationship where one person may be occupied as or even forcefully treated as a servant or slave to the other who designates themself the master — these services usually apply anywhere from tsundere/romantic-comedies to ecchi or to the more extreme in hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="11293" type="main character in" update="2010-04-26">
<rating votes="76">7.41</rating>
<name>Oribe Mafuyu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The titular female character, Mafuyu is the adopted daughter of St.Mihailov`s last dean, and the self-appointed protector of Yamanobe Tomo. Upbeat and cheerful, she is so proficient in kendo that she carries a wooden sword with her all the time. She has to endure hardship on a daily basis in form of her classmates picking harshly on her and especially Tomo. This changes when she encounters Sasha for the first time, where she starts living with him and, little by little, is pitted herself in the fights between Qwasers. Though at odds with Sasha`s coldness, Mafuyu has started to open up to him and the two have formed a stronger bond. A running gag has Mafuyu hit heavily Tomo when the latter makes mistakes.</description>
<picture>46957.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11294" type="main character in" update="2010-04-26">
<rating votes="71">6.24</rating>
<name>Yamanobe Tomo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Daughter of St. Mihailov`s last dean and currently best friend and roommate of Oribe Mafuyu, Tomo is her exact opposite, both physically and mentally: she herself is very childish and naïve, and while having the largest bust of the whole female cast so far, she is physically weak. Tomo is the spitting image of Sasha`s original protector, Olja, which explains why he took so willingly the role of Tomo`s guardian, much to Mafuyu`s chagrin. Also, sometimes an upside down Eastern Cross (with its third slab being a scar), the symbol of the Adepts, appears between her breasts. This is later revealed to be the presence of the Qwaser of Gold, which apparently inhabits Tomo`s body and, as itself stated, is slowly draining her of her life, which is why she has to replenish herself through Teresa`s Soma.</description>
<picture>46958.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11295" type="main character in" update="2010-04-26">
<rating votes="41">8.35</rating>
<name>Teresa Beria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Serbian Orthodox nun that serves at St. Mihailov in a variety of ordinary chores, such as taking care of children in the school`s kindergarten or tending to flowers, she is the only survivor of a brutal massacre occurred in Serbia during the Yugoslav Wars, where an expedition led by Croa raped and slaughtered all the inhabitants of Teresa`s church. Due to her assisting at the whole carnage while hidden, she became completely emotionless and stopped smiling, crying or feeling anything, and thus is presented as almost ghostly due to her quietness. Only when Croa reappears and Teresa has to recall the brutalities of her past, does she gain enough courage to face them and begin to show emotions again. She usually provides Sasha with her Soma, but can hold her own in combat by means of martial arts, a bow and huge blades concealed in her skirt.</description>
<picture>46972.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="245" picture="46862.jpg">Chihara Minori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11296" type="main character in" update="2010-04-26">
<rating votes="107">6.99</rating>
<name>Katya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A little Russian girl, no more than ten years old and with the beauty of a doll, she arrives in Japan shortly after the beginning of the war of the Qwasers. While she is presented as extremely shy and child-like, befitting her age (she has a habit of addressing herself in third person in these instances), her true colours depicts her as a domineering, arrogant, prideful and almost malicious queen, all maintaining a façade of childish innocence. She is a powerful Qwaser who wields the element of copper, which usually makes her gain control and manipulate electrical wires and redirect their flow to electrocute and incinerate her foes. She does not fight herself due to her frailty as a little girl, and this is why she is always guarded by a grim, archaic gynoid dressed in regal attire named Anastasia, which Ekaterina calls mother for reason currently unknown. Currently she attends at St. Mihailov`s primary school, being the subject of admiration and love of her classmates and teachers thanks to her doll-like features, and has Hana serve as her slave and replenish her of Soma. Recently, it has been revealed that she shares heavy connections with the Imperial Family of late Tsar Nicholas II, and it is heavily hinted that she herself is the same Tsarina Alexandra that served as Nicholas` consort, though this is has not been proved, just suggested by Ekaterina herself (although this would also explain why her guardian gynoid is named Anastasia).</description>
<picture>46967.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4" picture="177060.jpg">Hirano Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11297" type="main character in" update="2010-04-26">
<rating votes="55">6.45</rating>
<name>Sasha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The titular character and male protagonist of the story, Alexander is a young Qwaser of Russian origin that controls the element of Iron, with which he can manipulate the said element on a molecular level, thus being capable not only to morph it in any form he wishes, but also create extreme heat or cold. He was held captive and trained with the other Qwasers into harnessing his powers, and survived the brutal ordeal thanks to the affection received from an older girl named Olja, and whose murder by the Qwaser of Gold he witnessed. He received a large scar on the left side of his face from the same Qwaser. The scar is shaped like an Eastern Cross, and tends to bleed heavily when he draws upon his powers. He appeared out of nowhere on the grounds of St. Mihailov, and was quickly accepted into the school as a student of class 1-A, the same that Mafuyu Oribe and Tomo Yamanobe attend. He became Tomo`s protector because of her resemblance to Olja. Silver-haired with blue eyes, Alexander, or Sasha for short (though he allows only those close to him to call him by this nickname) is usually extremely cold, harsh and serious, although his weakness for borscht, his favourite dish, can soften him. He slowly changed and warmed to those around him, especially Mafuyu, though he remains extremely fierce when fighting other Qwasers. Usually he fights wielding an enormous black scythe that is at least twice his size. Sometimes he tends to comment on things in Russian.</description>
<picture>46956.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="81" picture="41282.jpg">Sanpei Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12417" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-26">
<rating votes="70">6.21</rating>
<name>Katsuragi Hana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A student of class 1-A, she acts as an enforcer on school grounds, but also she is the main architect of the physical abuses that Mafuyu and Tomo have to endure every day, such as regularly throwing the class` garbage can on them or forcing them to fill it after "casually" tripping on it, to covering Tomo`s desk with writings and trash. Being the right hand of Miyuri, she welcomes Ekaterina Kurae when she arrives in Japan, and it`s here that her apparent fondness for lolicon is discovered, as she becomes extremely embarrassed in Ekaterina`s presence and, while the latter fakes to fade out, she kisses her out of lust. These events let her become the unwilling slave of her new mistress, subject to humiliation and erotic torment on a daily basis (which, on a side note, made her very proficient in S&amp;M, such as making extremely complex nodes with little effort). She appears to have some masochistic tendencies, as she derives pleasure from Ekaterina`s abuses.</description>
<picture>46973.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12418" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-29">
<rating votes="66">7.81</rating>
<name>Tsujidou Miyuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The daughter of the current dean at St. Mihailov Academy, who succeeded Tomo`s father. While beautiful and well-endowed, Miyuri is extremely bossy, arrogant and prideful, making nothing to conceal her disrespect for Tomo and Mafuyu and to bully them on a daily basis, supported by Hana. Greatly humiliated by Sasha, who correctly defines her as a leecher of others` powers, she "takes revenge" by welcoming and taking care of Ekaterina Kurae, the Quaser of Copper. It can be noted that Miyuri is very rich and appears to have a sheltered upbringing, based on her drowning Ekaterina with expensive gifts. However, being treated as a fool after Sasha`s arrival made her somewhat of a comic relief character. On a positive note, it can be assumed that she truly cares even for those she bullies, as she stripped naked for a group of terrorists so as to spare the same ordeal to Ekaterina, Mafuyu and the others.</description>
<picture>39436.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12419" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-22">
<rating votes="58">6.77</rating>
<name>Mitarai Fumika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The class president.</description>
<picture>39437.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13999" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-10">
<rating votes="8">6.43</rating>
<name>Yuuri Noda</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41277.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="375" picture="17221.jpg">Chiba Susumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14000" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="4">3.18</rating>
<name>Minase Ayana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A bespectacled classmate of Tomo and Mafuyu, Ayana appears to be one of the only students of class 1-A willing to take their side despite them being bullied or ignored while mistreated. Though she appears to be gentle and weak, she is in fact the very first Adept to appear in the series.
Her true identity is that of a Qwaser, and she wields control over the element of magnesium, which she usually shapes in razor-sharp chakrams that she throws and controls in both trajectory and shape, being also capable of igniting them with fire. Revealing her friendship with Tomo and Mafuyu to be mere acting, she confronts Sasha three times, being killed during their third battle after failing to kidnap and held Tomo as a hostage. As a clone without will, she is later summoned to fight against Ootori Shin`ichiro.</description>
<picture>41278.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="411" picture="17475.jpg">Takagaki Ayahi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14145" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-17">
<rating votes="2">3.23</rating>
<name>Yamanobe Yuudai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41597.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="695" picture="38273.jpg">Ono Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15807" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-14">
<rating votes="3">1.77</rating>
<name>Fool</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44605.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2281" picture="171603.jpg">Katou Masayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15808" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-14">
<rating votes="35">8.52</rating>
<name>Oikawa Urara</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44606.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15809" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-14">
<rating votes="31">6.72</rating>
<name>Elizabeth</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl with short blonde hair and red eyes, whose undeveloped body, brash manners and manner of dressing make similar to a boy, she is a disciple to Shin`ichiro Ootori and a Qwaser herself, whose element is titanium, that she primarily wields in a massive double-handed greatsword she calls Excalibur, after the legendary blade from the Arthurian myth, which can not only cut through practically anything, but when drawn produces a deafening wail. Deeply loyal to her master, she bitterly followed him when he feigned treachery so as to draw the Qwaser of Gold out of hiding, where she provided defence for him by challenging Sasha, who however spared her life. After Ootori`s death she accepted Teresa as her partner and joined the ranks of Athos, thus becoming an ally to Sasha and his companions.</description>
<picture>44607.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="550" picture="151677.jpg">Shimizu Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15810" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-14">
<rating votes="6">8.47</rating>
<name>Ootori Shin`ichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44608.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15811" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-14">
<rating votes="7">6.58</rating>
<name>Kuchiba Aoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44609.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42" picture="155105.jpg">Hayamizu Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15812" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-14">
<rating votes="3">1.18</rating>
<name>Kuchiba Yuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44610.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42" picture="155105.jpg">Hayamizu Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15813" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-14">
<rating votes="3">3.91</rating>
<name>Joshua Phrygianos</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An unnumbered member of the Adepts, and a true rarity among them, serving somehow as the faction`s comic relief character. A young man whose sister, Jita, is ranked number four in the organization, he was mistreated by his peers due to his element, roentgenium, being weak and useless, which led others to treat him as inferior, someone unfit to be a Qwaser. He boasts himself with the title of Successor of Hermes Trismegistus, though he is in fact generous and caring, if somehow foolish sometimes. He tried in vain to kidnap Tomo, who peacefully succeeded in making him realize his mistake, and then he was the first one to welcome her to the Adept`s hideout.</description>
<picture>44611.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="263" picture="186711.jpg">Matsukaze Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15995" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-27">
<rating votes="15">4.93</rating>
<name>Eva Silver</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Queen of the Living Silver, controlling the element mercury, able to summon it in vast quantities and solidify it at will, turning the substance into razor-sharp wires and blades, droplets as powerful as bullets, and other solid objects or even traps. While Sasha and Ekaterina were fighting http://anidb.net/ch15996 [Eva-Q] and http://anidb.net/ch15997 [Eva-R], the real Eva Silver appeared out of nowhere in Mafuyu`s class, killing their teacher by smothering him with mercury and then proceeding to "teach" the class about the beauty of cruelty and humiliation upon others, ironically also reprimanding the students about their bullying of Mafuyu. One of the most sadistic and deranged characters appeared so far, Eva was the original source of all of her clones, younger versions of herself who were given physical immortality so as to endure the atrocious tortures imposed on them by their mistress, whom they adored as their only queen and were then massacred and reabsorbed into Eva`s body, so as to keep her young and beautiful. Highly prideful, Eva was initially defeated by Sasha, when she was crucified and set ablaze, yet she reappeared shortly after, gruesomely disfigured, kidnapping Mafuyu and forcing Sasha to fight once more. It was Ekaterina who shed light upon Eva`s identity, unmasking her as Eva Braun, the wife-lover of Nazi dictator http://anidb.net/ch21 [Adolf Hitler]. Believing her acts of depravity, especially cloning and reassimilating herself, as the true manifestation of the Nazi idea of a supreme being, she was defeated nonetheless, and completely torn apart by Ekaterina`s gynoid, in the end revealing herself to be fearful of death. A cloned corpse of Eva Silver was later used in the botched attempt, made by the Qwaser of Gold and Friederich Tanner, to summon Sword`s Maria. Her position in the Adepts` hierarchy is unknown.</description>
<picture>44992.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="82" picture="216596.jpg">Asakawa Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15996" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-27">
<rating votes="10">3.17</rating>
<name>Eva-Q</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A pair of deranged, ghastly twin sisters dressed in scandalous, bondage-looking suits and armed with a wide variety of obscene BDSM tools, which suddenly appeared at St. Mihailov, searching for Sasha, begging those they asked informations to "order" them - that is, to torture them to death with the array of gadgets they carried, with refusal immediately followed by "disqualification", the gruesome death of their would be-master. Probably the most extreme example of the brutality of the Adepts, Eva-Q and Eva-R were clones of their original, Eva Silver, engineered to be physically immortal, no matter how massive their injuries, capable of using the element mercury like their mistress, and also completely crazy, driven by constant rape and torture to such extremes of insanity that they recognized pain with pleasure, crying out in bliss even when superficially wounded. Possibly due to their pitiful condition, Sasha fought them only briefly, leaving the job to Ekaterina, who was much more eager to kill the twins. She only managed to keep them at bay however, until their "mother", Eva Silver, was wounded by Sasha and used them to cure herself. Another clone, Eva-S, briefly appeared when Eva kidnapped Mafuyu, though she was quickly incinerated from the inside-out by Shin`Ichiro Ootori, who ignited the sodium in her body and, thus, prevented her from regenerating.</description>
<picture>44993.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15997" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-27">
<rating votes="11">3.31</rating>
<name>Eva-R</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A pair of deranged, ghastly twin sisters dressed in scandalous, bondage-looking suits and armed with a wide variety of obscene BDSM tools, which suddenly appeared at St. Mihailov, searching for Sasha, begging those they asked informations to "order" them - that is, to torture them to death with the array of gadgets they carried, with refusal immediately followed by "disqualification", the gruesome death of their would be-master. Probably the most extreme example of the brutality of the Adepts, Eva-Q and Eva-R were clones of their original, Eva Silver, engineered to be physically immortal, no matter how massive their injuries, capable of using the element mercury like their mistress, and also completely crazy, driven by constant rape and torture to such extremes of insanity that they recognized pain with pleasure, crying out in bliss even when superficially wounded. Possibly due to their pitiful condition, Sasha fought them only briefly, leaving the job to Ekaterina, who was much more eager to kill the twins. She only managed to keep them at bay however, until their "mother", Eva Silver, was wounded by Sasha and used them to cure herself. Another clone, Eva-S, briefly appeared when Eva kidnapped Mafuyu, though she was quickly incinerated from the inside-out by Shin`Ichiro Ootori, who ignited the sodium in her body and, thus, prevented her from regenerating.</description>
<picture>44994.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17107" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-26">
<rating votes="8">6.94</rating>
<name>Sendou Mutsumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Former partner of Sasha and currently both partner and lover of Fujiomi Tasuku, Mutsumi is an upbeat, cheerful and well-endowed girl who rarely lets her inhibitions restrain her - for instance, she is bisexual and openly flirts with Mafuyu, much to her dismay. She encountered Tasuku shortly after Sasha left Athos, nursing him back to health and winning his trust and, with that, his love, which she reciprocates. Similarly to Teresa her primary role is to provide Soma to her partner, though she can defend herself using a pair of bladed tonfa.</description>
<picture>46953.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1980" picture="173075.jpg">Kurokawa Nami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17108" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-26">
<rating votes="3">4.52</rating>
<name>Fujiomi Tasuku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Japanese boy with a wild look and an aggressive personality, not to mention something of a womaniser, he confronted Sasha soon after his appearance, revealing himself to be a powerful Qwaser, whose abilities initially surprised Sasha, as Taisuku apparently had his same powers, though he managed to use them better. He is indeed a Qwaser, but his element is neodymium, which allows him to control any kind of metal through magnetism, not by interacting to it at the molecular level. He is also very skilled in Buddhist incantations, as he is the sole heir of a family of sorcerers and shamans, and thus can create elaborate incantations or even Buddhist-related weapons. His explosive personality and his occasional foolishness harbour a dark secret however: as a child he was greatly traumatized when his mother was brutally raped in front of him, which led him to become mad with ideas of revenge and turn to a life of constant conflict, slowly drifting to senseless anger. His encounter with Mutsumi Sendou saved him, and the two became inseparable since then. Though initially antagonistic, Taisuku quickly became a valuable ally, though he was accused of raping Hana and had to fight Ekaterina, when Friederich Tanner pitted the two against each other. When angered, he fights with a murderous frenzy that makes him attack with blind fury, especially if it`s Mutsumi who`s in danger.</description>
<picture>46954.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1692" picture="224934.jpg">Okitsu Kazuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18501" type="appears in" update="2010-06-05">
<rating votes="3">6.02</rating>
<name>Wilma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49165.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1439" picture="223493.jpg">Takahashi Ao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18502" type="appears in" update="2010-06-05">
<rating votes="2">1.38</rating>
<name>Croa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49164.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1942" picture="50629.jpg">Amada Masuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19029" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-20">
<rating votes="3">1.39</rating>
<name>Jackal</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50049.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19" picture="50583.jpg">Imaruoka Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19030" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-20">
<rating votes="9">5.59</rating>
<name>Jita Phrygianos</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50050.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="142" picture="68482.jpg">Ooura Fuyuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19031" type="appears in" update="2010-06-20">
<rating votes="3">5.36</rating>
<name>Astarte</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50051.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1671" picture="19766.jpg">Gotou Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19032" type="appears in" update="2010-06-20">
<rating votes="2">3.23</rating>
<name>Sanada Doukan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50053.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="19033" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-20">
<rating votes="3">2.71</rating>
<name>Wan Chen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50054.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="373" picture="191382.jpg">Hamada Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19034" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-20">
<rating votes="2">4.05</rating>
<name>Friederich Tanner</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50055.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="387" picture="17233.jpg">Narita Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19035" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-20">
<rating votes="2">2.55</rating>
<name>Georg Tanner</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50056.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19036" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-20">
<rating votes="2">4.99</rating>
<name>Milk</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50057.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="26397" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-03">
<rating votes="5">6.11</rating>
<name>Lulu no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61943.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="36173" type="appears in" update="2011-09-01">
<name>Athos</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="36174" type="appears in" update="2011-09-05">
<name>Adept</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Adept is a secret group of thirteen Qwasers who, much like Athos, desire to uncover the Theotokos, though apparently to use its powers for their own ends. They were introduced as a cult-like organisation best known for its extreme brutality and harsh ways to initiate new members, willing or not, to their cause. Sasha was part of their ranks before being wounded and banished by the Qwaser of Gold, who appears to be the sect`s leader. However, recent chapters have revealed the group to be far less sinister, showing them to be respectable - albeit still sinister - people. Subsidiary to the Adepts appears to be a secretive organisation known as Paracelsus, formed from the remnants of Japan`s Unit 731 and the Nazi eugenics program, whose members, through demented medical science, can conquer feat deemed impossible and blasphemous, such as reviving the dead and cloning at will. Their base appears to be a secluded place named Magnolia, the ruins of a fortress splendidly decorate by lush gardens, which stands in stark contrast with the grim portrait of the organisation.</description>
</character>
<character id="76933" type="appears in" update="2015-08-20">
<rating votes="5">7.23</rating>
<name>Big Mom</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The strongest tactician of the Athos. She is a strong muscled woman who wears a nun uniform, known as Big Ma`am. Her real name is Nikuma. Nikuma is a burly woman and the best strategist of Athos according to Teresa. Referred to as "Hell`s Dairy Cow" by Teresa, she is a master tactician and trainer for the Qwasers of Athos. She also handles the occasional training of the group of Qwasers at the St. Mihailov Academy. She has a military attitude and is harsh in her methods, but despite this she has the best intentions.</description>
<picture>176542.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36" picture="228350.jpg">Saitou Kimiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90887" type="appears in" update="2017-08-12">
<rating votes="1">4.08</rating>
<name>Lily Kamen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65293.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="112086" update="2009-12-16">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-10-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">聖痕のクェイサー 無修正PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Qwaser of Stigmata - Uncut Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112932" update="2010-01-09">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">震える夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Quavering Night</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Uma Noite Trêmula!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Furueru Yoru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112954" update="2010-01-10">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-01-17</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">仮面の友情</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Friendship of Masks</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kamen no Yuujou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112969" update="2011-04-23">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112970" update="2010-01-11">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="113077" update="2010-01-16">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-01-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">求めし者たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Seeker</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Motomeshimonotachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="113101" update="2010-01-18">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="113230" update="2010-01-24">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-01-31</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">女王様とあたし</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Queen &amp; I</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Joousama to Atashi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="113911" update="2010-01-31">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-02-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦場の白ユリ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">White Lilies of the Battlefield</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senjou no Shiroi Yuri</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116176" update="2010-02-03">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116314" update="2010-02-07">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-02-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">皇女の卵</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Princess` Egg</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koujo no Tamago</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116364" update="2010-02-10">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-02-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">漂白の生神女(マリア)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bleached White Maria</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hyouhaku no Maria</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116365" update="2010-02-10">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-02-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">双面のアトミス (前編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Atomis of Two Faces: Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futaomote no Atomis (Zenpen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116366" update="2010-02-10">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-03-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">双面のアトミス (後編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Atomis of Two Faces: Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futaomote no Atomis (Kouhen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116803" update="2010-03-07">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-03-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめて(?)のおるすばん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">House-Sitting for the First Time?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete (?) no Orusuban</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116831" update="2010-03-10">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-03-21</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔女の十字架</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Witch`s Crucifix</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Majo no Juujika</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116832" update="2010-03-10">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-03-28</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鮮血の剣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stigmata Sword</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senketsu no Tsurugi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116833" update="2010-03-10">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-04</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">含鉄泉の夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Night at the Iron Spring</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gantetsusen no Yoru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117426" update="2010-04-04">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-11</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">辻堂美由梨の憂鬱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Melancholy of Miyori Tsujido</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsujidou Miyori no Yuuutsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117492" update="2010-10-20">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-04-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117493" update="2010-07-19">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-04-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117606" update="2010-04-10">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-18</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Anglo-Russian Entente</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Anglo-Russian Entente</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anglo-Russian Entente</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117607" update="2010-04-10">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">断罪の不死鳥</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Phoenix of Conviction</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dansai no Fushichou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117608" update="2010-04-10">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-02</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">炎の福音</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gospel of Flames</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Honoo no Fukuin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117609" update="2010-04-10">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ウロボロスの罠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Uroboros` Trap</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uroboros no Wana</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117929" update="2011-04-23">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピクチャードラマ 「カーチャ様と遊ぼう ☆ 第二夜」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama: Play with Katya-sama - Second Night</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Picture Drama: Katya-sama to Asobou - Dainiya</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117930" update="2011-04-23">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピクチャードラマ 「ドキッ! 聖痕のクェイサー秘話 その2 華編」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama: Doki! Seikon no Qwaser Secret Episode 2 - Hana Edition</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Picture Drama: Doki! Seikon no Qwaser Hiwa Sono 2 - Hana Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117931" update="2010-07-31">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-04-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピクチャードラマ 「カーチャ様と遊ぼう ☆ 第一夜」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama: Play with Katya-sama - First Night</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Picture Drama: Katya-sama to Asobou - Daiichiya</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117932" update="2010-07-31">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-04-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピクチャードラマ 「ドキッ! 聖痕のクェイサー秘話 その1 燈編」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama: Doki! Seikon no Qwaser Secret Episode 1 - Tomo Edition</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Picture Drama: Doki! Seikon no Qwaser Hiwa Sono 1 - Tomo Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118248" update="2010-05-09">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-16</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">秘密の花園</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Secret Garden</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Himitsu no Hanazono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118271" update="2010-05-10">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-23</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハリボテ皇女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Figurehead Princess</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haribote Koujo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118272" update="2010-05-10">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-30</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">水の聖堂</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Aquatic Sanctuary</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mizu no Seidou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118273" update="2010-05-10">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-06</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トリニティ・ゲヘナ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trinity Gehenna</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Trinity Gehenna</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118712" update="2010-06-07">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-13</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">致命者サーシャ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sasha, the Fatal One</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chimeisha Sasha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118836" update="2010-06-10">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-20</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">汝, 青春することなかれ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You, Live Not Your Youth!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sonata, Seishun Suru Koto Nakare</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119271" update="2011-03-24">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-06-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピクチャードラマ 「カーチャ様と遊ぼう ☆ 第三夜」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama: Play with Katya-sama - Third Night</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Picture Drama: Katya-sama to Asobou - Daisan`ya</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119272" update="2011-03-24">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-06-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピクチャードラマ 「ドキッ! 聖痕のクェイサー秘話 その3 まふゆ編」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama: Doki! Seikon no Qwaser Secret Episode 3 - Mafuyu Edition</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Picture Drama: Doki! Seikon no Qwaser Hiwa Sono 3 - Mafuyu Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119940" update="2011-04-23">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-02-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119941" update="2010-08-11">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピクチャードラマ 「カーチャ様と遊ぼう ☆ 第四夜」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama: Play with Katya-sama - Fourth Night</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Picture Drama: Katya-sama to Asobou - Daiyon`ya</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119942" update="2010-08-11">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピクチャードラマ 「ドキッ! 聖痕のクェイサー秘話 その4 史伽編」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama: Doki! Seikon no Qwaser Secret Episode 4 - Fumika Edition</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Picture Drama: Doki! Seikon no Qwaser Hiwa Sono 4 - Fumika Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119943" update="2010-07-15">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-08-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピクチャードラマ 「カーチャ様と遊ぼう ☆ 第五夜」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama: Play with Katya-sama - Fifth Night</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Picture Drama: Katya-sama to Asobou - Daigoya</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119944" update="2010-07-15">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-08-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピクチャードラマ 「ドキッ! 聖痕のクェイサー秘話 その5 美由梨編」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama: Doki! Seikon no Qwaser Secret Episode 5 - Miyuri Edition</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Picture Drama: Doki! Seikon no Qwaser Hiwa Sono 5 - Miyuri Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121508" update="2010-08-27">
<epno type="2">S14</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピクチャードラマ 「カーチャ様と遊ぼう ☆ 第七夜」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama: Play with Katya-sama - Seventh Night</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Picture Drama: Katya-sama to Asobou - Dainanaya</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121509" update="2010-08-27">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピクチャードラマ 「ドキッ! 聖痕のクェイサー秘話 その7 燈編」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama: Doki! Seikon no Qwaser Secret Episode 7 - Tomo Edition</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Picture Drama: Doki! Seikon no Qwaser Hiwa Sono 7 - Tomo Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121510" update="2010-08-27">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-09-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピクチャードラマ 「カーチャ様と遊ぼう ☆ 第六夜」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama: Play with Katya-sama - Sixth Night</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Picture Drama: Katya-sama to Asobou - Dairokuya</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121511" update="2010-08-27">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-09-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピクチャードラマ 「ドキッ! 聖痕のクェイサー秘話 その6 華編」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama: Doki! Seikon no Qwaser Secret Episode 6 - Hana Edition</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Picture Drama: Doki! Seikon no Qwaser Hiwa Sono 6 - Hana Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125647" update="2010-11-30">
<epno type="2">S15</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-11-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピクチャードラマ 「ドキッ! 聖痕のクェイサー秘話 その8 まふゆ編」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama: Doki! Seikon no Qwaser Secret Episode 8 - Mafuyu Edition</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Picture Drama: Doki! Seikon no Qwaser Hiwa Sono 8 - Mafuyu Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125648" update="2010-11-30">
<epno type="2">S16</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-11-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピクチャードラマ 「カーチャ様と遊ぼう ☆ 第八夜」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama: Play with Katya-sama - Eighth Night</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Picture Drama: Katya-sama to Asobou - Daihachiya</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126494" update="2010-12-29">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>7</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Vol 08 Preview TV Edition + CDDrama by Mafuyu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126495" update="2010-12-29">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Vol 01 Preview TV Edition</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126496" update="2010-12-29">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview Notice Collection</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
