<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6818" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-04-12</startdate>
<enddate>2010-09-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Uragiri wa Boku no Namae o Shitte Iru</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Betrayal Knows My Name</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="synonym">Fesseln des Verrats</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">الغدر يعرف اسمي</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Uragiri wa Boku no Namae wo Shitteiru</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Uraboku</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">裏切りは僕の名前を知っている</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The Betrayal Knows My Name</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">无法逃离的背叛</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="5586" approval="27" total="41">Vampire Knight</anime>
<anime id="2815" approval="9" total="17">Loveless</anime>
<anime id="750" approval="8" total="12">Yami no Matsuei</anime>
<anime id="787" approval="3" total="3">Honoo no Mirage</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="6">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="353463">A cool touch of fantasy, bishounen and drama, this anime is a wonder for every fan-girls. Though it has an intriguing plot with many side stories, it tends to be too slow-paced and lagging at some point. This, plus the fact that it never truly has a proper ending, make this series a forgettable and mediocre one.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="417666">Bishie rating 10/10, decent-satifying anime plot rating 3/10 and our typical pure hearted, naive and clueless main character portrait rating -500/10... Watch if you dare...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="533493">A story about reincarnation, a never ending battle and love and friendship. The anime depicts friendship between men in a very strange, erotic way. The one real love-relation seems a bit weak and not much developed. The story overall is slow paced and not very emotional. Might be a so-so experience if you like men acting like girls in someone`s weird imagination. I didn`t like it very much.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="425705">i think,everyone,who like anime with demon type and romance -and beautiful boys-its a must.its also reminds me to vampire knight in a way.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="384866">This anime is gorgeous. Not only is it drawn almost perfect an meszmerising it will pull you right in. Some parts can be a little too mushy so if you`re into bloody fighting over nothing animes this is not your thing. Main theme here is friendship. Only dissapointing thing so far is the ending because it gives no closure at all....it`s a bit of a fairy tale now. Anyhow a must see in my opinion!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.uraboku.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="9166" type="Music">Kaida Shougo</name>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="11736" type="Character Design">Matsuura Mai</name>
<name id="4133" type="Character Design">Nakayama Yumi</name>
<name id="1465" type="Series Composition">Takahashi Natsuko</name>
<name id="21562" type="Original Work">Odagiri Hotaru</name>
<name id="4648" type="Direction">Sakurabi Katsushi</name>
<name id="4133" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nakayama Yumi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a shoujo manga by http://anidb.net/cr21562 [Odagiri Hotaru], serialised in http://anidb.net/cr22671 [Monthly Asuka].
http://anidb.net/ch15276 [Sakurai Yuki] is a mysterious boy with a mysterious power. Right after he was born, his mother left him near an orphanage, and he was later found. Because of that event, Yuki strives for independence. He hates being a burden to anyone near him, but at the same time, he is afraid of being left alone. Moreover, ever since he can remember he had a strange ability where when he touches others, he can feel their emotion. Unable to control it, he often made insensitive blunders in the past. He later meets with a mysterious yet beautiful man who saves his life, but somehow he feels so nostalgic, like he`s met him before. While death threats and his ability increasing, a man who claimed to be his older brother suddenly appears, so what will Yuki do when he learns the truth?</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="550">4.41</permanent>
<temporary count="556">6.44</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>42228.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11033</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7058</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4675</identifier>
<identifier>vmrobb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.uraboku.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Uragiri_wa_Boku_no_Namae_o_Shitteiru</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>裏切りは僕の名前を知っている</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1906</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>336388</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12525</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2580</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2010/uraboku</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B06WD1SFJS</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1244" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>summoning</name>
<description>Ability to call/materialize some kind of creature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1632" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-13">
<name>twin -- TO BE DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is meant to be purged in the short term. Please DO NOT assign it to any further characters; add the appropriate char-char relations to them instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2355" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>dragon</name>
<description>Very intelligent mythical beings - a cross between a very large lizard and a dinosaur - that breath fire, and have a knack for kidnapping damsels, thus distressing them. In Fantasy anime this perceptive species often lives secluded from human civilisation, protectors of long lost knowledge. Dragons seem to be on the verge of extinction.</description>
<picurl>32579.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2455" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>tsundere</name>
<description>Tsundere (ツンデレ) (pronounced /(t)sʌnˈdɪə(r)/ in English or /t͡sun.de.ɽe/ in Japanese) is a Japanese concept of a character archetype which describes a person with a conceited, irritable, and/or violent personality that suddenly becomes modest and loving when triggered by some sort of cause (such as being alone with someone). The inverse scenario, where a modest and loving person becomes conceited/irritable/violent, is also a tsundere.
The default state does not matter. The character can default to "tsuntsun" or "deredere"; the key concept is the fact that there`s a (generally very quick) flip from one mode to the other.
It can also describe a contradictory personality which is good-willed on the inside, but with a harsh attitude on the outside. Originally found in Japanese bishoujo games, the word is now part of the otaku moe phenomenon, reaching into other media such as anime, manga, novels, and even mass media.
Tsundere is a portmanteau of the two words tsuntsun (ツンツン), and deredere (デレデレ). Tsuntsun is defined as "aloof, morose, pointed", and deredere is defined as "exhausted, lovestruck". Tsunderekko (ツンデレっ娘) is a related noun, referring to a girl with a tsundere personality. Like nekomimi, tsundere is considered a moe-inspiring character trait. The concept has received increasing attention in Japan, with a tsundere cafe opened in Akihabara and tsundere-themed products released (like Tomy Co.`s portable television set), and the concept increasingly reflected in recent anime, from an extended discussion of the meaning of the concept and its origin on the internet in http://anidb.net/a4777 [Lucky Star]`s Lucky Channel segment to merchandise for http://anidb.net/a3651 [The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya] classifying the characters according to tsundere-ness. Another accepted definition of tsundere is a girl who has a combative attitude toward others but is also kind on the inside. She usually plays out as having an attitude toward the main character, usually a male, and often criticizing him in one way or another, but as the series progresses she eventually warms up to him and sometimes even falls in love with him.</description>
<picurl>30388.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2973" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-24">
<name>cute monster</name>
<description>Cute monster refers to animal soldiers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3528" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-05-13">
<name>reincarnation</name>
<description>One of the main characters was reborn in another body.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3663" parentid="6347" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-14">
<name>body takeover</name>
<description>A person`s body is taken over by some foreign intelligence. It`s not brainwashing, because they still have control of their own mind — but that`s all they have. Either they`ve been reduced to a spectator in their own body, or their soul has been booted out of their body entirely. Either way, the rest of the cast will soon find he`s not himself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4057" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-19">
<name>magical creatures</name>
<description>Magical creatures are beings associated with a fantasy setting, thus do not exist in reality. Apparently they were "created of" or "powered by" magic. An incantation may have brought them into existence.
Examples: A legendary creature, a mythological or folkloric creature, a fairy or demon, ...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4110" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>life force</name>
<description>Life force exists in many forms and is known under many names. It is the invisible fuel that runs human bodies and is resistent against scientific research and explanation. However, this very energy is one of the most powerful forces in the universe. Especially in mahou shoujo anime, the big bad evil will always try to steal it for their plans, bad guys from outer space will need it as food and even the good guys will often use their life force to bring back dead to life again, eventually sacrificing their life in the course of such an event.
Other energy sources known to mankind are the power of love and the power of friendship.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4182" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-01-22">
<name>hidden power</name>
<description>For some reason or another a character has powers (or potential) he or she can`t access and may not even know about. 
In some anime these hidden powers are used quite frequently to overcome an enemy or threat (e.g. Naruto, Bleach).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4481" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>protection complex</name>
<description>A character has a protection complex if the character is overly protective of other characters, beyond what would be considered a "normal" or "expected" duty of care.
The magnitude of overprotection can vary. It can be as low as constantly nagging someone to "stay safe". It can be as extreme as the protector making it their mission in life to protect the other character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4520" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>betrayal</name>
<description>Friends become enemies.
Strong bonds of trust receive violations of confidence while friendships are faithlessly given up or revealed to have been false from the start.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5865" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>manly tears</name>
<description>Somewhere down the line, it became the "norm" that boys don`t cry. The scenario does not matter; shedding tears is the ultimate no-no in terms of what you can and cannot do as a man (at least in the West, anyway). But there comes a time when a man`s emotions do get the better of him, and they pour forth - as prerequisite an impassioned speech may or may not be present - by cascading down his cheeks. These are what we like to call "manly tears". Extremely powerful. Not limited but often used in hot-blooded / super robot shows. Examples include Yuusha Ou GaoGaiGar, Getter Robo and Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann.
The opposite of manly tears are "girly tears".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5882" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>secret identity</name>
<description>The (usually main) protagonist has a secret identity that he or she desperately tries to keep secret.
This can lead to all sorts of amusing misunderstandings, thus is used as comedy element in some anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6347" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>body and host</name>
<description>When a foreign entity like that of a symbiote, body snatcher, puppeteer parasite, or even a hacker (when regarding machines like robots and computers) enters/outright hijacks a body, the possessed subject becomes what is usually called: the host.
The basic purpose of the host varies on what the point was for it to have been hijacked in the first place. Sometimes it`s used as a disguise, other times it`s used as a decoy and destraction, even simply being used as a weapon and piece of armor that the possessor uses to cause sheer chaos and destruction, but sometimes... a host can be used for fetish fuel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="15271" type="main character in" update="2012-04-22">
<rating votes="21">8.37</rating>
<name>Zesu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>43604.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15272" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-20">
<rating votes="2">3.72</rating>
<name>Yuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuki from his previous life. She was Luka`s lover.</description>
<picture>51125.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15273" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-25">
<rating votes="5">6.59</rating>
<name>Murasame Tsukumo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>43605.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15274" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-09-04">
<rating votes="8">5.27</rating>
<name>Murasame Touko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>43608.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15275" type="appears in" update="2010-02-25">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Kureha Aya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>43613.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="89" picture="148709.jpg">Yahagi Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15276" type="main character in" update="2010-02-25">
<rating votes="7">5.02</rating>
<name>Sakurai Yuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>43603.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="381" picture="186189.jpg">Hoshi Souichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15277" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-25">
<rating votes="6">8.90</rating>
<name>Usui Shuusei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>43611.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="255" picture="40713.jpg">Miyano Mamoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15278" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-25">
<rating votes="5">2.36</rating>
<name>Giou Takashiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>43612.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15279" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-09">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Giou Tachibana</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The curator at Twilight Mansion and a member of the Giou clan. Tachibana has an upbeat personality and likes to keep conversation going.</description>
<picture>56204.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15280" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-20">
<rating votes="2">6.83</rating>
<name>Wakamiya Kanata</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A childhood friend of Yuki, who grew up with him in the orphanage. Yuki considers him to be like an older brother figure to him. He carries the "Book of Raziel." 
also known as Reiga Gioh,the male antigonist.</description>
<picture>4740.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15281" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-11">
<rating votes="2">3.04</rating>
<name>Hourai Kuroto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>56334.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15282" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-25">
<rating votes="4">8.98</rating>
<name>Renjou Hotsuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>43610.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15283" type="appears in" update="2010-05-27">
<rating votes="2">4.13</rating>
<name>Fujiwara Isuzu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>As the private doctor of the Giou family, Fujiwara acts as both physician and Duras researcher. He seems to have great enthusiasm for his work, and often begs Zesu to agree to an examination.</description>
<picture>43615.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="387" picture="17233.jpg">Narita Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15284" type="appears in" update="2010-02-25">
<name>Tooma Katsumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>43614.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15285" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-11">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Furuori Senshirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>56335.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15289" type="appears in" update="2010-10-10">
<name>Kureha Fuyutoki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>56285.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="373" picture="191382.jpg">Hamada Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15290" type="appears in" update="2010-10-10">
<name>Shikibe Tsubaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>56287.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15291" type="appears in" update="2010-10-09">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Shikibe Ibuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>56202.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2054" picture="186267.jpg">Amano Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18125" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-27">
<rating votes="3">6.97</rating>
<name>Sodom</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sodom is a small, black dragon, and the familiar of Zesu. He takes an instant liking to Yuki, and is usually very friendly and curious - unless ordered otherwise by Zesu.</description>
<picture>48614.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3769" picture="25256.jpg">Ishikawa Momoko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="117447" update="2010-04-04">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117642" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-12</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">刻, 動き出す</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Set in Motion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koku, Ugokidasu</title>
<summary>Yuki Sakurai is plagued with the strangest dreams and an appearance of frightening notes. Weirder things start occurring when he tries to help out a struggling classmate but ends up in a trap! Luckily, he is saved by a mysterious stranger.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="117716" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">永劫の調べ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eternal Investigation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eigou no Shirabe</title>
<summary>After spending his life at Asahi Orphanage, Yuki is suddenly visited by a man claiming to be his brother. While deciding if he should live with family or stay, Yuki begins to lose control of his powers until his mysterious savior appears again.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="117837" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ワルプルギスの夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Walpurgis Night</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Walpurgis no Yoru</title>
<summary>Learning of the Giou clan and Duras leaves Yuki confused and shaken, but not quite ready to leave with them. Zess warns him to stay inside during the night of the blood-red moon—the Walpurgis Night. But when the red moon rises, danger comes with it.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="117982" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">帰らぬ日々 白き明日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lost Days and White Future</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaeranu Hibi Shiroki Ashita</title>
<summary>A Mid-Villain has taken over Uzuki and attacks Yuki. Tsukumo saves him but is dealt a deadly blow. Facing the danger of death, Zess jumps in, but the Duras reveals what he is. Can a betrayer be trusted or will Yuki’s power finally awaken and protect them?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="117996" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新たな出逢い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A New Encounter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arata na Deai</title>
<summary>Yuki learns about the danger behind his powers and his unavoidable fate. Zweilt Guardians, previous lives…it’s all so much to take in. And more pressure is added when new allies appear by his side. Is Yuki prepared for his destiny?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="118249" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">光と絶望の境目</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Boundary Between Light and Despair</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hikari to Zetsubou no Sakaime</title>
<summary>Yuki’s desire to help those in need lead him straight into a trap set up by the Duras. But just when they think they’ve finished them off, a Mid-Villain appears where Yuki least expects it.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="118291" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">キズアト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scars</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kizuato</title>
<summary>Yuki tries to understand more about Shusei and Hotsuma, but their complicated past leads to unspoken words and wounds that cannot be erased. But trying to learn about Hotsuma—will Yuki wind up burned?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="118292" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブランド・ゼス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Brand Zess</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Brand Zeise</title>
<summary>Yuki learns a little more about his past self and heads to his new school. He’s surprised when Kanata is there waiting for him. Has he regained his best friend, or are Kanata’s intentions sinister?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="118293" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黄昏[たそがれ]館</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Twilight Mansion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tasogare Kan</title>
<summary>Yuki meets the colorful characters he’ll be living with in the Twilight Mansion. They’re a rowdy and peculiar bunch, but Yuki quickly feels at home. As he settles in, he can’t help but worry about Kanata, who he still cannot reach.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="118707" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">慟哭</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cry of Despair</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Doukoku</title>
<summary>Shusei’s sudden disappearance has everyone on edge. While searching for him, they receive a video from an Opast that presents to them an ultimatum in order to get Shusei back. What dangers await in this deadly trap?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="118802" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">運命の皮肉</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Irony of Fate</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unmei no Hiniku</title>
<summary>The truth about Reiga shatters Yuki—is this really his beloved friend? The fighting rages on around them, but Yuki’s left frozen, despairing over this sudden betrayal. And when Takashiro appears, more questions arise.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="118803" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">"二人" ということ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To Be a `Pair`</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Futari" to Iukoto</title>
<summary>Hotsuma and Yuki finally reach Shusei but must face Ashley to save him. As the battle heats up, things start to look desperate. Will they make it out alive, or does this mean victory for the Duras?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="118804" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">儚く強く尊いもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">That Which Is Fleeting, Strong, and Precious</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakanaku Tsuyoku Toutoi Mono</title>
<summary>Tsukumo is gravely injured by the one called “Reiga.” Frustrated, Yuki makes the decision to find Shusei with Luka and Hotsuma. When they wind up at a deserted amusement park, a deadly game of chase may keep them from their goal.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119500" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">契役という名の鎖</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bound by Contract</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Keiyaku to Iu Na no Kusari</title>
<summary>After two days of sleeping, Yuki awakes and tries to keep himself busy by keeping everyone from worrying about him. As the group recovers, the day is filled with confrontations, confessions, and support.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119833" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">決意, そして...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">After Determination...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kestui, Soshite...</title>
<summary>Yuki is ready to face answers to all the questions that have been building up. What happened in his past life, what is the meaning behind the war? New faces and a new residence await Yuki with the answers he seeks.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119993" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">凍結された時間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Frozen Time</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Touketsu Sareta Jikan</title>
<summary>Takashiro explains his role and the history behind the thousand year war. Yuki learns shocking information about the Duras and their abilities, as well as the truth about Reiga.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="120341" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">桜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura</title>
<summary>A Sakura tree will bloom, given enough time and care. Takashiro recounts a time from a thousand years ago, before Reiga was their enemy. Yuki learns about his mother and her feelings towards him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="120351" update="2010-10-13">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-07-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120352" update="2010-10-13">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-04-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120353" update="2010-10-13">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-07-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120354" update="2010-07-24">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-04-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120525" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">あなたのいない世界</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A World Without You</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anata no Inai Sekai</title>
<summary>Yuki sorts through all the information he’s learned from Takashiro but muses over his connection with Luka. While Yuki seeks him out, Luka must face his own troubles when a Duras named Elegy seeks him out. Will his love for Yuki be his downfall?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="120940" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">復讐の戒めの手[ペア]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Vengeful Pair</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukushuu no Pair</title>
<summary>Loss, revenge, and love can weigh heavily on a soul throughout all of time. Yuki learns about Kuroto’s past and how he came to be Senshiro’s partner.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="121186" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">罪と罰と約束と</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sin and Punishment and Promise</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsumi to Batsu to Yakusoku to</title>
<summary>Kuroto tries to get Senshiro to quit being a Zweilt, to stay away from fighting Cadenza. But when Yuki leaves the grounds to seek out Luka, he finds himself in Cadenza’s trap. Kuroto and Senshiro must fight the Duras responsible for all their grief.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="121356" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">消えぬ面影</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Indelible Image</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kienu Omokage</title>
<summary>After Reiga’s sudden appearance, Yuki and the Zweilts learn a crucial detail about their enemy. The rest of their allies make their way to the battle, but can they get there in time? Or does Reiga intend to protect Yuki rather than kill him?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="121521" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦へ...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the Final Battle...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen e...</title>
<summary>After Reiga retreats, the Zweilts and Luka wait as Yuki recovers from using his powers, dwelling on what their next move must be. But despite Reiga’s orders, the Duras have other plans and attack.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="121828" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">裏切りの戦い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Traitors` Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uragiri no Tatakai</title>
<summary>Reiga has Yuki in his grasp, and Luka doesn’t plan on waiting to save him. But the Zweilts won’t let him do it alone. They make their move and prepare themselves for their final battle. While battling Reiga, a figure from Luka’s past suddenly appears!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="122110" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">心ヲツナグ者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Connected Hearts</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokoro o Tsunagu Mono</title>
<summary>As the battle heats up, Yuki’s resolve comes through, and he unleashes his power unlike ever before. With Luka’s devotion and Yuki’s feelings—can they finally find a way to end the thousand year war?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
