<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6841" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1928-09-04</startdate>
<enddate>1928-09-04</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Doubutsu Olympic Taikai</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Animal Olympic Games</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">動物オリムピック大会</title>
</titles>
<url>https://archive.today/67JVC</url>
<creators>
<name id="7967" type="Original Plan">Aochi Chuuzou</name>
</creators>
<description>Animals gather to compete in Olympic games. This animation was inspired by the 1928 Olympic Games held in Amsterdam.
Animals appear in a field all holding a lion flag in their hands. Following the opening address from the chairman lion, a monkey representing all the animals declares that they all will demonstrate the spirit of sportsbeastship (as opposed to sportsmanship). When the games start, a monkey who was filming a polar bear failing in an attempt at the pole vault tries it himself and successfully obtains a high mark. In the discus, a throw by an elephant flies over the mountains. In the 200-meter hurdles event for a black rabbit and pig, the rabbit wins, but the pig inflates like a balloon and flies off into the sky. In the javelin, the throw by the elephant follows the pig, hits it, and the pig lands. A camel, hippopotamus, bulldog, duck, and monkey are in the 1500-meter final. The bulldog was leading the race but fights with the monkey in the middle of the race and goes out of his lane, giving the lead to the duck. A trophy is given to the elephant who won first prize in his two events, and everyone tossed the elephant in the air celebrating his victory, but the trophy is smashed to pieces when the elephant falls down on it.
Source: National Film Archive of Japan</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="36">3.66</permanent>
<temporary count="36">4.43</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>33809.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5352</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7498</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://archive.today/67JVC</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://animation.filmarchives.jp/en/works/view/43800</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4677" parentid="2881" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-27">
<name>Olympics</name>
<description>The Olympic Games play a significant part in the plot. Either one or more characters dream(s) of going to the Olympics (as either a competitor or spectator), or part of the anime takes place at the Olympics.
Japan has hosted the Olympics three times: the 1964 Summer Olympics in Tokyo; the 1972 Winter Olympics in Sapporo, Hokkaidō Prefecture; and the 1998 Winter Olympics in Nagano, Nagano Prefecture, so do not be surprised when shows set during these time periods have a significant showing of the Olympics.
Olympic parodies may also count, so long as it is a significant part of the plot.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5939" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-09">
<name>CAST MISSING</name>
<description>Important characters are missing, either in-part or entirely. This includes basic entry info (name, gender, picture), appear episode range, seiyuu and/or tags.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="106591" update="2009-08-25">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
