<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6878" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1949-12</startdate>
<enddate>1949-12</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Doubutsu Dai Yakyuu Sen</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">動物大野球戦</title>
</titles>
<creators>
<name id="9919" type="Music">Sakamoto Yoshitaka</name>
</creators>
<description>A game of baseball featuring animals. One team is made up of gorillas, while the other is mixed animals. The gorilla team easily overpowers the other animals.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2">2.29</permanent>
<temporary count="2">3.50</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>33829.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>27577</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>135379</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="28" parentid="2881" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-16">
<name>baseball</name>
<description>Baseball is like a complicated version of Rounders. It involves hitting a ball with a stick, then running around several bases placed in the form of a diamond on a field. Big in the US, and also in Japan.</description>
<picurl>29801.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5939" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-09">
<name>CAST MISSING</name>
<description>Important characters are missing, either in-part or entirely. This includes basic entry info (name, gender, picture), appear episode range, seiyuu and/or tags.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="106617" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
