<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="692" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2003-04-17</startdate>
<enddate>2003-12-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gad Guard</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">GAD GUARD</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Gadguard</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">钢铁守护者</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">GG</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ガドガード</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Gad Guard</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Gad Guard</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">هاجيكي</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="427601">Great show, the review for this is overly cynical. Nothing ground breaking to be sure, but this is a giant robot show that appears to break free of some of the usual cliches. Can be somewhat episodic, but characters show some depth. A watch for mech/distopia fans.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.gonzo.co.jp/works/gadguard/</url>
<creators>
<name id="735" type="Original Work">Gonzo</name>
<name id="741" type="Work">Fuji TV</name>
<name id="759" type="Work">Media Factory</name>
<name id="806" type="Work">GDH</name>
<name id="807" type="Animation Work">Amber Film Works</name>
<name id="807" type="Work">Amber Film Works</name>
<name id="947" type="Work">Imagica Entertainment</name>
<name id="1048" type="Work">Hakuhodo DY Media Partners</name>
<name id="1602" type="Animation Work">Gonzo Digimation</name>
<name id="1177" type="Work">Hakuhodo</name>
<name id="1603" type="Direction">Nishikiori Hiroshi</name>
<name id="1604" type="Character Design">Aizawa Masahiro</name>
<name id="1604" type="Chief Animation Direction">Aizawa Masahiro</name>
<name id="4328" type="Series Composition">Ikeguchi Kazuhiko</name>
<name id="1603" type="Series Composition">Nishikiori Hiroshi</name>
<name id="1603" type="Original Work">Nishikiori Hiroshi</name>
<name id="11112" type="Original Work">Izuna Yoshitsune</name>
<name id="33773" type="Music">Pe`z</name>
<name id="1393" type="Music">Tanaka Kouhei</name>
<name id="6945" type="Music">Sawaguchi Kazuhiko</name>
</creators>
<description>In a street that was to be named Unit Blue in the near future, there is a town named Night Town. A town engulfed in darkness of the night due to a lack of electricity. A young man, http://anidb.net/ch33340 [Sanada Hajiki], works there part time in a transport business known as Hachisuka Transporation.
One day, Hajiki gets in touch with a client who wanted him to transport a mysterious material known as GAD for a high price. When the GAD ends up as scrap, it takes the form of a giant humanoid machine known as iron man Lightning.
From then on, all kinds of people who also owned an iron man appeared before Hajiki. http://anidb.net/ch33341 [Katana], an outlaw who used iron man Zero to destroy; http://anidb.net/ch33339 [Aiko], an upperclass young lady who searches for friends with iron man Messerschmitt; and http://anidb.net/ch33343 [Takumi], a young man who works for justice with his iron man Thunder Bolt.
Even though Hajiki is also a iron man user himself now, his thoughts differ... Those who are always seeking for danger, those who want to meet friends and those who fight for justice. As Hajiki is troubled over such differences, he must fight alongside his own iron man against other similar humanoid mechas.
Why did GAD and iron men appear before them? The gears of fate for the young men who posess iron men have begun to work...
Note: The real episode 6 ("The Five Masks") wasn`t aired in the first run. The correct order was restored in all subsequent airings on other channels and on the DVD release.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="577">4.55</permanent>
<temporary count="581">6.68</temporary>
<review count="1">6.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>229231.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>214</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>271</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1211</identifier>
<identifier>dceaih</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gonzo.co.jp/works/gadguard/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Gad_Guard</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>GAD_GUARD</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>240811</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5977</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/83</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2003/gadguard</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13542</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>8341</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4477" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-02">
<name>communication with the dead</name>
<description>This character is able of some manner of communication with the dead, or at least with one dead person. This includes talking to the dead, seeing the dead, outright mediumship, or any form of unidirectional or bidirectional form of communication that ordinary characters are not generally able to achieve.
This does not apply in environments where characters are expected to be dead, or where nobody is alive to begin with.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="33339" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-07">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Aiko Marie Harmony</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The adopted daughter of businessman Larry Harmony, the owner of Central Electronics - the biggest electric company in Unit Blue - Aiko is a sweet and loving girl, but very conflicted. Being the only child of a rich and rather famous family, she is constantly under pressure to succeed her father when he steps down from the company, something she, at only fifteen, is not perfectly certain she wants to do.
Unlike the others, Aiko lives in Gold Town, the rich district of Unit Blue, and because she has every luxury, she is not spoiled, but she is very idealistic, carrying the belief that, because all five of the kids in Gad Guard were "given" Techodes, they all have something in common and therefore should all be friends. Unfortunately for Aiko, she is often met with disagreement from the others, but that hardly gets her down, as she dogs each and every one of them with the prospect again and again. If anything, the girl is determined, believing that there is good in every person, and that every person should be given a chance. For this reason, Aiko is the bridge between the other four, acting as friend to Arashi, reassurance to Hajiki and Takumi, and a peacemaker to Katana. The latter two are the ones she is most in touch with, and has the greater impact on.
It seems that no one can really dislike Aiko. Because she saved Sayuri from being crushed by Zero in a battle, Katana holds her in slight trust, and so she tries to bring him into their sort-of group by being friendly, visiting he and Sayuri in their hideout and bringing them lunches and snacks from time to time, to show her good faith and that she`s concerned. She even invites Katana to a party at her father`s mansion, something Takumi thinks is insane (because Katana is "evil"). Of course, he doesn`t go, but it`s the thought that counts. Takumi, however, she grows attached to after recognizing him - despite his lack of costume - as Thunderbolt`s operator. From then on she hangs around with him, forever the ray of sunshine in any situation, cooking for him, keeping him company when he falls into depression and forever working to cheer him up, no matter how bitter and cruel he acts. Even Jacque Bruno, who kidnaps Aiko to hold her hostage, can`t help but like her for her determination and her friendliness (and the fact that she can eat his cooking).
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>4279.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="634" picture="18161.jpg">Kurata Masayo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33340" type="main character in" update="2011-10-07">
<name>Sanada Hajiki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hajiki is the main protagonist of Gad Guard and is a short-tempered and somewhat jaded boy. Being the eldest child and only son of the Sanada family, Hajiki works as a delivery boy in Unit Blue for Mr. Hachisuka of Hachisuka Express. A bit of a degenerate and a punk at first, Hajiki skips school, races the cops on his skateboard or moped, and hangs out at all hours with his similarly punkish friends for lack of anything better to do. His mother was widowed when his father, an astronaut, died in a freak accident concerning the launching of a ship into outer space. Now the man of the house, Hajiki works himself to the bone, losing sleep and even putting himself in danger to help his mother and his sister Satsuki survive.
The main events in the series center around Hajiki`s rivalry with Katana and the relationships he shares with the other Techode owners. After running into the justice-crazed Takumi, the friendly Aiko and the danger-prone Arashi the group forms a friendship over the course of the series. Their relationships vary from episode to episode, as Hajiki sees Takumi as overly-righteous, thinks Aiko`s a little too obsessed with mutual friendship, and can`t seem to figure out what to do with Arashi. Still, he seems to hold all four of the others close, even Katana, and like Aiko, he wishes they were all on the same side.
`Hajiki` is Japanese slang for `gun`, an object that is by nature quick, forceful and erratic. A gun is also commonly considered the weapon opposite of a sword which is by definition a sharp, precise and brutally personal weapon, qualities relatable to Katana.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>4280.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="191" picture="17006.jpg">Suzumura Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33341" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-07">
<name>Katana</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Katana (pronounced kah-ta-nah, as opposed to ka-tah-nah, like the sword) is the main anti-hero of the series who acts as antagonist to the main characters, though he constantly switches between villain and ally from situation to situation, depending on his ever-shifting mood. Appearing as a gothic mutation of a schoolboy in a striped shirt, sweater, tie and slacks, all under a trench coat, Katana is tall and narrow in appearance, gaunt and deathly pale, with a scar beneath his left eye and is constantly carrying a gun. Katana works as a man-for-hire, living on the garage-level of an abandoned building on the edge of a junk yard in Night Town. Dark, cold and stoic by nature, Katana lives alone, having no friends and seemingly not wanting any. However, Katana does develop a very strong and almost obsessive attachment to Saiyuri over the course of the story, her disappearance becoming the main motivation for his actions near the end of the series. Another person important to Katana is Radigue, who acted as Katana`s father after his family died in a shipwreck and is most likely to be the originator of Katana`s secret enjoyment of building machinery and digging up Heavy Metal parts. Personality-wise, he shows no interest in much of anything but money and rising to the top of the criminal ladder, his grand intention to rule over Night Town. While not evil, Katana is a sociopath.
Katana is a very proud Heavy Metal operator, having built his first one in the series, Seven, himself. However early in the series it is destroyed by Lightning and later replaced with Katana`s Techode, Zero. Katana becomes very bitter about the loss of his original Heavy Metal, and although Zero is stronger his attachment to Seven never truly leaves him, and its destruction becomes the basis of his rivalry with Hajiki, a rivalry that eventually grows into a battle to show who is the bigger man. His need to prove that he is better grows into an insane obsession over the course of the story.
Along with Hajiki, Katana meets up with the other three Techode operators, and shows a variety of opinions about them. Aiko earns Katana`s slight trust when she rescues Sayuri from a dangerous spot in the middle of one of his battles, who then proceeds to bring him lunch daily. She seems to sit on neutral ground with him, to the point that Katana rescues her from being ganged up on in a bad part of town. Takumi however earned Katana`s disdain almost to the level that of Hajiki because of his meddling and loudmouthed sense of justice, and he delights in baiting and teasing him in a cold manner only to prove that he is superior to the short-fused boy. Arashi stands as Katana`s way to get to Hajiki, using her as a messenger and even learning his name from her. They get into several fights, and he seems to despise her quite a bit, to the point of near-blind rage in their final confrontation.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>4281.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33342" type="main character in" update="2011-10-08">
<rating votes="3">7.64</rating>
<name>Shinozuka Arashi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The daughter of a great martial-artist, Arashi (referred to as Shinozuka by Hajiki) left her home in Day Town to live on her own in Night Town, going to the same neighborhood catholic school as Hajiki and his friends. She ran away from home feeling she would never be good enough for her father, who expected before her birth to have a son only to be disappointed with a daughter instead and Arashi was given a boy`s name because of that. As she came from a good part of town, Arashi has some trouble at first adjusting to life in the ghetto such as her belongings getting stolen and not having batteries to cope with the power shutting off at midnight. She soon learns and tries to teach herself to fit in, doing everything from making friends with some of the boys at school to getting a job as a billboard repair worker to support herself. She is witness to the creation of Lightning, and after seeing Zero (belonging to Katana), Thunderbolt (Takumi) and Messerschmitt (Aiko), she longs for a Gad of her own, something she later finds by accident.
Arashi is meant to be Hajiki`s love interest in the series, even though he all but ignores her through the first part of the series. At first she seems to annoy him, but Hajiki eventually grows accustomed to her even if her idealistic views don`t always coincide with his. Arashi follows after him relentlessly, seeming hellbent on staying with him to the point of following him to work and popping up in the middle of several of his Techode battles. In a few episodes when their views have clashed, Arashi has used her karate skills on Hajiki. By the end of the series, Arashi and Hajiki affirm their feelings for each other, much to the shock of the teachers who just happened to walk in when they kissed for the first time.
Relationship-wise, besides Hajiki, Arashi has little contact with the other characters, save for Katana. She finds people like Katana disgusting because they do bad things, although she herself, like Takumi and Aiko, do not understand the troubles of living in a place like Night Town. Several times, she is held at gun-point by him, and threatened or told to pass a message to Hajiki, and at one point tries to fight him, only to have him beat her without much effort. Arashi opposes Katana and his obsession with besting Hajiki repeatedly, and continues to act as a problem to him through the entire series, though Katana sacrifices Zero to save her from death in the final episode, something she never gets the chance to ask him about. Aiko is portrayed to be sort of a friend to Arashi, but when the two of them are in the room with Hajiki she seeks to vie for his attention, something Aiko doesn`t notice. Takumi and Arashi have little to no friendship short of acquaintance.
Souce: wiki</description>
<picture>4282.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33343" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-23">
<name>Kisaragi Takumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takumi is a short and wealthy boy who lives in Day Town, his most defining attribute in the series being almost obsessed with justice and the differences between right and wrong. When Takumi was young, his parents left him alone with a very large sum of money, more than he claims he could ever use and will never have to get a job. So because of his abundance of money and free time, using his Techode Thunderbolt, he goes out and attempts to solve crimes and punish evil-doers, because he wants to do something good, as he feels the local police force is very lacking. Takumi is also noted to have a very short temper and constantly takes out his anger on people, usually ending up in him getting in wide variety of trouble.
Takumi`s main adversary in the series is Katana who is essentially his polar opposite, using his Techode to commit crimes and not caring about others at all along with several polarities in appearance, personality and back story. Takumi refers to Katana as evil and is more obsessed with Katana than Katana is with Hajiki. Time and again, Takumi claims that Katana is a beast, raised in violence, and for that reason, violence is all he knows, saying that he cannot be made friends with and he is not a real person at all. Despite all of Takumi`s loathing, Katana sees him only as a pest that he`s done nothing to provoke and on more than one occasion beats Takumi severely.
Later in the series it becomes apparent that Takumi`s constant ranting about Katana being violent and vicious is actually Takumi casting his own control issues on Katana because it is easier for the "bad guy" to be the one with problems, as "heroes" are good and just and can never be wrong. It is Hajiki that tells Takumi he could never truly understand how hard it is to live without money, as his parents left him enough so that he would never have to "waste his life" in a job. Unlike Hajiki, who works for a living, and Katana, who steals and is a mercenary for a living, Takumi is "too busy being high and mighty and righteous" to see that the world isn`t black and white. Takumi later admits to himself that he has no idea what he was talking about and didn`t know anything about the people he was fighting or who he was protecting.
Hajiki is on Takumi`s side in the belief that Katana must be stopped when he is doing something wrong, but unlike Takumi, Hajiki does not believe that it is their job to stop every single evil, and for this reason they are not horribly close. Aiko, however, acts much as Sayuri does to Katana and insists to Takumi that they should all be friends, even suffering to deal with his temper and bad attitude, only to smile and continue to talk with him. After the loss of Thunderbolt, Takumi grows close to Aiko and gets a job at Hajiki`s mother`s restaurant.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>4283.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3336" picture="177136.jpg">Satou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33344" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-08">
<name>Hachisuka Kogorou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hajiki`s boss and sort of his stand-in father figure. Manager of Hachisuka Express, his motto is "we`ll deliver anything", and by we, he means Hajiki, on a moped, at all hours, to wherever, as long as he gets paid.
Hachisuka isn`t a bad guy, but he has a weird sense of morals. Most of the time, his policy is don`t ask, don`t tell. Slimeball money is as green as anybody else`s and can be spent accordingly.
He does nag Hajiki about going to school every now and again though, but he doesn`t push it. He argues constantly with Catherine and can`t seem to stand her, less when she`s being nice to him. He smokes too much, lectures every once in a while, and will usually be there to bring Hajiki back down to earth and out of the I`m-a-hero clouds.
He has some connection to Catherine from the past, but not much is said on the subject.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>4284.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33345" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-08">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Catherine Flaubert</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Catherine is one of the weirder female characters. Originally having hired Hachisuka Express to bring her a Gad, Wanda Woman impersonated her and got Hajiki to give it to her at her apartment while she wasn`t home. For this reason, Catherine won`t leave Hachisuka or Hajiki alone, because she lost her Gad thanks to them, and now she can`t use it because it`s become Lightning.
She is dead-set on getting a Gad of her own for some reason never truly explained. All she said was that a Gad stole her real name, and she needed to get it back. For this, she has Hachisuka, Hajiki and his friends running around trying to find every Gad on the planet for her. She even tries to hire Katana.
Catherine never gets a Gad, but sticks around to make a nuisance of herself, reminding Hachisuka that he owes her the money she paid him for the Gad`s delivery, plus the "damages" in her losing it.
In the end, she suggests that she`d like to start seeing him, and Hachisuka hightails it out of Night Town, closing his office. She chases him on a bicycle. She and Hachisuka were part of some organization in the past, before "the gad had stolen her name", but not much is said on this subject.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>4285.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33346" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-08">
<name>Sanada Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kyoko is Hajiki`s widowed mother. She works in a restaurant until all hours of the night to support her family.
Kyoko is a big woman, and like most single mothers, she has no problem punishing her degenerate son for skipping school and falling asleep in class.
She is a good woman though, constantly worrying about her children, especially Hajiki, and trying to do the best she can for them. She fusses about his eating, his school attendance and even yells at his boss when he disappears for hiding him and trying to pretend she`s stupid.
Late in the show, she takes Takumi on as an apprentice of sorts to teach him to cook, and in the process teaches him that all people, bad or good, should not be judged, but should be treated well.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>65572.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="653" picture="18181.jpg">Tsuda Shouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33347" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-08">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Sanada Satsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Satsuki is Hajiki`s younger sister. A dancer, Satsuki is convinced she will someday become a professional, if she gets a new leotard so she doesn`t look shabby in front of the other girls. Both Hajiki and her mother give her money for this, because it`s the one thing she likes to do, and they support her in that, even if they`re poor.
Satsuki is always worried about her brother and knows he`s out getting himself in trouble, and has no problem shouting at him for being out too late and worrying their poor Mom. Katana takes her hostage to get to Hajiki.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>65574.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="312" picture="245047.jpg">Nakanishi Tamaki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="7457" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">同じ空を見ていた</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Looking Up at the Same Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Nous regardions le même ciel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onaji Sora o Miteita</title>
<summary>When Hajiki is assigned to make a special delivery to a mysterious client, his entire world changes with the discovery of a mysterious GAD!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="7535" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">欠片(かけら)繋ぎ合わせ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Putting the Pieces Together</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">En rassemblant les morceaux</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakera Tsunagiawase</title>
<summary>Hajiki finds that even his most dangerous enemies are no match for his Techode - but that might not be the case when his last client starts wondering why he never received his GAD.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="7599" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナイトタウンの街角で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">On a Street Corner in Night Town</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Au coin de la rue de Night Town</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Night Town no Machikado de</title>
<summary>Following a lead on another GAD, Hajiki is ambushed by some enemies he’d already dealt with. And this time they have a Techode of their very own.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="7784" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">瞳涼やかに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">With Bright Eyes</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les yeux doux</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitomi Suzuyaka ni</title>
<summary>Hajiki forms a bond with a boy he rescued from a gang of thugs. As they trail a jewel thief, Hajiki finds there’s more to the little boy than it seems.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="7875" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そして雨が降る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">And Then the Rain Will Fall</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Puis la pluie tombe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soshite Ame ga Furu</title>
<summary>Katana and Wanda work together to steal a GAD that’s being transported to the Day Town Museum after being mistaken for a jewel.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="7979" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">空を飛べたら</title>
<title xml:lang="en">If I Can Fly</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Si je pouvais voler</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sora o Tobetara</title>
<summary>Hajiki and Lightning have been hired to steal a coffin that’s suspected to contain a GAD - and the cops are on their tail!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="8350" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さすらいの二人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Two Lost Souls</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les deux vagabonds</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sasurai no Futari</title>
<summary>Two Guardian Techode Hunters have come to Night Town in order to eliminate the Techode population - but as the battle rages, Hajiki isn’t convinced the Techodes are as dangerous as the Hunters say.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="8489" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雪が心を融かす</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Snow Melts the Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La neige touche les cœurs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuki ga Kokoro o Tokasu</title>
<summary>Katana sets out on a search for someone to repair Zero after the Techode sustained serious damage in a brawl with an Atechode.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="8570" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夕日に札束</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bundle of Bills in the Setting Sun</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une liasse de billets au crépuscule</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuuhi ni Satsutaba</title>
<summary>Lightning and Hajiki are chased through Night Town by Mary and Chris.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9028" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">虹の町には帰れない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">No Returning to Rainbow Town</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je ne rentrerai pas à la ville de l`arc-en-ciel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Niji no Machi ni wa Kaerenai</title>
<summary>Two crime families are waging war in Night Town - and Hajiki is thrown right in the middle of their fight!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9203" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブルーバード</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bluebird</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Blue Bird</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bluebird</title>
<summary>Hajiki’s school attendance problem is causing him trouble, but his life only gets more complicated when Hachisuka assigns him to deliver 100 wedding invitations.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9460" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">闇に住む者たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dwellers of the Dark</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ceux qui vivent dans l`ombre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yami ni Sumu Mono-tachi</title>
<summary>Hajiki and Katana must work together like never before to survive a lethal assassin who wields the gruesome power to fuse man with machine!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9712" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">失われた時を求めて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seeking Lost Time</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">En cherchant le temps perdu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ushiwareta Toki o Motomete</title>
<summary>At the docks to investigate a lead on a GAD, Hajiki and Lightning must rescue Catherine after a strange statue puts her life in serious danger.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="10394" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-08-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">陽の当たる庭</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Garden in the Sun</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le jardin que la lumière du soleil atteint</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hi no Ataru Niwa</title>
<summary>Aiko`s father is trying to get his hands on a GAD that’s locked away in a museum - and his approach to claiming it is a little shady.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="10479" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">牙を剥く日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Day We Bare Our Fangs</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le jour où les crocs furent montrés</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiba o Muku Hi</title>
<summary>Takumi and Katana are tangling with the mob and running from the police. And Aiko’s father wants everyone with a Techode to join him for dinner, but his reasons why aren’t clear.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="10856" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">銃・刀・獣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Guns - Swords - Beasts</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Hajiki, Katana, Kemono : Flingue, sabre et fauve</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Juu - Katana - Kemono</title>
<summary>Hajiki’s in a tough spot when a police officer comes to his house to demand help in apprehending Katana - and the cop won’t leave unless Hajiki agrees to the plan.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="11536" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">道連れ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Road Companion</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Compagnon de voyage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Michizure</title>
<summary>Even though nobody will help her find him, Arashi continues her search for Hajiki. The kid might be tough to find considering he’s already left town!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="11537" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">去る者の論理</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Logic of Those Who Leave</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La logique de celui qui part</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sarumono no Ronri</title>
<summary>Jack Bruno offers Hajiki the option to leave town with him - but the kid doesn’t realize his mom is nearby and looking to reconnect.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="12451" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">この世の果て</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The End of the World</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le bout de ce monde</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kono Yo no Hate</title>
<summary>Hajiki finds a job in a small village and suspects there’s more to the place than he can see. When Lightning and Hayate are stolen, his suspicions are confirmed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="14251" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-10-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">五つの仮面</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Five Masks</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les 5 masques</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itsutsu no Kamen</title>
<summary>Hajiki, Lightning, and the other Techodes must defend the city after a smuggler’s GAD becomes a powerful Atechode!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="15261" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-12-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蒼い眠り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blue Slumber</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le sommeil bleu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aoi Nemuri</title>
<summary>When Zero starts malfunctioning in the middle of a brawl with the police, it looks pretty grim for Katana - until an unlikely savior appears.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16862" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-12-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガラスの輪舞(ロンド)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Spiral Dance of Glass</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La ronde de verre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Glass no Rondo</title>
<summary>Hajiki and Arashi get jobs to pay for passage across the ocean. Somewhere past the other shore, they hope to find Hajiki’s father.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="23664" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-12-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">償う男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Atoning Man</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`homme qui expie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsugunau Otoko</title>
<summary>During their journey across the ocean, Hajiki and Arashi come to Chenis Island. The man they meet there could possibly be Hajiki’s dad!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="26195" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-12-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天を目指す意志</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Will to Aspire to the Heavens</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La volonté d`atteindre le ciel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ten o Mezasu Ishi</title>
<summary>As Hajiki considers Sayuri’s sudden offer to take him to space, Katana and Zero show up looking to settle the score.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="26196" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-12-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">空への時間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Time for the Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le temps au ciel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sora e no Jikan</title>
<summary>While preparing to launch, Sayuri is captured by Katana! Hajiki has only one choice. The time for the final battle has come.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="26197" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-12-30</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">若き旅人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Young Traveller</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le jeune voyageur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakaki Tabibito</title>
<summary>Hajiki successfully launches into space thanks to the sacrifices of Zero and Hayate - and the trip will only be one-way.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="62100" update="2006-09-02">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62101" update="2006-09-02">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
