<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6947" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>25</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-10-03</startdate>
<enddate>2010-03-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shugo Chara Party!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">しゅごキャラ!!!どっきどきっ</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">しゅごキャラ! パーティー!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Чара-хранители! (сезон третий)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Shugo Chara! Party!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Shugo Chara ! Dokki Doki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Shugo Chara!!! Dokki Doki</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">SC3</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">しゅごキャラパーティー!</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6144" type="Prequel">Shugo Chara!! Doki</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1"/>
<url>http://shugo-chara.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1043" type="Animation Work">Satelight</name>
<name id="4212" type="Character Design">Sai Fumihide</name>
<name id="2711" type="Series Composition">Oonogi Hiroshi</name>
<name id="1312" type="Original Work">Peach Pit</name>
<name id="7679" type="Chief Direction">Yasuda Kenji</name>
<name id="23192" type="Direction">Itou Tatsufumi</name>
</creators>
<description>The Third Season of Shugo Chara!
Each 24-25 minute episode consists of a series of variety show style shorts (including Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi / しゅごキャラ! ぷっちぷち) totaling approx. 9-10 minutes, followed by the main 11-12 minute animation titled Shugo Chara!!! Dokki Doki / しゅごキャラ!!! どっきどき which is the actual continuation of season 2 and comes with its own opening animation. The remaining time is occupied by live action padding between each section and capped off with the opening/ending themes at the beginning and end of the episode.
Several groups have released subsections separately under their respective titles (e.g. Chihiro`s 13 minute releases, which include only the main animation and the episode ending theme, released as Shugo Chara Dokki Doki).</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="396">3.31</permanent>
<temporary count="401">5.90</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>36478.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11104</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7082</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4607</identifier>
<identifier>oaffix</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://shugo-chara.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Shugo_Chara!#Anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>しゅごキャラパーティー!#.E3.83.86.E3.83.AC.E3.83.93.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1777</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>334955</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12104</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2424</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>shugo-chara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1063" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-11">
<name>elementary school</name>
<description>The term elementary school is used in some countries for schools where children from the age of about five receive primary education.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2345" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-02-06">
<name>zettai ryouiki</name>
<description>"Absolute Territory" (絶対領域, Zettai Ryouiki in Japanese) describes the area of uncovered thigh between the skirt and the knee sock.
As per usual for fandom who obsess about costumes, this can be considered a moe attribute and thus, present prominently in character designs and schoolgirl outfits. The term originates from http://anidb.net/a22 [Neon Genesis Evangelion] to designate an area of Absolute Terror, although it`s had considerable semantic drift. In this case, it may jokingly refer to the fact it emphasizes a shorter skirt without actually becoming creepy and showing the underpants.
As if that wasn`t enough, some even categorize it into five "Grades", from E to A. Only the top two (A and B) are considered true Zettai Ryouiki and they are only usable by female characters. Some researchers additionally introduce Grade S, the highest one which consists of Grade A plus further requirements to personality and hairstyle.
Just to make it clear, Zettai Ryouiki is made up of three components: socks, skin, and skirt. An Action Girl may trade the latter for hotpants but if it doesn`t include knee-highs and thighs, it`s not Zettai Ryouiki. Panty Shot is an entirely different zone.
For more information on sock lengths in general, see also: http://anidb.net/t6419 [hosiery]
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>165582.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5768" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>intact family</name>
<description>The main character`s family is a so-called "nuclear family". Wherein both parents are alive and present in his or her life. This is actually relatively rare for anime, where "parental abandonment" is the norm.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5822" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-01">
<name>series end</name>
<description>This marks the end of the anime series. The series may include many types, (TV, OVA, movies, etc.) but this marks the wrap-up point for all of the major story threads. The entire thing feels complete at the conclusion of this. It may or may not be the actual end of the anime series. Sometimes the producers will try to milk a dead cow and add extra episodes at the end of an anime run but those only open up new threads that usually never get closed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5850" parentid="2869" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-13">
<name>absurdly powerful student council</name>
<description>A student council is a student-managed body inside a school which engages in administrative affairs, usually usually working in a partnership with management, staff and parents, for the benefit of the whole school environment. In real life, a student council holds no actual power; however, in many anime/manga, they have an insane amount of power, which usually allows them to overrule nearly everyone else (the school board, the mayor, the prime minster, you name it). In those cases, that device is explored as a major source of slapstick comedy.</description>
<picurl>70561.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6137" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-09">
<name>catchphrase</name>
<description>A catchphrase is a sound, word or phrase commonly used by a person. That may be simply out of habit, or in an attempt to deliver some form of image, like that of cuteness. In fiction, characters often use catchphrases as a way to deliver specific personality traits. Examples include Otohime Mutsumi`s "ara ara" in Love Hina, Yang Wenli`s "yare yare" in Legend of the Galactic Heroes, Misuzu`s "gao" in AIR, Sakura`s "hoe" in Card Captor Sakura, Suiseiseki`s "desu" in Rozen Maiden, and Ayu`s "uguu" in Kanon (as well as several other characters in the same show).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6577" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-17">
<name>student government</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1247" type="main character in" update="2009-03-07">
<rating votes="88">8.38</rating>
<name>Hinamori Amu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hinamori Amu is a 5th grader attending Seiya Academy. Thought to be a cool, tough person by all, deep down she is a shy girl who wishes for the courage to express her true feelings. These wishes gave birth to Guardian Characters, tiny expressions of her would-be self.
She has a crush on Hotori Tadase, and confesses, thanks to one of here Guardian Characters, Ran, but after his rejection, develops interests in several other boys as well as time goes on.</description>
<picture>20552.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1248" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-07">
<rating votes="14">3.70</rating>
<name>Hotori Tadase</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hotori Tadase attends Seiyo Academy, and is the Kings Chair and leader of the Guardians. He is in love with Amu`s transformation "Amulet Heart", but not her herself.
He has aspirations for world domination, and whenever anyone calls him a prince, or princely (because of his looks), he changes character and goes on a tirade about how he is a king.</description>
<picture>20553.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1436" picture="18822.jpg">Takagi Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4456" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-07">
<rating votes="6">8.79</rating>
<name>Ran</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ran is the first to hatch from Amu`s eggs and represents Amu`s desire to be more honest and athletic. Ran is frequently cheering Amu on. During Character Change, Amu gains increased athletic abilities. During Character Transformation, Amu becomes Amulet Heart.</description>
<picture>20536.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4457" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-07">
<rating votes="8">5.63</rating>
<name>Kiseki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kiseki is Tadase`s Guardian Character. Kiseki was born for a combination of Tadase`s desire to be stronger and the dream of world domination. Because of this, Kiseki is extremely egotistical and often demanding, and doesn`t like obeying others. He frequently calls other Guardian Characters to go on "Special Secret Meetings." A running gag is that the other Guardian Characters will ignore him sometimes. Kiseki is aware of Tadase`s crush on Amu and acts the same way as Amu`s Guardian Characters whenever Tadase seems to be confessing to Amu. Kiseki holds a grudge against Ikuto`s Guardian Character, Yoru. During Character Change, Tadase gains the confidence to overcome his shyness. However, sometimes Tadase will become an egotistical person who seeks world domination.</description>
<picture>20539.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="269" picture="25727.jpg">Miyake Kaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4458" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-07">
<rating votes="83">8.41</rating>
<name>Tsukiyomi Ikuto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A teenage boy contracted by Easter to find the Embryo. He often helps Amu even though he works for Easter. Ikuto actually despises Easter and tries to wrench himself free from them by trying to find the Embryo to grant his own wish. He possesses the Dumpty Key which pairs with Amu`s Humpty Lock which at first did not fit in the keyhole. Like his father, Ikuto is a skilled violinist.</description>
<picture>20541.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4459" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-07">
<rating votes="33">8.43</rating>
<name>Yoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ikuto`s cat-like Guardian Character and represents Ikuto`s desire to be free like a stray cat. Yoru often goes out by himself and enjoys causing trouble for the Guardians and their Guardian Characters for fun. When Ikuto and Yoru undergo a Character Transformation, they become Black Lynx.</description>
<picture>20540.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4460" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-07">
<rating votes="36">8.24</rating>
<name>Hoshina Utau</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A junior high student model turned singing idol. Utau is very attracted to Ikuto and becomes extremely jealous of Amu because Ikuto shows an interest teasing her.</description>
<picture>20542.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4461" type="appears in" update="2011-06-06">
<rating votes="16">6.50</rating>
<name>Fujisaki Nadeshiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A student in the same year as Amu and serves as Queen`s Chair of the Guardians. When Amu rejected the offer to join the Guardians, Nadeshiko tries several tactics to convince Amu to join. The two become best friends and Nadeshiko looks over and supports Amu in her love life.</description>
<picture>20543.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="311" picture="44706.jpg">Chiba Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4462" type="appears in" update="2009-03-07">
<rating votes="7">5.63</rating>
<name>Temari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Temari is Nagihiko`s first Guardian Character. Temari appears to be elegant and Nagihiko`s desire to be more mannered and become a Japanese dancer. However, during Character Change, both Temari and Nagihiko (as Nadeshiko) become aggressive and very masculine; Nagihiko, inadvertantly, also gains a naginata, which he promptly uses.</description>
<picture>20544.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4463" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-14">
<rating votes="12">6.09</rating>
<name>Souma Kuukai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Souma Kuukai is the upbeat and energetic Jack`s Chair of the Guardians. One year senior to Amu, Kuukai helps Amu with her training as the Joker. Although he was the captain of the football club, Kuukai loves and excels at all sports.</description>
<picture>20545.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="545" picture="188506.jpg">Abe Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4464" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-07">
<rating votes="10">3.56</rating>
<name>Daichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kukai`s Guardian Character is Daichi. He is very good at sports and cannot seem to sit still. He was born when Kukai wanted to do many sports but had to choose. When Daichi and Kukai Character Change, Kukai becomes even more athletic.</description>
<picture>20546.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4465" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-07">
<rating votes="13">6.94</rating>
<name>Yuiki Yaya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The childish girl serving as the Ace Chair and is one year junior to Amu. Yaya often acts immature for her age, such as having an enormous sweet tooth, a great soft spot for items like ribbons, as well as tending to be hyperactive. She is also a ballerina, though a rather clumsy one. She has a newborn baby brother named Tsubasa, who, she claims, gets all her parents` attention.</description>
<picture>20547.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3202" picture="24193.jpg">Nakamura Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4466" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-07">
<rating votes="9">4.63</rating>
<name>Pepe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pepe is a baby-like Guardian Character that belongs to Yaya. When either she or Yaya get hurt or something goes wrong, both of them will begin to whine and cry in unison. During Character Transformation, they become Dear Baby.</description>
<picture>20548.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="546" picture="17760.jpg">Koyama Kimiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4467" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-07">
<rating votes="13">6.63</rating>
<name>Nikaidou Yuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A former employee member of Easter. In order to find the Embryo, he joined Seiyo Elementary and became in charge of Amu`s class in the disguise of a ditzy but kind-hearted teacher. His childhood dream was to become a robot engineer, but when his mentor quit, due to his ailing wife, and his parents opposed the idea, he lost sight of his dream and became a twisted person. He recovered with help from Amu and Su. He resigned from Easter Company and officially become the teacher in charge of Amu`s class.</description>
<picture>20550.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="400" picture="171989.jpg">Majima Junji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4468" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-14">
<rating votes="15">6.02</rating>
<name>Miki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The second Guardian Character to hatch is Miki. Miki represents Amu`s desire to be more level headed and artistic. Miki is also the one to help Amu make fashion choices. Reflecting Amu`s love interests, Miki has shown an interest in Tadase`s Guardian Character, Kiseki, Ikuto`s Guardian Character, Yoru, Kukai`s Guardian Character, Daichi, and Kairi`s Guardian Character, Musashi. During Character Change, Amu gains increased artistic abilities. During Character Transformation, Amu becomes Amulet Spade. In Shugo Chara! Doki, Miki is the only one out of Amu`s Guardian Characters able to sense Mystery Eggs clearly.</description>
<picture>20537.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="402" picture="17249.jpg">Katou Nanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4469" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-07">
<rating votes="9">7.79</rating>
<name>Suu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The third Guardian Character, Suu, represents Amu`s desire to be more caring and improve her domestic skills. However, Suu is prone to silly mistakes. She is very fond of Amu`s teacher, Yuu Nikaidou, after helping Nikaidou realise that he was a good person and can still pursue his own dreams. Amu gains an improvement in cooking and sewing skills during Character Change, as well as becoming</description>
<picture>20538.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5650" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-06">
<rating votes="5">5.09</rating>
<name>Il</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The devilish Il is the first of Utau`s two Character Guardians introduced in the story. Il is mean and unkind, but dislikes nagging. She represents Utau`s energetic and playful side. During Character Transformation, Utau becomes Lunatic Charm, with the attack Nightmare Lorelei and later, Dream Trident. When Il felt lonely because El wasn`t there for her to tease and when she felt that Utau was ignoring her because of Diamond, she Character Transforms with Amu, becoming Amulet Devil.</description>
<picture>22640.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1429" picture="18686.jpg">Konno Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5651" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-06">
<rating votes="17">6.53</rating>
<name>Fujisaki Nagihiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nadeshiko`s real identity is that of a boy named Fujisaki Nagihiko, called "Nagi" as a nickname by Amu and the girls. It is tradition in the Fujisaki family for males to be raised as females as part of their training so that they may play female roles in Japanese dance. Nagihiko`s secret is known by his family, Kukai, Tadase, the school`s principal Amakawa Tsukasa.</description>
<picture>22642.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="311" picture="44706.jpg">Chiba Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5652" type="appears in" update="2009-04-06">
<rating votes="8">6.46</rating>
<name>Lulu De Morcerf</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The new Easter Company worker who can turn Heart`s Eggs into Confused Heart`s Eggs using a ruby necklace. Lulu can also corrupt the owners by forcing the egg to do a confused Character Change and Transform with him/her. Her mother is an actress and her father is a French chef. She wants to find the Embryo so her mother will regain her radiance and make acting history.</description>
<picture>22643.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="349" picture="79057.jpg">Kanda Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5653" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-06">
<rating votes="31">6.41</rating>
<name>Mashiro Rima</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mashiro Rima replaces Nadeshiko as the new Queen`s Chair. Although Rima is the same age as Amu, she is extremely petite and has relatively poor athletic ability. Most of the boys in her class admire her because of her beauty and passive personality, while the girls are annoyed by her because of her selfishness.
Because of a kidnapping incident that happened before she transferred to Seiyo Elementary, her parents pick her up after school, but since it interferes with their work schedules, they often argue about who cares more for Rima over work, resulting in Rima often having no one but Kusukusu as company for her secret interest in gag comedy.</description>
<picture>22645.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="89" picture="148709.jpg">Yahagi Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5654" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-06">
<rating votes="9">3.57</rating>
<name>Kusukusu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rima`s Guardian Character and represents Rima`s desire to make others laugh. When she Character Changes, Rima becomes a gag character (which she is embarrassed to use) and uses a signature phrase and pose: "Bala-Balance" (Balancing Balance) from the magazine Great Gag Manga King. During Character Transformation, Rima becomes Clown Drop.</description>
<picture>22646.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1927" picture="21136.jpg">Narita Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5655" type="appears in" update="2009-04-06">
<rating votes="3">6.59</rating>
<name>Nana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Her speciality is making jewellery. During Character Change, Lulu`s hair clip becomes a purple flower. This allows Lulu to use her necklace to corrupt Heart`s Eggs. Unlike Lulu`s heritage, Nana has a Nagoya accent which results with Lulu sometimes speaking in the same dialect, which embarrasses her greatly. When Lulu used the accent in front of Amu, she complimented it by being cute surprising Lulu.</description>
<picture>22644.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5656" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-06">
<rating votes="17">5.67</rating>
<name>El</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Utau`s second Guardian Character and is the complete angelic opposite of Il. El often nags, likes correcting people about their choices that she considers wrong herself and help those who are troubled by love. Because El was treated badly by Il and ignored by Utau, she left home and wound up in Amu`s care. El can perform a Character Transformation with Amu, resulting in Amulet Angel, which surprised Utau. However, as Amu is not El`s real owner, the Character Transformation remains powerless with no real abilities. Whenever El performs a Character Transformation with Amu, Amu usually ends up being embarrassed due to El`s over-the-top antics. El finally performed a Character Transformation with Utau, forming Seraphic Charm.</description>
<picture>22641.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="650" picture="233419.jpg">Hyousei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7785" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-31">
<rating votes="11">3.10</rating>
<name>Hinamori Tsumugu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2157.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="4587" picture="26895.jpg">Oda Yuusei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8092" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-22">
<rating votes="12">2.17</rating>
<name>Hinamori Ami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hinamori Ami is Amu`s little sister who is innocent and pure-hearted. Ami is able to see Guardian Characters despite the fact that she does not have one. Unlike Amu, Ami is dressed in "Sweet Lolita" clothing. She respects and looks up to both Utau and Amu and loves to sing. She is a huge fan of Utau and played a big role in helping Utau to rediscover her good side.</description>
<picture>43327.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2766" picture="181834.jpg">Mamiya Kurumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8103" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-22">
<rating votes="21">5.34</rating>
<name>Dia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>43330.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11200" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="4">4.79</rating>
<name>Rhythm</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rhythm is Nagihiko`s second Shugo Chara. When they chara-nari, Nagihiko changes into Beat Jumper. He shows up in episode 91 in the anime. "Zenkai! Boku no Rizumu" (全開! 僕のリズム) or "Full Throttle! My Rhythm"</description>
<picture>33212.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="689" picture="170354.jpg">Miyata Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11201" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-15">
<rating votes="11">2.58</rating>
<name>Hoshina Kazuomi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kazuomi Hoshina formerly Kazuomi Ichinomiya, is the managing director of Easter company, a middle-aged man who is also the stepfather of Ikuto Tsukiyomi and Utau Hoshina, and the former superior of Nikaidou and Yukari. After his repeated failure to obtain the Embryo, he started fearing that Gozen may abandon him, so he forms a plan to brainwash Ikuto to collect X-Eggs.</description>
<picture>33213.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="264" picture="228626.jpg">Ogata Mitsuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11203" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-24">
<rating votes="6">4.12</rating>
<name>Sanjou Yukari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Staff of Easter Company. Utau`s manager, was competing with Nikaidou to see who is the first to find the Embryo. Yukari dated Nikaidou in the past.
She came up with a new project "Black Diamond" to at the same find the Embryo and mass-produce X eggs. The CDs of the band were freely distributed and the people listening to it had their Eggs removed by force. As the band became more famous their song is slated to be released to the Internet together with the unveiling of the band. In Seiyo it is branded as a cursed CD. Kairi snuck the CD into Tadase`s bag. When Tadase listened to it, he became infected causing Kiseki to almost change into an X egg, but Amu came and saved him.
After she quit Easter, she and Utau open a company of their own and Utau continues to pursue her career.
Ever since then, Yukari has become friends with the Guardians, though they don`t get along very well.</description>
<picture>43329.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1917" picture="151688.jpg">Natsuki Rio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11205" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-22">
<rating votes="11">3.96</rating>
<name>Amakawa Tsukasa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He was the first King`s Chair of the "Guardians" and their founder. Manages the planetarium as a part-time job. Artist of the artbook "Kokoro no Tamago" (The Heart`s Egg). Looks similar to Tadase. At first, he is thought to hold the Humpty Lock. A cat lover and has a liking for Ikuto`s cat ears. He plays as a minor character but seems to have a bigger role in the story, considering that it is he who assigns the Guardian Chairs and is often seen counseling Tadase.</description>
<picture>43326.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12239" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-14">
<rating votes="5">4.04</rating>
<name>Hiiragi Rikka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130760.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="543" picture="17747.jpg">Erika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12240" type="appears in" update="2017-04-17">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Batsu tama</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Batsu tama are the eggs of Shugo Chara that have become corrupt, due to the children who created them doubting themselves. When they hatch they are called Batsu Charas.</description>
<picture>39808.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12241" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-14">
<rating votes="3">5.83</rating>
<name>Ichinomiya Hikaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130758.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="218" picture="17036.jpg">Nakao Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12422" type="appears in" update="2010-02-22">
<rating votes="5">5.15</rating>
<name>Sanjou Kairi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kairi is tall, despite being two years junior to Amu. Unlike the spontaneous Kukai, Kairi is intelligent, uptight, very organized, and blunt about faults. Even with these traits, he is so capable that Amu and Yaya call him "class president". He can also become very shy in certain situations. He has a tendency to be the "planner" of the group, ad he usually leads the meetings and instructs what is to be done by each member.</description>
<picture>43328.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="180" picture="171567.jpg">Saiga Mitsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12423" type="appears in" update="2009-10-21">
<rating votes="7">4.82</rating>
<name>Musashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Musashi`s appearance and name are that of a real samurai. He has traditional, green Samurai clothing, with what appears to be a Kendo sword strapped to the side. He has purple eyes, green hair styled as a chonmage, and wears glasses like Kairi.</description>
<picture>2695.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12424" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-21">
<rating votes="14">4.58</rating>
<name>Hinamori Midori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Midori Hinamori works as an editor for the magazine Housewives` Knowledge. Midori is the one responsible for choosing Amu`s and Ami`s clothing styles.
Unlike their father, Midori is more understanding of Amu`s relationship with boys.</description>
<picture>2696.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="1983" picture="151694.jpg">Murai Kazusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15116" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-21">
<rating votes="1">7.41</rating>
<name>Hotaru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hotaru is polite and elegant, providing a balance to Rikka`s energy and spunk.</description>
<picture>43289.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="162" picture="23208.jpg">Satou Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="108505" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">元気いっぱい転校生!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Super-Peppy Transfer Student!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Genki Ippai Tenkousei!</title>
<summary>Amu meets a super-peppy transfer student to Seiyo Academy Elementary School named Hiiragi Rikka at school one day. Not only can she see Guardian Characters, but it seems she has some other, mysterious powers as well. When she sees the work that Amu and the other Guardians to at school, she`s awestruck.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>534422</identifier>
<identifier>shugo-chara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="109019" update="2009-10-02">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="109089" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ややの張り切りガーデニング!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yaya`s Limitless Gardening!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yaya no Harikiri Gardening!!</title>
<summary>Yaya takes along Rikka and Hikaru to help with her job of taking care of the flower beds, but with more enthusiasm than usual because it`s her first time mentoring younger students! Rikka is totally impressed, but the next day an X Egg appears and does something terrible!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>534432</identifier>
<identifier>shugo-chara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="109090" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひかるvsウサギ? 初仕事は大変!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hikaru vs the Rabbit? The Very First Job!</title>
<title xml:lang="sk">Hikaru vs Králik? Celkom prvá práca!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hikaru vs Usagi? Hatsu Shigoto ha Taihen!</title>
<summary>Hikaru-kun is given the responsibility to take care of a rabbit as part of the Guardian`s work, but although he`s knowledgeable he doesn`t understand why anyone would want to. Amu, Rikka and the Guardian Characters help out with the various jobs, but during a walk the rabbit doesn`t look so well...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>534430</identifier>
<identifier>shugo-chara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="109091" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ココロ輝け! 歌パワー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sparkling Heart! Power Song!</title>
<title xml:lang="sk">Žiariace srdce! Pieseň sily!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokoro Kagayake! Uta Power!</title>
<summary>Amu is invited to the big concert Utau is having today, and she brings along Rikka and Hikaru.  Rikka is a giant fan and really revved up unlike Hikaru who has his usual cool composure.  He doesn`t understand what Rikka means when she says that listening to music can energize you.  But just then, an X Egg appears in the concert hall... What will become of the performance?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>534428</identifier>
<identifier>shugo-chara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="109107" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">誕生! ガーディアン見習い!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Birth! Guardian Apprentice!?</title>
<title xml:lang="sk">Zrodenie! Učeň Strážcu!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tanjou! Guardian Minarai!?</title>
<summary>Amu meets a super-peppy transfer student to Seiyo Academy Elementary School named Hiiragi Rikka at school one day. Not only can she see Guardian Characters, but it seems she has some other, mysterious power as well. When she sees the work that Amu and the other Guardians do at school, she`s awestruck.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>534426</identifier>
<identifier>shugo-chara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="110717" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-11-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">たまごの帰る場所!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Placing the Eggs Back!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tamago no Kaeru Basho!</title>
<summary>Rikka forgets about her job and spaces out in the Royal Garden, so to get her mind back in the game she`s asked to get Yaya and Hikaru from the flower garden.  Amu is a little worried so she has her Guardian Characters go with her, but just as expected Rikka gets distracted on the way.  She runs into an X Egg, and chases after it by herself.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>534434</identifier>
<identifier>shugo-chara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="111203" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-12-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">なりたいあたし!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Who I Want to be!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Naritai Atashi!</title>
<summary>Amu and the others follow after their Guardian Characters when they sense something strange, and come across a young girl who has lost her heart`s egg. The girl is holding a broken stuffed animal in her hand, but they don`t know what happened. As they search for the X Egg, Rikka begins to think about who she wants to be.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>537094</identifier>
<identifier>shugo-chara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="111204" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-12-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">へろへろ~あむちゃん, ママになる?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m Beat~ Amu-chan Becomes a Mom?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hero Hero~ Amu-chan, Mama ni Naru?</title>
<summary>It`s finally Sunday, but Amu doesn`t just have a ton of homework to do, her parents leave her to handle everything at home, too!  She ends up getting caught up playing around with her Guardian Characters and Ami, just as high spirited as ever, but there`s plenty of cooking and cleaning she also has to handle! Can Amu be Ami`s "Mom for a day?"
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>537014</identifier>
<identifier>shugo-chara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="111205" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-12-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">キラキラな宝物!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">That Sparkling Treasure!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kirakira na Takaramono!</title>
<summary>Rikka loses her special treasure, a necklace that her dad gave her when she entered elementary school, and is desperately retracing her steps in order to find it.  Amu and her Guardian Characters all help Rikka out, but Hikaru doesn`t understand what all the fuss is about. Hikaru can`t comprehend how something as trivial as a gift from someone can be so precious...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>536014</identifier>
<identifier>shugo-chara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="111206" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-12-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">えっ! 唯世くんに好きな人!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What? Tadase-kun has a Crush on Someone?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eh! Tadase-kun ni Suki na Hito!?</title>
<summary>Walking down the street, Amu spots Tadase and Kukai talking to each other. "Could it be love they`re discussing," Amu thinks, when she listens in and hears Tadase talking about a "cute little thing!" The Guardian Characters head to Tadase`s place to ascertain the truth. Amu stays behind in her room, depressed, when she gets a call from you-know-who...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>536012</identifier>
<identifier>shugo-chara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="111207" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-11-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">どうして!? りま先輩!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Why!? Rima-senpai!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Doushite!? Rima-senpai!</title>
<summary>Rikka is so overjoyed that the seeds they`d just planted had sprouted. She drags Amu and Rima to take a look. When Rima starts to thin out the buds that don`t look so healthy, Rikka is upset because she thought that every sprout has the possibility to turn into a flower.  The two have a misunderstanding, and Rikka runs off while Rima continues her work...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>536010</identifier>
<identifier>shugo-chara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="111208" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-11-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">魅惑のキャラチェンジ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Charming Chara Change!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Miwaku no Chara Change!</title>
<summary>Amu and Tadase are walking home together, which they hadn`t done in a while. Amu is not honest with her feelings as usual, and Ran can`t stand it so Character Changes Amu! Rikka happens to see it walking by, and thinks it`s totally great! She asks Amu to change one after another until she`s completely worn out.  Eventually Rikka asks to Character Change with Miki to help her with arts and crafts, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>536008</identifier>
<identifier>shugo-chara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="111209" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-11-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おかえり! なでしこ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome Back! Nadeshiko!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Okaeri! Nadeshiko!</title>
<summary>Nadeshiko is back! Amu goes to see her after noticing that she`d be performing at a Fujisaki house dance recital, but Nagihiko is all worried she`ll discover the truth. Despite the help of a miraculous (?) assist from Rima, just as things were starting up again an X egg appears, so Nadeshiko...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>536006</identifier>
<identifier>shugo-chara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="112281" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-01-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぐるんぐるん! まわる世界!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Round-and-Round! Our Spinning World!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gurungurun! Mawaru Sekai!</title>
<summary>Hikaru has a test in gym class tomorrow where he has to do a spin on the horizontal bar, and after school Nagihiko and Amu help him practice. However Hikaru, always focused on efficiency, doesn`t understand the purpose of working to be able to do a spin. Amu practices with him to find the answer, but will they be able to complete a spin?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>537102</identifier>
<identifier>shugo-chara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="112282" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-01-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">進めりっか! ガーディアンへの道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Go Rikka! Follow the Way of the Guardians!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Susume Rikka! Guardian e no Machi</title>
<summary>Rikka finally had her Guardian Egg be born!!! She`s so excited that she does her Guardian Apprentice job even more enthusiastically than before, but thanks to some teasing by other students she begins to question the role of the Guardians. Amu and the others get worried about Rikka suddenly losing her sparkle...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>537100</identifier>
<identifier>shugo-chara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="112283" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-01-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ケンカはやめて!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stop Fighting!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kenka wa Yamete!</title>
<summary>Rikka gets angry and slaps Hikaru-kun after she offers to let her friend, Kimi, read his palm and he dismisses it as unscientific which makes Kimi upset. Neither of them have many regrets until they slowly start to understand what they did wrong after listening to what Amu and Tadase have to say.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>537098</identifier>
<identifier>shugo-chara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="112284" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-01-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">初対面! これが×(バツ)キャラ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Encounter of the X Character Kind!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shotaimen! Kore ga Kakeru (Batsu) Kyara!?</title>
<summary>Rikka continues to think about what kind of person she wants to become, but she can`t come up with anything. Amu and the gang try to give her suggestions, but she just gets frustrated. Just then, an X Egg appears. As it`s the first X Character she`s ever seen, Rikka tries to calm it down, but it begins to attack!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>537096</identifier>
<identifier>shugo-chara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="116295" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-02-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">どっきどきのピクニック!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Heart-Racing Picnic!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dokidoki no Picnic!</title>
<summary>Amu and Hikaru all head out with Rikka`s family together for a picnic, but Hikaru doesn`t seem to understand what`s so fun about it. But as he spends time with Rikka`s mom and dad, Hikaru starts to understand a little about what it`s like having a family.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>539224</identifier>
<identifier>shugo-chara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="116395" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-02-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">めまして, ほたると申します.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How do you do? My Name is Hotaru</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimemashite, Hotaru to Moushimasu</title>
<summary>After Hotaru is born, Rikka runs around introducing her to everyone bright and early in the morning! It would seem like the perfect time for a celebration in the Royal Garden, but instead she`s picked to do a presentation at the next general Guardian Assembly! Can Rikka get over her unease and nerves and step into her new, important role?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>539230</identifier>
<identifier>shugo-chara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="116396" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-02-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">どきっ! たまごに×が付いちゃった?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shock! My Egg Got an X on it?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Doki! Tamago ni X ga Tsuichatta?</title>
<summary>Rikka is worried that her Guardian Egg will never hatch until she figures out who she wants to be, so she decides to become the coolest person in the school, Amu! But the Guardians and her friends just think she`s acting weird and are worried about her. Rikka gets depressed that she can never be cool like Amu, and suddenly her Guardian Egg turns into an X Egg! How can she ever show her face to Amu again?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>539228</identifier>
<identifier>shugo-chara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="116397" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-02-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">歌唄, 揺れるココロ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Utau`s Wavering Heart!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Utau, Yureru Kokoro!</title>
<summary>Utau storms out of a recording session for her new song, and goes to eat ramen with Kukai to cool her head. But when even her favorite ramen shop changes their recipe in response to customer feedback, Utau goes to ask for advice the only place she can... Amu`s house!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>539226</identifier>
<identifier>shugo-chara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="116781" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-03-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひかると楽しい遊園地!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hikaru and the Fun Amusement Park!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hikaru to Tanoshii Yuuenchi!</title>
<summary>Rikka has a fun time playing "Dadashiko" with the Guardian Characters in the Royal Garden, but Hikaru doesn`t seem amused. After some questioning, it seems that Hikaru has never really laughed in his entire life! Amu decides to fix this problem, and invites him and Rikka for a fun Sunday at the amusement park. Even though Hikaru says he`s having a lot of fun, he still isn`t laughing. Is there nothing that will make him laugh?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>539232</identifier>
<identifier>shugo-chara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="116786" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-03-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">信じて! あたしのピュアハート!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Believe! In my Pure Heart!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinjite! Atashi no Pure Heart!</title>
<summary>Amu and Tadase head to Rikka`s room and find Rikka crying over the remains of a shattered X egg. Rikka confesses that she was keeping all those X eggs in her room to Amu, and after Su helps explain that the X eggs didn`t do anything bad on purpose, Rikka realizes it was all her fault. Meanwhile, Nagihiko and Rima chase after the X eggs, but every time they try and get near them they burst, sending out a wave of sadness! Can Rikka save what remains of her X egg friends before its too late?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>539236</identifier>
<identifier>shugo-chara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="116787" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-03-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大変! りっかと×タマが?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Oh, no! Rikka and the X Eggs...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taihen! Rikka to X Tama ga?</title>
<summary>Rikka stays up late at night playing card games with Hotaru, and ends up being late to a Sunday Guardian meeting where they`re preparing for a graduation party. Back at her home, the X Eggs notice that she forgot to bring paints with her, and try to help out Rikka because they feel neglected with Hotaru taking up Rikka`s attention lately, but they only screw up and make things worse. Rikka doesn`t realize they were trying to help, however, and yells at them all.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>539234</identifier>
<identifier>shugo-chara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117008" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-03-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">どっきどきのドッキドキ!!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heartbeat of Heartbeat!!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dokki Doki no Dokki Doki!!!</title>
<summary>Why is Ikuto in Amu`s room? Amu ends up getting caught up in Ikuto`s flow as usual and taken to the amusement park, but this time Tadase-kun shows up and Amu`s shocked and nervous! But... Then, a few days later, there`s the final Guardian`s meeting a few days before the graduation ceremony.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>539238</identifier>
<identifier>shugo-chara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="211333" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-10-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211334" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-10-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211335" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-10-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211336" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-10-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211337" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-10-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211338" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-10-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211339" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-10-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211340" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-10-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211341" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-10-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211342" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-10-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211343" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-11-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211344" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-11-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211345" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-11-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 13</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211346" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S14</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-11-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 14</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211347" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S15</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-11-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 15</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211348" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S16</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-11-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 16</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211349" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S17</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-11-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 17</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211350" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S18</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-11-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 18</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211351" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S19</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-12-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 19</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211352" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S20</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-12-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 20</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211353" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S21</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-12-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 21</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211354" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S22</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-12-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 22</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211355" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S23</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-12-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 23</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211356" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S24</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-12-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 24</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211357" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S25</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-12-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 25</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211358" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S26</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-12-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 26</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211359" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S27</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-01-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 27</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211360" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S28</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-01-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 28</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211361" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S29</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-01-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 29</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211362" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S30</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-01-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 30</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211363" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S31</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-01-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 31</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211364" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S32</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-01-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 32</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211365" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S33</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-01-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 33</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211366" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S34</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-01-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 34</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211367" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S35</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-02-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 35</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211368" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S37</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-02-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 37</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211369" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S38</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-02-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 38</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211370" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S39</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-02-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 39</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211371" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S40</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-02-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 40</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211372" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S41</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-02-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 41</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211373" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S42</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-02-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 42</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211374" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S43</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-03-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 43</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211375" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S44</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-03-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 44</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211376" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S45</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-03-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 45</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211377" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S46</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-03-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 46</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211378" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S47</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-03-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 47</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211379" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S48</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-03-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 48</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211380" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S49</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-03-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 49</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211381" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S50</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-03-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 50</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211382" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="2">S36</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-02-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Shugo Chara! Pucchi Puchi 36</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
