<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6968" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-04-03</startdate>
<enddate>2010-06-19</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ichiban Ushiro no Daimaou</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Color Wars</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Князь тьмы с задней парты</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">언젠가는 대마왕</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">En Arka Sıradaki Şeytan Kral</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Най-силният демоничен крал</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Князь темряви з останньої парти</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="synonym">最後大魔王</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Ichiban</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Daimao</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">いちばんうしろの大魔王</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Demon King Daimao</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Demon King Daimao</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">最后大魔王</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9015" approval="134" total="151">Hagure Yuusha no Aesthetica</anime>
<anime id="8660" approval="128" total="150">High School DxD</anime>
<anime id="8861" approval="83" total="96">Campione! Matsurowanu Kamigami to Kamigoroshi no Maou</anime>
<anime id="5273" approval="66" total="93">Rosario to Vampire</anime>
<anime id="10441" approval="25" total="29">Trinity Seven</anime>
<anime id="10529" approval="23" total="29">Shinmai Maou no Testament</anime>
<anime id="9999" approval="9" total="18">Seirei Tsukai no Blade Dance</anime>
<anime id="7900" approval="8" total="24">Freezing</anime>
<anime id="6564" approval="2" total="29">Angel Beats!</anime>
<anime id="14391" approval="2" total="7">Maou-sama, Retry!</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="10">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="733904">It bogged down in the middle. I still enjoyed it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="364765">I have to say, I agree with sammy321. This anime was good at the beginning and that one action scene in the first episode made me think that it would be awesome but it just fell from its potential glory. It was still a good anime though.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="436338">Would love to say something like "totaly awesome" since this anime started out rly great, but 2nd part of it rly cooled me off, its good anime and its definately recommended, but ending could have been muuuuuuuuuch better.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="521503">I read all the reviews before i watched it, deciding in advance that it was alot of story cramped into 12 episodes. Also, i think the first half is more liked since it follows the manga, wich is right after the dragon part right about now. But, deciding in before hand about it faults, it actually became better. I`d still recommend it, as long as you dont expect "WOOOOOW!!!" in advance.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.mmv.co.jp/special/daimao/</url>
<creators>
<name id="7259" type="Character Design">Ozeki Miyabi</name>
<name id="3730" type="Series Composition">Yoshioka Takao</name>
<name id="2120" type="Direction">Watanabe Takashi</name>
<name id="7259" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ozeki Miyabi</name>
<name id="16740" type="Original Work">Mizuki Shoutarou</name>
<name id="1417" type="Character Design">Kobayashi Toshimitsu</name>
<name id="999" type="Work">Artland</name>
<name id="1417" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kobayashi Toshimitsu</name>
<name id="10106" type="Music">Katou Tatsuya</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr16740 [Mizuki Shoutarou]`s magical fantasy romance novel series of the same name, with illustrations by http://anidb.net/cr16742 [Itou Souichi].
http://anidb.net/ch13359 [Sai Akuto] aims to become part of his country`s highest order of magicians and contribute to society as one of its clergy. On the day he is admitted into the Constan Magical Academy, his aptitude test predicts the following though: "Future Occupation... Devil King". Thus begins his difficult school life in which he is resented by the combative female class head, http://anidb.net/ch13361 [Hattori Junko], desired by a girl with mysterious powers, http://anidb.net/ch13360 [Soga Keena], and guarded by a beautiful female android, http://anidb.net/ch13362 [Korone].
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="4579">4.89</permanent>
<temporary count="4623">6.95</temporary>
<review count="3">4.55</review>
</ratings>
<picture>45614.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11179</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8465</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>7088</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4655</identifier>
<identifier>ykkiln</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.mmv.co.jp/special/daimao/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ichiban_Ushiro_no_Dai_Maō</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>いちばんうしろの大魔王</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1888</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>336377</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12524</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>demon-king-daimao</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B00DAA5ZPW</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="920" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-03-22">
<name>perverted</name>
<description>Is a concept describing those types of human behavior that are excessive or deviated from what is considered to be orthodox or normal.</description>
<picurl>245189.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1136" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-18">
<name>transfer student</name>
<description>A transfer student is a student who changes from one institution or course to another at the same level. Their arrival, when not at the beginning of the school year, tends to cause a stir.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1783" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>immature</name>
<description>Marked by or indicating a lack of maturity</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2355" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>dragon</name>
<description>Very intelligent mythical beings - a cross between a very large lizard and a dinosaur - that breath fire, and have a knack for kidnapping damsels, thus distressing them. In Fantasy anime this perceptive species often lives secluded from human civilisation, protectors of long lost knowledge. Dragons seem to be on the verge of extinction.</description>
<picurl>32579.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2578" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-12">
<name>vulgar</name>
<description>Talking (and acting) in a way that is considered uncultivated, bawdy, common, coarse or unrefined, or "taboo" according to existing cultural standards. Includes boorish manners and obtrusive display of carnal "assets".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2706" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>masturbation</name>
<description>Manual erotic stimulation of the genitals or other erogenous regions, often to orgasm, either by oneself or a partner.</description>
<picurl>210612.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2821" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sudden naked girl appearance</name>
<description>A character or group of characters are simply minding their own business, when suddenly, a naked girl appears. It does not matter how or why, but a naked someone is there. Sometimes the naked girl is not happy about this. 
Usually this is a fanservice element, but not always.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2823" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>paper clothes</name>
<description>Worn clothing appears paper-thin and takes little abuse to be shredded or torn from the body. This is common in ecchi anime where the main storyline involves some type of fighting but consists primarily of dialogue and fanservice (Ikkitousen and Platonic Heart). Various girls’ clothing exploding as if made of rice paper is a very enticing prospect.</description>
<picurl>150776.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2824" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>pseudo tentacle rape scene</name>
<description>If this was porn she (or rather the audience) would have even more fun!</description>
<picurl>160554.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3107" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-10-12">
<name>unfoundedly feared character</name>
<description>Due to some strange misunderstanding, or some other unfounded reason the character in the anime is feared by his contemporaries.
Example: A male student with an "evil eye" is mistaken for a delinquent, and thus feared by the students in his class.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3315" parentid="2623" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-28">
<name>superhero</name>
<description>In modern popular fiction, a superhero is a type of costumed heroic character who possesses supernatural or superhuman powers and who is dedicated to fighting crime, protecting the public, and usually battling supervillains. A female superhero is sometimes called a superheroine. Fiction centered on such characters, especially in American comic books since the 1930s, is known as superhero fiction.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3327" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-08">
<name>manly</name>
<description>Masculinity is possessing qualities or characteristics considered typical of or appropriate to a man.
Typical characteristics associated with masculinity are: courage, a strong physique, competitive, strong willed, and a sense of honor.
Very important for being considered masculine however is the ability to inspire respect from your fellow brethren and/or being perceived as a virile man by the opposite sex.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3444" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>hot springs visit</name>
<description>An onsen is a term for hot springs in the Japanese language, though the term is often used to describe the bathing facilities and inns around the hot springs. Often the cast of a show somehow ends up going to an onsen because of various reasons, such as winning a lottery ticket. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters nude and raise the DVD sales.
Another cheap variant is the http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160784.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3898" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-11">
<name>science and magic coexist</name>
<description>In this anime science and magic do not exclude each other. Magic here is actually very advanced, artefact- and/or ritual-based science.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4182" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-01-22">
<name>hidden power</name>
<description>For some reason or another a character has powers (or potential) he or she can`t access and may not even know about. 
In some anime these hidden powers are used quite frequently to overcome an enemy or threat (e.g. Naruto, Bleach).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4290" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>bath house visit</name>
<description>A sentou is a type of Japanese communal bath house where customers pay for entrance. Some Japanese find social importance in going to public baths, out of the theory that physical intimacy brings emotional intimacy, which is termed skinship in Japanese. Traditionally it is gender-segregated — men usually bathe only with men, and women with women. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales.
See also http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode], http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160783.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4323" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-04">
<name>spacing out</name>
<description>A comedy element: The character starts to daydream or fantasize about some topic. The typical complete lack of reality makes the spacing out funny. Especially when the protagonist mumbles to himself / herself and friends hear this. Promptly teasing the possibly lovestruck and very embarrassed protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5807" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2007-08-08">
<name>cosmic reset</name>
<description>All events that occurred up to a certain point are mysteriously undone, as if the Universe pressed a rewind button. This usually means some characters are being given another chance to unknowingly play out events differently, perhaps to prevent certain consequences from the previous time line`s actions. Occasionally they become doomed to repeat portions of their life over and over again until an individual event or series of events are performed correctly in just the right way, as seemingly to gain the Universe`s approval.</description>
<picurl>36685.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5943" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-14">
<name>misunderstanding</name>
<description>Suggests that a large portion of storyline revolves around a rather large misunderstanding between two or more characters, usually forming long lasting situations of separation or hostility between all those involved.
A large portion of the story may be dedicated to gradually working all parties into a mutual understanding to true intentions or changes of heart.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6072" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-25">
<name>just as planned</name>
<description>A term usually used to describe a situation, where a seemingly smart and cunning villain sets up a plan that seems grand and impressive, but is actually long winding, ridiculous, and convoluted. And all of that just to trick his opponent(s), like the hero or anybody else, into doing things exactly as he planned. Suffice to say that the villain could have reached his goal by much shorter and easier means, it just wouldn`t seem as awesome anymore.
The phrase is also known as the original Japanese "keikaku doori" where keikaku stands translated for "plan" or "schedule", and doori for "in accordance with ..." or "following ...".
The phrase is a reference to http://anidb.net/ch301 [Yagami Light] from http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], and his love for plans.</description>
<picurl>211219.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="13359" type="main character in" update="2012-01-28">
<rating votes="63">8.32</rating>
<name>Sai Akuto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A new transferee into the Constan Magical Academy, he is foretold by the Yata Garasu to have the eventual destiny of Demon Lord. This causes much controversy and fear among the rest of the students of the Academy once this becomes widely known, although some remain by his side. The Empire takes an interest in him as well, although it is unclear what exactly their plans for him entail.
Despite his frightful destiny, Sai Akuto appears to be a good person, and is actually rather kind and friendly, especially to the few who have befriended him and the women who have become attached to him, such as Hattori Junko and Soga Keena. However, he is also a staunch atheist who believes that the various gods that humanity has are really personifications of an oppressive system, and that humanity would be better off without gods or religion.</description>
<picture>40617.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="616" picture="18138.jpg">Kondou Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13360" type="main character in" update="2010-06-12">
<rating votes="59">6.43</rating>
<name>Soga Keena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Soga Keena is Akuto`s classmate, who always wears a strange bird-shaped pendant that allows her to become completely invisible, even to the point of cloaking her mana, although this only applies to her body: anything she may be carrying, including her clothes and the pendant itself, remain visible. She doesn`t appear to have any other powers or magical skill apart from invisibility and flight. She is rather nonsensical, often acting based on unlikely and bizarre reasoning. She frequently steals dangerous objects from Fujiko`s room, which more often than not result in thwarting Fujiko`s carefully laid plans.
She is later revealed to have been childhood friends with Sai Akuto since they were at the same orphanage together, and that he had given her the bird pendant shortly before his departure. She flatly denies ever having met Akuto before meeting him at Constan for some reason, despite Akuto`s vague memories.</description>
<picture>40619.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13361" type="main character in" update="2010-06-12">
<rating votes="74">7.32</rating>
<name>Hattori Junko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hattori Junko is a student at Constan Magical Academy and a disciple of Suhara, a samurai-like order of warriors charged to protect the Empire. She meets Akuto on the train to the school, and makes a pact with him to make the world a better place. She feels betrayed when his destiny as a Demon Lord is revealed after their arrival at the school, and at first believes the world would be a better place if he were destroyed, and frequently misinterprets his attempts at kindness and good deeds as being evil. However, she develops strong romantic feelings for Sai Akuto in spite of herself.</description>
<picture>40620.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13362" type="main character in" update="2010-06-12">
<rating votes="92">7.70</rating>
<name>Korone</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Korone is a Liladan, a type of android, sent by the Imperial government to observe Sai Akuto at all times. Usually, she is emotionless and stolid, however, also she seems to enjoy teasing Akuto and frequently does perverted things to him. She sleeps in a closet in Akuto`s dorm room, and carries a magical handbag containing implausibly large weapons and other useful items. Like all Liladans, she has a small rabbit-like tail which deactivates her when pulled.</description>
<picture>40621.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13363" type="main character in" update="2010-06-12">
<rating votes="34">1.90</rating>
<name>Miwa Hiroshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiroshi is Akuto`s self-described minion much to Akuto`s dismay. A boy of small stature, he is frequently and savagely bullied and he sees Akuto as his protector. His desire to become Akuto`s servant began when Akuto gave a speech in class that touched him, although its debatably anarchistic climax terrified the rest of the class. Despite looking up to Akuto, he believes him to actually be evil and often misinterprets his intentions, giving counterproductive advice as a result.</description>
<picture>40618.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="586" picture="171556.jpg">Yonaga Tsubasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13364" type="main character in" update="2010-06-12">
<rating votes="53">6.78</rating>
<name>Etou Fujiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Etou Fujiko is the current head of the Etou family, the leader of the girls` dormitory at Constan Magical Academy, and also the leader of a secret society of students who use black magic for evil purposes. She is one of the few who are aware of Sai Akuto`s situation, and plans to use Akuto`s demon lord powers for her own ends. Despite her plans to manipulate Akuto for her own ends, she is romantically attracted to him.</description>
<picture>40622.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13365" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-01">
<rating votes="19">4.41</rating>
<name>Torii Mitsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Torii Mitsuko is a teacher and school nurse at the Constan Magical Academy. She is rather mischievous, and always likes to half-jokingly tell Akuto of how, should he be killed for any reason, she would turn him undead and study his Demon Lord makeup that way.</description>
<picture>45610.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1665" picture="19756.jpg">Takahashi Chiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13366" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-12">
<rating votes="44">6.22</rating>
<name>Lily Shiraishi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lily Shiraishi is president of the Constan Magical Academy Student Council, and is, as such, Sai Akuto`s superior in his capacity as part of the Disciplinary Committee. She is always seen wearing a pointed witch`s hat, and possesses significant magical power. She is the first girl to actually kiss Akuto, and appears to have romantic feelings for him as well.</description>
<picture>40623.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="346" picture="17184.jpg">Hirohashi Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16355" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-12">
<rating votes="7">3.43</rating>
<name>Yata Garasu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Yata Garasu is a strange, bird-like creature kept in a bell jar in Constan Magical Academy, with the strange power of being able to see the future occupations of all students presented to it. This is done whenever new students enter the Academy, and chaos erupted when he declared Sai Akuto`s destined future occupation as `Demon Lord`.</description>
<picture>45612.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2605" picture="22592.jpg">Shiratori Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16770" type="appears in" update="2010-04-15">
<rating votes="9">6.00</rating>
<name>Gakuchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46386.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3135" picture="24120.jpg">Fujimoto Yuzuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16813" type="appears in" update="2010-06-12">
<rating votes="7">5.38</rating>
<name>Fujiko no Ani</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The preserved head of Etou Fujiko`s elder brother, which she keeps in her room and with whom she frequently talks.
It is revealed that he failed in an important mission to determine the whereabouts of Peterhausen, the dragon used by the previous demon lord and later on by Sai Akuto.</description>
<picture>46486.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16814" type="appears in" update="2010-04-19">
<rating votes="11">5.14</rating>
<name>Ootake Michie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46607.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16815" type="appears in" update="2010-04-19">
<rating votes="11">5.67</rating>
<name>Kamiyama Kanna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46608.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1609" picture="19579.jpg">Mizuhara Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16816" type="appears in" update="2010-04-19">
<rating votes="16">2.83</rating>
<name>Aru`nuuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46609.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1798" picture="20493.jpg">Kotobuki Minako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16817" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-12">
<rating votes="37">4.07</rating>
<name>Teruya Eiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Eiko is a government agent sent out to see if Akuto can avert his predestined occupation as Demon Lord. She is very clingy and possesive to Akuto and she occasionally rides on his shoulders much to his discomfort. Similar to Junko, Eiko is also a disciple of Suhara and she and Junko are bitter rivals.</description>
<picture>48552.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16818" type="appears in" update="2010-04-17">
<rating votes="5">2.80</rating>
<name>Fujiko no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46494.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12600" picture="42565.jpg">Toujou Kanako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17291" type="appears in" update="2010-06-12">
<rating votes="15">8.32</rating>
<name>Peterhausen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Peterhausen is a dragon that lay dormant within a secret chamber near Constan Magical Academy, where he slept since the previous Demon Lord was slain a century ago. He is unswervingly loyal to Akuto since his awakening.</description>
<picture>47208.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17641" type="appears in" update="2010-05-14">
<rating votes="7">4.68</rating>
<name>Miwa Yukiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47968.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="89" picture="148709.jpg">Yahagi Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17642" type="appears in" update="2010-06-12">
<rating votes="18">1.77</rating>
<name>Brave</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Brave is the superhero alter-ego of Miwa Hiroshi, which he acquired after he found the AI Unit D13 in the depths of the lake near his village, in accordance with a prophecy from his grandfather. The unit gave him a power suit armed with many weapons such as lasers, plasma cannons, and energy blades. Hiroshi keeps his identity as Brave a secret from everyone else.</description>
<picture>47969.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="586" picture="171556.jpg">Yonaga Tsubasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17643" type="appears in" update="2010-05-14">
<rating votes="3">4.51</rating>
<name>Mister X</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47970.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="646" picture="186183.jpg">Satou Haruo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17644" type="appears in" update="2010-05-14">
<rating votes="2">3.23</rating>
<name>Hiroshi no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47971.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12648" picture="172620.jpg">Kibe Kimiyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17898" type="appears in" update="2012-09-21">
<rating votes="17">3.80</rating>
<name>Hattori Yuuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hattori Yuuko, better known to the general public as the idol and reporter Hoshino Yuri, is Junko`s younger sister, and also a Suhara disciple. She was contaminated with monster blood in her childhood, and as a result experiences adverse reactions to Akuto`s Demon Lord mana.</description>
<picture>48553.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18103" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-25">
<rating votes="11">2.58</rating>
<name>Yamato Bouichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48554.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2802" picture="176252.jpg">Shingaki Tarusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18160" type="appears in" update="2010-05-28">
<rating votes="2">4.06</rating>
<name>Teruya Keizou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48704.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10832" picture="233750.jpg">Nakamura Koutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18161" type="appears in" update="2010-05-28">
<rating votes="2">3.23</rating>
<name>Hattori Youzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48705.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="695" picture="38273.jpg">Ono Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18475" type="appears in" update="2010-06-04">
<rating votes="3">2.60</rating>
<name>2V</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49107.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10190" picture="48563.jpg">Higuchi Tomoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18476" type="appears in" update="2010-06-04">
<rating votes="2">4.99</rating>
<name>Rubbers</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49108.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12387" picture="223823.jpg">Yanai Hitoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18703" type="appears in" update="2010-06-11">
<rating votes="3">4.21</rating>
<name>Kamiyama Kanna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49492.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="116478" update="2010-02-18">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116829" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-03</airdate>
<rating votes="20">6.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔王が誕生しちゃった!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Demon King Is Born!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maou ga Tanjou Shichatta!</title>
<summary>The year is 3000 where magic is common place. Transferring to the Constant Academy of Magical Arts just as the new quarter begins, Sai Akuto hopes to become a High Priest.  But during his aptitude test on the first day, the artificial spirit Yata-garasu says that he`s destined to become a "Demon Lord"!  So now Hattori Junko, who he`d sworn an oath of friendship with earlier that day, challenges him to a duel. The duel is interrupted by a girl named Keena as the misunderstandings get worse and worse!
Akuto, potential future Demon Lord, begins his days of trying to fix these misunderstandings!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>539996</identifier>
<identifier>demon-king-daimao</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117396" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-10</airdate>
<rating votes="16">6.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おかしな監視員</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Strange Surveillance Agent</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Okashina Kanshiin</title>
<summary>On his first day, Akuto was told he was destined to become a Demon Lord. He tries his best to tell everyone it`s all a misunderstanding, but everything he does just makes matters worse. And then things get even crazier: the government sends an artificial human called a Liladan to watch over him 24/7 and Keena shows up suddenly and jumps him while naked! But then, the most popular girl at school, the head of the girl`s dorm Etou Fujiko says that she understands him, and that she`ll patch things up with Junko. However...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>539998</identifier>
<identifier>demon-king-daimao</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117591" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="16">6.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ちょっと怖い先輩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Slightly Intimidating Senior</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chotto Kowai Senpai</title>
<summary>Akuto applies for the position of Disciplinary Committee member at Fujiko`s suggestion so he can get back in Junko`s good graces.  But that job entails defeating those who threaten the school`s discipline, and is considered perfect for the "Future Demon Lord".  Akuto is suspicious of Fujiko, but his doubts disappear when she arranges for him to meet her.  He goes to the designated spot, but there he`s ambushed by a bunch of thugs.  He defeats them, but Junko sees him beating them up and gets the idea that he`s planning on making them his personal army so he can take over the school.  Junko submits an application to the school to take him down, and Akuto is forced to go up against the entire student body...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>540000</identifier>
<identifier>demon-king-daimao</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117600" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="15">6.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">独房は楽しい?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Isolation Cell Is Fun?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dokubou wa Tanoshii?</title>
<summary>Keena`s intervention manages to somehow make Junko and Akuto friends again.  But during a class on mana control he knocks her unconscious again.  His teacher, Mitsuko, recommends that he go into the Mental Self-Discipline Chamber.  Inside the chamber, where people are said to have died, Akuto gets depressed.  For some reason Korone and Keena came along, and he`s caught between the two of them. However, they find a mysterious map. Keena is intrigued and wonders if it is a treasure map. The next day, Keena copies the map and it ends up all over school. It becomes the talk of the whole academy. But, Fujiko recognizes something on the map...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>540002</identifier>
<identifier>demon-king-daimao</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117601" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-01</airdate>
<rating votes="17">6.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地下迷宮にご用心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Caution! Underground Labyrinth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chika Meikyuu ni Goyoujin</title>
<summary>Students keep getting hurt as they try to find the treasure on the map Keena put up. Akuto, in his role as disciplinary committee member, insists that they give up looking, but a girl named Teruya Eiko appears suddenly and he ends up having to find it himself. Akuto, Korone, and Hiroshi go to the school`s underground labyrinth to find the spot on the map. But they find there a treasure once allowed only to a Demon Lord.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>540004</identifier>
<identifier>demon-king-daimao</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117602" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-08</airdate>
<rating votes="14">6.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">臨海学校へ行こう!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Go to the Beach School!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rinkaigakkou e Ikou!</title>
<summary>By defending Fujiko, Akuto finds himself in control of the Demon Lord`s secret treasure: a dragon named Peterhausen. Despite his wishes, his reputation as a Demon Lord grows. Under observation by the government, Aktuo is depressed to find out he can`t go to the seaside school. But Korone arranges for him to go by offering to take responsiblity for him herself. Akuto is enjoying (is he?) the beach with Junko and the others, and things with Junko are about to a the beach with Junko and the others, and things with Junko are about to about to start getting better, but Korone and Keena show up and screw things up in their usual way.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>540006</identifier>
<identifier>demon-king-daimao</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117807" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="17">3.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おしまいは完璧?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Perfect Ending?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oshimai wa Kanpeki?</title>
<summary>Bouichiro has taken Kena to the Suhara Shrine.  He attempts to make the contract with the Law of Identity, but Akuto appears and the battle begins in the presence of the God.  
Akuto at last defeats Bouichiro and takes back Keena.  He learns that the Demon Lord was created by the Gods to make the contract with the Law of Identity and destroy humanity.  But Akuto refuses and declares his intent to kill the Gods, causing their defense system to activate. Akuto puts his life on the line to battle the Gods, and put and end to the story they`ve created.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>540018</identifier>
<identifier>demon-king-daimao</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117808" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-12</airdate>
<rating votes="14">3.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">女たちの最終決戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Girls` Final Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onna-tachi no Saishuu Kessen</title>
<summary>Sai Akuto takes flight with Peaterhausen, having sworn to kill the Gods to protect Keena, but the imperial aircraft carrier "Black Crane" makes it debut and due to the work of 2V, an agent of the Cabinet Intelligence Magick Office, Sai Akuto is flattened by the Black Crane.
At the same time, the troops that are under the command of Teruya Eiko raid the school to destroy the monsters infesting it, but the student council president, Riri Shiraishi, repells them. Eiko uses Hattori Yuuko to protect herself, and orders Junko to take out Riri!
Meanwhile, in the school, Fujiko is taken aback by Sai Akuto`s apparent death, but Keena is convinced Sai Akuto is still alive. Bouichiro appears once more and kidnaps Keena...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>540016</identifier>
<identifier>demon-king-daimao</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117809" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-05</airdate>
<rating votes="14">5.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">阿九斗の帝都大戦争</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Akuto`s Great Capital War</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akuto no Teito Dai Sensou</title>
<summary>Yamato Bouichirou, head of CIMO8, saves Keena from being assassinated. But he was only interested in making her, who calls the "law of identity", his own in order to control the gods. Akuto uses his power as the Demon Lord to return to the school and faces off with Bouchirou, but is wounded as Boichiro`s attacks surpass his mana controlling ability. Then, Fujiko appears with a horde of monsters, saving the two and going back to Peterhausen. 
Meanwhile, the government army under the command of Teruya Eiko arrivesoutside the school and begins "Operation Battering Ram" to defeat the Demon Lord. At last, the battle between the demon lord and his monsters and humanity begins...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>540014</identifier>
<identifier>demon-king-daimao</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117810" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-29</airdate>
<rating votes="15">5.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">とんだお見合い騒動</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crazy Fuss About an Arranged Marriage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tonda Omiai Soudou</title>
<summary>Without either of their input, it`s decided that an arrianged marriage meeting is to be held between Junko and Akuto at Iga Village. Junko, who has feelings for Akuto, is unable to tell him, and so invites him to the village for other reasons. Akuto knows nothing of the marriage interview, but feels responsible for the messes he`s caused and decides to go with her. 
That night, Junko readies herself and visits his room, but another misunderstand occurs. As Akuto flees, he is confronted by Teruya Eiko who tells him that the God Suhara has decided Keena is a threat and ordered the Teruya Family to eliminate her.
The Demon Lord awakens within an enraged Akuto!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>540012</identifier>
<identifier>demon-king-daimao</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117811" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-22</airdate>
<rating votes="14">3.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あの子にご執心?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eyeing Her Over?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ano Ko ni Goshuushin?</title>
<summary>Hiroshi gets the legendary blade, and becomes the hero Brave. But he didn`t tell anybody his true identity. Meanwhile, Akuto starts to think about Keena more as he wonders if the hairpiece she wears is something he gave her when she was a child. Bu Keena herself is as easygoing as ever, still skipping class constantly. Akuto decides to try to persuade her to go to class. Junko watches him unhappily. She`s been acting odd since the seaside school. And then Korone tells her to have a marriage interview with Akuto at her family`s home...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>540010</identifier>
<identifier>demon-king-daimao</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117812" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-15</airdate>
<rating votes="17">2.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">伝説の勇者現る!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Legendary Hero Emerges!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Densetsu no Yuusha Arawaru!</title>
<summary>The island they`d come to was Hiroshi`s hometown. There was a legend there: When the demon lord revives, a beast would appear, and a hero would appear who would defeat it and the Demon Lord. It was just a legend, but Hiro was depressed. That night, his little sister Yukiko appeared and asked which of them was the Demon Lord. She believed firmly that Hiroshi was the legendary hero, and if there was a demon lord, he could be the hero as well. But she cries and runs away when Akito denies it, and is captured by a mysterious man! As they chase after her, a gigantic beast appears!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>540008</identifier>
<identifier>demon-king-daimao</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="118155" update="2010-05-04">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-04-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118156" update="2010-05-04">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-04-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119348" update="2010-06-28">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2010-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">もひとつおまけの大魔王: ACT 01 ドキ!? 女子だらけの水泳大会! ポ○リもあるよ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Another Extra Daimaou: Thump!? A Swimming Tournament with Girls Everywhere! There`s Also an Accident or Two!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mo Hitotsu Omake no Daimaou: ACT 01 Doki!? Joshi Darake Suieitaikai! Pori Moaru yo!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119655" update="2010-07-08">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119656" update="2010-09-07">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120611" update="2011-01-24">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-08-25</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">もひとつおまけの大魔王: ACT 03 けーなの愛のエプロン!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Another Extra Daimaou: Keina`s Apron of Love!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mo Hitotsu Omake no Daimaou: Act 03 Keena no Ai no Apron!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120612" update="2010-09-07">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">もひとつおまけの大魔王: ACT 02 絢子のドキドキ忍法帖!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Another Extra Daimaou: Junko`s Exciting Ninja Scroll!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mo Hitotsu Omake no Daimaou: Act 02 Junko no Dokidoki Ninpouchou!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122812" update="2010-10-02">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-09-22</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">もひとつおまけの大魔王: ACT 04 遭難サバイバル!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Another Extra Daimaou: Disaster Survival!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mo Hitotsu Omake no Daimaou: Act 04 Sounan Survival!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124739" update="2010-10-30">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-10-22</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">もひとつおまけの大魔王: ACT 05 ころねリポート. 或いは紗伊阿九斗のつつがない日常</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Another Extra Daimaou: Korone`s Report. Or Rather, Sai Akuto`s Uneventful, Daily Life.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mo Hitotsu Omake no Daimaou: Act 05 Korone Report. Aruiwa Sai Akuto no Tsutsuganai Nichijou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125687" update="2010-12-07">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-11-25</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">もひとつおまけの大魔王: ACT 06 ユカイツーカイ生徒会!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Another Extra Daimaou: The Student Council`s in Ecstasy!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mo Hitotsu Omake no Daimaou: Act 06 Yukai Tsuukai Seitokai!?</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
