<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="697" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1995-03-04</startdate>
<enddate>1995-03-04</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Slam Dunk: Shouhoku Saidai no Kiki! Moero Sakuragi Hanamichi</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">スラムダンク 湘北最大の危機! 燃えろ桜木花道</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Slam Dunk Movie 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">SDM3</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">SLAM DUNK 湘北最大の危機! 燃えろ桜木花道</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="590" type="Parent Story">Slam Dunk</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="864" type="Original Work">Inoue Takehiko</name>
<name id="5055" type="Direction">Kakudou Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="6533" type="Music">BMF</name>
</creators>
<description>After losing the titanic match against Kainan High, Team Shohoku and a newly shaven Hanamichi Sakuragi are challenged to an exhibition match by virtual basketball unknowns Ryoukufu High. Coach Anzai sees this as an opportunity for Shohoku to regain their confidence, but Ryoukufu are revealed to have a newly assembled championship calibre lineup and may give Sakuragi &amp; Co their toughest test yet.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="510">6.10</permanent>
<temporary count="512">7.19</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>13030.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1143</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2498</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2439</identifier>
<identifier>dzxcql</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1010</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>152459</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3598</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2760" parentid="2881" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>basketball</name>
<description>Basketball is Netball for men, the real game that encourages dribbling and other such uncouth behaviour that was sanitised out of the ladies` version. However, it is itself woozy compared to Ulama, as the losing side are seldom publicly sacrificed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="3418" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-16">
<rating votes="43">8.66</rating>
<name>Mitsuyoshi Anzai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The coach of the Shohoku High basketball team, and one of the best ones in Japan. Even the coaches of other teams call him "Anzai-sensei" with respect. His calm and collected attitude contrasts with the temper he had in the past, when he was nicknameed "White-Haired Devil" as a demanding college coach.</description>
<picture>19167.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7225" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="239">9.28</rating>
<name>Sakuragi Hanamichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hanamichi Sakuragi is the protagonist of Slam Dunk. At the beginning of the series, Sakuragi was a slacker, good for nothing other than fighting (he was on the brink of getting identified by those around him as a delinquent). He is the leader of the feared "Sakuragi Legion", which consists of his four friends Mito, Noma, Ohkusu and Takamiya.
Sakuragi`s quest for love was nothing but humiliating. He was always trying to ask girls out, but was rejected constantly, the 50th rejection occurring at the start of the series. He then met Haruko Akagi, a lovely basketball fangirl, whom he fell in love with immediately. This and Haruko`s encouragement led to him to join the Shohoku basketball team.</description>
<picture>1120.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="198" picture="202893.jpg">Kusao Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8314" type="main character in" update="2009-06-05">
<rating votes="92">8.16</rating>
<name>Rukawa Kaede</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rukawa Kaede is Sakuragi`s rival as well as almost his opposite; he is attractive to girls, skilled at basketball, and very cold and unfeeling. The only traits they share are that they are not academically inclined and good fighters. He regards Sakuragi as an idiot and both normally fight. Actually, he knows Sakuragi can put his talents to a better use, but is ashamed to see the immaturity with which he deals with things. His hobby is sleeping, and is usually seen asleep whenever he`s not on the court; he can even ride his bike while asleep often crashing with objects when doing so. Waking Rukawa from a nap is considered unforgivable, since he will almost automatically beat up the culprit. Unsurprisingly, he has also been in his fair share of off-court fights, but can hold his own. Rukawa`s goal is to be the best high school player in Japan, and he considers Sendou of Ryonan to be his greatest rival. A fact being that he is often nicknamed the "super-rookie", the "ace of Shohoku", even.</description>
<picture>27437.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8316" type="main character in" update="2010-03-27">
<rating votes="63">8.45</rating>
<name>Akagi Takenori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akagi Takenori is the captain of the Shohoku basketball team and Haruko`s older brother. Despite at first not thinking too much of Sakuragi (who addresses him as "Gori" for gorilla due to his immense physical presence), he actually realizes Sakuragi`s potential as a basketball player. Serious and disciplined, Akagi`s dream is to lead Shohoku to the national championship. His determination is shown in the match against Kainan, where he played on despite a serious injury to his ankle. Akagi considers Uozumi of Ryonan to be his biggest rival, though their rivalry is not antagonistic; indeed, there is respect that borders on friendship.</description>
<picture>27439.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="287" picture="73062.jpg">Yanada Kiyoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8317" type="main character in" update="2009-06-05">
<rating votes="50">7.32</rating>
<name>Miyagi Ryouta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miyagi Ryouta is Sakuragi`s closest friend on the team, making him the only person apart from Akagi whose advice Sakuragi will actually heed both on and off the basketball court. After an initial misunderstanding that caused conflict between them (he was fighting Mitsui when Sakuragi and Ayako came around, and he thought she was dating him), both found comradeship in the fact that they had both been unlucky in love, although Miyagi, having only been rejected 10 times, still falls short of Sakuragi`s record of 50 rejections. Like Sakuragi, Miyagi is motivated to play by his love for a girl: his best friend and classmate Ayako, the manager of the team, whom he refers to as "Aya-chan". He has been known to pose for Ayako during matches. Off-court, Miyagi has a reputation for being a bad boy. He was hospitalized for a while after his fight against Mitsui`s gang.</description>
<picture>27442.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="107" picture="172060.jpg">Shioya Yoku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8319" type="main character in" update="2009-06-05">
<rating votes="75">8.26</rating>
<name>Mitsui Hisashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hisashi Mitsui was an MVP for Takeishi Junior High. Despite having opportunities to join more prestigious high schools like Ryonan, he choose to go to Shohoku because of Coach Anzai; Anzai had given him the courage to win in the Junior High tournament by encouraging him during the last seconds of the match. However, an injury to his left knee in a training session interrupted his basketball career. An imprudent early return to the basketball court reinjured the knee more severely, leading to a basketball hiatus of over a year. Although he eventually healed, he was embittered by his exclusion from the court, and quit basketball to become the leader of a gang. His gang picked on Miyagi during his first year, and during a fight that ensued Miyagi beat Mitsui senseless before taking a beating himself.
Afterwards, Mitsui attempted to ruin the basketball team by instigating them into fighting with his gang, as the team would have been banned from competition for fighting. In the end, Sakuragi`s own gang - Youhei, Takamiya, Ookusu and Noma - voluntarily took the blame for the fight, and Mitsui was filled with remorse when he saw Anzai again. He rejoined the team and vowed never to fight again.</description>
<picture>27441.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="7482" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>1995-03-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
