<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7008" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-04-02</startdate>
<enddate>2010-09-24</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kaichou wa Maid-sama!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Class President is a Maid!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">kaichou wa maidsama</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Президент студенческого совета - горничная!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Президент - горничная!</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Przewodnicząca jest Pokojówką!</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="synonym">Şefa clasei e servitoare.</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Училищната президентка е прислужничка!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Kaichou wa Maid-sama</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Президент студради - покоївка</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="synonym">نماینده مدرسه پیشخدمته!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">KwMs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Maidsama</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">KaichouMaid</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">会長はメイド様!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Maid Sama!</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Maid-sama</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Maid Sama!</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Służąca Przewodnicząca</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">会长是女仆大人!</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="5584" approval="303" total="329">Special A</anime>
<anime id="199" approval="149" total="230">Kareshi Kanojo no Jijou</anime>
<anime id="4148" approval="146" total="201">Ouran Koukou Host Club</anime>
<anime id="5678" approval="86" total="133">Itazura na Kiss</anime>
<anime id="5053" approval="85" total="130">Lovely Complex</anime>
<anime id="9235" approval="75" total="104">Tonari no Kaibutsu-kun</anime>
<anime id="6466" approval="16" total="45">Kimi ni Todoke</anime>
<anime id="6103" approval="15" total="35">Skip Beat!</anime>
<anime id="5909" approval="15" total="35">Toradora!</anime>
<anime id="8564" approval="6" total="23">Inu x Boku Secret Service</anime>
<anime id="4917" approval="2" total="17">Hayate no Gotoku!</anime>
<anime id="35" approval="1" total="13">Love Hina</anime>
<anime id="12694" approval="1" total="8">Blend S</anime>
<anime id="7995" approval="1" total="7">Hiyokoi</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="36">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="489452">Very funny one :D the teasing moments, the emotional faces, and the romance...very itching at some points :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="659266">Fun little series 4 all age groups who r in2 romantic high school comedies plus it has maid cafe setting thrown in.so those who like tht sub genre will luv it.watch it without thinking 2 much about what it`s trying 2 say about apparently strong female characters` inherent submissiveness.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="387097">first eps were quit good, but that`s just it. the rest of the eps were boring as hell. one of the worst love-comedy I have ever watched, NO plot, NO character development, NO good side characters. BIG FAIL. 

also I can`t seem to understand what`s so special about Misaki, why everyone is crazy about her.

watch it at your own risk.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="424950">This is for yakumofan. ryougishikifan is already watching this anime, right? It`s related to Ouran High School Host Club and Special A.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="19194">gotta agree with tessachan`s comments.

its pretty much a formulaic show, that succeeds in its mediocrity. it tries to be funny and dramatic, but in all the expected ways, without bringing anything new. but hey, if thats your thing go for it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="291829">Had a lot of fun watching this series, I think anyone would ....</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="31044">This just show how you dont need to be sick to have a success. No need to show panties or boobs every scene. This is trully a master piece. Weird if came from JC staff lol.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="217023">This is one of the best, animes I have seen...
it reminded me of Ouran host club at some points, and even though I knew how it would end, I really enjoyed the entire ride.
Greatly looking forward to a second season...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="449832">Love this anime!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="178645">you wont regret..</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="457039">A hilarious and yet fast paced anime. Even who don`t enjoy shojo anime will enjoy this.

Also read the manga after seeing the anime, if you are curious to what happens next.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="389334">I just love watching this anime. Its a must watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="484701">Very romantic and funny.  Includes very good aspects of comedy.  Defiantly a must see even if you aren`t into this type of anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="281743">follows the manga very well so far. allows for cheap laughs at the main characters expense</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="719319">I loved it....Really You are definitely gonna like it..just gi it a try</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="69105">I don`t think there is a better romance anime than this. And I have practically seen pretty much all romance :) Though of course it depends on each individual.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="111332">The best love comedy lately.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="429615">Flippin` Awesome!
Must watch!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="205022">This is the first anime in a long time that I really really enjoy watching!  This is a great romantic comedy.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="419578">This is my favourite anime, it´s quite the explosive mix of comedy and love. Whenever yyou think its over Misaki gets a comeback. The end is quite expectable, but each episode bears a suprise. And if that doesn´t count for you ...then the extaordinary lovable characters.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="302120">one of the "must see" shoujo of these years, even if you, like me, don`t like shoujo a lot, this is fantastic!!!.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="379231">i didnt regret watching it!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="527292">The only reason i mark this as a must see is because there is not a mark for... U must watch this or you will die without seeing one of the best anime`s ever!!! lol
All joking aside this is a must watch is simply perfect that realy rhe only word i can use to describe the experience i had when watching this.
U people can thank us later for telling you this</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="460400">awsome anime. it is very simple and yet very catching, fun and just lovely to watch. great characters and animation</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="428629">easy to catch on ..romance. this anime have a good soundtrack , simple animation ..and a lot of comedies. kindly old but still a gem of shoujo.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/maidsama/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3172" type="Series Composition">Ikeda Mamiko</name>
<name id="2194" type="Direction">Sakurai Hiroaki</name>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="5187" type="Music">Maeguchi Wataru</name>
<name id="3562" type="Chief Animation Direction">Onji Masayuki</name>
<name id="7482" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nomura Fusako</name>
<name id="11916" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hara Shuuichi</name>
<name id="11182" type="Chief Animation Direction">Imoto Yuki</name>
<name id="11182" type="Character Design">Imoto Yuki</name>
<name id="13745" type="Original Work">Fujiwara Hiro</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr13745 [Fujiwara Hiro]`s Kaichou wa Maid-sama! shoujo manga, serialised in LaLa.
The romantic comedy centres on the student council head named http://anidb.net/ch15147 [Ayuzawa Misaki], who despises the mostly male, slovenly population at her school, which was once an all-boys school. However, Misaki`s quite handsome schoolmate, http://anidb.net/ch15148 [Usui Takumi], just discovered her secret — that she works after school at a maid cafe.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="4654">7.15</permanent>
<temporary count="4703">7.75</temporary>
<review count="2">6.08</review>
</ratings>
<picture>52987.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11037</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9366</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>7054</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>10298</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4652</identifier>
<identifier>pseuuo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/maidsama/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Maid_Sama!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>会長はメイド様!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1890</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>336315</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12521</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="618" parentid="2565" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>trap</name>
<description>A trap is a plot device where a male character is mistaken for a female, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the male (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the male, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the male character as a female; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through his behaviour, and/or language. A male character misinterpreted by others as female, without action from the male (explicitly feminine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t1637 [reverse trap].
Note: the tag image is from http://anidb.net/a10475 [Himegoto].</description>
<picurl>161537.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1262" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-11-07">
<name>naive</name>
<description>A naive (also spelled naïve, keeping its French diacritic) person lacks worldly knowledge, experience, wisdom, understanding, or judgement.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1632" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-13">
<name>twin -- TO BE DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is meant to be purged in the short term. Please DO NOT assign it to any further characters; add the appropriate char-char relations to them instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1637" parentid="2565" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>reverse trap</name>
<description>A reverse trap is a plot device where a female character is mistaken for a male, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the female (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the female, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the female character as a male; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through her behaviour, and/or language. A female character misinterpreted by others as male, without action from the female (explicitly masculine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a reverse trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t618 [trap].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1876" parentid="2794" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>musical band</name>
<description>A musical ensemble also known as a music(al) group or music(al) band is a group of people who perform instrumental or vocal music, typically known by a distinct name.</description>
<picurl>10249.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2072" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>maid</name>
<description>A maid is a female employed in domestic service. They usually wear uniforms. Since their nature is to be obedient and serve their goshujin-sama (master), they are one of the most desired types of women in Japan, a dream of every Japanese man, particularly http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku]. Often seen in so-called Maid Cafes in Akihabara, where male customers can for a little time enjoy the feeling of being served by a woman. The male gender opposite is the butler.</description>
<picurl>4954.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2520" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>school swimsuit</name>
<description>A school swimsuit (also known as sukumizu, shorthand for school mizugi) is a standardised navy blue one-piece swimsuit worn by schoolgirls. Typically they also have a name tag on the front. Sukumizu can also be black or white.
Normally worn at schools though sometimes also worn at beaches when the character feels this to be easier, forgot to buy a normal swimsuit of their own or wants to give some fan service to those that like school swimsuits better than regular swimsuits.
In http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] anime, a swimsuit of this type sometimes serves censoring purposes when characters take a bath. If there is a group of female characters donning swimsuits, you can expect the youngest or youngest-looking girl to wear one of these.</description>
<picurl>52174.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2792" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>reverse harem</name>
<description>Reverse harem, or sometimes also male harem, is the common name for the gender-reversed version of the usual http://anidb.net/t2859 [harem genre]. In a reverse harem, instead of the usual situation with several female characters focused on one male character, the viewer sees several male characters surrounding a single female character. Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. The most notable exception is that, due to the most relevant characteristics of the trope`s fan base, reverse harem authors tend to go for http://anidb.net/t1760 [bishounen] looks. Though they are also exceptions to the common harem genre, harems with homosexual relationships are not covered by reverse harem.</description>
<picurl>126787.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2795" parentid="1973" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>baking</name>
<description>The art of making bread, cakes, pastries, pies, tarts, quiches, cookies and similar food in the oven.
Mmmm.... smells nice.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2822" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>skirt flipping</name>
<description>Naughty characters — usually boys — flip the skirts of female protagonists to ascertain what panties they are wearing (also see Pantsu category).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2845" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-04-30">
<name>blackmail</name>
<description>In general usage, blackmail is a crime involving unjustified threats against a person or organization in order to make a gain or harm or cause material loss to them unless a demand is met. It may be considered similar to or a form of extortion, although some jurisdictions will consider them as separate crimes. Most often, blackmail involves the threat of revealing some secret to a given third party, which may be another person, a rival organization, or a state institution such as the police, or to the general public. In anime and related media, and more specifically in pornographic works, blackmail is also a device used to coerce people, generally female and often schoolgirls, into having sex with another or others; in such cases, it may be considered similar to or a form of rape.</description>
<picurl>136031.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3103" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-11">
<name>first love</name>
<description>Ah… first love. The love that is remembered the most fondly by the participant, as this is commonly what people experience when they first have a first crush, but it is also the love before the Second Love, if that should ever happen, and for a guy, he usually holds her memory very close to him if he is a widower whereas for young girls, the memory of the First Love they ever had is a special memory to them, especially if he later becomes the boyfriend they`ve longed for.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>204995.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3119" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-24">
<name>restaurant</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3150" parentid="4522" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>social class issues</name>
<description>A character`s standing in society is cause of many issues. More generally, the society`s class structure is the source of many problems in the anime.
A common example is class division; a strong and rigid class division between rich/elite and poor/commoners, with the elites having disproportionately more privilege than the common class.
This can be applied not only when royalty and nobility are present, but also dystopian societies display often these divisions.
Another example is a division between employees and management, with employees akin to the common class, and management akin to the elite class.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3202" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-04">
<name>adoring fan club</name>
<description>A character, group or characters, or an organisation is considered so awesome that a adoring fan club is formed to idolise them. Not only do they have notable admirers, but their fans become organised in such a fashion to have a following that could only be guaranteed in real life by precise and long increments of paparazzi-like stalking.
If the character is sufficiently cool, an instant fan club may happen practically overnight (i.e., within a few episodes of them being introduced), although the subject of admiration typically has mixed feelings about the entire affair.</description>
<picurl>48684.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3395" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-18">
<name>promise</name>
<description>A dramatically-made promise that serves as foreshadowing. The promise will eventually be called in and action will be required.
Whether they succeed, fail or refuse to keep their promise depends almost entirely on the idealism-level of the story. Other factors, such as whether they were told what they had to do, or if it was a Leonine Contract, may come into play. Even Releasing from the Promise is usually a scene of high drama.
Source: TVTropes</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3508" parentid="2869" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-09-26">
<name>school for the rich elite</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3606" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-11">
<name>family without father</name>
<description>For some reason the protagonists father is no longer among the living. The much too early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family: Possibly the grieve-stricken mother and children barely function as humans. Or adding emphasis to the overall financial predicament of the family, should the father have been the money earner.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3734" parentid="5826" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-14">
<name>school rivalry</name>
<description>Simple description for a "School vs School in all-out physical-combat" series.
No matter how geographically close or far apart the schools are, students from different schools are enemies by default and are likely to engage in physical fights on sight (except on the occasion that certain schools form pacts of alliance or peace).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3863" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-05">
<name>competition</name>
<description>Some sort of confrontation occurs in this show. The protagonists "duke it out" via various competitions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3872" parentid="2869" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>formerly one-gender school</name>
<description>This anime takes place at a school that was formerly one-gender, but has recently begun to admit the opposite sex. This can be a set-up for harem situations stemming from a still-skewed gender ratio.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4030" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-13">
<name>mental cinema</name>
<description>The ability to imagine all kinds of things, as if they were real.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4148" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-11">
<name>late for school</name>
<description>A common device for a series opening or Establishing Character Moment. Things begin in a frantic rush which usually results in taking short cuts, such as eating breakfast on the run. The classic image is of someone running down the street with a slice of toast hanging out of their mouth, dragging their backpack with one hand while trying to put on their jacket or sweater one-handed with the other, bumping into important people in a manner that gets the plot started.
Basically, they`re never on time for school. While some are Heavy Sleepers, it would appear that they may have simply set their alarm clocks so as to give them insufficient time to get to class. 
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>161002.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4198" parentid="5604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-14">
<name>hard work and guts</name>
<description>One of the character`s motto in the anime. Because there is nothing that cannot be achieved by hard work and guts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4246" parentid="3395" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-01">
<name>childhood promise</name>
<description>Sweet childhood promises... who remembers them other than the Japanese anime characters?
It keeps the main characters obsessed with promises that they made when they were children, mostly related to love, with lines like "I will always protect you" or "I will marry you when we grow up".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4394" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-21">
<name>defeat means friendship</name>
<description>In a series based around an endless series of one-on-one fights, defeating a Worthy Opponent or The Rival will sometimes convert them to the hero`s side, if not always to his cause. 
Furthermore, no matter how many people the Worthy Opponent has killed, how much grief he has caused, even if he slaughtered helpless children or the hero`s own family, as soon as he shows a bit of remorse or goes out of his way to help the hero even once, he will be welcomed into the hero`s circle of True Companions with open arms.
(Source: TVTropes)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5420" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-03-24">
<name>it`s funny because they`re poor</name>
<description>A character`s relative lack of wealth is used as a source of humour.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5459" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>poverty</name>
<description>It refers to the condition of not having the means to afford basic human needs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5515" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>faceless background characters</name>
<description>Unimportant random/extra characters that appear mostly as part of the background are often drawn without much facial details, normally to save money, effort and manpower for more important parts of the show. Sometimes, they have almost or no facial details, meaning their heads only have indications of the presence of parts such as hair or mouth, or not even that. This can go as far as only drawing an abstracted silhouette of the whole body.</description>
<picurl>233515.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5834" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>show within a show</name>
<description>A fictional TV (or radio, or stage) show that takes place within an actual TV show; or, occasionally, a fictional instalment or incarnation of an actual show. Many comedies have short one-off gags where they parody existing shows.
Example: A large part of Martian Successor Nadesico is centred around the fictional popular anime Gekigangar III, which is being watched by several characters of the Nadesico crew.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5850" parentid="2869" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-13">
<name>absurdly powerful student council</name>
<description>A student council is a student-managed body inside a school which engages in administrative affairs, usually usually working in a partnership with management, staff and parents, for the benefit of the whole school environment. In real life, a student council holds no actual power; however, in many anime/manga, they have an insane amount of power, which usually allows them to overrule nearly everyone else (the school board, the mayor, the prime minster, you name it). In those cases, that device is explored as a major source of slapstick comedy.</description>
<picurl>70561.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5882" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>secret identity</name>
<description>The (usually main) protagonist has a secret identity that he or she desperately tries to keep secret.
This can lead to all sorts of amusing misunderstandings, thus is used as comedy element in some anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6019" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-20">
<name>brainwashing</name>
<description>Brainwashing, the application of coercive techniques to change the values and beliefs, perceptions and judgements, and subsequent mindsets and behaviours of one or more people, usually for political, financial, personal, or religious purposes. Often features in dark anime or pornography.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6023" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-01">
<name>cosplay restaurant</name>
<description>Cosplay restaurants are theme restaurants and pubs that originated in Akihabara, Tokyo, Japan around the year 1999. They include maid cafés and butler cafés, where the service staff dress as elegant maids, or as butlers. Such restaurants and cafés have quickly become a staple of Japanese otaku culture. Compared with service at normal cafés, the service at cosplay cafés involves the creation of a rather different atmosphere. The staff treat the customers as masters and mistresses in a private home rather than merely as café customers.
The popularity of the cosplay restaurants and maid cafés has spread to other regions in Japan, such as Osaka`s Den Den Town as well as other countries, such as Hong Kong, Taiwan, Singapore, Mexico, and Canada.
Often such cafés or a more simple kissaten, small Japanese-style coffee shops, are part of school festivals where the protagonists` class runs one.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6577" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-17">
<name>student government</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7117" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-06-12">
<name>sexism</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="15147" type="main character in" update="2010-09-26">
<rating votes="143">8.41</rating>
<name>Ayuzawa Misaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ayuzawa Misaki is the heroine of Kaichou wa Maid-sama!. She lives alone with her mother and sister because her father abandoned them, leaving them with a huge debt. Because of her father`s actions, she has a deep hatred for most boys (except the gentlemanly type).
She goes to Seika high school, which only recently became co-ed. It was an all-boy`s school only a few years ago. Because of this, the student body is 80% male and 20% female. Misaki worked hard to become the student council president and "protect the girls". However, she has a secret. To help her mother pay off her father`s debt, she has a part-time job... at a maid cafe! She doesn`t want anyone at school to discover her, because she thinks that if they do, she will lose her authority as student council president.
She is sixteen years old, and practises aikido (a form of martial arts/self-defence).</description>
<picture>3587.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15148" type="main character in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="133">8.76</rating>
<name>Usui Takumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the most popular boys at Seika High, Usui appears to take little interest in anything and prefers to observe things as they unfold, though proves to be extraordinarily talented in numerous areas. He develops an interest in Misaki and is the first to learn she is working at a maid café, but chooses to keep her secret and soon falls in love with her. While she dismisses his behavior simply as harassment, he continues to watch over and protect her, as well as offering insightful advice on how to deal with the boys at Seika effectively and fairly. He appears to be the only male student at school that Misaki is willing to speak to as an equal. Little is known about Usui`s background and he is reluctant to speak about it, though he reveals a willingness to tell Misaki. He has an older brother and lives alone in an apartment.
He`s a pro in cooking, can play chess, is smart, jumps down roofs (but doesn`t die), free all the time and always appears unexpectedly.</description>
<picture>3588.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15246" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-04-30">
<rating votes="17">6.33</rating>
<name>Subaru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An employee at Café Latte. Like Honoka, she does not have a full-time job and makes a living from part-time work. She considers Misaki to be hard working.</description>
<picture>3590.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="210" picture="71057.jpg">Ueda Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15247" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-04-30">
<rating votes="21">5.60</rating>
<name>Honoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An employee at Café Latte. She can become somewhat maniacal about getting in character for her job and criticizes Misaki for her initial resistance to acting parts outside of her comfort range, as well as for being ashamed of working at Maid Latte and hiding it from her peers.</description>
<picture>3589.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15248" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-04-30">
<rating votes="17">5.93</rating>
<name>Erika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A college student working at Café Latte. She notes that Misaki is strong and picks up work quickly, and claims that it doesn`t feel like Misaki is younger than her. She has a tendency to eavesdrop and is described as having a "voice fetish".</description>
<picture>3591.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="101" picture="16709.jpg">Ise Mariya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15249" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-04-30">
<rating votes="14">1.38</rating>
<name>Igarashi Tora</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Student Council President at Miyabigaoka High School, he initially appears as a gentleman who marvels at Misaki and the changes she has brought to Seika High, offering her a chance to come to Miyabigaoka with an exceptional loan. He is quickly revealed to be a lecherous young man who has become bored with the women surrounding him, who are easily submissive because of his wealth. He enjoys causing drama around him and he thinks that money can buy anything. Misaki`s strong will and outright rejection of his monetary bribe to have her join the Miyabigaoka Student Council captures his interest. It is later revealed that Tora has some ties to or knowledge of Usui`s past or background, which he may be exploiting to some as of yet unknown end.</description>
<picture>3593.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="191" picture="17006.jpg">Suzumura Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15250" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-04-30">
<rating votes="26">7.24</rating>
<name>Hyoudou Satsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The manager of Café Latte and Misaki`s boss, a 30 year old woman who has a tendency to voice out her fantasies. She is a cheerful woman who enjoys her job because it allows her to make others happier. She is very understanding of Misaki`s circumstances, knowing that Misaki does not particularly enjoy working at a maid café, and is perceptive of other people`s feelings. Satsuki also ends up hiring Usui as a part-time cook, much to Misaki`s chagrin.</description>
<picture>43581.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15251" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-04-30">
<rating votes="25">5.54</rating>
<name>Hyoudou Aoi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Satsuki`s nephew, the son of Satsuki`s older brother, a junior high school student who enjoys dressing like a girl, "cute things", and being the center of attention. His androgynous features allow him to pass off as a girl and his female persona is well-known as a cute internet idol. Aoi enjoys toying with the feelings of men, but is eventually exposed as a boy by Misaki. He is generally short-tempered and has little patience. He becomes embarrassed after doing something kind or showing affection for someone, then becomes angry(he can`t show his true feelings very well). Misaki is under the impression that he hates her; he frequently scolds her for her poor fashion sense and unfeminine strength. Even so, it seems he has some sort of interest in her (not necessarily romantic). He later yells at Misaki for not being more decisive about her relationship with Usui, and for leading Shintani on, even if she was doing it unintentionally. It`s this scolding that eventually pushes her admit to Shintani (and probably for the first time, clearly, to herself) that she does in fact have feelings for Usui.</description>
<picture>3592.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="5663" picture="228631.jpg">Igarashi Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15252" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-04-30">
<rating votes="19">4.01</rating>
<name>Kaga Shizuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of Misaki and Sakura`s friends, a sensible and intelligent girl who often spends lunchtime with them. Shizuko is a member of the flower arranging club and is good at math, but isn`t very good at physical activities. She has an older brother in university and a younger sister in junior high school; according to Sakura, the three of them look very alike.</description>
<picture>43582.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15253" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-04-30">
<rating votes="11">4.82</rating>
<name>Yukimura Shouichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Vice President of the Student Council, he tries to help Misaki where he can, and enjoys office routine. At first, he, like the rest of the student council, is fearful of Misaki, but he eventually comes to be on fairly close terms with both her and Usui. Yukimura is hard-working, earnest, and capable of doing most administrative work, but is not athletic in the least, especially in comparison to Misaki and Usui. His gentle, almost feminine demeanour and slight stature make him appear somewhat weak, a fact he is sensitive about, even lamenting his lack of strength for his inability to be more helpful to Misaki. He`s both terrified and in awe of Usui, after Usui kisses him as a "reward for his hardwork" (which, unbeknownst to all, Usui only did to make light of kissing Misaki, after noticing that she was visibly upset and incredibly jumpy around him). Yukimura has a seven-year-old sister named Rui.</description>
<picture>43584.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13866" picture="43577.jpg">Shiibashi Kazuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15254" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="13">5.21</rating>
<name>Sarashina Ikuto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The second of the "idiot trio", which includes Shirakawa Naoya and Ryuunosuke Kurosaki. A closet otaku, he is actually good at drawing manga illustrations and enjoys writing. His friends call him "Ikkun".</description>
<picture>43583.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="202" picture="25743.jpg">Terashima Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15255" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="15">5.62</rating>
<name>Shirokawa Naoya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A male student at Seika High School who initially dislikes Misaki because of her forceful methods of reforming Seika. He and his friends discover that she works at a maid café early on in the story, but after he is defended by Usui, they quickly become her biggest fans, as well as regulars at Cafe Maid Latte, often referred to as the "idiot trio". His nickname is "Shiroyan". He also used to be a delinquent in middle school known as White Demon.</description>
<picture>43580.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="71" picture="171537.jpg">Ichiki Mitsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15256" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-04-30">
<rating votes="24">4.98</rating>
<name>Hanazono Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A good friend of Misaki`s and one of the few female students at Seika High, Sakura is friendly and cheerful and, like the rest of the girls, relies on Misaki for protection from the wild behaviour of the boys. She is quite popular amongst the boys, but frequently rejects their confessions; in particular, she`s rejected ex-rugby captain Gouda Masaru (剛田将) one hundred times. According to Shizuko, Sakura falls in love without carefully considering what the person is really like, as exampled by her persistent feelings for the two-faced, womanising singer of a popular band from a nearby high school.</description>
<picture>43578.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15257" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="13">4.03</rating>
<name>Kurosaki Ryuunosuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The third member of the "idiot trio" who frequent Cafe Maid Latte, nicknamed "Kurotatsu". Known for being the perverted one and likes "erotic things". Also used to be a delinquent in middle school with Shiroyan.</description>
<picture>43579.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3709" picture="84359.jpg">Hosoya Yoshimasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16433" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-18">
<rating votes="48">7.83</rating>
<name>Ayuzawa Suzuna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ayuzawa Suzuna is a http://anidb.net/ch15147 [Misaki]`s younger sister. She is very apathetic and shows little to no emotion. She does not work at any part time jobs and appears to be in middle school. In the anime, she often enters magazine contests and always seems to win food prizes. Her first appearance occurs late in the manga, while she is a frequent recurring character in the anime.</description>
<picture>45762.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16763" picture="45795.jpg">Ishihara Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16434" type="appears in" update="2017-04-30">
<rating votes="9">6.69</rating>
<name>Ayuzawa Minako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mother of Ayuzawa Misaki</description>
<picture>45763.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16460" type="appears in" update="2010-04-06">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Takezawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45817.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2708" picture="37823.jpg">Oohara Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16461" type="appears in" update="2010-04-06">
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<name>Sawa Kenji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Student council accountant.</description>
<picture>45819.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2502" picture="22437.jpg">Nakanishi Hideki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16462" type="appears in" update="2010-09-06">
<rating votes="3">5.41</rating>
<name>Gon-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gon-chan is an employee at http://anidb.net/ch17771 [Maid Latte]. She does not appear often.</description>
<picture>48227.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2228" picture="21776.jpg">Gibu Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16463" type="appears in" update="2010-09-06">
<rating votes="3">5.41</rating>
<name>Sayu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sayu is an employee at http://anidb.net/ch17771 [Maid Latte]. She does not appear often.</description>
<picture>48229.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1918" picture="225099.jpg">Sakurai Harumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16469" type="appears in" update="2010-04-06">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Katada Kiyomasa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Head disciplinary officer.</description>
<picture>45828.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16777" picture="45814.jpg">Bandou Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16598" type="appears in" update="2016-10-13">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Iwakura</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192752.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5400" picture="29628.jpg">Souma Yukito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17232" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-04-30">
<rating votes="23">6.09</rating>
<name>Hyoudou Aoi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47108.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5663" picture="228631.jpg">Igarashi Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17770" type="appears in" update="2010-05-18">
<rating votes="3">4.20</rating>
<name>Inuyama Go Kyoudai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>48138.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="191" picture="17006.jpg">Suzumura Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17771" type="appears in" update="2010-05-18">
<rating votes="1">7.98</rating>
<name>Maid Latte</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>48142.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="17778" type="appears in" update="2017-04-30">
<rating votes="4">3.81</rating>
<name>Maki Kanade</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Vice President of the Student Council at Miyabigaoka High, he and Igarashi attempt to buy out Café Latte and change it into a butler café. Misaki, Usui, and the Café Latte staff are able to prevent him from realizing his plans through a competition.</description>
<picture>48146.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="612" picture="79531.jpg">Maeno Tomoaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17783" type="appears in" update="2010-05-18">
<rating votes="2">2.01</rating>
<name>Koganei Hirofumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A bespectacled student at Miyabigaoka High School who looks down upon Seika students. After insulting two students for taking an interest in chess, they hit him and Misaki forces them to go with her to apologize to him. When she discovers the reason why they attacked Koganei, she demands that Koganei apologize to her students as well. He agrees, only on the condition that they defeat him in chess, which Usui does with no trouble. Koganei is ranked fourth in the nation as a chess player. He was originally intended to be the president of Miyabigaoka High School Council by the author, but rejected by the editor.</description>
<picture>48152.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10797" picture="188719.jpg">Okabayashi Fumihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19290" type="appears in" update="2010-08-10">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Gouda Masaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He has been rejected by Sakura one hundred times.</description>
<picture>50546.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3801" picture="171533.jpg">Sakamaki Manabu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19291" type="appears in" update="2010-07-01">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Hagimoto Takashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50547.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2708" picture="37823.jpg">Oohara Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19292" type="appears in" update="2016-10-13">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Takamizawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192754.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2013" picture="21316.jpg">Shimowada Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19293" type="appears in" update="2013-04-19">
<rating votes="2">5.89</rating>
<name>Sakurai Kuuga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakurai Kuuga is the vocalist of the rock band http://anidb.net/ch20613 [Yumemishi]. While he seems sweet and kind to his fans, in reality he is very arrogant, rude and insensitive to others feelings. It is due to his attitude that http://anidb.net/ch15147 [Misaki] dislikes him as he was very insensitive to http://anidb.net/ch15256 [Sakura] feelings while hitting on http://anidb.net/ch15147 [Misaki] herself.</description>
<picture>50549.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19294" type="appears in" update="2010-08-10">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Kosugi Bunta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Student council secretary.</description>
<picture>51006.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10797" picture="188719.jpg">Okabayashi Fumihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19295" type="appears in" update="2012-03-05">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Utsumi Yuuta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>82927.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1692" picture="224934.jpg">Okitsu Kazuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19296" type="appears in" update="2010-08-09">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Ono Yuujirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ono Yuujirou is the drummer of the rock band http://anidb.net/ch20613 [Yumemishi].</description>
<picture>50552.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2502" picture="22437.jpg">Nakanishi Hideki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19297" type="appears in" update="2010-07-01">
<name>Baito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2502" picture="22437.jpg">Nakanishi Hideki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19298" type="appears in" update="2016-10-13">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Ishida</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192755.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2502" picture="22437.jpg">Nakanishi Hideki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19299" type="appears in" update="2016-10-13">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Sudou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192756.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="169" picture="16976.jpg">Takahashi Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19300" type="appears in" update="2014-11-23">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Aramaki Chinatsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is the P.E. representative of the Seika High student council.</description>
<picture>164624.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18133" picture="48155.jpg">Kuriyama Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19301" type="appears in" update="2010-08-09">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Yabu Kouma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yabu Kouma is the bassist of the rock band http://anidb.net/ch20613 [Yumemishi]. He is very respectful and always scolds http://anidb.net/ch19293 [Kuuga]`s rude behavior.</description>
<picture>50550.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1692" picture="224934.jpg">Okitsu Kazuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19302" type="appears in" update="2010-08-09">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Nikaidou Shousei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nikaidou Shousei is the guitarist of the rock band http://anidb.net/ch20613 [Yumemishi]. He doesn`t express himself that much.</description>
<picture>50551.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3155" picture="24137.jpg">Ono Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19303" type="appears in" update="2010-07-01">
<rating votes="2">5.40</rating>
<name>Aratake Gouki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50553.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="174" picture="41158.jpg">Kakihara Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19499" type="appears in" update="2010-08-10">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Hayase Kouta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Infirmary head.</description>
<picture>51007.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3801" picture="171533.jpg">Sakamaki Manabu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19500" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="14">5.79</rating>
<name>Kanou Soutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kanou Soutarou is a withdrawn male student who is initially against http://anidb.net/ch15147 [Misaki] as the student council president because of her aspirations of increasing the female population of Seika High. In order to sabotage her presidency, Kanou tries to hypnotize http://anidb.net/ch15147 [Misaki], http://anidb.net/ch15148 [Usui], and the student council into ruining http://anidb.net/ch15147 [Misaki]`s reputation. It is revealed that his gynophobic attitude comes from his mother abandoning his family when he was young (ironically the very opposite of what http://anidb.net/ch15147 [Misaki] experienced) and his father warning him to be wary of women, and after failing to hypnotize http://anidb.net/ch15147 [Misaki], she punishes him by assigning him to work closely with his female classmates during the school`s cultural festival, in hopes of forcing him to get over his fear. The punishment is ultimately successful, and he slowly becomes friendlier with http://anidb.net/ch15147 [Misaki] and the rest of his female peers, as well as with http://anidb.net/ch15253 [Yukimura] (who gives off the aura of a female, as Kanou states).
Though he runs against http://anidb.net/ch15147 [Misaki] during her re-election as President, he opposes using underhanded means to gain victory, remaining on good terms with her. He also knows about the relationship between http://anidb.net/ch15148 [Usui] and http://anidb.net/ch15147 [Misaki] and often wonders why they won`t admit that they like each other.</description>
<picture>3492.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19845" type="appears in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="5">6.78</rating>
<name>Hyoudou Nagisa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Satsuki`s younger sister and Aoi`s aunt, Nagisa is the manager of a beach house known as "Ocean House".
She asks for Satsuki and her employees to come and work at her beach house during the summer since her shop is not as popular as she would like. Nagisa is somewhat tough on Aoi for trying to dress like a girl because her older brother sent Aoi to her beach house to become more masculine.</description>
<picture>51598.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20613" type="appears in" update="2010-08-09">
<name>Yumemishi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>53075.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="20651" type="appears in" update="2017-04-30">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Yukimura Shouichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53149.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13866" picture="43577.jpg">Shiibashi Kazuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20652" type="appears in" update="2010-08-10">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Kanou Soutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53150.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20653" type="appears in" update="2010-08-10">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Kanou no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch20652 [Kanou]`s father.</description>
<picture>53151.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5400" picture="29628.jpg">Souma Yukito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20919" type="appears in" update="2010-08-18">
<rating votes="3">7.07</rating>
<name>Yukimura Ruri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53596.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16794" picture="214757.jpg">Ogura Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20920" type="appears in" update="2010-08-18">
<name>Pheromone Seijin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53599.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20384" picture="53598.jpg">Kiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20969" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-26">
<rating votes="22">2.52</rating>
<name>Shintani Hinata</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3594.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="545" picture="188506.jpg">Abe Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20970" type="appears in" update="2010-08-21">
<rating votes="10">6.79</rating>
<name>Ayuzawa Misaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53679.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9036" picture="215515.jpg">Morohoshi Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20971" type="appears in" update="2010-09-26">
<rating votes="2">6.06</rating>
<name>Hinata no Jii-chan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch20969 [Hinata]`s grandfather.</description>
<picture>55466.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1406" picture="18432.jpg">Suzuki Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20973" type="appears in" update="2010-08-21">
<rating votes="3">4.37</rating>
<name>Shintani Hinata</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53682.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21423" type="appears in" update="2010-09-06">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Erika Inochi Otoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54595.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3155" picture="24137.jpg">Ono Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33010" type="appears in" update="2011-06-01">
<rating votes="4">5.99</rating>
<name>Ayuzawa Misaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Misaki in episode 9 as Momotarou (Peach Boy).</description>
<picture>72665.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33011" type="appears in" update="2011-06-01">
<rating votes="6">7.55</rating>
<name>Ayuzawa Misaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Crossdressed Misaki as butler Misaki-kun.</description>
<picture>72666.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85465" type="appears in" update="2016-10-13">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Kamakari</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192753.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10797" picture="188719.jpg">Okabayashi Fumihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85862" type="appears in" update="2016-10-28">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Kondou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193717.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10797" picture="188719.jpg">Okabayashi Fumihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85863" type="appears in" update="2016-10-28">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Tahara</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193718.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18133" picture="48155.jpg">Kuriyama Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85864" type="appears in" update="2016-10-28">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Naoe</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193719.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3155" picture="24137.jpg">Ono Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="117095" update="2010-03-26">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-02</airdate>
<rating votes="19">6.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">美咲(ミサ)ちゃんはメイド様!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Misaki Is a Maid-sama!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Misa-chan wa Maid-sama!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117096" update="2010-03-26">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="14">5.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">学園祭でもメイド様</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maid-sama at the School Festival</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gakuensai de mo Maid-sama</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117385" update="2010-04-02">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バカと不良とヒーローと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Idiots, Juviniles &amp; Heroes &amp;...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Baka to Furyou to Hero to</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117386" update="2010-04-02">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-18</airdate>
<rating votes="15">3.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">体育祭でもメイド様</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maid-sama &amp; the Sports Festival</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiikusai de mo Maid-sama</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117387" update="2010-04-02">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-11</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">碓氷拓海の秘密に迫る!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Secret of Takumi Usui Approaches!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Usui Takumi no Himitsu ni Semaru!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117388" update="2010-04-02">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-04</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらの恋はインディーズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura`s Indie-Label Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura no Koi wa Indies</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117389" update="2010-04-02">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="15">2.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">桃太郎までもメイド様</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maid-sama Does Momotaro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Momotarou made mo Maid-sama</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117390" update="2010-04-02">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">美咲, 雅ヶ丘学園へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Misaki Goes to Miyabigaoka</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Misaki, Miyabigaoka Gakuen e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117391" update="2010-04-02">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-14</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雅ヶ丘(みやびがおか)学園生徒会長登場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Enter the Student Council President of Miyabigaoka</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Miyabigaoka Gakuen Seitokaichou Toujou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117392" update="2010-04-02">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-07</airdate>
<rating votes="16">7.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">男・鮎沢塾!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Men &amp; the Ayuzawa Cram School</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otoko, Ayuzawa Juku!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117393" update="2010-04-02">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-30</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">初めてのお留守番</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Time Minding the Shop</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no Orusuban</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117394" update="2010-04-02">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="13">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ネットアイドルAOIちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Net Idol Aoi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Net Idol Aoi-chan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117395" update="2010-04-02">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">美咲は何色? 天然色?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What Color Is Misaki? Natural Color?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Misaki wa Nani Iro? Tennenshoku?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117467" update="2010-04-05">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-04-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117468" update="2010-04-05">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-04-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118812" update="2010-06-10">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">学校見学会で眼鏡うさぎ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bespectacled Rabbit at the Open Campus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gakkou Kengakukai de Megane Usagi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118813" update="2010-06-10">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">1年7組 叶爽太郎(かのうそうたろう)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Soutarou Kano of Class 1-7</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">1-nen 7-kumi Kanou Soutarou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118932" update="2010-06-13">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="12">8.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">碓氷, 敵に回る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Usui Becomes the Enemy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Usui, Teki ni Mawaru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118933" update="2010-06-13">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">海の家でもメイドラテ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maid Latte at the Beach House</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Umi no Ie de mo Maid Latte</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118996" update="2010-06-19">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="9">4.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">林間学校オニごっこ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tag at the Forest School</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rinkan Gakkou Onigokko</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118997" update="2010-06-19">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">碓氷のライバル? 深谷陽向</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Usui`s Rival?! Hinata Shintani</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Usui no Rival? Shintani Hinata</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118998" update="2010-06-19">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="11">4.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">副会長は王子様!? / AOIとユカイな仲間たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Vice President Is a Prince?! Aoi &amp; Her Fun Companions</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukukaichou wa Ouji-sama? / Aoi to Yukai na Nakama-tachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118999" update="2010-06-19">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ペア組み直しでフットマン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Footmen Through a Change of Pairs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pair Kuminaoshi de Footman</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119000" update="2010-06-19">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">メイド様でもフットマン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maid-sama Is a Footman</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maid-sama de mo Footman</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119227" update="2010-06-24">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-24</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ずるすぎるよ鮎沢, 碓氷のアホ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Too Cruel Ayuzawa &amp; Usui the Idiot!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zurusugiru yo Ayuzawa, Usui no Aho!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119228" update="2010-06-24">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">陽向と美咲と碓氷くん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hinata &amp; Misaki &amp; Usui</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hinata to Misaki to Usui-kun</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119229" update="2010-06-24">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラテ・マジックでメロメロリン♥</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lovey-Dovey Through Latte Magic</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Latte Magic de Melomelorin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119230" update="2010-06-24">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スイーツ大盛りメイドラテ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maid Latte &amp; a Whole Bunch of Sweets</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sweets Oomori Maid Latte</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120026" update="2010-07-19">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-07-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122548" update="2010-09-19">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview video</title>
</episode>
<episode id="127869" update="2018-09-24">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>2010-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ご主人様と遊んじゃお♥DVD</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Play with the Master! DVD</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Goshujin-sama to Asonjao DVD</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130160" update="2018-09-24">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-05-11</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おまけだよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s an Extra</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omake Da yo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145717" update="2012-11-29">
<epno type="6">O3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2011-05-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">∞ループ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Video Clips 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mugen Loop</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145718" update="2012-11-29">
<epno type="6">O2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2011-05-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">予感</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Video Clips 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yokan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145719" update="2012-11-29">
<epno type="6">O1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2011-05-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">My Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Video Clips 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">My Secret</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
