<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7019" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>11</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-01-15</startdate>
<enddate>2010-03-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Nodame Cantabile: Finale</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Nodame Cantabile 3</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Нодамэ Кантабиле (третий сезон)</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="synonym">交響情人夢 最終篇</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">交响情人梦 最终篇</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Ncf</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">NC3</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">のだめカンタービレ フィナーレ</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">交响情人梦Finale</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6779" type="Sequel">Nodame Cantabile (2009)</anime>
<anime id="5941" type="Prequel">Nodame Cantabile: Paris Hen</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4509" approval="4" total="11">Kin`iro no Chord: Primo Passo</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="8">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="306093">FInaly!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="387470">totallyy enjoyed it and loved it!
but somewhat a let down because it was only 11 episodes</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="261604">This is a must see, by all means!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="960">like the first 2 seasons, wonderfully and superp *highly recommended*

but with only 11 episodes way to short.
i`m a man, but i was crying on all 3 seasons, because of the fine characters, and it *sometimes* felt like a piece of my own time i had on this planet.

totemo subarasi katta desu</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.nodame-anime.com</url>
<creators>
<name id="4906" type="Music">Matsutani Suguru</name>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="2187" type="Character Design">Shimamura Hidekazu</name>
<name id="1568" type="Series Composition">Nakashima Kazuki</name>
<name id="558" type="Original Work">Ninomiya Tomoko</name>
<name id="1482" type="Direction">Kon Chiaki</name>
<name id="23403" type="Music">Nodame Orchestra</name>
</creators>
<description>The musical love-story continues between Noda Megumi, the talented yet distracted (almost childish) piano player, and Chiaki Shinichi, the prodigious, always focused on advancing forward, orchesta conductor. How love will finally find its way for these two. Will it be able to surpass the challenges ahead or will it die prematurely. Paris, the city of light, is the more accurate place to find out how this "love musical" will reach its finale.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="3067">8.65</permanent>
<temporary count="3082">8.36</temporary>
<review count="3">7.60</review>
</ratings>
<picture>84034.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10950</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8038</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>5690</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4509</identifier>
<identifier>rikmwk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.nodame-anime.com</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Nodame_Cantabile</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>のだめカンタービレ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1826</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>335597</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12211</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2010/nodame_finale</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2614" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>josei</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word josei refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 15 and 44. In Japanese, the word means simply "woman", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2807" parentid="2831" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>France</name>
<description>France, officially the French Republic, is a country whose territory consists of metropolitan France in western Europe, as well as several overseas regions and territories. The metropolitan area of France extends from the Mediterranean Sea to the English Channel and the North Sea, and from the Rhine to the Atlantic Ocean. The overseas territories include French Guiana in South America and several islands in the Atlantic, Pacific and Indian oceans.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214343.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3865" parentid="6153" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>noitaminA</name>
<description>noitaminA (ノイタミナ) – Animation written backwards – is a Fuji Television programming block, devoted to anime, broadcast each Thursday night from 00:45 to 1:15. It was launched with the intention of expanding the target audience beyond the typical young male demographic.
The timeslot was expanded from half an hour to a full hour in 2010, and now airs Thursday nights from 00:45 to 1:45.
noitaminA aired its first non-anime series in 2010, with the premiere of the live-action adaptation of Moyashimon. On April 15, 2010, Fuji TV and FUNimation announced an agreement that allows FUNimation to simulcast series from the noitaminA block in North America within an hour of their airing in Japan.</description>
<picurl>36897.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5705" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-08-18">
<name>butchered foreign languages</name>
<description>In this anime, some characters "speak" foreign languages, successfully making the audience`s ears bleed. That is especially true if the viewer is a native speaker of or otherwise proficient in the languages in question.
The foreigners in the show do not seem to take much notice of the fact that their supposed native languages are being massacred. In fact, oftentimes they also actively participate in the butchering of said languages. That happens, of course, because they, too, are voiced by Japanese people without knowledge of the language they`re supposed to speak, or to pretend to speak at any rate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5917" parentid="2794" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-24">
<name>classical music</name>
<description>Classical music is art music produced or rooted in the traditions of Western music (both liturgical and secular). It encompasses a broad span of time from roughly the 11th century to the present day.
Anime tagged have classical music as a central theme.</description>
<picurl>169132.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6137" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-09">
<name>catchphrase</name>
<description>A catchphrase is a sound, word or phrase commonly used by a person. That may be simply out of habit, or in an attempt to deliver some form of image, like that of cuteness. In fiction, characters often use catchphrases as a way to deliver specific personality traits. Examples include Otohime Mutsumi`s "ara ara" in Love Hina, Yang Wenli`s "yare yare" in Legend of the Galactic Heroes, Misuzu`s "gao" in AIR, Sakura`s "hoe" in Card Captor Sakura, Suiseiseki`s "desu" in Rozen Maiden, and Ayu`s "uguu" in Kanon (as well as several other characters in the same show).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7075" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-05-07">
<name>adapted into Japanese movie</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a Japanese movie.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2106" type="main character in" update="2013-07-05">
<rating votes="532">9.02</rating>
<name>Noda Megumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Noda is, at the start of the series, a twenty-year-old free-spirited second-year music student. She is depicted as a complete slob: her cooking and cleaning skills are atrocious to the point of having mushrooms growing on her clothes. However she is an incredibly talented pianist who primarily plays by ear, in a cantabile style. In love with Chiaki, she follows him around constantly, claiming to be his wife, and leans on him to help her get through sticky situations. She sometimes compulsively needs to play the piano, neglecting everything in order to do it. She also seems to enjoy childish manga and movies. She is constantly hungry, and is fed dinners by Chiaki; she also steals many lunches from her fellow friend, Maki.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>139560.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2128" type="main character in" update="2013-07-05">
<rating votes="278">8.54</rating>
<name>Chiaki Shin`ichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chiaki is twenty-one years old and a 3rd-year piano student at Momogaoka Music Academy at the start of the series. He is an accomplished pianist and violinist, but is also known to be a perfectionist and highly critical of himself and others. He comes from a distinguished and well-off family, and is a fairly good cook. He seems to think that most "poor" people (such as Sakura Saku) are like the little match girl. While he dreams of studying abroad and becoming a famous conductor like his mentor, Sebastiano Viella, he must overcome his fear of flying and the sea to do so. He is dismayed to discover that this freakish but talented girl, Nodame, lives in the apartment next door to him,. However, he develops a sort of empathy with Nodame as he discovers her hidden potential to be a great pianist, and he begins to transcend his perfectionism and begins to enjoy his music and the music of others.
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>139562.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2467" type="appears in" update="2010-02-25">
<rating votes="2">7.20</rating>
<name>Jean Donnadieu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Another of Viella`s students, who also works in Paris and considers himself a rival to Chiaki. He has a very affectionate and devoted girlfriend named Yuko, whom Jean regards as his "Goddess of Victory".</description>
<picture>2588.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2468" type="appears in" update="2010-02-25">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Sebastiano Viella</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>World renowned conductor and Chiaki`s mentor. Stresemann is rather adverse towards Viella and initially extended his dislike of the conductor to Chiaki. Viella has considered Chiaki as his apprentice since the boy was twelve and is a surrogate father figure to Chiaki.
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>2605.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="467" picture="38026.jpg">Ebara Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2502" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-19">
<rating votes="66">7.51</rating>
<name>Franz von Stresemann</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Stresemann is a highly respected and internationally famous conductor who comes to Momogaoka Music Academy as a guest instructor. In love with the Academy`s director, he comes as a favor and is immediately pegged as an oddball lecher. Perverted, demanding, and not at all dignified, Stresemann seems to be the opposite of what is expected from a man of his reputation. He, however, immediately takes to Nodame, and even accepts Chiaki as his one and only apprentice after repeatedly rejecting his application to enroll in his conducting classes. His wild behavior constantly gets Chiaki in trouble, but he also teaches him how to feel and express music in a way that only he can. He often takes his orchestra out for mixers or group dates, and goes to night clubs and host clubs (especially Club One More Kiss) instead of attending the rehearsals he is supposed to conduct. He also gets drunk easily, forcing Chiaki to take over for him as assistant conductor.
Adapted from Wikipedia</description>
<picture>2603.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="544" picture="238510.jpg">Ogawa Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2517" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="40">6.53</rating>
<name>Mine Ryuutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mine Ryuutarou is 2nd-year violin student at Momogaoka academy, Mine is something of a prima donna whose violin technique is seen by himself to be deeply personal but by others to be simply sloppy. He is a member of the academy`s S-Orchestra and the R☆S Orchestra. His father, http://anidb.net/ch2774 [Mine Tatsumi], owns a Chinese restaurant "Uraken" right next to the university.
Adapted from Wikipedia</description>
<picture>2617.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="60" picture="171602.jpg">Kawada Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2518" type="appears in" update="2009-06-23">
<rating votes="20">5.43</rating>
<name>Miki Kiyora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A prodigious violinist whom Chiaki meets at the Nina Lutz seminar and joins to form the R☆S Orchestra, Kiyora Miki studies abroad in Vienna and is a student of former Berlin Philharmonic Orchestra concertmaster, Kai Dowin.
Adapted from Wikipedia</description>
<picture>29822.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2530" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-24">
<rating votes="37">7.09</rating>
<name>Kuroki Yasunori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A talented oboe player who falls for Nodame at first sight (oblivious to her true nature) and performs the inaugural solo of the R☆S orchestra. Because he tends to be phlegmatic and quiet, many members of the R☆S orchestra think of him as "samurai-like".</description>
<picture>2604.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="263" picture="186711.jpg">Matsukaze Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2531" type="appears in" update="2009-06-18">
<rating votes="25">3.57</rating>
<name>Okuyama Masumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A claustrophobic timpanist and an okama, 3rd-year studen Masumi has a crush on Chiaki and considers Nodame a rival and often bullies her and anyone else who tries to get close to Chiaki. Despite his idiosyncrasies, he excels on his percussion skills, earning him the title of "Queen of Percussion" and a place in the S and R☆S orchestras conducted by Chiaki.
Adapted from Wikipedia</description>
<picture>2616.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="408" picture="17255.jpg">Fujita Yoshinori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2533" type="appears in" update="2009-06-18">
<rating votes="10">3.62</rating>
<name>Etou Kouzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A piano teacher for the elites at Momogaoka Academy, Etou Sensei has been dubbed "the harisen teacher" because he always carries one during his classes and uses it to punish his students for their mistakes.
Adapted from Wikipedia</description>
<picture>25861.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2561" type="appears in" update="2009-06-21">
<rating votes="1">7.36</rating>
<name>Tanioka Hajime</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A piano teacher at Momogaoka, said to specialise in "drop-out" students. Chiaki is reassigned to Tanioka after his loud argument with Etou Kouzou in chapter 1. He discovers that Nodame is already a student of Tanioka`s, and one of the first assignments Tanioka assigns him is to perform a Mozart piano duet with Nodame, which also entails teaching her, and himself, the focus and discipline to play well with others.
Adapted from Wikipedia</description>
<picture>29606.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2582" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-24">
<rating votes="24">5.96</rating>
<name>Charles Auclair</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Charles Auclair is a judge at the Maradona piano competition in which Nodame features as one of the contestants. He is quite taken with her performances and recommends her to apply for a place at the Paris conservatoire where he is a teacher.</description>
<picture>2593.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="564" picture="146195.jpg">Kiyokawa Motomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2592" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-22">
<rating votes="12">3.48</rating>
<name>Franck Latoine</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A French piano student who lives in the same apartment complex as Chiaki and Nodame. He befriended Nodame when they were taking the entrance exam to study in Paris. He is a fan of Japanese anime, particularly Nodame`s favourite series, the fictional Puri Gorota. He had a slight crush on Nodame, but fell out of it once he saw her obsession with anime and Chiaki. Franck previously studied at the same school as Yunlong, but after seeing Professor Auclair, chose to transfer to the Conservatory.
Adapted from Wikipedia</description>
<picture>2586.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="567" picture="80605.jpg">Asanuma Shintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2593" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-22">
<rating votes="35">6.94</rating>
<name>Tatiana Vishnyova</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An attractive Russian senior piano student who lives in the same apartment complex as Chiaki, Nodame, Franck, and Yunlong. Her piano playing is somewhat mediocre and she lacks confidence in her ability, which seems to be the reason behind her fixation on finding an affluent boyfriend in France. She initially finds Kuroki rather gloomy, but eventually develops strong feelings for him.
Adapted from Wikipedia</description>
<picture>2583.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2594" type="appears in" update="2009-07-24">
<rating votes="15">4.35</rating>
<name>Elise</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Elise is Stresemann`s jerky-chewing, hard-nosed agent, and business manager. Aided by her bodyguard Oliver she kidnapped Chiaki and forced him to sign with her agency too.
Adapted from Wikipedia</description>
<picture>2606.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="563" picture="73156.jpg">Kawakami Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2595" type="appears in" update="2010-04-27">
<name>Namiki Yuuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Namiki Yuuko is http://anidb.net/ch2467 [Jean Donnadieu]`s lover and lucky charm, Yuuko is fiercely protective of him and is ever-suspicious of http://anidb.net/ch2128 [Chiaki].</description>
<picture>2589.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="252" picture="149852.jpg">Shindou Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2596" type="appears in" update="2009-06-26">
<name>Noda Youko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Youko is Nodame`s mother who moonlights as a dressmaker. She enjoys copying designer brands.</description>
<picture>30016.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="580" picture="17973.jpg">Yuya Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2607" type="appears in" update="2009-06-26">
<name>Noda Tatsuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nodame`s father and Fukuoka seaweed farmer. Noda Tatsuo also prides himself on being a Wadaiko (drum) performer at the local festival.</description>
<picture>30014.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2608" type="appears in" update="2009-06-26">
<name>Noda Yoshitaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nodame`s brother and the brighter sibling of the Noda family, Yoshitaka is of an entrepreneurial bent and has an online store. He is university student.</description>
<picture>30015.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="586" picture="171556.jpg">Yonaga Tsubasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2609" type="appears in" update="2009-06-26">
<name>Noda Kisaburou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nodame`s paternal grandfather.</description>
<picture>30012.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="587" picture="228627.jpg">Sonoe Osamu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2610" type="appears in" update="2009-06-26">
<name>Noda Shizuyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nodame`s paternal grandmother.</description>
<picture>30013.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="579" picture="25835.jpg">Uemura Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2620" type="appears in" update="2009-07-21">
<rating votes="3">6.73</rating>
<name>Miyoshi Seiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Seiko is Chiaki`s mother and a divorcee. She currently resides at her ancestral home with the Miyoshis and manages a foundation for disadvantaged students of the arts.</description>
<picture>2602.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2632" type="appears in" update="2010-01-18">
<rating votes="6">4.33</rating>
<name>Chiaki Masayuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A world famous pianist and Shin`ichi`s estranged father. Masayuki and Seiko, divorced each other when Shin`ichi was 12.
He primarily resides in Berlin.</description>
<picture>41641.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2633" type="appears in" update="2009-03-01">
<name>Miyoshi Takehiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shin`ichi`s maternal uncle and 2nd generation president of the Miyoshi corporation. He`s been taking care of Chiaki`s tuition and living expenses while at Momogaoka. But, in truth, he`d prefer it if Chiaki succeeds him in his business.</description>
<picture>2598.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="297" picture="233915.jpg">Ootsuka Houchuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2634" type="appears in" update="2009-03-01">
<name>Miyoshi Toshihiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Toshihiko is Shin`ichi`s cousin and used to idolise him when he was younger. He used to play the violin as well.</description>
<picture>2599.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2635" type="appears in" update="2010-05-01">
<rating votes="9">4.55</rating>
<name>Miyoshi Yuiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miyoshi Yuiko is http://anidb.net/ch2128 [Chiaki]`s cousin and addresses him as Shin-niichama. While initially unimpressed with http://anidb.net/ch2106 [Nodame], they get along famously later on.</description>
<picture>2600.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2720" type="appears in" update="2010-04-28">
<rating votes="5">5.55</rating>
<name>Suzuki Moe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Suzuki Moe is a flautist and part of the S-Orchestra. Moe is the twin sister of http://anidb.net/ch2721 [Kaoru] and is distinguished by her permed hairstyle.</description>
<picture>30021.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2721" type="appears in" update="2009-06-26">
<rating votes="4">5.42</rating>
<name>Suzuki Kaoru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A clarinetist and part of the S-Orchestra. Kaoru is the twin sister of Moe and is distinguished by her straight hairstyle.</description>
<picture>30022.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2746" type="appears in" update="2009-03-03">
<name>Nina Lutz</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A renowned French pianist and instructor, Nina is also a friend of the Chiaki family. She conducts an annual seminar and festival where experts from around the world hold master classes for budding musicians in Japan.</description>
<picture>2615.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="653" picture="18181.jpg">Tsuda Shouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2765" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-07-22">
<name>Momodaira Sayoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31754.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3007" picture="23764.jpg">Adachi Tomo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2771" type="appears in" update="2009-07-21">
<name>Tanaka Makiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A piano major and one of Nodame`s friends at Momogaoka.</description>
<picture>29609.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2774" type="appears in" update="2009-06-23">
<rating votes="2">8.37</rating>
<name>Mine Tatsumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The senior Mine is the owner of the Chinese restaurant `Uraken` and also one of the sponsors of the Rising Star Orchestra.</description>
<picture>29823.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="694" picture="52187.jpg">Choo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2777" type="appears in" update="2009-06-24">
<name>Takahashi Noriyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A world-class violinist who passes on an offer from the entertainment world to join the Rising Star Orchestra as its new concertmaster instead. He is enamoured with Chiaki.</description>
<picture>29845.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2778" type="appears in" update="2009-06-26">
<rating votes="4">2.17</rating>
<name>Kimura Tomohito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A violinist and a member of the Rising Star Orchestra. Kimura is good friends with Mine and prefer to communicate with each other via snail-mail.</description>
<picture>30023.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2820" type="appears in" update="2009-07-22">
<name>Katahira Hajime</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Katahira Hajime is a Japanese conductor who meets Chiaki during the Platini international conductors competition.</description>
<picture>2587.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="3875" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-24">
<rating votes="17">6.52</rating>
<name>Son Rui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Chinese prodigy on the piano who has performed all around the world. Chiaki and Rui play together when he has to step in for Stresemann.
She has taken a year`s sabbatical from performing to study in Paris.</description>
<picture>2620.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3876" type="appears in" update="2009-07-23">
<rating votes="2">3.92</rating>
<name>Paul Dubois</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A bassoon player who attends the same conservatoire as Nodame and Kuroki and forms a trio with them.</description>
<picture>2619.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="68" picture="16675.jpg">Yasumura Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3877" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-24">
<rating votes="13">3.24</rating>
<name>Li YunLong</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Chinese piano student who stays in the same apartment complex as Nodame and Chiaki.</description>
<picture>2578.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3878" type="appears in" update="2009-03-03">
<name>Osada Katsuhiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A painter who lives in the attic of the same apartment complex as Nodame and Chiaki.</description>
<picture>2621.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1683" picture="223030.jpg">Kanemitsu Nobuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3966" type="appears in" update="2009-07-23">
<rating votes="2">4.37</rating>
<name>Toma Simon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The concertmaster of the Roux Marlet Orchestra.</description>
<picture>2577.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="562" picture="17888.jpg">Tsuda Eizou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3967" type="appears in" update="2009-07-23">
<name>Theo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The manager of the Roux Marlet Orchestra.</description>
<picture>2618.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1692" picture="224934.jpg">Okitsu Kazuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3968" type="appears in" update="2009-07-22">
<rating votes="2">3.04</rating>
<name>Anna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Manager of the Miyoshi apartment complex in Paris where Nodame, Chiaki et al. are all staying.</description>
<picture>2585.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1693" picture="19890.jpg">Sudou Erika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3969" type="appears in" update="2010-05-01">
<rating votes="7">2.55</rating>
<name>Lucas Beaudry</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lucas Beaudry is a piano prodigy studying at the same conservatoire and good friends with http://anidb.net/ch2106 [Nodame].</description>
<picture>2601.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3970" type="appears in" update="2009-07-22">
<rating votes="2">7.12</rating>
<name>Roland Chevalier</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Viola player in the Wiltord Orchestra and a big fan of Chiaki.</description>
<picture>2594.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="605" picture="226544.jpg">Ishii Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4149" type="appears in" update="2009-07-23">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Oliver</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Elise`s beefy assistant.</description>
<picture>2607.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4470" type="appears in" update="2009-03-10">
<name>Pierre de Benoit</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The head of the Benoit family and a Mozart fanatic. At professor Auclair`s request, he invites Nodame to his castle in Saint-Malo, to give her first recital at a nearby church.</description>
<picture>2642.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="369" picture="223406.jpg">Aoyama Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10579" type="appears in" update="2009-07-20">
<rating votes="3">3.04</rating>
<name>Gorota</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Protagonist character of Puri Gorota (プリごろ太) anime.</description>
<picture>31582.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="10580" type="appears in" update="2009-07-20">
<name>Puririn</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A fairy from outer space.</description>
<picture>31584.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="563" picture="73156.jpg">Kawakami Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10581" type="appears in" update="2009-07-20">
<name>Kazuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31585.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="10582" type="appears in" update="2009-07-20">
<name>Riona</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31586.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="10659" type="appears in" update="2009-07-21">
<rating votes="8">4.39</rating>
<name>Ishikawa Rena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nodame`s friend studying at piano course. She played a pianica at festival with disguised S Orchestra.</description>
<picture>31703.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="10689" type="appears in" update="2009-07-23">
<name>Rui no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch3875 [Rui]`s mother.</description>
<picture>31800.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1693" picture="19890.jpg">Sudou Erika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10690" type="appears in" update="2009-07-23">
<rating votes="2">3.04</rating>
<name>Celine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A flutist of the Wiltord Orchestra.</description>
<picture>31801.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="10712" type="appears in" update="2009-07-24">
<name>Noemi Creve</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A cellist in Roux-Marlet Orchestra.</description>
<picture>31902.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6958" picture="31903.jpg">Takita Juri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10713" type="appears in" update="2009-07-24">
<rating votes="2">3.04</rating>
<name>Alex Solan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An oboe player in Roux-Marlet Orchestra.</description>
<picture>31904.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2802" picture="176252.jpg">Shingaki Tarusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10714" type="appears in" update="2009-07-24">
<rating votes="2">3.04</rating>
<name>Catherine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31906.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10715" type="appears in" update="2009-07-24">
<rating votes="2">3.04</rating>
<name>Daniel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A cello player and a new member of Roux-Marlet Orchestra.</description>
<picture>31918.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6935" picture="77710.jpg">Matsubara Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15112" type="appears in" update="2010-02-21">
<name>Maginot</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>43274.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="314" picture="10231.jpeg">Seto Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15113" type="appears in" update="2010-02-21">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Arman</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>43277.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6916" picture="187044.jpg">Sekiyama Misaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15292" type="appears in" update="2010-02-25">
<name>Lambert</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>43629.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13871" picture="48741.jpg">Ono Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15399" type="appears in" update="2010-03-01">
<name>Robert</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>43881.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6918" picture="222918.jpg">Densaka Tsutomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15405" type="appears in" update="2010-03-01">
<name>Namura Rima</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>43888.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="475" picture="17433.jpg">Makino Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16059" type="appears in" update="2010-03-24">
<name>Serge</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45122.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3712" picture="240126.jpg">Tamura Mutsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16060" type="appears in" update="2010-03-24">
<name>Mifa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45123.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1961" picture="222838.jpg">Yonezawa Madoka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16181" type="appears in" update="2010-03-28">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Michelle</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45327.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="162" picture="23208.jpg">Satou Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="110775" update="2009-10-18">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-10-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="113041" update="2015-12-31">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-01-15</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="113176" update="2015-12-31">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="113178" update="2015-12-31">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-01-29</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="113356" update="2015-12-31">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-02-05</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116199" update="2015-12-31">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-02-12</airdate>
<rating votes="9">9.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116410" update="2015-12-31">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-02-19</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116411" update="2015-12-31">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116412" update="2015-12-31">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-03-05</airdate>
<rating votes="12">8.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116413" update="2015-12-31">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-03-12</airdate>
<rating votes="10">9.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116414" update="2015-12-31">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-03-19</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116918" update="2015-12-31">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-03-26</airdate>
<rating votes="9">9.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117950" update="2010-05-01">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">峰と清良の再会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mine and Kiyora`s Reunion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mine to Kiyora no Saikai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134872" update="2011-11-18">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2010-01-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134873" update="2015-12-31">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2010-01-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
