<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7025" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1959-10</startdate>
<enddate>1959-10</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Inemuri Buuchan</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Sleeping Buu-chan</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">いねむりぶうちゃん</title>
</titles>
<description>A modified version of The Little Red Hen folk tale. It stars a squirrel and the moral of the story (no work=no prize) is removed as the animals who didn`t contribute at all to making the bread were allowed to eat it.
Source: MAL</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="8">3.36</permanent>
<temporary count="8">4.00</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>182653.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>32227</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3968" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>animal protagonist</name>
<description>The anime revolves around an animal, usually only communicating with typical onomatopoeia. The animal mostly lives in a human family and has adventures on a regular base. This can be the discovery of a new room, or being lost by having taken a wrong turn in the outside world.
Typical example: http://anidb.net/a5801 [Chii`s Sweet Home].
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t4259 [animal world], where the whole world is composed of animals.</description>
<picurl>10255.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4349" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>puppetmation</name>
<description>A puppet is an inanimate object or representational figure animated or manipulated by a puppeteer. It is usually (but by no means always) a depiction of a human character, and is used in puppetry, a play or a presentation that is a very ancient form of theatre. The puppet undergoes a process of transformation through being animated, and is normally manipulated by at least one puppeteer.
There are many different varieties of puppets, and they are made of a wide range of materials, depending on their form and intended use. They can be extremely complex or very simple in their construction. They may even be found objects. As Oscar Wilde wrote, "There are many advantages in puppets. They never argue. They have no crude views about art. They have no private lives".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4664" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-18">
<name>short movie</name>
<description>Typically used when an OVA only has one part and is less than the usual 20 to 25 minutes in length.
So instead of calling it a `short episode`, the `short movie` tag is more appropriate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5529" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-05">
<name>black and white</name>
<description>Some or all of this anime is in black and white, typical of older anime made before ~1960. Some modern anime may intentionally shift to black and white for certain scenes or episodes as an artistic effect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5939" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-09">
<name>CAST MISSING</name>
<description>Important characters are missing, either in-part or entirely. This includes basic entry info (name, gender, picture), appear episode range, seiyuu and/or tags.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="108514" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
