<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7031" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-10-09</startdate>
<enddate>2009-10-09</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">King of Thorn</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Король Терний</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Кралят на тръните</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Ibara no Ou</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">古城荆棘王</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">いばらの王 -King of Thorn-</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">King of Thorn</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">King of Thorn</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Le roi des ronces</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">El Rey Espino</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Král trnů</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="416" approval="6" total="11">Blue Gender</anime>
<anime id="6644" approval="2" total="7">Darker Than Black: Ryuusei no Gemini</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="7">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="60976">Great but complicated story. Up to real end we don`t know what is going on and what happened.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="239259">Epic</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="383524">The movie is good, if you do not know the manga, which is many times better. The right order should be: watch the movie and then read the manga to find out, why you had the feeling, that somethig is missing while watching.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="256742">Pertamax!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="173182">Another great story that motivates to think.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="302803">one of the most coolest anime i ever watch, with superb story.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.kingofthorn.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3174" type="Music">Sahashi Toshihiko</name>
<name id="7054" type="Original Work">Iwahara Yuuji</name>
<name id="1466" type="Character Design">Matsubara Hidenori</name>
<name id="1760" type="Direction">Katayama Kazuyoshi</name>
<name id="2163" type="Chief Animation Direction">Onda Naoyuki</name>
<name id="726" type="Animation Work">Sunrise</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the seinen science fiction manga series by http://anidb.net/cr7054 [Iwahara Yuuji], serialised in http://anidb.net/cr30451 [Monthly Comic Beam].
A mysterious virus, named Medusa, is spreading around the world, turning its victims into stone. Given the impossibility of finding an immediate cure, a corporation offers to cryo-preserve a select group of patients until they come up with a solution.
http://anidb.net/ch20295 [Kasumi], one of the chosen ones, wakes up after being asleep for an unknown period of time and her awakening, not a bed of roses, is a bed of thorns, and happens in the midst of total chaos where monstrous creatures lie in wait all around.
Note: Premiered in the Anima`t section of the 42nd annual Sitges International Film Festival, which was held on October 1-12, 2009 in Catalonia, Spain.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1694">5.84</permanent>
<temporary count="1697">6.99</temporary>
<review count="1">6.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>127706.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10915</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6610</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4611</identifier>
<identifier>zcetlm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.kingofthorn.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>King_of_Thorn</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2247</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>335986</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12465</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2668</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1262" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-11-07">
<name>naive</name>
<description>A naive (also spelled naïve, keeping its French diacritic) person lacks worldly knowledge, experience, wisdom, understanding, or judgement.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1656" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-27">
<name>corrupt</name>
<description>The character is spiritually or morally impure and may accept payment or other benefits for services or material which the recipient is not due, under law.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1773" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-12">
<name>tentacle</name>
<description>A tentacle or bothrium (plural: bothria) is one of usually two or more elongated flexible organs present in animals, especially invertebrates. Usually, Tentacles are used for feeding, feeling and grasping.</description>
<picurl>236087.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2019" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-16">
<name>suicidal</name>
<description>The character has suicidal tendencies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2090" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-17">
<name>trauma</name>
<description>Character with emotional or psychological injury, caused by single or multiple events/experiences in the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2684" parentid="2812" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>New York</name>
<description>The City of New York, often called New York City or simply New York, is the most populous city in the United States. New York City is also the most densely populated major city in the United States. Located at the southern tip of the state of New York, the city is the center of the New York metropolitan area, one of the most populous urban agglomerations in the world.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214276.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2809" parentid="2831" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>United Kingdom</name>
<description>The United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, commonly known as the United Kingdom (UK) or Britain, is a sovereign country in western Europe. Lying off the north-western coast of the European mainland, the UK includes the island of Great Britain, the north-eastern part of the island of Ireland and many smaller islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>64254.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2812" parentid="2832" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>United States</name>
<description>The United States of America (commonly referred to as the United States, the U.S., the USA, or America) is a federal constitutional republic comprising fifty states and a federal district. The country is situated mostly in central North America, where its forty-eight contiguous states and Washington, D.C., the capital district, lie between the Pacific and Atlantic Oceans, bordered by Canada to the north and Mexico to the south. The state of Alaska is in the north-west of the continent, with Canada to the east and Russia to the west across the Bering Strait. The state of Hawaii is an archipelago in the mid-Pacific. The country also possesses several territories in the Caribbean and Pacific.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>45504.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2832" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Americas</name>
<description>The Americas, also collectively called America, encompass the totality of the continents of North America and South America. Together they make up most of Earth`s western hemisphere and comprise the New World.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192247.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2852" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>thriller</name>
<description>The thriller is a genre of fiction in which tough, resourceful, but essentially ordinary heroes are pitted against villains determined to destroy them, their country, or the stability of the free world. The hero of a typical thriller faces danger alone or in the company of a small band of companions. The protagonist may be a law enforcement agent, a journalist, or a soldier, but typically he or she is cut off from the resources of "their" organization. More often the hero is an ordinary citizen drawn into danger and intrigue by circumstances beyond their control.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214683.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2924" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>earthquake</name>
<description>*rumble rumble rumble rumble*
Upheaval of the Earth`s crust, usually resulting in widespread destruction.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3267" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>everybody dies</name>
<description>Not necessarily everyone, but a good portion of the characters kick the bucket.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3369" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-06-23">
<name>human psyche</name>
<description>How that grey mass inside the skulls of us earthlings works.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3395" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-18">
<name>promise</name>
<description>A dramatically-made promise that serves as foreshadowing. The promise will eventually be called in and action will be required.
Whether they succeed, fail or refuse to keep their promise depends almost entirely on the idealism-level of the story. Other factors, such as whether they were told what they had to do, or if it was a Leonine Contract, may come into play. Even Releasing from the Promise is usually a scene of high drama.
Source: TVTropes</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3435" parentid="2851" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>eating of humans</name>
<description>The eating of humans, also called man-eating, is the practice of some species to prey on human beings for nourishment. Examples of possible hunters may include Earth animals, alien species, zombies or other undead, and so forth. Eating of humans is not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t3815 [human cannibalism]; the former is about other species eating people, while the latter is about humans eating fellow humans.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3934" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-10">
<name>non-linear</name>
<description>The story is told achronologically.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4084" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-03-20">
<name>dark atmosphere</name>
<description>Usually metaphorical. Sometimes literal. At times both!
Typically this refers to the fact that the story is set in a grim, dog eat dog milieu — for example a decaying city.
Often the characters are just doing what they need to do to survive, with little or no expectation that their lives can be better. And often characters may feel they do not have any real choice in what they do.
And yes, occasionally the setting is actually dark — be it night or perpetually heavy cloudy sky and rain. It all adds to the oppressive, hopeless feeling of the show.
You probably will not feel uplifted or happy after watching this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4257" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>survival</name>
<description>The theme/genre of survival typically depicts the act or process of continuing to live, generally in a hostile, possibly post-apocalyptic environment. Survival-centered media tends to be dark, set most commonly in a contemporary context, and generally leads either to small groups of people forming closely knit and functional units or to individuals turning against their fellows in a return to the survival of the fittest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4308" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-03-26">
<name>delayed death</name>
<description>The Final Battle has begun. The two opponents square off, and one of them hits the other with a series of mighty blows that would fell a mountain. But what`s this? Nothing seems to be happening! That`s when your opponent tells you that You Are Already Dead, right before your head explodes, your body separates in two, or you disintegrate into a fine mist. If you`re unlucky, only one of those happens. Sometimes, you may also discover that you were Made of Explodium.
A common trope in martial arts series, this involves some form of Finishing Move that does not take effect immediately. When used with martial arts, it may involve Pressure Point attacks or some form of Ki Attacks. Assassins may use Universal Poison to achieve a similar effect. In video games, Damage Over Time abilities often have this effect.
When used with swords there are a number of common variations, often shown with a Diagonal Cut. In sword duels, the two sides charge each other and attack. There will be a pause as the two pose, then one (or both) will fall down. Another one is for a Master Swordsman to perform a series of lightning-fast slashes, and then slowly and dramatically sheath their sword (with an audible *click*) before their attacks take effect.
This trope is not necessarily limited to martial arts, either. In more modern settings, gunshot wounds can often have this effect, since getting shot typically feels like getting punched hard and it is not uncommon for victims to take some time to realize it. This can be exploited for dramatic effect in war movies, where fatally wounded soldiers wander the battlefield before succumbing.
Source: TVTropes</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4314" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-04-11">
<name>psychological</name>
<description>Directed toward dealing with or affecting the mind, especially as a function of awareness, feeling, or motivation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4327" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-18">
<name>be careful what you wish for</name>
<description>Be careful what you wish for... your wish may actually come true. This is an age-old philosophical problem of what human beings think they want and what is actually good for them. The power to wish for anything can be very dangerous and usually — as a moral lesson — yields unexpected / unwanted results.
A contract with the devil is a specific case of this; receiving great power, especially from a devil, is usually a double edged sword.</description>
<picurl>230309.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4340" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-26">
<name>suicide</name>
<description>One or several characters in this anime commit suicide.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4499" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-07-28">
<name>some weird shit goin` on</name>
<description>Scenes of this show point to insanely strange events which seem to be taking place; throughout its episodes, the show may or may not explain what is going on. Either way, many viewers will find that a succinct and accurate way to describe the show is "WTF?", and the show`s explanations (or lack thereof) to the events will often be subject of heated debate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4537" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-15">
<name>time skip</name>
<description>The plot features at least one skip or jump in time.
Example: A skip from the present into the past, or time skips in increments, e.g. every hour there is a time skip by a day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4753" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-15">
<name>disturbing</name>
<description>Watching the show may cause the viewer to have unpleasant feelings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5335" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-10">
<name>dreams and reality</name>
<description>This genre of anime is typically set in both the world as we know it (reality) and a world of dreams, mythology or imagination.
Sometimes this dreamworld is actually real, sometimes it is not. Other times what we think is the real world is the dreamworld, and vice versa. They are not always easy to distinguish from each other, neither by the characters nor the viewer.
Whatever is real, and whatever is reality, both worlds are integral in shaping both the plot of this anime and the development of the characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5417" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>mind fuck</name>
<description>A `mind fuck` is a slang term which describes a work that uses literary devices such as nonlinear storytelling and plot twists in order to present convoluted, yet not conflicting, themes.
A creation is usually considered a mind fuck when a casual observer is not able to discern the true meaning of a work without making a serious attempt to unravel the themes presented or when the plot is incredibly difficult to follow.
Special examples of mind fucks involve a single plot twist which completely changes the viewer`s understanding of the events in a film or novel as well as the ideas it presents.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5466" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-17">
<name>epidemic</name>
<description>A rapid spread or increase of something (e.g. a disease) affecting many persons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5567" parentid="6397" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-08-21">
<name>Sleeping Beauty</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5571" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-08-27">
<name>Greek mythology</name>
<description>The anime is derived or draws elements from the Greek mythology, and as such features some mythological characteristics of Ancient Greece. Those may be creatures, such as the Centaur or Hydra, tales, such as that of the Trojan War, or even the Gods themselves, like Zeus or Poseidon. More subtle references also count, such as the careful usage of names of places or people that hold significance in the myths.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5843" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>sibling yin yang</name>
<description>In real life, siblings hardly ever act the same. Fiction sometimes takes this to an extreme.
Enter Sibling Yin Yang, the occurrence of siblings that are nearly polar opposites. If he`s cool and reckless, she`s responsible and thoughtful. If she`s a spiky-haired hooligan, he`s the nerdy wimpy one. If he`s an immature brat, she`s... well, you get the picture.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5952" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-25">
<name>end of the world</name>
<description>The imminent end of the world may range from the total destruction of the planet Earth, to the destruction of Earth`s surface, or to the point where human life on the planet is no longer possible, aka the end of humanity.
In any case it looks grim, and the protagonists battle to preserve what they can.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6062" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-05">
<name>heroic sacrifice</name>
<description>"In order to save the many, the few will need to sacrifice their lives..." or so this character may think. 
In a seemingly hopeless situation, against impossible odds, the character does not choose the path of the coward and run, he or she chooses to bravely face the enemy, fully aware that this will mean death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6397" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-02">
<name>tales</name>
<description>Tales are stories told time and again and passed down from generation to generation, and some of those show up in anime not just once or twice, but several times.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="20295" type="main character in" update="2010-08-03">
<rating votes="10">7.27</rating>
<name>Kasumi Ishiki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52484.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20296" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-03">
<rating votes="6">7.50</rating>
<name>Shizuku Ishiki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52485.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1932" picture="65403.jpg">Sendai Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20297" type="main character in" update="2010-08-03">
<rating votes="9">7.75</rating>
<name>Marco Owen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52486.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20298" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-03">
<rating votes="5">3.59</rating>
<name>Laura Owen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52487.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20299" type="main character in" update="2010-08-03">
<rating votes="7">6.05</rating>
<name>Ron Portman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52488.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="611" picture="18094.jpg">Nomura Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20300" type="main character in" update="2010-08-03">
<rating votes="8">6.13</rating>
<name>Katherine Turner</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52489.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20301" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-03">
<rating votes="6">4.60</rating>
<name>Timothy Laisenbach</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52490.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20302" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-03">
<rating votes="3">3.55</rating>
<name>Alessandro Peccino</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52491.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4688" picture="29259.jpg">Hirota Kousei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20303" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-03">
<rating votes="6">5.48</rating>
<name>Peter Stevens</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52492.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20304" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-03">
<rating votes="4">3.27</rating>
<name>Ivan Coral Vega</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52493.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="560" picture="41051.jpg">Isobe Tsutomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20305" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-03">
<rating votes="3">3.78</rating>
<name>Walter</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52494.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="408" picture="17255.jpg">Fujita Yoshinori</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="108587" update="2014-12-23">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108647" update="2017-08-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>110</length>
<airdate>2009-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
<summary>A fatal pandemic threatens to wipe out the human race. Kasumi and six others struggle to survive a labyrinthine nightmare when they awaken from a cryogenic freeze to find the facility overrun with thorny vines and ravenous monsters.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="124711" update="2010-10-28">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Spot</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124712" update="2014-12-23">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Pilot Film</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124713" update="2010-10-28">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Overseas Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124714" update="2010-10-28">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Competition First Prize Trailer</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
