<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7105" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2003-07-23</startdate>
<enddate>2004-02-11</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-kot" type="main">Hey Yo Yorang</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Kang Hyeon and Yorang</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">My Little Fox</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">꼬마여우 요랑</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">瑶玲啊瑶玲</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.kbs.co.kr/end_program/2tv/enter/yorang/index.html</url>
<description>Yorang, a fox living in heaven, is banished to the Earth to find the book of wishes, which she had lost while working as a librarian. The lost book has the power to unseal the demon, and now heaven is in the great danger. Yorang comes down to the Earth to find the book of wishes, and there is only one year of time given to her. The only clue that is to be found is that the form of the book was changed while falling to the ground.
Source: http://kbsworld.kbs.co.kr</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="11">4.07</permanent>
<temporary count="11">4.81</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>37133.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15479</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.kbs.co.kr/end_program/2tv/enter/yorang/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2406" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-13">
<name>talking animal</name>
<description>Talking animals are a common theme in mythology and folk tales, as well as children`s literature. Fictional talking creatures often are anthropomorphic, possessing human-like qualities but appearing as a creature. An animal that only knows how to say its name (for example, 99.9% of all http://anidb.net/t2493 [Pokemon]), are not talking animals.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2673" parentid="2834" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Korea</name>
<description>Korea is a historical country in East Asia; since 1945, it has been divided into two distinct sovereign states: North Korea (officially the "Democratic People`s Republic of Korea") and South Korea (officially the "Republic of Korea"). Located on the Korean Peninsula, Korea is bordered by China to the northwest and Russia to the northeast. It is separated from Japan to the east by the Korea Strait and the Sea of Japan.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214324.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3697" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-05">
<name>particularly suitable for children</name>
<description>No sex or drugs, but probably rock and roll. Very watchable for children.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="130360" update="2012-01-30">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-02-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Friends Forever</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">친구야 사랑해</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130361" update="2012-01-30">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-02-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Sea Dragon`s Wedding Present</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">바다용의 선물</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130362" update="2012-01-30">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-01-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Dream Camera</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">꿈을 찍는 사진기</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130363" update="2012-01-30">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-01-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Gyeonwoo and Jiknyeo</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">견우와 직녀</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130364" update="2012-01-30">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-12-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Bbuddu`s Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">두 얼굴의 뿌뚜</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130365" update="2012-01-30">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-12-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">The Magic Snail</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">우렁각시</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130366" update="2012-01-30">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-12-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">The Shepherd Boy`s Lie</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">양치기 소년의 거짓말</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130367" update="2012-01-30">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-12-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Dad Is Sick</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">아빠가 편찮으시던 날</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130368" update="2012-01-30">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-11-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">The Adventure of Tarzan Boy</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">타잔 소년의 모험</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130369" update="2012-01-30">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-11-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Go Roller Skating</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">인라인 스케이트 소동</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130370" update="2012-01-30">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-11-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">School Picnic</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">가을 소풍</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130371" update="2012-01-30">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-11-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Mr. Pen`s Wish</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">펜 아저씨의 소원</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130372" update="2012-01-30">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-10-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Messenger of My Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">내 마음의 전령사</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130373" update="2012-01-30">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-10-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Sphinx and its Riddles</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">수수께끼 풍선껌</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130374" update="2012-01-30">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-10-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">The Adventure of Frankenstein Jr.</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">프랑켄슈타인 주니어의 모험</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130375" update="2012-01-30">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-10-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Crazy Hairdos Commotion</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">헤어 스타일 대소동</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130376" update="2012-01-30">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-10-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Chorani, the Muse</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">뮤즈의 꿈</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130377" update="2012-01-30">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Snow White</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">백설공주</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130378" update="2012-01-30">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Mother`s Birthday</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">엄마의 생일</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130379" update="2012-01-30">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-09-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Christmas Carol</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">크리스마스 유령</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130380" update="2012-01-30">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-08-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Midsummer Christmas</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">한여름의 크리스마스</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130381" update="2012-01-30">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-08-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Sister Sun, Brother Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">해님 달님</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130382" update="2012-01-30">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-08-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Dad`s Sketchbook</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">아빠의 스케치북</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130383" update="2012-01-30">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-08-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Promise of Their Own</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">둘만의 약속</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130384" update="2012-01-30">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">The Book of Wish</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">소원의 책</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130385" update="2012-01-30">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fox Village</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">여우가 사는 마을</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
