<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7116" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1989-03-11</startdate>
<enddate>1989-03-11</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Dorami-chan: Mini-Dora SOS!!!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ドラミちゃん ミニドラSOS!!!</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6591" type="Other">Doraemon: Nobita no Nippon Tanjou</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.dora-world.com</url>
<creators>
<name id="4732" type="Original Work">Fujiko F. Fujio</name>
<name id="4496" type="Direction">Moriwaki Makoto</name>
<name id="1393" type="Music">Tanaka Kouhei</name>
<name id="1082" type="Work">Shogakukan</name>
<name id="745" type="Work">TV Asahi</name>
<name id="1284" type="Work">Shin-Ei Animation</name>
</creators>
<description>This episode is set in the future where the main characters from Doraemon are all grown up and have kids. Minidora (mini doraemon) accidently gets delivered to the Nobita`s future house. The sons of Jyaiyan, Suneo and Nobita plays with Minidora with the special goods he brings out of his pocket. But trouble happens when they ran away from Dorami, who came to retrieve Minidora.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="18">5.87</permanent>
<temporary count="18">6.27</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>37417.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1897</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2647</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2504</identifier>
<identifier>dlamtp</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.dora-world.com</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ドラミちゃん_ミニドラSOS!!!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>150716</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1338</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1846" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>kodomo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word kodomo refers to a children`s audience roughly for the ages 12 and younger. In Japanese, the word means simply "child", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="8465" type="main character in" update="2010-08-16">
<rating votes="185">2.75</rating>
<name>Nobi Nobita</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nobita is the main character of the series and the center of the story. He is a fourth grader in Tokyo`s Nerima Ward and an only child. He wears glasses, a red or yellow polo shirt with a white collar, and blue shorts. Nobita`s character flaws are endless: he is lazy, uncoordinated, dim-witted, frail, plain-looking, unlucky, and bad at sports. Nobita`s typical day consists of arriving late on classes, scoring zeros in his tests, getting lectured by his teacher, being bullied by his classmates Gian and Suneo, falling into curbside rain gutters, being chased by dogs, and getting scolded by his mom for his sloth and poor academic results.
Despite his flaws, Nobita possesses some unique talents such as his unrivaled marksmanship and ability to weave intricate string figures. Although Nobita is usually portrayed as being cowardly, he has often risked his life to help save others or even entire civilizations (as seen in full-length stories). He has a tendency of acquiring a grade of zero every once out of five tests and has only scored perfect once in his lifetime.</description>
<picture>27735.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3414" picture="223019.jpg">Ohara Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8466" type="main character in" update="2009-06-05">
<rating votes="371">8.33</rating>
<name>Minamoto Shizuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shizuka, usually called Shizu-chan or Shizuka-chan, is the smart, kind, and pretty neighbourhood girl who is the object of Nobita`s affections. She takes baths several times a day. Nobita often disrupts her in the bath due to some misuse of Doraemon`s gadgets, resulting in Nobita`s head getting dunked. She is also known for taking piano lessons unwillingly, which is sometimes used as an excuse for declining to hang out with Nobita. Her true passions are sweet potatoes, which she`d rather keep to herself out of the knowledge of others, and the violin, in which her playing is as atrocious as Gian`s singing. Due to Doraemon`s intervention, Shizuka will become Nobita`s wife in the future timeline.</description>
<picture>27612.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24" picture="16606.jpg">Nomura Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8549" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-22">
<rating votes="127">3.47</rating>
<name>Gouda Takeshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gouda Takeshi, usually known by the nickname "Gian" from English word "giant", is the big, strong, and quick-tempered local bully. His nickname may be derived from giant. He is known for his confidence in his terrible singing voice. He regularly subjects the neighborhood children to horrendous singing recitals, which is sometimes combined with his equally bad homemade dinner. He also frequently steals other children`s toys and books under the pretext of "borrowing" them, unless the toy is damaged. This is how most fans considered Gian to be a major antagonist mostly to http://anidb.net/ch8465 [Nobita] and his friends. However, he does not hesitate to help them, including Nobita when they are in real trouble, which often occurs in the movies.
Several of the stories revolve around Nobita and his friends` efforts to avoid Gian`s concerts or in one particular episode or chapter, which summarize his friends avoid visiting Gian`s house on his birthday because of his selfish nature. After reflecting on one event about his birthday, Gian thought of himself why he wasn`t popular among his peers. After getting a lecture from http://anidb.net/ch8456 [Doraemon] to see what an unruly character he is, Gian realize that he should`ve been a better person and he begs Doraemon to give him another chance. However, things didn`t go exactly as planned when his friends at school or at the streets mock him to see how weird Gian was acting and get kicked by http://anidb.net/ch8553 [Suneo] after learning his attempt to become gentle to his peers. This led him to lose control of his temper and start attacking his friends again.
Although he bullies the other children (mostly Nobita), he is terrified of his mother, who runs the local grocery store. He founded his own baseball team named after himself. Although Nobita is often blamed for the losses against the baseball team`s rival, the "Tyranos", Gian and Suneo still force Nobita to play because they do not have enough players.
Gian also has a younger sister named Jaiko, whom he adores.</description>
<picture>27733.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="652" picture="18178.jpg">Tatekabe Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8553" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-05">
<rating votes="223">3.69</rating>
<name>Honekawa Suneo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Suneo is the fox-faced (inherited from his mother) rich kid who loves to flaunt his material wealth before everyone. He is often seen with Gian, serving as Gian`s lackey while they bully Nobita together. Some of the stories start with Suneo showing off some new video game or toy which evokes Nobita`s envy. He has an extensive knowledge of science, and is a talented artist and designer.
In some scenes, Suneo is seen as a narcissist who loves to stare at himself in the mirror while telling himself that he is the most handsome guy in the world. He is still a bed-wetter and needs to wear diapers when he sleeps, despite being in the fourth grade. He considers this humiliating habit his secret weakness. Suneo is also very self-conscious about his height, being the shortest kid in his class.</description>
<picture>27739.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3285" picture="193568.jpg">Kimotsuki Kaneta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12372" type="main character in" update="2016-08-29">
<rating votes="32">6.84</rating>
<name>Dorami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dorami, also known as Dorami-chan, is the sister of http://anidb.net/ch8456 [Doraemon]. She happens to be about 2 years younger than him. Strangely enough, they are siblings due to the fact that they shared half of the oil from a can. She lives in the 22nd-century Tokyo with http://anidb.net/ch76800 [Sewashi], http://anidb.net/ch8465 [Nobita]`s great-great-grandson. She is yellow and has ears that resemble a large red bow. She likes melonpan and is afraid of cockroaches. She is also shown to be a more advanced robot than Doraemon (Dorami is able to produce 10,000 horse power, in comparison to Doraemon`s 129.3). She sometimes visits Nobita with a time machine when Doraemon is "off-duty" or to help Doraemon with something. She also has her own spin-off manga.</description>
<picture>37408.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9582" picture="219362.jpg">Yokozawa Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="110784" update="2009-10-19">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>1989-03-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
