<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7117" restricted="false">
<type>TV Special</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2001-12-30</startdate>
<enddate>2001-12-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Pocket Monsters Crystal: Raikou Ikazuchi no Densetsu</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pocket Monsters Crystal: Raikou - Legend of Thunder</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Raikou Special</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Карманные монстры Кристалл: Райко - легенда грома</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ポケットモンスタークリスタル ライコウ雷の伝説</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The Legend of Thunder</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">A Lenda do Trovão</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="230" type="Parent Story">Pocket Monsters</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="5780" type="Original Plan">Tajiri Satoshi</name>
<name id="1642" type="Direction">Hidaka Masamitsu</name>
<name id="4464" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ichiishi Sayuri</name>
<name id="4235" type="Chief Direction">Yuyama Kunihiko</name>
<name id="5660" type="Music">Miyazaki Shinji</name>
<name id="727" type="Animation Work">OLM</name>
<name id="5573" type="Character Design">Matsubara Norihiro</name>
<name id="4464" type="Character Design">Ichiishi Sayuri</name>
</creators>
<description>Kenta, a Pokemon master in the making, meets up with his childhood friend, Marina, at a Pokemon Center, to see how their skills have developed. Their battle is interrupted by a thunderstorm and the arrival of Bashou and Buson, two Rocket-dan members using the Crystal System (which attracts Electric-type Pokemon). Their ultimate goal is to, under the guidance of professor Shiranui, bring Pokemon back to Sakaki. Kenta and Marina stumble upon this plan, and they try to stop it, but things get more difficult when the legendary Pokemon http://anidb.net/ch843 [Raikou] is captured.
Note: Released in the US as episodes 1-3 of Pokémon Chronicles.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="271">4.70</permanent>
<temporary count="276">6.29</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>37458.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2268</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1525</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>187</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>323576</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1552</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2801" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>RPG</name>
<description>Any anime that is based on a role-playing game aka RPG. A role-playing video game is a video game which includes elements of non-electronic role-playing games. The player assumes control of one or several fictional characters (a party) who have joined forces in order to perform quests and overcome a great number of challenges and enemies, usually monsters inspired by fantasy, and, to a lesser extent, science fiction and classic mythology. During the course of the game the characters, or avatars, which are generally defined by quantized characteristics, evolve and improve in that their various attributes increase, as well as by gaining more powerful artefacts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2863" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>proxy battles</name>
<description>In our terms, a proxy battle is a battle where humans use creatures/robots to do the fighting for them, either by commanding those creatures/robots or by simply evolving them/changing them into battle mode. Often the training aspect is also involved, or in some cases the proxies are nothing more than holographic representatives of some other variation of competition (like for example a card game). While many popular shounen anime fit under this category, it`s not limited to shounen anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="58" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="18">7.27</rating>
<name>Poppo</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pidgey, known as the Tiny Bird Pokémon, is a bird-like Pokémon, whose original name in the English beta version of Pokémon Red and Blue was "Pidge". Pidgey was first introduced in the United States in Red and Blue. They are one of the first wild Pokémon that players encounter in those games. Pidgey does not like to fight, and will use its wings to stir up clouds of sand in an attempt to distract its would-be opponent and escape. Pidgey also uses this technique to bring its preferred prey of small insects into the open. Pidgey seems to possess magnetoception, as it is capable of returning to its nest from any location without fail.
Pidgey also appeared in the first television episode, Pokémon, I Choose You!, when the main character, Ash Ketchum, attempts to catch one. He fails when it uses its Gust attack to blow him away and escapes. Afterwards, it uses its Sand Attack to blind Ash, allowing it to get away.</description>
<picture>242941.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="16">7.53</rating>
<name>Pigeot</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pidgeot, known as the Bird Pokémon, is a bird-like Pokémon, whose original name in the English beta version of Pokémon Red and Blue was "Pidgeott", is the fully grown and developed form of the Pidgey species evolution line. In the main Pokémon game series, a Pidgeot is only acquired when a Pidgeotto grows past experience level 36 and is evolved into a Pidgeot. Pidgeot are large, powerful birds admired for their glossy plumage and their battling ability. With their powerful chest muscles at work, Pidgeot can flap their wings fast enough to whip up gusts of winds to rival tornadoes. Pidgeot are very aerodynamic, capable of soaring to an altitude of 3300 feet and reaching speeds of up to Mach 2. Like Pidgeotto, Pidgeot feed on Magikarp by swooping from the sky and snatching them out of the water with their talons. Pidgeot appear very similar to Pidgeotto, so much so that one has been easily mistaken for the other, even by official sources.
In the Pokémon anime, Ash`s Pidgeotto evolves into a Pidgeot near the end of the Kanto saga, and remained in Pallet Town to watch over a flock of Pidgey and Pidgeotto while Ash went off to the Orange Islands.</description>
<picture>64488.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="62" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="14">3.20</rating>
<name>Koratta</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rattata, known as the Mouse Pokémon, are a basic Pokémon species found very commonly in the wild in the Kanto and Johto regions of the Pokémon world. Rattata are among the earliest Pokémon that can be caught by players, so much so that it is said that the presence of one Rattata indicates the presence of more than forty Rattata in the area. They make their nests almost anywhere and as extreme omnivores eat anything they can scavenge. A Rattata`s fangs grow continuously throughout its lifespan, so it whittles them down to a comfortable size by gnawing on hard objects.</description>
<picture>64416.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="64" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="10">1.31</rating>
<name>Ratta</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Raticate, known as the Mouse Pokémon, is a larger and stronger form that Rattata takes when it gains enough experience. In the main Pokémon game series, a Raticate is only acquired when a Rattata grows past experience level 20 and is evolved into a Raticate. Compared to a Rattata, a Raticate is far more of a predator, and the majority of its features are adapted for this purpose. Its whiskers give it balance and it slows down if they are cut off. Its webbed feet allow it to swim as it hunts prey, and its fangs are tough enough to topple concrete buildings.</description>
<picture>64415.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="160" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="10">10.00</rating>
<name>Raichuu</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Raichu is a taller, potbellied form that Pikachu takes when he is given a thunder stone, causing its tail to grow long and black with a lightning bolt on the end and fur to turn orange. It also has a white underbelly, brown stripes on its back, and yellow cheeks, in contrast to Pikachu`s red cheeks and Pichu`s pink cheeks. In the main Pokemon game series, a Raichu is only acquired when an item called a Thunderstone is applied to a Pikachu so that it evolves into a Raichu. Raichu can only learn moves in the Pikachu stage, so the only way to make Raichu learn more moves is by using a TM. Raichu can generate 10,000 or even 100,000 volts of electricity, enough to knock out Pokemon several times its size, such as a Dragonite, as stated in the anime. Raichu`s name is a portmanteau of the kanji 雷 rai, meaning thunder, or lightning bolt, and chuu, which is the Japanese onomatopoeia for a mouse`s squeak.</description>
<picture>64418.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="161" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="34">9.37</rating>
<name>Sand</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sandshrew are a species of brick-skinned mouse-like Pokémon found in several regions throughout the Pokémon world. Despite its name, Sandshrew`s appearance borrows more from the armadillo or the pangolin than from the shrew; its primary means of defense when threatened is to instantly curl up its body into a ball, leaving only its tough skin exposed. When it is rolled up like this, Sandshrew has the potential to withstand many attacks, as well as being dropped from a great height (also similar to hedgehogs). Sandshrew`s natural environment is deep underground in arid, sandy locations with very little moisture, such as a desert. It chooses this habitat to keep its hide as dry and tough as possible, while the sand also provides it with good camouflage.
In keeping with its physical characteristics, Sandshrew has high Defense in the video games, but low Speed. From Ruby and Sapphire onwards, it has the ability Sand Veil, which increases its evasion during a sandstorm. Sandshrew also appears in the spin-off game Pokémon Snap.
A Sandshrew owned by A.J. is featured in the eighth anime episode, "The Path to the Pokémon League." It had many notable traits, such as the ability to withstand water and its knowledge of Fissure, which it used to dispatch Team Rocket.</description>
<picture>64420.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="162" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="24">7.68</rating>
<name>Sandpan</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sandslash are a larger and stronger form that Sandshrew take when they gain enough experience to reach level 22. Generally they are a moderately large, bipedal hedgehog or pangolin-like creature with hard yellow skin, lengthy claws, and a back loaded with an assemblage of large brown spikes. These spikes are hardened sections of Sandslash`s hide that grow to form a natural self-defense when Sandslash curls into a ball. Each spike remains on Sandslash for one year, after which it falls off and a new spike grows in its place. Sandslash can be found in desert areas, particularly close to dry forests. Sandslash`s spikes serve a number of purposes to help cope with its environment, such as providing shade to protect it from the sun and heatstroke or using them offensively to harm both predators and prey. It uses its claws to climb trees, cut up food and dig, the latter being an activity that can cause them to break if done too quickly. It cannot run very quickly, but it is very quick with its claws.</description>
<picture>64419.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="164" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="11">3.20</rating>
<name>Nidorina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nidorina are a larger and stronger form that female Nidoran take when they gain enough experience. In the main Pokémon game series, a Nidorina can be found as wild Pokémon in the Kanto and Johto regions of the Pokémon world, and it can also be acquired when a female Nidoran grows past experience level 16 and is evolved into a Nidorina.</description>
<picture>242948.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="167" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="9">3.20</rating>
<name>Nidorino</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nidorino are a larger and stronger form that male Nidoran take when they gain enough experience. Nidorino look somewhat like a rhinoceros and a rabbit with needles and horns covering its body. Nidorino is more aggressive than male Nidoran and is quick to attack when it notices a threat; its large ears are always on the lookout. The diamond-hard horn on its head secretes a powerful venom and on impact with an enemy, poison leaks out. If it senses a hostile presence, all the barbs on its back bristle up. Nidorino is the male counterpart of Nidorina.
In the main Pokémon game series, a Nidorino can be found as wild Pokémon in the Kanto and Johto regions of the Pokémon world, and it can also be acquired when a male Nidoran grows past experience level 16 and is evolved into a Nidorino. It is also notable for being one of the first two Pokémon seen in the anime and in the intro to the game Pokémon Red.</description>
<picture>242951.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="168" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="12">7.27</rating>
<name>Nidoking</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nidoking are a fully grown and developed species of male possum-like Pokémon and the final stage in the male Nidoran evolutionary line. Its horn is hard enough to pierce a diamond and contains secreted venom, making it a powerful stabbing tool upon prey and Pokémon battle opponents. Nidoking have immense upper-body strength, being able to snap a telephone pole like it were a twig. It uses its tail to smash down its target, then constrict it to break its bones. Its thick tail packs enormously destructive power capable of toppling a metal transmission tower.
As several Pokémon seem to have been designed to resemble other aspects of Japanese pop culture and mythology, it is interesting to note that Nidoking bears a resemblance to Baragon, a monster that has appeared in the Godzilla movie series.
In the main Pokémon game series, a Nidoking can only be acquired when a Moon Stone item is applied to a Nidorino so that the creature is evolved into a Nidoking. They are the masculine equivalent to Nidoqueen. Also, they are more primal, fighting other Nidoking for such matters as territory or food. (Or a Nidoqueen, in mating season.)</description>
<picture>242952.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="177" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="23">9.04</rating>
<name>Nazonokusa</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Oddish are a weed-like Pokémon found in all regions throughout the Pokémon world. (with the exception of Pokémon Blue and Pokémon Leaf Green) Oddish looks like a small animated onion/turnip plant with a rounded body. Its body is blue or purple with two small feet and red eyes. On top of its head grows a large clump of 5 long green blades of grass. Its name likely came from the words "odd" and "radish".
Oddish is a nocturnal Pokémon, using moonlight rather than the sun`s rays for photosynthesis. During the day, Oddish avoids the sun`s heat and brightness by burying itself into the earth, leaving only the leaves on top of its head visible above ground. In this way it disguises itself as a plant, misdirecting its carnivorous diurnal predators.
While buried, Oddish nourishes itself by absorbing nutrients from the soil using its feet, which are said to temporarily change into a root-like structure for this purpose.
Oddish has been known to use its leaves as hands, such as one who used this to climb a rope net and tried to fly like a Hoppip.
If anyone pulls at Oddish`s leaves and tries to uproot it while it is buried underground, Oddish will react by shrieking in a cute, high-pitched voice. This mirrors the behavior of the legendary mandrake in a similar situation, although it seems that Oddish`s squeaks do not have the same dire consequences as a mandrake`s.</description>
<picture>242959.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="184" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="17">3.20</rating>
<name>Digda</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Diglett is a basic mole-like creature that can be found only in Diglett`s Cave. Capable of burrowing at the speed of sound, it thrives in dark underground caves since exposure to bright light can weaken it. The burrow and excretions left by a Diglett, rather like those of a real-life earthworm, keep the soil aerated and fertile. For this reason, Diglett are prized by farmers.
The mysterious feet or hands of Diglett are unknown of what they look like, for the fact that Diglett can use moves such as slash and fury swipes. Only the head of a Diglett can be seen popping out of the ground.</description>
<picture>64422.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="185" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="17">3.27</rating>
<name>Dugtrio</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dugtrio is a large and faster evolution of Diglett. Dugtrio consists of three Diglett together. Dugtrio can be found in the wild in Diglett`s Cave and can be obtained when a Diglett grows to level 26.
Like its pre-evolved form Diglett, Dugtrio`s feet have never been seen. People have only seen a Dugtrio`s head(s).</description>
<picture>64421.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="222" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="35">4.03</rating>
<name>Golduck</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Golduck are large bipedal ducks, with blue skin and strong, webbed appendages that given them the ability to swim at high speeds. Due to their bluish color and webbed hands and feet, Golduck are sometimes mistaken for Kappa. They have more formidable psychic powers than the Psyduck they evolve from, and they lose the headaches that they constantly suffer from. The gem on their heads glows when they use psychic powers as well as when they swim at full speed.
They live in fresh-water lakes and rivers, where they are seen gracefully swimming, especially at dusk. As the fastest swimmers out of all Pokémon, they can out swim even the most athletic of humans, though they often train with swimmers. As they are able to swim in severe storms, they are sometimes found rescuing people lost at sea from danger.</description>
<picture>242967.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="223" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="10">7.27</rating>
<name>Mankey</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mankey is a basic fighting type monkey Pokémon have a round, pig like snout that can be found in the grassy areas of Kanto and Johto. It is usually calm and somewhat mischievous, but if it gets angry it can be very dangerous.
In the anime series, a Mankey stole Ash Ketchum`s trademark red cap. After chasing the Mankey for a while, it evolved into a Primeape which Ash then caught.</description>
<picture>242968.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="230" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Nyoromo</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Poliwag is a basic tadpole Pokémon that is found by fishing or surfing in several water areas in Kanto and Johto. Poliwag have blue skin. The swirl on the stomach is semi-transparent, and the insides are visible through it, and is often used to hypnotize enemies.
In the anime, Misty obtained a Poliwag during the Orange Islands saga, which evolved into Poliwhirl and then Politoed.</description>
<picture>242972.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="325" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="18">3.20</rating>
<name>Madatsubomi</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bellsprout is a carnivorous, flower-like Pokémon, hunting small insects with blinding agility despite its skinny body. It is said to ensnare its prey in its vines and devour it, and can also spit a highly corrosive fluid that can melt even iron. Bellsprout`s preferred habitat is warm and humid climates, since it can absorb more moisture from the ground by planting its root-like feet. In battle, Bellsprout can take advantage of its flexibility to bend and sway its way out of the range of its opponent`s attacks, no matter how powerful they may be.
In the video games, Bellsprout is commonly found among grassy routes, and is used by many Trainers who favor the Grass-type. In Pokémon Gold, Silver, and Crystal, the Sprout Tower in Violet City is dedicated to Bellsprout.
Bellsprout has appeared numerous times in the anime series, most notably in "The Fourth Round Rumble," where Ash battled one during the Indigo League. He eventually defeated it with Muk.</description>
<picture>242979.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="328" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="30">2.20</rating>
<name>Menokurage</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tentacool (メノクラゲ, Menokurage?) is an aquatic Pokémon based on the box jellyfish. It drifts aimlessly wherever the ocean currents take it, sometimes ending up in shallow waters where it may be accidentally caught in fishing lines. Tentacool may also end up stuck on beaches when low tide comes; since its body is largely composed of water, it will shrivel up, risking death from dehydration if it stays out of the sea for too long. Tentacool has two main weapons. At the tips of its tentacles are toxic feelers, which it uses to stab anything it touches with stinging acid. Due to its excellent camouflage in the water, Tentacool can often remain undetected by swimmers right up to the moment it stings them. Tentacool`s gelatinous, watery body can also absorb sunlight and refract it within, producing beam energy it shoots from its crystal-like eyes.
Tentacool is available in all Pokémon games to date. It is extremely common, especially while surfing on sea routes, and is in almost every single body of water.
In the anime, Tentacool was featured in the episode "Tentacool and Tentacruel" in which a raging mob of the titular Pokémon attacked the Porta Vista resort. The episode was banned after the attacks on September 11, 2001 due to its scenes depicting Tentacools and Tentacruels destroying buildings at a seaside resort.</description>
<picture>242982.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="339" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="33">6.04</rating>
<name>Coil</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Magnemite is almost more of a machine than a creature, as it is a solid ball of metal with a pair of horseshoe magnets on either side, as well as a single, lidless eye. It has a pair of screws protruding from below the eye, and a large screw forming a sort of "cap" on top of its head.
It floats through the air, through a sort of electromagnetic antigravity field generated by the two magnets on either side of its body. When defending itself in the wild or fighting in a Pokémon battle at the orders of a Pokémon trainer, it can also generate powerful electric shocks. Magnemite consumes electricity, so they`re attracted to power lines and electronic gadgets. Magnemite tend to crowd around generators and power plants, and an individual Magnemite might be attracted to someone with a pocket radio or a Pokégear.
Despite their mechanical appearance, lack of gender, and alien tendencies, Magnemite are living things; they are not built, they feel the need to eat, and they have something similar to a mating urge. A trio of Magnemite may come together to create their evolved form, Magneton.</description>
<picture>242984.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="340" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="11">3.20</rating>
<name>Rarecoil</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Magneton is composed of 3 Magnemite linked together by a strong magnetic force. It levitates on an electromagnetic anti-gravity field like its pre-evolution, Magnemite. Its electromagnetic powers are so strong that it has been known to cause total blackouts in cities in which it gathers.</description>
<picture>242985.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="344" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="7">1.17</rating>
<name>Pawou</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Seel are well suited to life in the most frigid reaches of the planet. They are nocturnal; in the daytime they are seen asleep on the seabed in shallow water. When hunting, Seel stay in the ocean because they cannot walk on land. Instead, they swim in a rather graceful fashion literally underneath sheets of ice floating on the water`s surface in their environment in search of their prey. Even though the air is a frigid 14 degrees Fahrenheit and the water itself is a somewhat less chilling 40 degrees, their fur hides are thick enough to insulate Seel from either degree of cold and their nostrils automatically close by themselves to ensure their ability to remain underwater. When they need to take in air, they will use their hard horns to punch holes through the ice sheet above and pop their heads out.</description>
<picture>242988.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="345" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Jugon</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dewgong`s name is derived from the real animal which has a similar, but much larger, body: the dugong. In the beta versions of Red/Blue, Dewgong`s name was originally going to be Manaty, a reference to the manatee. The Pokémon first appears in the arsenal of a trainer named "Allison" outside of Saffron City, who cites her similar body fat percentage as a reason for her choosing to utilize the Water/Ice type Pokémon.</description>
<picture>242989.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="363" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="35">5.07</rating>
<name>Biriridama</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Voltorb are aggressive red and white ball shaped Pokémon that looks strikingly similar to a Poké Ball. Coincidently it was discovered shortly after Poké Balls were invented, some believe there is a connection. Though roughly ten times larger, many trainers get a surprise when they pick one up thinking it is a Poké Ball. The strength of their explosions is dependent on how much electricity they store in their bodies. When jarred or angered, a Voltorb can and will explode, causing massive damage to their aggressor and themselves (as seen in the video games when they use the moves `Self-Destruct` or `Explosion`, both of which causes fainting to the user). It is so unstable that even the slightest bump in the road will make it explode spontaneously. Voltorb do not have a mouth, but do have two eyes that are normally slanted into an aggressive or angry stare.</description>
<picture>242998.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="366" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Marumine</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Electrode is a red and white ball shaped Pokémon that looks strikingly similar to a Pokéball with its colors reversed (white on top and red on bottom instead of red on top and white on bottom, like Voltorb). They are known to explode at the slightest shock and without warning. Electrodes feed on and stores electricity from power plants and lightning storms, but rarely do they use it to attack foes. It instead uses its stored electric to increase its rolling speed. The amount of electricity in an Electrode is relative to how powerful its explosions are. The stored energy also generates strong static electricity around Electrode`s body, sometimes paralyzing enemies on contact. If it is bored, it often amuses itself by exploding. Electrode has two beady eyes and an almost nonstop grin.</description>
<picture>242999.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="381" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="16">8.07</rating>
<name>Sihorn</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rhyhorn is a rhinoceros like Pokemon with a rock like hide consisting of plates. Ryhorn stands on all four legs and evolves into Rhydon. Rhyhorn is a portmanteau of rhinoceros (which it resembles) and horn. Its spelling is also influenced by the rock rhyolite. Its Japanese name is a portmanteau of sai (犀), meaning rhinoceros and horn (ホーン). Rhyhorn are easily angered and will not hesitate to charge at what ever or who ever angered it. Rhyhorn are powerful enough to topple buildings with their tackle. Rhyhorn are prime examples of "more brawn than brains", as they often charge head first into things but forget why. In Gold, Silver, and Crystal, Brock uses a Rhyhorn to battle. There is also a Rhyhorn in the Brock Gym Leader set of the trading card game.</description>
<picture>243006.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="428" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Tattu</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Horsea`s name comes from an inverting of the parts of the compound word seahorse. It is also a pun on the word "Horsey" but is spelled "horsea" because of its habitat. Its Japanese name seems to be derived from 辰 tatsu, the zodiac dragon.</description>
<picture>243010.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="429" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Seadra</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Seadra`s name is simply a shortening of "Sea Dragon", although there is a speculation it may have derived from Hydra, a mythic creature.</description>
<picture>243011.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="434" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="13">8.07</rating>
<name>Starmie</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Starmie is an aquatic starfish Pokémon that evolves from Staryu through use of a Water Stone. It moves through the water by spinning its star-shaped body in a manner like that of a propeller. It consists of two five-point, purple star-shaped structures superimposed on top of each other. At its center is a large gem, surrounded by a golden crest like structure. Starmie`s center section - the gem - is known as its "core". This gem is considered very valuable among collectors. The gem`s hue can change to any color in the visual spectrum, earning Starmie the nickname "the gem of the sea". When Starmie is weak, the core grows dim and starts flickering whilst producing distinctive warning sounds.
In the Pokémon world, the aforementioned peculiar properties of Starmie`s anatomy leads some people to theorize that Starmie`s origins are not of this planet, and that its luminescent core is used to send electromagnetic signals into outer space. It may have some connection with Deoxys having a similar core and the ability to regenerate. In ancient times, Starmie was attributed an equally mystical origin: that it was created from the reflection of the stars upon the waves at night.
In the anime, Starmie is one of the Pokémon used in Misty`s team during the most of the Kanto arc, along with its pre-evolved form, Staryu. Misty also often used Starmie outside of battle for transportation through water or for fire-fighting purposes. Misty eventually left Starmie in the care of her sisters at the Cerulean City Gym, and later reobtained it upon her return.</description>
<picture>243015.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="444" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="64">7.09</rating>
<name>Koiking</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Magikarp is a commonly found Pokémon that can survive in rivers, lakes,and oceans. Despite its adaptability, the Pokédex states that the Magikarp species has grown weaker over time, and it is one of the least viable for battling in the series. It eventually evolves into another, far more powerful Pokémon, Gyarados.
Magikarp is commonly thought of as the weakest Pokémon. They are only able to learn three moves: Splash (does absolutely nothing), Tackle (a weak attack), and Flail (which does more damage as Magikarp is more damaged.)
In the anime, Magikarp has appeared several times, most notably as the subject of a running gag in which a salesman attempts to trick Team Rocket into buying Magikarp in various guises. (This man also appears in Pokémon Red, Blue, Yellow, FireRed, and LeafGreen.) Team Rocket later adopted a Magikarp-shaped submarine.
Magikarp also appear many times in the video games. They can be found in almost any pond, river, lake, or sea. Many trainers have them, along with other weak Water Pokémon like Goldeen or Horsea. In Pokémon Pearl, one trainer named "Ander," found outside Lake Valor, possesses a Magikarp whose move "Quake" replaces the normal Magikarp`s equally useless "Splash".</description>
<picture>243021.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="447" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="14">9.04</rating>
<name>Laplace</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lapras is a dual-type Water/Ice Pokémon introduced in Generation I.
While it is not known to evolve into or from any other Pokémon, it has a Gigantamax form.
Lapras is a large sea Pokémon that resembles a plesiosaur. It has a blue hide with darker blue spots and a cream-colored underside. It has large brown eyes, a short horn on its forehead, and tightly curled ears. It has a long neck and four flippers. The foremost flippers are larger than the hind. On its back is a heavy, gray shell covered in blunt knobs.
Lapras is a gentle, helpful Pokémon that enjoys ferrying people across bodies of water. In the past, its docility made it an easy target for hunters, and it was driven to near-extinction. Recent protection efforts have seen Lapras become overabundant instead, which is now affecting the fish Pokémon numbers in some areas. An intelligent Pokémon, it is able to understand human speech. Lapras have been known to travel in large pods across the seas, spanning both polar and tropical areas. To keep in touch with other of its kind, it sings enchanting melodies. In the anime it was shown that Lapras is able to develop psychic abilities such as telepathy.
As Gigantamax Lapras, it becomes larger in size and more armored. Its shell resembles a cruise ship with four gray and red stripes surrounding it, and it has four spikes on top of its shell with one steel spike resembling a funnel, which has three red clouds surrounding it. The sclera in Lapras` eyes change colors to white, yellow, and blue. A light blue ring of fine thin lines resembling a musical sheet created from ice particles circles around its shell.
5,000 people can ride on the shell of Gigantamax Lapras for a very comfortable ride without any issues. Lapras can use it giant ring to break any icebergs that may prevent it from swimming.
Gigantamax Lapras is the only known Pokémon capable of using the exclusive G-Max Move G-Max Resonance.</description>
<picture>68374.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="450" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Showers</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vaporeon is one of the evolutions of Eevee that is caused by radiation from a water stone. Upon evolving, it gains fins and gills that give it the ability to live underwater. It has small scales that are hard to see. Its finned tail is similar to a mermaid`s, so it is often mistaken for one. Vaporeon`s cells are similar in structure to water molecules, and this allows it to have a unique control over the water around it. This includes being able to transform itself into liquid as a form of camouflage (this being portrayed in the games as its ability to learn the attack Acid Armor), and detect rain through subtle vibrations in its fins. Its base scale color is aqua with darker aqua that makes a line along the spine from the tail to the neck where it forms into a base for its white frill. A darker-aqua patch on the head is similar in shape to a diving cap, and upon the head are three yellow fins, two resembling ears, and the middle one, a Dorsal fin. Its ability is `Water Absorb`, which allows it to gain HP when struck with a water type move.</description>
<picture>243023.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="542" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="11">3.20</rating>
<name>Otachi</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sentret is a very cautious Pokémon, it raises itself up onto its tail to get a better view of its surroundings. While standing on its tail, it can see a long way. If it spots an enemy, it will cry out loudly to warn its kind. It will also hit the ground with its tail. A Sentret will only sleep when another one is standing guard. The Sentret will wake the others at the first sign of danger. Because of this, if one is separated from its pack, then it will be unable to sleep due to fear.
Sentret is based on a squirrel.</description>
<picture>243047.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="543" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="14">7.27</rating>
<name>Ootachi</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Furret live in colonies with tunnels much too small for normal Pokemon to traverse, yet it is a perfect fit for the slim build of Furret as it hides from the outside world at the surface by traversing through these tunnels like gophers. These tunnel colonies become very complex, especially if they are very deep, and can potentially stretch for miles. Occasionally, these colonies are found intertwined with Diglett colonies. The Furret evolves from Sentret at level 15.
Furret`s rudimentary paws and legs are deceptively nimble, making Furret a quick, unpredictable predator especially skillful at hunting Rattata, its main prey. Also, the fur of the Pokemon is thicker than it appears, and Furret can fluff up its fur to make itself look much stronger and larger than it actually is as an intimidation tactic towards potential foes.
Furret is based on a ferret or squirrel.</description>
<picture>243048.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="545" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Hoho</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hoothoot is one of two owl Pokémon. Hoothoot seems to have one foot. However, it actually has two feet; at least one is retracted against its body at almost all times, and Hoothoot can switch between one foot and the other at speeds almost too fast for the human eye. Hoothoot are also known for having precise senses of time, due to a special mechanism in their brain that measures the rotation of the earth. Properly trained, they can be more accurate than all but the most precise of clocks. In nature, they always begin hooting at the same time every night.</description>
<picture>243049.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="547" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Rediba</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ledyba has a red thorax (ladybug) with black spots, a cream-coloured underbelly, six legs and two black antennae. By itself a Ledyba is very timid, to the point of being afraid to move. When Ledyba become part of a swarm, they become much more active and can cluster next to each other for warmth in cold weather. A Ledyba communicates with others through an aromatic fluid excreted from the points where its legs meet its thorax. By subtly changing the fluid`s scent, the Ledyba can convey a number of different feelings. The fluid can also help to determine a Ledyba`s location as well as its current feelings.
Ledyba is based on a ladybug.</description>
<picture>243051.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="549" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="6">9.04</rating>
<name>Itomaru</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Spinarak is a six legged spider-like Pokémon with a marking on its back that is similar to a face. It spins a web of fine silk and then waits patiently and with complete motionlessness until prey, such as a bug Pokémon, becomes ensnared in the sticky web. It then waits until nightfall, at which point Spinarak prepares and then devours the prey. The web can be called Spinarak`s "second nervous system" because the Pokémon is able to determine the type of prey that has become trapped simply through the vibrations that are created.
In the anime, there is a small town whose police force uses Spinarak to fight crime, honoring a Spinarak that had caught a criminal called the black arachnid in the past. This was shown in the episode Spinarak attack.</description>
<picture>243053.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="552" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Chonchie</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chinchou has a small blue body and two antennae sprouting from its head, both of which have a yellow globe at the end. These antennae are said to have evolved from fins. A Chinchou`s eyes are yellow and their pupils have the shape of plus signs. When blinking or closing its eyes, only the vertical parts close, making the pupils look like minus signs. Its habitat is the dark depths of the ocean floor. In the absence of any other light, Chinchou sees its surroundings and communicates by shooting positive and negative charged electricity particles between the tips of its antennae, creating an electric current and thus light. This can be said to be a form of bioluminescence. The charges Chinchou shoots between its antennae can also be used offensively, to stun its opponents with a flash of light or shock them with electricity.</description>
<picture>243056.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="553" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="9">3.84</rating>
<name>Lantern</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lanturn uses the bright part of its body, which gradually evolved from a dorsal fin, to lure prey. Given the nickname "deep-sea star", the light it emits is so bright that it can illuminate the sea`s surface from a depth of over 3 miles. It uses this light to attract and blind prey, and then swallow the immobilized prey in a single gulp. The light is also useful for Lanturn to navigate through the deep, murky waters. The light from its antenna is produced by bacterial symbiosis. Bioluminescent bacteria in Lanturn`s antenna cause a chemical reaction with Lanturn`s bodily fluids to create the bright light.</description>
<picture>243057.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="562" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Merriep</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mareep are blue skinned sheep or lamb-like creatures which have long, striped tails with a yellow ball at the tip. Their fleece is yellow, while their bodies are a dark blue color. Their ears are a rounded cone shape and channel the electricity that they keep in their fleece. Mareep are said to build up a stockpile of static electricity by rubbing the fluffy woolen fleece on their body, with that of other Mareep. The electricity is then stored in their fleece, and will shock predators on contact. The more electricity that is stored, the brighter the ball on the tip of a Mareep`s tail is thought to glow. In summer, the fleece is fully shed, but would grow back within a week. Mareep also are thought to store air in the fleece, enabling it to control its body temperature whatever the weather.</description>
<picture>243064.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="564" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Mokoko</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Flaaffy is the evolution of Mareep. Flaaffy is dark pink in color. Its fleece is white, and it grows over the top half of its body and its head. It has black stripes on its ears and its long tail, and it has small, beady eyes that look like black dots. It has a blue ball on the tip of its tail. Flaaffy usually likes to sit upright, although it can stand on two legs if necessary. Its wool quality changes as it matures so that it can generate a high amount of strong static electricity while still having a small amount of wool. Its bare, electric-resistant, parts of its hides enable it to prevent electrocution. As a result of storing too much, it develops patches even where wool won`t grow.</description>
<picture>243065.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="566" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="15">5.12</rating>
<name>Kireihana</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bellossom is a diurnal plant Pokémon. It evolves from Gloom if exposed to a Sun Stone. Bellossom`s petals can rotate, and they usually do when it is absorbing sunlight. The color of their leaves vary from a sickly brown and gray to a fluorescent yellow and red, depending on how much sunlight it has absorbed in the past few hours. When its petals are moving, either due to rotating or dancing, they rub together to make relaxing, bell-like sounds. The petals on its head also create a sweet scent.
It is also noted that a Bellossom will be even more beautiful if it was an especially rancid Gloom. The worse it smells as a Gloom, the prettier its petals will be as a Bellossom. Although naturally a peaceful and friendly Pokémon, it can be very territorial and violent fights can break out if there is an intruder or a challenger. Despite this, it is very social in areas outside of its self-determined territory, and the most common time to find a group of Bellossom together is when they all meet in one location to dance. It is said that these dances summon the sun.
Its Japanese name, "Kireihana", translates to "Beautiful" (kirei) and "Flower" (hana).</description>
<picture>243066.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="589" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Hanecco</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hoppip are small, spherical creatures, with long leaves protruding from their head. They have small, gripping feet and ears disproportionate to their body, used to listen for winds. Hoppip have extremely petite and almost weightless bodies, and are susceptible to strong winds due to this. When a Hoppip feels a gale approaching, it will lock the leaves on its head with the leaves of other Hoppip, in an attempt to avoid being blown away. If a Hoppip is by itself when in heavy winds, it may grip the ground with its feet to prevent this. Despite the dangers Hoppip face in strong winds, they enjoy gentle breezes and can float in the calmest of winds, which can carry them across vast distances.</description>
<picture>243071.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="601" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Upah</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wooper are similar to Axolotl. They are light teal-colored Pokémon with round feet, no arms, and a long tail. Their simplistic face consists of mainly of a large mouth, primarily while open. They have purplish barbed antennae on the sides of their head. Three purple, though sometimes shaded blue or pink, gills are on its stomach. Wooper will usually live in cold water: however, they occasionally come out onto land in search of food. When doing so, they coat their bodies with slimy, poisonous film. Touching the slime with bare hands will cause a shooting pain. Male Wooper have two barbs on their antennae, while female Wooper have one barb. Males also have larger gills.</description>
<picture>243078.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="602" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Nuoh</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Quagsire has an appearance and habitat similar to that of a giant salamander. Quagsire live a carefree life in muddy ponds and rivers. It acts oblivious to its environment, accidentally bumping its head on the hulls of boats and bottoms of whatever body of water it swims in as it swims, but seeming not to care. Quagsire always bear an absent-looking facial expression. This is likely due to Quagsire`s easy-going nature. It hunts by staying still in the water with its mouth open, waiting for small prey to swim into its mouth. It doesn`t move, and therefore, doesn`t get hungry. It`s not uncommon that a fishermen`s hook will get caught in the gaping mouth of a feeding Quagsire. Trying to eat what it has caught, the Quagsire would try to swallow, and end up pulling the fishermen off his boat and into the water. Male Quagsire have larger fins on their backs. They wait at the bottom of lakes waiting for prey to wander into its mouth. It also loves eating cherries.</description>
<picture>243079.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="620" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Nokocchi</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dunsparce is a land snake based on the tsuchinoko, a legendary snake-like cryptid from Japan. It has a yellow hourglass shaped body, two tiny wings on its sides, a drill for a tail, and two spikes under its chin. Its underbelly is blue, as well as the markings on its back. Dunsparce lives in caves and deep underground in nests of complex design. Its rudimentary wings enable it to hover just above the ground, providing it with an alternate method of motion besides crawling. Despite these wings and bug-like appearance, Dunsparce is solely a normal type Pokémon.</description>
<picture>243089.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="626" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Harysen</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Qwilfish is a porcupinefish-like fish that has a round body with many toxin-containing spikes and a teardrop-shaped tail. The spikes give it trouble swimming, but it also has defensive measures against predators. Qwilfish can swallow large quantities of water in very short notice, causing itself to inflate to a much larger size, which it uses to intimidate larger opponents. If the opponent isn`t scared, Qwilfish uses the pressure of the water it swallowed to shoot out its toxic spikes at, thus weakening, the opponent.</description>
<picture>243093.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="633" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Himeguma</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Teddiursa is a bear cub, resembling a teddy bear more than a real bear. Teddiursa have a crescent mark on their forehead, which grows (both in thickness and in circumference) as the Pokémon ages. Once the crescent fully closes into a circle, the Teddiursa is ready to evolve into an Ursaring. Teddiursa, although an omnivore, has a diet that almost exclusively consists of honey. It makes its own honey out of fruit and pollen from Beedrill. It lets the honey soak in its paws, making it often lick its paws.</description>
<picture>243096.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="634" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Ringuma</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ursaring is a large (although arboreal) bear with a yellow ring on its stomach. Ursaring eats food obtained from digging deep underground as well as berries from trees. Ursaring can hibernate through an entire winter without any food. Ursaring`s sense of smell is among the most developed of all Pokémon; it can detect subtle differences in scents. For this reason, Ursaring is sometimes used by police in the Pokémon universe, both as a strong enforcer, and as an explosive-sniffing Pokémon. If criminals are hiding in trees, it can use its claws to cut down the tree.
Its Japanese name, "Ringuma", originates from "ring" (ringu) and "bear" (kuma). In the anime, Ursaring is caught by Paul, after it is angered by Turtwig.</description>
<picture>243097.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="832" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Donfan</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Donphan is an armored elephant-like Pokémon that can easily take normal attacks without receiving a scratch. Its large, sharp tusks that take long to grow serve as a status symbol in their herds. It is very strong; as it is able to easily haul dump trucks and demolish houses by tackling them. This strength is often used to clear rock and mud slides that block trails. Its favorite attack is the "Rollout", where it curls into a ball and charges at high speeds, though it is hard for it to stop.
Its stats in the video games are reasonably good; its attack and defense have a base stat of 120. It can learn Fire Fang, Thunder Fang, Ice Shard, Earthquake, and Rock Polish among other useful attacks.</description>
<picture>243110.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="834" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="8">7.27</rating>
<name>Odoshishi</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Stantler is a Pokémon with large, curved antlers. These antlers change the flow of the air, causing the space around them to act as a distorted reality, and leaving other beings around the Stantler confused and lost in their senses. This allows it to create hallucinations to aid it in battle or allow it to escape. The antlers are considered art in the Pokémon world, causing the Stantler to almost be hunted to extinction as the trading market of the antlers reached very high prices. The orbs on fallen antlers is often grounded up to a powder that helps people sleep. Stantler`s name is derived from stag, meaning a male deer, and antler, referring to the horn-like growths on its head.</description>
<picture>243112.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="843" type="main character in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="16">8.63</rating>
<name>Raikou</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Raikou is one of the three "Legendary Beasts" that are featured in Pokémon Gold, Silver, and Crystal. According to legend, the Legendary Beasts were reincarnated by Ho-Oh from the spirits of three Pokémon which died in the fire that gave Burnt Tower its name. They are awakened in this tower in their first appearance. Another myth maintains that Raikou descended to earth together with a lightning bolt. Each Beast personifies a force of nature - Raikou, in particular, embodies the speed of lightning.
Like many Electric-type Pokémon, Raikou stores tremendous energy inside its body. This grants it extraordinary vitality, allowing it to run continuously across the land while shooting off electricity from the rain cloud that is on its back. Raikou`s roar is aptly described as "thunderous": it is loud enough to create shock waves and shake the ground as if actual thunder had struck.
Raikou is featured in a special anime episode called Raikou - The Legend of Thunder that forms the first three episodes of Pokémon Chronicles. In the special, two Team Rocket agents named Attila and Hun scheme to capture Raikou with a device that reflects and deflects energy blasts. Three New Bark Town trainers risk their own lives to try and save Raikou. It is thought by the trainers that Raikou attempts to guard other electric Pokémon from danger whenever possible.</description>
<picture>243121.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2614" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="2">7.72</rating>
<name>Bashou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hun is a member of Team Rocket. He appeared along with his partner, Attila, in "The Legend of Thunder!".
Like the other Rocket duos, his and his partner`s names together form the name of a famous historical villain, in this case, Attila the Hun.
Hun and Attila both seem somewhat set in their rank, and approach missions casually. They seem to be able to keep their cool even when they lose; even in these situations, they calmly retreat. Despite physical stereotypes, Hun is the dominant partner telling Attila to do things that he could do himself. Attila doesn`t object or show any signs of aggravation over this role.
Attila has no recorded history with his partner Hun though, while the dub states that they are new partners, their body language and the familiarity of the behavior towards each other shows that they do have some history together.
The pair takes mission orders from Professor Sebastian, but it is implied in the original that they have never met him before "The Legend of Thunder!". Still, in the dub, he seems to have some kind of friendship with the professor.
Hun was male in the original Japanese version. However, his gender was controversially changed to female in the English dubbed version. Closer analysis showed that Hun was never referred to as a female (but he has long hair and bangs, a feminine hairstyle in some countries). The only pronouns are those used collectively with Attila, such as "those men" or "those guys". So, Hun may just be a male with a female voice. In the Brazilian version, however, Hun was referred to as ela and dela. Likewise, in the European Portuguese he is named Ana, which is a name that usually is given to woman.</description>
<picture>17968.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2615" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="2">7.72</rating>
<name>Buson</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Attila is a member of Team Rocket. He appeared along with his partner, Hun, in "The Legend of Thunder!".
Attila and Hun both seem somewhat set in their rank, and approach missions casually. They seem to be keep their cool even when they lose. Even in these situations, they beat a calm retreat. Despite physical stereotypes, Hun is the dominant partner, telling Attila to do things that he could do himself. Attila doesn`t object, or show any signs of aggravation over this role. One particular event where Attila loses his temper is when he finds that Marina has called for help. He yells through her PokéGear, causing Vincent and Jimmy on the other end to nearly fall over, and then smashes it.
Attila has no recorded history with his partner Hun though, while the dub states that they are new partners, their body language and the familiarity of the behaviour towards each other shows that they do have history together.
The pair takes mission orders from Professor Sebastian, but it is implied in the Japanese dub that they have never met him before.</description>
<picture>17969.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2628" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<name>Shiranui-hakase</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Professor Sebastian is a member of Team Rocket who has appeared in several episodes of the Pokémon anime.
He appeared in "The Legend of Thunder!", and later on in the main series during "Talkin` `Bout an Evolution" and "Rage of Innocence".
Every occasion he is seen by the viewer, he remains calm and talks with a steady even tone. As he is only seen in moments of scientific importance and victory, it cannot be said if this demeanor carries over to every situation, or if this behavior has been modulated to the scientific environment and all business that stems from there on in.
Some within fanon speculate that he might be the most powerful Rocket scientist. Not taking in other issues, one can say that he has spent an impressive amount time working for the group.
He works with Tyson and gives commands to Hun and Attila. Tyson seems to hold at least his scientific mind in great regard. As Hun, Attila, and Tyson are of the same rank, Sebastian might work with agents of their rank often.
He is in charge of a sizeable crew of scientists, and they seem to work on a variety of things. He is known for the creation of the crystal system that traps Electric-type Pokémon with their own power and a beam that forces Pokémon to evolve.
The origin of his Japanese name is probably after the sword style Shiranui-ryu. Humorously, Jessie refers to him as "pointy" when she meets him.</description>
<picture>17981.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="601" picture="165793.jpg">Nakamura Hidetoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8804" type="appears in" update="2011-01-15">
<name>Betbeton (Buson)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Attila`s Muk was sent out to help assist Attila`s Steelix capture Raikou. After the Crystal system was heavily damaged, it retreated with Attila.</description>
<picture>56400.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8818" type="appears in" update="2011-01-15">
<name>Haganeil (Bashou)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hun`s Steelix was sent out to battle Jimmy and Marina while Hun and Attila attempted to complete their capture of Raikou. During Hun`s Steelix first encounter with Marina, her Misdreavus managed to disable it with Perish Song causing it to be unable to battle.</description>
<picture>56404.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8821" type="appears in" update="2011-01-15">
<name>Airmd (Buson)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Attila`s Skarmory was sent out to battle Jimmy and Marina while Hun and Attila attempted to complete their capture of Raikou. During Attila`s Skarmory first encounter with Marina, her Misdreavus managed to disable it with Perish Song causing it to be unable to battle.</description>
<picture>56399.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22314" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-12">
<rating votes="34">5.99</rating>
<name>Junsaa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is part of a family of policewomen found in almost every town. All of her sisters are named the same, and look identical. They are responsible for enforcing the law, and are often called on when Team Rocket is causing trouble. They typically use Growlithe as an attacking Pokemon. They are also part of Brock`s innumerable fantasies about girls, and he seems to be the only one able to tell the various officers apart.
The Officer Jennys that are apart of the Orange Islands Police Force have lighter uniforms than those of the Kanto Region.</description>
<picture>56471.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="551" picture="228658.jpg">Nishimura Chinami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22315" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="21">6.69</rating>
<name>Joy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is part of a large family of nurses, found in almost every town. Her sisters are named the same and look identical. They are responsible for healing sick and injured Pokemon, as well as the registration for various tournaments and contests. They use Chanseys as their assistants.
They are also part of Brock`s innumerable fantasies about girls, and he seems to be the only one able to tell the various nurses apart.</description>
<picture>56472.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4953">Shiraishi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22317" type="appears in" update="2011-01-15">
<name>Lucky (Joy)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nurse Joy`s Chansey works at the Pokemon Center to help with injured Pokemon.</description>
<picture>56474.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22723" type="appears in" update="2010-10-19">
<name>Utsugi-hakase</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Professor Elm is a former student of Professor Oak and currently lives in New Bark Town where he does his Pokémon Reasearch.
Professor Elm is also responsible for giving out either a Chikorita, Totodile or a Cyndaquil to new Pokémon Trainers.</description>
<picture>57317.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22775" type="appears in" update="2010-10-19">
<rating votes="3">1.63</rating>
<name>Wataru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lance is a master Dragon-type Trainer and member of the Kanto Elite Four.</description>
<picture>57349.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22777" type="appears in" update="2010-10-19">
<name>Kairyu (Wataru)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lance`s Dragonite helped stop the legendary battle between Kyogre and Groudon.</description>
<picture>57351.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="23049" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-21">
<name>Minaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Eusine is a researcher and expert in legendary Pokemon.</description>
<picture>57770.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="60" picture="171602.jpg">Kawada Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23050" type="appears in" update="2010-10-21">
<name>Foodin (Minaki)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Eusine`s Alakazam was sent out to protect the group that was under attack by a bunch of Pokemon.</description>
<picture>57771.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="23132" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-21">
<name>Jun`ichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>During the Johto Silver Conference his name is Jackson but during the Raikou special it is Vincent.</description>
<picture>57814.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="336" picture="17172.jpg">Sakaguchi Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23135" type="appears in" update="2010-10-21">
<name>Meganium (Jun`ichi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vincent (Jackson)`s Meganium got into a conflict with Ash`s Bulbasaur and Squirtle which was later broken up by Harrison`s Miltank.</description>
<picture>57817.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="24275" type="main character in" update="2011-01-10">
<rating votes="2">6.08</rating>
<name>Marina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Marina is a Trainer from New Bark Town that appeared in the The Legend of Thunder! special.</description>
<picture>62767.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1983" picture="151694.jpg">Murai Kazusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24277" type="appears in" update="2011-01-10">
<name>Purin (Marina)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Marina`s Jigglypuff seems to enter double contests with her other Pokemon.</description>
<picture>62775.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27500" type="main character in" update="2011-01-25">
<name>Kenta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jimmy is the main character of the Raikou Special. He started off in New Bark Town and chose Cyndaquil as his starter Pokémon. He received his starter Pokémon from Professor Elm at the same time as Vincent and Marina.</description>
<picture>64408.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27501" type="appears in" update="2011-01-25">
<rating votes="1">6.64</rating>
<name>Shinji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shinji was seen at the beginning of the Raikou special battling against Jimmy. He sent out his Hitmonlee to battle against Jimmy`s Typhlosion but he lost the battle.</description>
<picture>64409.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1446" picture="19314.jpg">Touma Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27502" type="appears in" update="2011-01-25">
<name>Sawamular (Shinji)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shinji`s Hitmonlee battled against Jimmy`s Typhlosion. Typhlosion defeated Hitmonlee in a one-on-one battle fairly easily, impressing the crowd.</description>
<picture>64410.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27503" type="appears in" update="2011-01-25">
<name>Bakphoon (Kenta)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jimmy`s Typhlosion was first seen battling against Shinji`s Hitmonlee in a one-on-one battle. It easily defeated Hitmonlee and the crowd cheered at the end of the battle.
Typhlosion showed it had a good sense of humor and a fun personality as it turned on Jimmy when Marina asked if Jimmy was shy. It smirked giving Marina the answer to her question.</description>
<picture>64411.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27504" type="appears in" update="2011-01-25">
<name>Spear (Kenta)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jimmy`s Beedrill battled against Marina`s Jigglypuff and was victorious. Marina remember playing with Beedrill during its previous evolutions and wanted to know if it was the same Pokémon she remembered.</description>
<picture>64412.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27505" type="appears in" update="2011-01-25">
<name>Alligates (Marina)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Marina`s Croconaw is the evolved form of her original starter Pokémon Totodile that she received from Professor Elm. Marina`s Croconaw started a battle against Jimmy`s Typhlosion but it was cut short due to extremely bad weather.</description>
<picture>64413.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27506" type="appears in" update="2011-01-25">
<name>Muuma (Marina)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Like Ash`s Pikachu, Marina`s Misdreavus seems to say out of its Pokeball most of the time. During a confrontation with Team Rocket grunts Attila and Hun, Misdreavus used its Perish Song to disable Steelix and Skarmory before they retreated.</description>
<picture>64414.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27507" type="appears in" update="2011-01-25">
<name>Gyarados (Wataru)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lance`s Gyarados was seen as Marina explained to Jimmy that she wants to be an Pokemon Idol Trainer like Lance. A sticker of Lance`s Gyarados was also seen in Marina`s book that she showed to Jimmy.</description>
<picture>64415.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27508" type="appears in" update="2011-01-25">
<name>Kudou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kudo is a friend of Professor Elm who was in the area when Raikou was injured and Jimmy and Marina took it to the nearest Pokemon Center. Professor Elm wanted Jimmy and Marina to meet him.</description>
<picture>64416.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27219" picture="74192.jpg">Fukawa Toshikazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27509" type="appears in" update="2011-01-25">
<name>Chicorita (Jun`ichi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vincent (Jackson)`s Chikorita was his starter Pokemon that he received from Professor Elm.</description>
<picture>64417.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27510" type="appears in" update="2011-01-25">
<name>Hinoarashi (Kenta)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jimmy`s Cyndaquil was his starter Pokemon that he received from Professor Elm. It later evolved into a Quilava and then a Typhlosion.</description>
<picture>64418.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27511" type="appears in" update="2011-01-25">
<name>Waninoko (Marina)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Marina`s Totodile was her starter Pokemon that she received from Professor Elm. It evolved into a Croconaw and then a Feraligatr.</description>
<picture>64419.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="110835" update="2009-10-23">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>70</length>
<airdate>2001-12-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="110836" update="2017-03-28">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>2001-12-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="110837" update="2017-03-28">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>2001-12-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="110838" update="2017-03-28">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-12-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="110839" update="2017-03-28">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-12-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="110840" update="2017-03-28">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-12-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 3 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116966" update="2010-04-12">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2001-12-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">新たなる誓い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Renewed Oath (Opening)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arata Naru Chikai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117030" update="2010-04-12">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2001-12-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">新たなる誓い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Renewed Oath (Ending)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arata Naru Chikai</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
