<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="712" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>55</episodecount>
<startdate>1995-01-14</startdate>
<enddate>1996-02-24</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ninkuu</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">忍空</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">NINKŪ</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1730" type="Sequel">Ninkuu (1995)</anime>
<anime id="3209" type="Other">Ninkuu: Knife no Bohyou</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://pierrot.jp/archives/tv_list_1995/tv_029.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="5442" type="Series Composition">Hashimoto Hiroshi</name>
<name id="4326" type="Music">Honma Yuusuke</name>
<name id="18672" type="Character Design">Kitayama Mari</name>
<name id="3051" type="Character Design">Nishio Tetsuya</name>
<name id="9245" type="Original Work">Kiriyama Kouji</name>
<name id="7075" type="Direction">Abe Noriyuki</name>
<name id="733" type="Work">Yomiko Advertising</name>
<name id="741" type="Work">Fuji TV</name>
<name id="724" type="Work">Studio Pierrot</name>
</creators>
<description>"Ninku" combines karate and ninja techniques, and is the strongest form of martial arts.
It is said that no one can defeat a master of Ninku by any other means. This is a story of a world ruled by oppressive tyrants. Although a tragic war has been ended three years ago, people still suffer from the post war depression and are looking for a peaceful life.
Fusuke , the hero of the story, strongly oppose this vicious world created by the tyrants.
Fusuke, with other Ninku masters, try to save the world and the people from the vicious tyrants.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="154">3.97</permanent>
<temporary count="161">6.48</temporary>
<review count="1">7.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>126399.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2603</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>912</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1124</identifier>
<identifier>vghnbw</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://pierrot.jp/archives/tv_list_1995/tv_029.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ninku</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>NINKU_-忍空-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88979</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2572" parentid="2282" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-09">
<name>ninja</name>
<description>A ninja was a covert agent or mercenary of feudal Japan specializing in unorthodox arts of war.
The functions of the ninja included espionage, sabotage, infiltration, and assassination, as well as open combat in certain situations.
The ninja, using covert methods of waging war, were contrasted with the samurai, who had strict rules about honor and combat.</description>
<picurl>244347.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2926" parentid="2874" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>post-war</name>
<description>An armed conflict has ended not too long ago, devastation of the world or society is still evident.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3421" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-03">
<name>aviation</name>
<description>"These magnificant men in their flying machines"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3575" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-13">
<name>damsel in distress</name>
<description>The damsel in distress is usually a young, nubile woman placed in a dire predicament by a villain or a monster and requires a hero to dash to her rescue. Often used to unite the cast of a show for this one goal, to make them put differences aside and become a band of nakama. 
Examples: Sakoshita Yanagi from Rekka no Honoo, Yuuki Miaka from Fushigi Yuugi or Higurashi Kagome from Inuyasha.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5863" parentid="2798" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-06">
<name>Weekly Shounen Jump</name>
<description>The Weekly Shounen Jump is a Japanese manga magazine released on a weekly basis. Its main target audience consists of young males and it features several manga titles. The magazine was created by http://anidb.net/cr780 [Shueisha] in July, 1968, and was originally only called Shounen Jump, because it was not published every week at the time. A number of very famous shounen manga were or are published in it, such as http://anidb.net/a386 [Hokuto no Ken], http://anidb.net/a231 [Dragon Ball], http://anidb.net/a942 [City Hunter], http://anidb.net/a826 [Saint Seiya], http://anidb.net/a590 [Slam Dunk], http://anidb.net/a312 [Yuu Yuu Hakushou], http://anidb.net/a69 [One Piece], http://anidb.net/a239 [Naruto], http://anidb.net/a2369 [Bleach], http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], http://anidb.net/a3468 [Gintama], to name a few of the most well-known.</description>
<picurl>66685.png</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="20648" type="main character in" update="2011-05-09">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Aichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71214.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="231" picture="23486.jpg">Madono Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20708" type="main character in" update="2011-05-09">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Fuusuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71218.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1682" picture="41033.jpg">Matsumoto Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20709" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-09">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Ajirada</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71209.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20710" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-15">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Basara</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="455" picture="17356.jpg">Matsumoto Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20711" type="main character in" update="2011-05-09">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Hiroyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71216.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3196" picture="218728.jpg">Suzuki Katsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20712" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-15">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Kouchin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3363" picture="24393.jpg">Taniguchi Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20713" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-15">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Mekira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="692" picture="188445.jpg">Hiramatsu Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20714" type="main character in" update="2011-05-09">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Rihoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71215.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20715" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-15">
<name>Yamabuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="4718" picture="27537.jpg">Takizawa Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20716" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-15">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Sekirai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20718" type="main character in" update="2011-05-09">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Touji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71217.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="18655" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-01-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">子忍の風助!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fuusuke of Mouse Ninku Squad!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nenin no Fuusuke!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22901" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-01-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">酉忍隊長登場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Appearance of the Tori-nin Captain</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23079" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-01-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大地の橙次!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Touji of the Land!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23665" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-02-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">襲撃者たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Attackers</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37450" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-02-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勝身煙たつ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Release of the Kachimi-kemuri (Victory Smoke)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37451" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-02-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恐怖の要塞城</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fearful Fort Castle</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37568" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-02-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">氷の黄純!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kisumi of the Ice!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koori no Kisumi!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38583" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-03-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">閉ざされた心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The locked away feelings</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38596" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-03-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">母の子守唄</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mother`s Lullaby</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51372" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-03-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">悲しい別れ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sad Parting</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51373" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">苦狼門の試練</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Trial</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51374" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-04-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">強くなる方法</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Way to Become Strong</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51375" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-04-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">遠い約束!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Faraway Promise</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51376" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-04-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">痛みを越えて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Overcome the Pain</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51377" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-04-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">本当の勇気!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">True Courage</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51378" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-04-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">伝説の森!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Legendary Forest</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51379" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-05-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">忍空狼の罠!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ninku Trap!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51380" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-05-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶体絶命!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Desperation!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51381" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-05-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">激闘の果てに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Till the End of the Battle</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51382" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-05-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">イルカと少年</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dolphin and Youth</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51383" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-06-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">地獄の洞くつ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hole of Hell</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51384" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-06-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">雷鳴拳の恐怖</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Terror of the Fist</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51385" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-06-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">炎の赤雷!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Flame of Sekirai!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51386" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-06-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">自由への反乱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rebellion for Freedom</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51387" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-07-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">父と子!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Father and Son!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51388" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-07-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらばヒロユキ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell, Hiroyuki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51389" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-07-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">風水の谷!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Feng Shui Valley!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51390" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-07-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔の三獣士!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Three Demonic Warriors</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51391" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-07-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">天空龍現る!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sky Dragon Appears!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51392" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-08-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">姿なき狙撃者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Shapeless Sniper</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51393" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-08-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">包囲網を破れ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Break Through the Barrier</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51394" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-08-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">目覚めろ赤雷!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Awakened Sekirai!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51395" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-08-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">危機への序章</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Prologue to Crisis</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51396" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-09-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">死を呼ぶ幻!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Magic that Summons Death</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51397" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-09-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大空の勇者!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heroes of the Sky!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51398" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-09-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">謎の少年!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mysterious Youth</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51399" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-09-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">別れの約束</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Departing Promise</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51400" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-10-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">風水の岬!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fuusui`s Cape</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51401" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-10-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">砕けた氷!? 天空龍再び!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Crushed Ice!? The Sky Dragon Reappears</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51402" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-10-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">技激突!霧使いVS風使い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Confrontation! The Use of Fog versus the Use of Wind</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51403" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-11-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">里穂子の涙・父のおもかげ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rihoko`s Tears, Father`s Hometown</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51404" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-11-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">怒りの拳!忍空斬りの男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fist of Wrath! The Man who Slashes Ninku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51405" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-11-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恐怖の館!謎の幽霊屋敷</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Horror Building! The Mysterious Haunted House</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51406" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-11-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">対決!? 手裏剣使いの友情</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Confrontation!? Friendship that Uses Secret Weapons</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51407" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-12-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミス忍空!検問突破作戦!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Miss Ninku! Operation Breakthrough!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51408" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-12-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">月夜の刺客!封じられた技</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Assassin of the Night! The Sealed Technique</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51409" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-12-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">首都へ!正義の反乱者たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the Capital! The Rebels of Justice</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51410" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-12-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">蘇る記憶!母をさらった男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Revived Memories! The Man who Captured Mother</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51411" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-01-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">解き放たれた力!決戦の時</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Unleashed Power! The Time of Battle</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51412" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-01-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">力を越えろ風助!最大空力!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fuusuke Overcomes Power! The Strongest Ninku!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51413" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-01-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">雇われ用心棒!夕日の決闘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Employed Bodyguard! Duel in the Evening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51414" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-02-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">風助の強盗退治!仮面男の謎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Decline of Fuusuke`s Adversary! Mystery of the Masked Man</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51415" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">53</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-02-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">友情の舞台!ヒロユキの秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Stage of Friendship! Hiroyuki`s Secret</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51416" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">54</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-02-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">消えた札束!!悪者は誰だ?!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Missing Bills!! Who is the Culprit?!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51417" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">55</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-02-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">風助, 映画スターになる?!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fuusuke becomes a Movie Star?!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="174987" update="2016-02-13">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1995-01-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="174988" update="2016-02-13">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1995-01-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="213122" update="2019-03-02">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1995-07-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
