<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7141" restricted="false">
<type>TV Special</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>2001-01-28</startdate>
<enddate>2001</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sekai Meisaku Gekijou Kanketsu Ban: Perrine Monogatari</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">World Masterpiece Theater Complete Edition: Perrine de "En Famille"</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">世界名作劇場・完結版 ペリーヌ物語</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2304" type="Full Story">Perrine Monogatari</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://dbeat.bandaivisual.co.jp/meisaku/perrine.php</url>
<creators>
<name id="728" type="Work">Nippon Animation</name>
<name id="1102" type="Work">BS Fuji</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the novel En Famille by the French author http://anidb.net/cr9700 [Hector-Henri Malot], a follow-up to his better known work Sans Famille.
Perrine travels across Europe with her mother, a photographer, in a cabin drawn by a donkey. They are heading to a small village in northern France, the home of Perrine`s dead father.
Perrine doesn`t know that they are unwanted in the village; Perrine`s father left the village after having quarrelled with his father (Perrine`s grandfather) and married in India against his father`s will. After her mother falls ill, Perrine has to sell everything, including her beloved donkey Palikare, to pay for medicine.
Mother dies in Paris and before dying tells the girl that she has to make her grandfather love her before he knows who she really is. After a journey full of hardships, Perrine finally arrives in the village where she learns that her grandfather is the rich owner of the factory that feeds all the villagers.
Presenting herself under a false name, Perrine gets a job on the factory, searching for a way to the heart of her grandfather.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="3">7.07</permanent>
<temporary count="3">4.00</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>37984.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16460</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://dbeat.bandaivisual.co.jp/meisaku/perrine.php</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ペリーヌ物語#.E5.AE.8C.E7.B5.90.E7.89.88.EF.BC.882001.E5.B9.B4.EF.BC.89</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="110990" update="2009-10-29">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>2001-01-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="110991" update="2009-10-29">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>45</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
