<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7142" restricted="false">
<type>TV Special</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>2001-02-11</startdate>
<enddate>2001</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sekai Meisaku Gekijou Kanketsu Ban: Akage no Anne</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">World Masterpiece Theater Complete Edition: Anne of Green Gables</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">世界名作劇場・完結版 赤毛のアン</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1061" type="Full Story">Akage no Anne</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://dbeat.bandaivisual.co.jp/meisaku/anne.php</url>
<creators>
<name id="728" type="Work">Nippon Animation</name>
<name id="1102" type="Work">BS Fuji</name>
</creators>
<description>Anne is an orphan full of imagination. When she arrives at her new home she learns that sometimes you have to be a sensible person too; at the same time her unique character changes, or at least attracts, the people around her. The story covers Anne`s growth from about eleven to seventeen years old as she makes friends, goes to school and studies. At a difficult point in her life, Anne will have to make a hard choice and perhaps find a new dream.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="7">5.61</permanent>
<temporary count="7">5.00</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>37985.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>23583</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://dbeat.bandaivisual.co.jp/meisaku/anne.php</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2814" parentid="2832" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Canada</name>
<description>Canada is a country located in the northern part of North America. Its ten provinces and three territories extend from the Atlantic to the Pacific and northward into the Arctic Ocean. Canada is sparsely populated, the majority of its land territory being dominated by forest and tundra and the Rocky Mountains. Its capital is Ottawa, and its three largest metropolitan areas are Toronto, Montreal, and Vancouver.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214271.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2832" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Americas</name>
<description>The Americas, also collectively called America, encompass the totality of the continents of North America and South America. Together they make up most of Earth`s western hemisphere and comprise the New World.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192247.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5939" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-09">
<name>CAST MISSING</name>
<description>Important characters are missing, either in-part or entirely. This includes basic entry info (name, gender, picture), appear episode range, seiyuu and/or tags.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="110993" update="2009-10-30">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>2001-02-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="110994" update="2009-10-29">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>45</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
