<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7158" restricted="false">
<type>TV Special</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>2001</startdate>
<enddate>2001</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sekai Meisaku Gekijou Kanketsu Ban: Romeo no Aoi Sora</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">World Masterpiece Theater Complete Edition: Romeo and the Black Brothers</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">世界名作劇場・完結版 ロミオの青い空</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2023" type="Full Story">Romeo no Aoi Sora</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://dbeat.bandaivisual.co.jp/meisaku/romeo.php</url>
<creators>
<name id="728" type="Work">Nippon Animation</name>
<name id="1102" type="Work">BS Fuji</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the novel Die Schwarzen Brüder by the Swiss author http://anidb.net/cr10123 [Lisa Tetzner].
To get the money to pay for a doctor for his father, Romeo bravely sells himself as a chimney sweep. On the way to Milan he meets Alfredo, a mysterious boy on the run heading to the same fate. Upon being separated and sold to their new bosses, the two boys swear eternal friendship. Romeo has to learn the hardships of a chimney sweep`s job. His boss` daughter, Angeletta, is a girl with a heart illness who is not allowed to leave her room. She asks Romeo to bring the blue sky to her. Alfredo unites the sweeps in a secret union, the Black Brothers to face together the Wolf Pack gang, who constantly attack them. With their help, Romeo succeeds in bringing Angeletta`s dream to her. Soon the brotherhood faces more hardships than cruel bosses or street hooligans. Alfredo reveals his secret: he has sold himself in the name of his sister Bianca. It is now up to the Black Brothers to stand up for the truth, to save Bianca and to protect their leader`s life with their own.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="7">6.67</permanent>
<temporary count="7">5.85</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>38017.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>23581</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://dbeat.bandaivisual.co.jp/meisaku/romeo.php</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5939" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-09">
<name>CAST MISSING</name>
<description>Important characters are missing, either in-part or entirely. This includes basic entry info (name, gender, picture), appear episode range, seiyuu and/or tags.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="111036" update="2009-10-30">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>45</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111037" update="2009-10-30">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>45</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
