<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7163" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-12-20</startdate>
<enddate>2008-12-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gekijouban Gegege no Kitarou: Nippon Bakuretsu!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Gegege no Kitaro: Japan Explodes!!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">劇場版 ゲゲゲの鬼太郎 日本爆裂!!</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5049" type="Parent Story">Gegege no Kitarou (2007)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.kitaro.cx/</url>
<creators>
<name id="5452" type="Character Design">Ueno Ken</name>
<name id="4341" type="Original Work">Mizuki Shigeru</name>
<name id="4295" type="Music">Yokoyama Seiji</name>
<name id="11914" type="Direction">Koga Gou</name>
<name id="18282" type="Chief Animation Direction">Asanuma Akihiro</name>
</creators>
<ratings>
<permanent count="39">6.15</permanent>
<temporary count="39">5.94</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>38103.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9865</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8145</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.kitaro.cx/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2885</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>330773</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10188</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2616" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>mina</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word mina refers to a broad audience, which can be said to be "the entire family", from the grumpy grandpa to the newborn baby. In Japanese, the word means simply "everyone", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic. Mina works are deliberately targeted at a range of people as wide as possible, and are commonly associated with high-budget releases that require a very large audience to be financially viable. They usually bring mildly philosophical themes so that the adults can be interested, but do so without bringing objectionable content so that the children can be allowed to watch, and indeed also feature content specifically geared to spark their interest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3295" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>world domination</name>
<description>"Gee, Brain, what do you want to do tonight?"
"The same thing we do every night, Pinky: try to take over the world!"
A main objective for one of the characters is absolute control of not just one country, but a whole planet!</description>
<picurl>38878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3955" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>DESCRIPTION MISSING</name>
<description>The description for this entry is missing. e.g plot, biography...
Please help by adding it, and remove this tag afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4048" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>Japanese mythology</name>
<description>Japanese mythology is a system of beliefs that embraces Shinto and Buddhist traditions as well as agriculture-based folk religion. The Shinto pantheon alone consists of an uncountable number of kami (Japanese for "gods" or "spirits").
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4564" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-06-01">
<name>spirits</name>
<description>Spirits will appear throughout this anime. These will often be depicted as small orbs of glowing light, or transparent images of the deceased.
Not to be mistaken with "I see dead people", these spirits will usually appear at the location of their departure when the characters have gotten close to the truth surrounding their death. Or as plot element, when a spirit will often stay close to a character as a sort of "Guardian Angel". Although they are never actually seen, their presence is sometimes felt.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7811" type="main character in" update="2010-04-12">
<rating votes="93">8.97</rating>
<name>Kitarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kitarou is a youkai boy born in a cemetery, and aside from his mostly-decayed father, the last living member of the Ghost Tribe (幽霊族, yuurei zoku). He is missing his left eye, but his hair usually covers the empty socket. He fights for peace between humans and youkai, which generally involves protecting the former from the wiles of the latter. When questioned in the 2007 movie, Kitarou responds that he is three hundred and fifty years old.
Kitarou has an assortment of strange weapons at his disposal, including:
* * remote-controlled geta sandals

* * a detachable hand, also remote-controlled

* * a magic chanchanko vest which can protect its wearer from danger; it occasionally seems to act of its own accord, wrapping around enemies or aiding friends, even when Kitaro is not available to command it

* * spiny hairs which can be shot like arrows

* * another hair which can serve as an antenna for detecting spirit activity

* * a magical ocarina (usually used for calling Ittan Momen), which contains a baton, a whip and occasionally music which has the power to damage certain ghosts.

* * the power of electrocution, usually employed when an enemy has pinned or restrained him and he can no longer kick or use other weapons

</description>
<picture>26842.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="393" picture="46104.jpg">Takayama Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7812" type="main character in" update="2010-04-12">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Medama-oyaji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Medama-oyaji is Kitarou`s father. Once a fully-formed adult ghost, he perished of a disease, only to be reborn out of his decayed body as an anthropomorphic version of his own eyeball. He looks small and fragile, but has a strong spirit and a great love for his son. He is also extremely knowledgeable about ghosts and monsters. He enjoys staying clean, and is often seen bathing in a small bowl. He has a great love for sake.</description>
<picture>26843.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2942" picture="23713.jpg">Tanonaka Isamu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7813" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-12">
<rating votes="39">1.78</rating>
<name>Nezumi Otoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nezumi Otoko is a rodent-like youkai-human halfbreed. He has been alive for three hundred and sixty years, and in that time has almost never taken a bath, rendering him filthy, foul-smelling, and covered in welts and sores. While he is usually Kitarou`s friend, Nezumi Otoko will waste no time cooking up vile schemes or betraying his companions if he thinks there`s money to be had or a powerful enemy to side with. He claims to be a college graduate of the University of the Bizarre (怪奇大学, Kaiki Daigaku).
Nezumi-Otoko first appears in the story The Lodging House (Rental manga version) as Dracula IV`s minion.</description>
<picture>26844.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11363" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="80">6.90</rating>
<name>Neko Musume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Neko Musume is a normally-quiet youkai girl, who transforms into a frightening cat monster with fangs and feline eyes when she is angry or hungry for fish. Predictably, she does not get along well with Nezumi Otoko. She seems to harbor a slight crush on Kitaro, who sees her only as a friend. She bears some resemblance to the bakeneko of Japanese folklore.
Neko-Musume first appears in the story Neko-Musume and Nezumi-Otoko (Weekly Shounen Magazine version), however another cat-girl named Neko (寝子) appears in the earlier stories The Vampire Tree and the Neko-Musume and A Walk to Hell (Rental version).</description>
<picture>33849.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1429" picture="18686.jpg">Konno Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25238" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-14">
<rating votes="10">1.50</rating>
<name>Sunakake Baba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sunakake Babaa is an old youkai woman who carries sand which she throws into the eyes of enemies to blind them. She serves as an advisor to Kitarou and his companions, and manages a youkai apartment building. The original sunakake-baba is an invisible sand-throwing spirit from the folklore of Nara Prefecture.
Sunakake-babaa first appears in a cameo as one of many youkai attending a sukiyaki party in the story A Walk to Hell (Rental version) before making a more prominent appearance in The Great Youkai War (Shounen Magazine version).</description>
<picture>66561.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3645" picture="25834.jpg">Yamamoto Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25239" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-14">
<rating votes="9">3.33</rating>
<name>Konaki Jijii</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Konaki Jijii is a comic, absent-minded old youkai man who attacks enemies by clinging to them and turning himself to stone, increasing his weight and mass immensely and pinning them down. He and Sunakake Babaa often work as a team. The original konaki jijii is a ghost which is said to appear in the woods of Tokushima Prefecture in the form of a crying infant. When it is picked up by some hapless traveller, it increases its weight until it crushes him.
Konaki-jijii first appears in a cameo as one of many youkai attending a sukiyaki party in the story A Walk to Hell (Rental version) before making a more prominent appearance in The Great Youkai War (Shounen Magazine version).</description>
<picture>66558.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="368" picture="25838.jpg">Tatsuta Naoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25240" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-14">
<rating votes="28">1.64</rating>
<name>Ittan Momen</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ittan Momen is a flying youkai resembling a strip of white cloth. Kitarou and friends often ride on him when traveling. The original ittan-momen is a spirit from Kagoshima Prefecture myth which wraps itself around the faces of humans in an attempt to smother them.
Ittan Momen first appears in the story The Great Youkai War (Shounen Magazine version).</description>
<picture>66566.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3241" picture="24745.jpg">Yanami Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25241" type="appears in" update="2013-02-14">
<rating votes="6">3.33</rating>
<name>Nurikabe</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nurikabe is a large, sleepy-eyed wall-shaped youkai, who uses his massive size to protect Kitarou and his friends. The original Nurikabe is a spirit which blocks the passage of people walking at night.
Nurikabe first appears in a cameo as one of many youkai attending a sukiyaki party in the story A Walk to Hell (Rental version) before making a more prominent appearance in The Great Youkai War (Shounen Magazine version).</description>
<picture>66562.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="368" picture="25838.jpg">Tatsuta Naoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25242" type="appears in" update="2011-02-27">
<name>Rokurokubi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66575.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3834" picture="25805.jpg">Toyoshima Machiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25243" type="appears in" update="2011-02-27">
<rating votes="4">3.33</rating>
<name>Kawauso</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66574.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16398" picture="171244.jpg">Maruyama Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25244" type="appears in" update="2011-02-26">
<name>Amabie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66523.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="394" picture="17239.jpg">Ikezawa Haruna</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25245" type="appears in" update="2011-02-27">
<rating votes="4">3.33</rating>
<name>Yobuko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66564.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="29204" type="appears in" update="2011-02-27">
<name>Nurarihyon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66556.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28" picture="23184.jpg">Aono Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="111004" update="2009-10-30">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>75</length>
<airdate>2008-12-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197245" update="2018-12-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2008-12-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ご当地バージョン連続再生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chapter 7 Local Versions` Events Reconstruction</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gotouchi Version Renzoku Saisei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197246" update="2018-12-20">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">特別予告 75秒</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 75 Sec. Version (1:15)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokubetsu Yokoku 75-byou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197247" update="2018-12-20">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1 (0:30)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210548" update="2018-12-20">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2008-12-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ご当地バージョン 北海道・東北</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chapter 7 Local Version (Hokkaidou and Touhoku)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gotouchi Version: Hokkaidou, Touhoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210549" update="2018-12-20">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2008-12-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ご当地バージョン 関東・甲信</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chapter 7 Local Version (Kantou and Koushin)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gotouchi Version: Kantou, Koushin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210550" update="2018-12-20">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2008-12-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ご当地バージョン 中部・北陸</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chapter 7 Local Version (Chuubu and Hokuriku)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gotouchi Version: Chuubu, Hokuriku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210551" update="2018-12-20">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2008-12-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ご当地バージョン 近畿</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chapter 7 Local Version (Kinki)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gotouchi Version: Kinki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210552" update="2018-12-20">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2008-12-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ご当地バージョン 中国・四国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chapter 7 Local Version (Chuugoku and Shikoku)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gotouchi Version: Chuugoku, Shikoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210553" update="2018-12-20">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2008-12-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ご当地バージョン 九州・沖縄</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chapter 7 Local Version (Kyuushuu and Okinawa)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gotouchi Version: Kyuushuu, Okinawa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210554" update="2018-12-05">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2009-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">討ち入りイベント at 新宿バルト9 2008年12月13日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Raid Event at Shinjuku Wald 9 on 2008.12.13</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchiiri Event at Shinjuku Wald 9, 2008-nen 12-gatsu 13-nichi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210555" update="2018-12-05">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2009-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">密着! 初日舞台挨拶</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening Day On Stage Greetings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Micchaku! Shonichi Butai Aisatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210556" update="2018-12-05">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2009-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">鬼太郎, ネコ娘がいく! 全国縦断キャンペーン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kitarou and Neko Musume Hit the Road! Country-Wide Campaign</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kitarou, Neko Musume ga Iku! Zenkoku Juudan Campaign</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210557" update="2018-12-05">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2009-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">フジテレビ ホットファンタジーイベント 2009.1.4</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fuji TV Hot Fantasy Event on 2009.01.04</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuji TV Hot Fantasy Event 2009.1.4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210558" update="2018-12-05">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">のり平鬼太郎アフレコ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dubbing Norihei-Kitarou`s Lines</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Norihei-Kitarou Af-Reco</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210559" update="2018-12-05">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2009-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">宮崎県 東国原知事がアフレコ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dubbing by Miyazaki Prefecture`s Governor Higashikokubaru!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Miyazaki-ken Higashikokubaru-chiji ga Af-Reco!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210560" update="2018-12-05">
<epno type="2">S14</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">横浜市 中田市長がアフレコ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dubbing by Yokohama City`s Mayor Nakada!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yokohama-shi Nakada-shichou ga Af-Reco!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210561" update="2018-12-05">
<epno type="2">S15</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">鬼太郎, ドアラに会う!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kitarou Meets Doala!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kitarou, Doala ni Au!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210562" update="2018-12-05">
<epno type="2">S16</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2009-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">完全収録! 五大鬼太郎, 奇跡の勢ぞろい!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Edition! Godai-Kitarou`s Miraculous Full Force!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanzen Shuuroku! Godai Kitarou, Kiseki no Seizoroi!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210563" update="2018-12-05">
<epno type="2">S17</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2009-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">「日本爆裂!!」ができるまで!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Until "Nippon Bakuretsu!!" Is Finished!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Nippon Bakuretsu!!" ga Dekiru made!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210564" update="2018-12-05">
<epno type="2">S18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">全て見せます!「日本爆裂!!」アフレコの現場!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Completely Exposed! At the Scene of Dubbing "Nippon Bakuretsu!!"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Subete Misemasu! "Nippon Bakuretsu!!" Af-Reco no Genba!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210565" update="2018-12-05">
<epno type="2">S19</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">討ち入りイベントの妖怪たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Spirits of the Raid Event</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchiiri Event no Youkai-tachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210566" update="2018-12-05">
<epno type="2">S20</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2009-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">劇場版 ゲゲゲの鬼太郎 日本爆裂!! DVD·BD豪華限定版 特別妖怪特典!! ようこそ妖怪の街へ! 鬼太郎と行く水木しげるロード</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gekijouban Gegege no Kitarou: Nippon Bakuretsu!! Gorgeous DVD/BD Limited Edition Special Spirit Bonus!! Welcome to the Town of Spirits! Walking the Mizuki Shigeru Road with Kitarou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekijouban Gegege no Kitarou: Nippon Bakuretsu!! DVD/BD Gouka Genteiban Tokubetsu Youkai Tokuten!! Youkoso Youkai no Machi e! Kitarou to Iku Mizuki Shigeru Road</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210567" update="2018-12-05">
<epno type="2">S21</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2009-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">鬼太郎が駅長!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kitarou Is a Station Manager!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kitarou ga Ekichou!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210568" update="2018-12-05">
<epno type="2">S22</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">水木しげる記念館へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the Memorial Hall of Mizuki Shigeru</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mizuki Shigeru Kinenkan e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210570" update="2018-12-20">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">特別予告 40秒</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 40 Sec. Version (0:40)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokubetsu Yokoku 40-byou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210571" update="2018-12-20">
<epno type="4">T14</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">シネコン予告編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 8 (1:15)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cinecom Yokokuhen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210572" update="2018-12-20">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 4 (Before Premiere; 0:15)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211196" update="2018-12-19">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 3 (0:15)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211197" update="2018-12-19">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 4 (After Premiere; 0:15)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211198" update="2018-12-19">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 5 (Before Premiere; 0:15)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211199" update="2018-12-19">
<epno type="4">T10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 5 (After Premiere; 0:15)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211200" update="2018-12-19">
<epno type="4">T11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 6 (Before Premiere; 0:15)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211201" update="2018-12-19">
<epno type="4">T12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 6 (After Premiere; 0:15)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211202" update="2018-12-19">
<epno type="4">T13</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 7 (0:15)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211203" update="2018-12-19">
<epno type="4">T15</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">スペシャルリポート ライバル編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special Report: Rival Version (1:00)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Special Report: Rival Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211204" update="2018-12-19">
<epno type="4">T16</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">スペシャルリポート 美少女編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special Report: Pretty Woman Version (1:00)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Special Report: Bishoujo Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211205" update="2018-12-19">
<epno type="4">T17</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">スペシャルリポート ねこ娘コスチューム編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special Report: Neko Musume`s Costume Version (0:40)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Special Report: Neko Musume Costume Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211206" update="2018-12-19">
<epno type="4">T18</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">スペシャルリポート 妖怪横丁ぶらり旅編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special Report: Spirits Alley Version (0:40)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Special Report: Youkai Yokochou Furari Tabi Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211207" update="2018-12-19">
<epno type="4">T19</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">スペシャルリポート 五大鬼太郎編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special Report: Godai Kitarou Version (1:15)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Special Report: Godai Kitarou Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211208" update="2018-12-20">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">特別予告 30秒</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 30 Sec. Version (0:30)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokubetsu Yokoku 30-byou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211209" update="2018-12-20">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 2 (0:15)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
