<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="717" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>1991-05-23</startdate>
<enddate>1992-09-24</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kidou Senshi Gundam 0083: Stardust Memory</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Gundam 0083: Stardust Memories</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">机动战士高达0083: 星尘的回忆</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">MSG 0083</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">機動戦士ガンダム 0083 スターダストメモリー</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Mobile Suit Gundam 0083: Stardust Memory</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">기동전사 건담 0083: 스타더스트 메모리</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">โมบิลสูทกันดั้ม 0083 สตาร์ดัสท์ เมมโมรี่</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="718" type="Sequel">Kidou Senshi Z Gundam</anime>
<anime id="715" type="Prequel">Kidou Senshi Gundam</anime>
<anime id="2009" type="Summary">Kidou Senshi Gundam 0083: Zeon no Zankou</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="20183">One of the best Gundam series, Good story, characters.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="467099">very uninteresting characters as others have said but the rest was good i would recommend this though it does start off slow.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.gundam0083.net</url>
<creators>
<name id="1352" type="Original Work">Yatate Hajime</name>
<name id="662" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kawamoto Toshihiro</name>
<name id="7072" type="Music">Hagita Mitsuo</name>
<name id="662" type="Character Design">Kawamoto Toshihiro</name>
<name id="147" type="Original Work">Tomino Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="1542" type="Direction">Kase Mitsuko</name>
<name id="659" type="Direction">Imanishi Takashi</name>
</creators>
<description>October U.C. 0083 - December U.C. 0083
Three years after the end of the war between the Zeon and the Federation, a group called the Delaz Fleet is formed by the survivors of the Zeon army. Their goals is to rebuild Zeon. Its ace pilot, Major Anavel Gato steals the Gundam GP02, a nuclear equipped model in development by the Federation. Lieutenant Kou Uraki pilots the Gundam GP01, the only one left, in an attempt to stop him. Operation Stardust, the plan of the Delaz Fleet, is such a large-scale operation that it shakes up the Federation.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1284">6.45</permanent>
<temporary count="1291">7.32</temporary>
<review count="4">6.54</review>
</ratings>
<picture>148805.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>23</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>32898</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>84</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>10581</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>193</identifier>
<identifier>jjijmo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gundam0083.net</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Mobile_Suit_Gundam_0083:_Stardust_Memory</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>機動戦士ガンダム0083_STARDUST_MEMORY</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>813</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88499</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2709" parentid="4656" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-30">
<name>netorare</name>
<description>Netorare is what happens when the protagonist gets his wife/girlfriend stolen from him by someone else. It is a sexual fetish designed to cause sexual jealousy by way of having the heroine indulge in sexual activity with someone other than the protagonist.
The intent or reason causing the scenario does not have any bearing as to whether the scenario is netorare or netori; perspective is the only differentiating factor.
Netorare is generally caused by, but not limited to: the stealing party has malicious intent to harm the protagonist, or the wife/girlfriend hopes to improve their relationship by causing the protagonist to be jealous.
Netorare Type A
The heroine is willingly cheating on the protagonist with another guy, and enjoys every second of it. No rape, blackmail, drugs etc. involved; it`s consensual sex from the very beginning.
Netorare Type B
Initially, the heroine is raped, blackmailed, drugged, or otherwise tricked to have sex with someone other than the protagonist. However, she eventually starts enjoying it, and the sex becomes fully consensual in the end.
Netorare Type C
The heroine is raped in front of the protagonist, and he can only helplessly watch it. It`s non-consensual from start to finish.
Note: Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t2716 [Netori].</description>
<picurl>150946.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2829" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-21">
<name>shower scene</name>
<description>The anime contains a shower scene, obligatory for ecchi anime. The person under the shower will most likely be female — providing "fanservice".</description>
<picurl>208635.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2867" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>politics</name>
<description>From commies to fat capitalist pigs, all the stuff done by the "guys with the power", mainly evil tactics for gaining more power over the masses.
Watching this title may remind you why CNN is boring.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3145" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-14">
<name>impact event</name>
<description>An impact event is a collision between celestial objects causing measurable effects. Impact events have physical consequences and have been found to regularly occur in planetary systems, though the most frequent involve asteroids, comets or meteoroids and have minimal impact. When large objects impact terrestrial planets like the Earth, there can be significant physical and biospheric consequences, though atmospheres mitigate many surface impacts through atmospheric entry. Impact structures are dominant landforms on many celestial solid objects and present the strongest empirical evidence for their frequency and scale. In fiction, an impact event is a common way to end the world as we know it, either through the impact itself or through its aftermath, and it may happen either naturally or through human hands; this may include man-made objects, such as space debris and fictional space colonies.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3216" parentid="2626" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-25">
<name>Universal Century</name>
<description>Refers to the Universal Century timeline in Gundam anime. Gundam anime with this tag all belong in the same universe.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3266" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-17">
<name>space Nazis</name>
<description>The term space Nazi refers to any futuristic society or group, whose appearance, politics, or culture are modelled after the Nazis.</description>
<picurl>223948.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4081" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space battles</name>
<description>There are space battles in this anime. Usually between Earth forces and some alien invader, but ship to ship skirmishes in deep space are just as common.</description>
<picurl>242377.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4404" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-28">
<name>real robot</name>
<description>A smaller form of mecha with no special abilities. They are mostly used by deploying them in battle just like modern tanks. They can be mass produced and their pilots (usually military officers or soldiers) are (mostly) interchangeable. Tanks are often a threat to them and they are more easily destroyed than their bigger counterparts.</description>
<picurl>42787.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4520" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>betrayal</name>
<description>Friends become enemies.
Strong bonds of trust receive violations of confidence while friendships are faithlessly given up or revealed to have been false from the start.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4656" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-06">
<name>infidelity</name>
<description>Infidelity is a violation of a couple`s assumed or stated contract regarding emotional and/or sexual exclusivity, sometimes according to the subjective feeling that one`s partner has violated a set of rules or relationship norms; this violation results in feelings of sexual jealousy and rivalry. What constitutes an act of infidelity is dependent upon the exclusivity expectations within the relationship. In marital relationships, exclusivity expectations are commonly assumed although they are not always met. When they are not met, research has found that psychological damage can occur, including feelings of rage and betrayal, lowering of sexual and personal confidence, and damage to self-image.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>191139.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5805" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-06-11">
<name>post-credits scene</name>
<description>A little bit of the story is found after the credit titles. A little bonus for those patient enough!
This applies regardless of if the credits play over an ED sequence, or over the "regular episode" that continues to air into the credits.
A sequence at the end of an episode, showing what will happen in the next episode, is NOT a post-credits scene; that is a preview.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2422" type="appears in" update="2009-01-15">
<rating votes="85">8.42</rating>
<name>Principality of Zeon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Republic of Zeon was initially founded by Zeon Zum Deikun, who declared the colony located at the second Earth-Luna Lagrangian Point, named Side 3, independent from the Earth Federation in U.C.0058. For the next several years, Zeon Zum Deikun and his followers dealt with diplomatic issues surrounding their independence, chiefly the economic pressure applied to Side 3 by the Earth Federation, in their efforts to force Side 3 back into the Federation. During this time, Side 3 formed its first national guard unit. Unfortunately, for the Republic of Zeon, Zeon Zum Deikun unexpectedly died (almost certainly assassinated by the Zabis) in UC 0068, leaving Side 3 without a leader. After the end of the One Year War, the Republic was re-established with a pro-Earth Federation puppet government.</description>
<picture>17677.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2441" type="appears in" update="2009-01-15">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Earth Federation</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The unified world government that launched the space settlement program and now rules over both Earth and the space colonies. Its main decision-making body is the Earth Federation Assembly, which meets occasionally to pass new legislation.
Though not as cruel and aggressive as the Principality of Zeon`s leaders, the bureaucrats who rule over the Earth Federation are corrupt, weak-willed, and insensitive to the space colonists` desire for independence. After the One Year War, the Federation decides to concentrate its energies on reconstructing Earth instead of the space colonies, further increasing political tensions.</description>
<picture>17701.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2452" type="appears in" update="2009-01-15">
<name>Earth Federation Forces</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The military arm of the Earth Federation. The Federation Forces are divided into several branches, including land, sea, air, and space forces. Until mass production of the RGM-79 GM begins in the final weeks of the One Year War, the Federation Forces are forced to battle the Principality of Zeon`s mobile suits using conventional tanks, planes, and space fighters. Even in the postwar years, the Federation Forces are usually inferior to their opponents in terms of skill, morale, and equipment.</description>
<picture>1824.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="2665" type="main character in" update="2009-01-22">
<rating votes="4">8.51</rating>
<name>Kou Uraki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>After graduating from the Federation`s military academy, this young officer is stationed at the Torrington base in Australia as a test pilot - an assignment which amounts to little more than serving as a moving target in combat simulations. But when enemy ace Anavel Gato steals the Gundam GP02A from the Torrington base, Kou attempts to stop him with the prototype Gundam GP01, and demonstrates a natural talent as a pilot. As a result, he`s assigned to the carrier Albion as it takes off in pursuit of the stolen Gundam. Initially naive, inexperienced, and socially inept, Kou begins to mature through his relationship with Nina and his wrenching experiences in battle.</description>
<picture>18035.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4932" picture="16806.jpg">Horikawa Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2667" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<rating votes="5">5.69</rating>
<name>Nina Purpleton</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A brilliant young systems engineer in the employ of Anaheim Electronics, who is responsible for fine-tuning her company`s prototype Gundams. After the theft of the Gundam GP02A, Nina stays aboard the Albion in order to aid in the recovery of the stolen Gundam and keep an eye on the remaining GP01. Her working relationship with Kou soon develops into a clumsy romance, but Nina`s feelings are complicated by her mysterious past...</description>
<picture>18036.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="555" picture="23759.jpg">Sakuma Rei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2668" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<rating votes="1">6.28</rating>
<name>Chuck Keith</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chuck, like his military academy classmate Kou, was stationed at the Torrington base after graduation. After the theft of the Gundam GP02A, he is likewise reassigned to the Albion as part of its mobile suit pilot team. Piloting a GM Cannon II, Chuck provides artillery support for the Albion`s other mobile suits, and in a similar fashion his happy-go-lucky personality provides a valuable counterbalance to the intense and moody Kou.</description>
<picture>18038.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3226" picture="184249.jpg">Yamada Yoshiharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2669" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<rating votes="4">7.74</rating>
<name>Mora Bascht</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A big, boisterous female mechanic, who`s been assigned to the Albion as maintenance chief for the prototype Gundams. Happy to play the big sister, Mora is often seen playing confidant to Nina or protecting her pretty assistants from the grabby hands of Bernard Monsha. Early on, she takes a shine to Chuck Keith, and this happy couple provides a cheery contrast to the tempestuous relationship between Kou and Nina.</description>
<picture>18040.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8" picture="171393.jpg">Ikura Kazue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2670" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<rating votes="3">6.09</rating>
<name>Alpha A. Bate</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Another of the Albion`s pilot reinforcements, Bate is calmer and less obnoxious than Monsha, but can be relied upon to encourage his friend`s misbehaviour. Together with Monsha and Adel, he served under Burning during the One Year War, and his experience makes him a natural choice for deputy commander of the Albion`s mobile suit team.</description>
<picture>18041.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3220" picture="24200.jpg">Totani Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2671" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<rating votes="1">8.68</rating>
<name>Eiphar Synapse</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The captain of the assault carrier Albion is a grizzled veteran, with a commanding personality and a keen tactical mind. Originally dispatched to collect the prototype Gundams from the Federation`s Torrington base, Synapse soon finds himself charged with pursuing the stolen Gundam GP02A. Well aware that he can expect little guidance or support from the Federation`s upper ranks, Synapse is often forced to rely on his own judgement... and his own sense of right and wrong.</description>
<picture>18042.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="456" picture="17358.jpg">Ootsuka Chikao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2672" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-21">
<rating votes="1">8.68</rating>
<name>South Burning</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>As the senior pilot at the Federation`s Torrington base, Burning supervises the testing of new equipment and acts a mentor to the inexperienced Kou and Chuck. After the theft of the Gundam GP02A, he joins the crew of the Albion as mobile suit company commander. Though Burning is a clever and skilled pilot, he is gradually slowing down due to the effects of age.</description>
<picture>18043.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2730" picture="22755.jpg">Sugawara Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2673" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<rating votes="2">7.29</rating>
<name>Chap Adel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The third of the new pilots assigned to the Albion, Adel is quiet and mild-mannered, generally going along with his comrades` hijinks rather than actively instigating them. Like Chuck Keith, he plays a supporting role in combat as a GM Cannon II pilot.</description>
<picture>18044.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2246" picture="186215.jpg">Mikimoto Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2674" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<rating votes="4">7.71</rating>
<name>Bernard Monsha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Monsha is one of three new pilots assigned to the Albion as it sets off in pursuit of the stolen Gundam GP02A. A veteran pilot who served under Burning in the One Year War, he takes an immediate dislike to the young upstart Kou. Meanwhile, Monsha makes a general nuisance of himself aboard the ship with his boozing, gambling, and incorrigible woman-chasing.</description>
<picture>18045.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="173" picture="150067.jpg">Chafuurin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2675" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<name>William Morris</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18046.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2207" picture="41549.jpg">Makishima Naoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2676" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<name>Jacqueline Simone</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18047.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2439" picture="166338.jpg">Araki Kae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2677" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<name>Peter Scott</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18048.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="468" picture="17383.jpg">Kikuchi Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2678" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<name>Ivan Pasrof</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18049.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2490" picture="151704.jpg">Kishino Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2679" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<name>John Kowen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18050.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3225" picture="24205.jpg">Watabe Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2680" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="13">4.63</rating>
<name>Bask Om</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The brutal field commander of the Titans. While the Titans are effectively a private army controlled by Admiral Jamitov Hymem, Bask is the organisation`s day-to-day leader, responsible for devising strategies and commanding operations. Bask considers his troops above the law and beyond the reach of the Earth Federation command structure, and doesn`t hesitate to take hostages or commit mass murder if it seems like the most effective way to crush dissent.</description>
<picture>85194.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2946" picture="23373.jpg">Gouri Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2681" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="2">8.68</rating>
<name>Jamitov Hymem</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The sinister politician who controls the Titans from behind the scenes. From his perch at the pinnacle of the Earth Federation`s military command structure, Jamitov uses the Titans as a private army to further his own scheme for world domination. Cruel, devious, and utterly amoral, this evil genius will stop at nothing to impose his own brand of Earth-supremacist ideology on the suffering peoples of the space colonies.</description>
<picture>85193.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2682" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<rating votes="1">6.28</rating>
<name>Dick Allen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18053.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="420" picture="186676.jpg">Akimoto Yousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2683" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<name>Hawkins Marnery</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18054.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="416" picture="23206.jpg">Saka Osamu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2684" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<name>Akron Halidda</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18055.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="275" picture="17102.jpg">Tahara Aruno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2685" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<name>Y. Bicok</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18056.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3277" picture="192234.jpg">Hashimoto Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2686" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<name>Green Wyatt</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18057.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1733" picture="25839.jpg">Tanaka Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2687" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<name>Raban Karcs</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18058.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2688" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<name>Gene Corini</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18059.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2490" picture="151704.jpg">Kishino Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2689" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<name>Nakaha Nakato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18060.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3223" picture="88844.jpg">Ootaki Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2690" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<name>Alloys Mozley</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18065.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2201" picture="34284.jpg">Matsuo Ginzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2691" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<name>Stephen Hepburn</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18066.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3222" picture="24203.jpg">Fujishiro Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2692" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<rating votes="3">8.37</rating>
<name>Aiguille Delaz</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>As a captain of the Zeon space fleet during the One Year War, Delaz chose to withdraw from A Baoa Qu, forfeiting that hopeless final battle in order to strike back at the Earth Federation later on. At his makeshift headquarters in a debris-strewn shoal zone, Delaz has spent three years gathering his forces for the master plan he calls "Operation Stardust." Thanks to his strategic genius, Delaz can easily outwit the Federation`s commanders, but his idealism blinds him to the possibility of betrayal from within his own ranks.</description>
<picture>18067.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37" picture="43092.jpg">Kobayashi Kiyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2693" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<rating votes="8">6.75</rating>
<name>Anavel Gato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>During the One Year War, Gato was a famous ace pilot, dreaded by Federation soldiers as the "Nightmare of Solomon." During the last battle of the war he grudgingly agreed to leave the battlefield with Delaz, living to fight another day rather than going out in a blaze of glory. Now this master warrior lives only for the resurrection of the Zeon cause, displaying little emotion other than contempt for the incompetence of his Federation foes. While Kou becomes obsessed with avenging Gato`s theft of the Gundam GP02A, this rivalry is decidedly one-sided - it`s almost beneath Gato`s dignity to acknowledge a clumsy Federation rookie as his adversary.</description>
<picture>18068.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2694" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<rating votes="8">5.57</rating>
<name>Cima Garahau</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cima is the commander of a group of former Zeon marines, an elite force which was renowned for war crimes and ruthless tactics during the One Year War. Long shunned by her former comrades, Cima grudgingly agrees to join forces with Delaz and aid him with Operation Stardust. Her fleet consists of the Zanzibar-class cruiser Lili Marleen, a half-dozen Musai cruisers, and some 30 Gelgoog mobile suits - including a souped-up commander`s model, which Cima personally takes into battle whenever the craving for combat strikes her.</description>
<picture>18069.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3221" picture="24202.jpg">Mashiba Mari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2695" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<name>Bob</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18070.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2279" picture="23207.jpg">Satou Masaharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2696" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<name>Adamski</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18071.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="275" picture="17102.jpg">Tahara Aruno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2697" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<name>Gaily</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18072.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27206" picture="73948.jpg">Taguchi Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2698" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<name>Neuen Bitter</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18073.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="261" picture="151648.jpg">Ikeda Masaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2699" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<name>Karius Otto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18074.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2700" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<name>Kult</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18075.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2220" picture="188715.jpg">Inaba Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2701" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<name>Wily Glardle</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18076.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2220" picture="188715.jpg">Inaba Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2702" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<name>Deatroaf Kocsel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18077.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3099" picture="24698.jpg">Kakegawa Hirohiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2703" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<rating votes="2">8.14</rating>
<name>Kelly Layzner</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>This former Zeon lieutenant fought alongside Gato in the One Year War, ultimately losing his arm in battle. Now the operator of a junkyard near the lunar metropolis of Von Braun City, Kelly secretly dreams of returning to the battlefield, and in his spare time he works to restore a leftover Zeon mobile armour. When he meets Kou, the two form a friendship based on their shared experience as warriors, but both men are well aware that if they meet in battle then it will be as enemies.</description>
<picture>18078.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2704" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<name>Wolfgang Val</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18079.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2490" picture="151704.jpg">Kishino Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2705" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<name>Yuri Hussler</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18080.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="609" picture="1835.gif">Aomori Shin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2706" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<name>Nick Orville</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18081.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="107" picture="172060.jpg">Shioya Yoku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2707" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<name>Paula Guilish</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18082.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="291" picture="17122.jpg">Matsui Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2708" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<name>Dorize</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18083.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3276" picture="24272.jpg">Nakagi Ryuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2709" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<name>Lucette Audevie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18084.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1813" picture="172159.jpg">Katsuki Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2710" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Clehna Hacswel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18085.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="494" picture="17485.jpg">Ichijou Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2712" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<rating votes="2">5.64</rating>
<name>Latuera Chapra</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18087.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1901" picture="186579.jpg">Kobayashi Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2713" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<name>Peter Purpleton</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18088.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2490" picture="151704.jpg">Kishino Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2714" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-22">
<name>O`Sullivan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>18089.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3227" picture="24207.jpg">Ichikawa Osamu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2715" type="appears in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="43">8.95</rating>
<name>Haman Karn</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>After the fall of the Principality, a ragtag fleet of Zeon renegades makes its way to the asteroid belt, taking refuge at the asteroid base Axis. By U.C. 0083, the leadership of the this group has passed to a young woman named Haman Karn, the daughter of a Zeon admiral. Rallying the demoralized Axis renegades to the goal of an eventual triumphant return to the Earth sphere, Haman dispatches an advance fleet to aid Delaz in his master plan. Years later, the seeds of rebellion sown by Operation Stardust will be harvested by Haman and her Axis forces.</description>
<picture>85246.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="571" picture="172734.jpg">Sakakibara Yoshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2733" type="appears in" update="2013-06-25">
<name>Titans</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>An elite branch of the Federation Forces created in the aftermath of Operation Stardust. The Titans are charged with hunting down the renegade soldiers of the Principality of Zeon, and suppressing anti-Federation movements, but their overzealous actions soon create a new generation of resistance groups. The Titans are initially headquartered at the Gryps space colony, but as they gain control over the regular Federation Forces and form an alliance with the Republic of Zeon, they also take over Luna II and the Gate of Zedan.</description>
<picture>139051.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13526" type="appears in" update="2009-12-03">
<name>Anaheim Electronics</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Anaheim Electronics is a fictional civilian manufacturing company that appeared in the Universal Century timeline of the Gundam anime metaseries. The company appeared first in Mobile Suit Zeta Gundam(aired in 1985) as the main funder, as well as the main military supplier and manufacturer of the faction AEUG. However, the company also design and manufacture weapons for both the Earth Federation, its elite faction Titans, enemy of the AEUG, and third party faction Axis Zeon, which in turn became the enemies of the AEUG later in the series until the end of the sequel, Mobile Suit Gundam ZZ(aired in 1986). The company continues its manufacturing contracts in Mobile Suit Gundam ZZ and Mobile Suit Gundam: Char`s Counterattack(aired in 1988), where its weapons are always seen in both sides of the conflicting factions. In the novel, Gundam Sentinel(serialized in 1989), which happens between the conflicts of the anime series Mobile Suit Zeta Gundam and Mobile suit Gundam ZZ, Anaheim Electronics became the main contractor of the Earth Federation of its new mass-production units like Nero and the Z Plus series for the Task Force alpha and also provided prototype units such as S Gundam as a testbed for the Federation. The Gundam Sentinel`s Model Graphix special edition, Gundam Wars III, the battle of real Gundam in turn gave a detail analysis of the company and retconned the production and testing history. The company`s earlier history was then told in the anime Mobile Suit Gundam 0083: Stardust Memory(OVA first released in 1991), where it first became the contract manufacturer of the Earth Federation. In December 2003, celebrating the 20th Anniversary of the Gundam metaseries, a book Anaheim Journal was released, disguised as a monthly magazine published by Anaheim Electronics in UC0100. The company also appeared in the comic Silhouette Formula 91, and later in the anime Mobile Suit V Gundam.
Based on the Moon, Anaheim Electronics originally produced a wide range of technological applications from consumer electronics to battleships and even space colonies. Their service do not end at electronic goods, according to Anaheim Journal, they also have departments providing cosmetics, vacation travelling plans (with their own resort space colonies) and credit cards, ultimately fitting the definition of a zaibatsu. Upon the end of the One Year War, Anaheim was able to acquire the assets and personnel of the Zeonic Corporation - a mobile suit manufacturing firm of the defeated Principality of Zeon. This merger enabled Anaheim Electronics to enter the lucrative business of mobile suit production. As such, the firm was contracted by the Earth Federation to become its principal mobile suit provider until the end of the second Neo Zeon movement.
Anaheim Electronics is known for its profit-oriented mindset - creating advanced mobile weapons for any faction that would be willing to pay, then selling the same technology to the former`s enemy. During the rise of the oppressive Titans taskforce, Anaheim funded the AEUG and gave it access to their technology and safe shelter as the Titans restricted their trading engagements, despite the Earth Federation Forces and the Titans being their primary customer. Later, the company would service contracts from the remnants of the Principality of Zeon such as Axis and Neo Zeon. According to GundamOfficials, this is due to the gigantic company structure. With several development departments, each departments can be contracted by different factions without needing to notify the main executive board. This policy is simply adopted to minimize the companies overall responsibility; after the main battle, they can always just apply the penalty on a single department`s head instead of making the whole company suffer.
In the story of Silhouette Formula 91, after U.C. 0123, Anaheim Electronics lost its contract bid with the EFF to SNRI`s new miniaturized mobile suit designs, which were cheaper, more versatile and higher in performance. Anaheim Electronics had to maintain its low profile until U.C. 0153, and financially supported League Militaire in secrecy defending Earth from Zanscare Empire.
According to the official timeline, Anaheim Electronics remains as the main manufacturer of mobile suits in the Earth Sphere until the Earth Federation itself was disbanded in the U.C. 0200s, although its monopoly in the field was literally obliterated since the second Universal Century with the entrance of the Federation-backed competitor SNRI.
Corporate Profile
Name: Anaheim Electronics, Inc.
Main Office: Anaheim, Moon
Chairman of the Board: Melanie Hue Carbine (as of U.C. 0087)
Known Factories:
Von Braun City
Granada
La Vie en Rose mobile factory/docking ship</description>
<picture>39669.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="45275" type="appears in" update="2012-05-27">
<name>MS-21C Dra-C</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>A mass production mobile suit developed during the Delaz Conflict. Thanks to upgrades such as a gatling gun on its right arm, and the engravings added all over its body, this mobile suit doesn`t look at all like an antique.</description>
<picture>88543.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="53343" type="appears in" update="2013-03-02">
<name>RX-78GP02A Gundam GP02 Physalis</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>133015.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54001" type="appears in" update="2013-03-20">
<name>RX-78GP01 Gundam GP01 Zephyranthes</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>133873.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54002" type="appears in" update="2013-03-20">
<name>RX-78GP01-Fb Gundam GP01Fb Zephyrantes Full Burnern</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>133874.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54006" type="appears in" update="2013-03-20">
<name>RX-78GP03 Gundam GP03 Dendrobium Orchis</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>133878.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54007" type="appears in" update="2017-02-22">
<name>RX-78GP03S Gundam GP03 Dendrobium Stamen</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>133879.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54102" type="appears in" update="2013-03-21">
<name>RGM-79C GM Kai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>133990.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54103" type="appears in" update="2013-03-21">
<name>RGM-79 Powered GM</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>133992.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54104" type="appears in" update="2013-03-21">
<name>RGC-83 GM Cannon II</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>133993.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54105" type="appears in" update="2013-03-21">
<name>RGM-79N GM Custom</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>133994.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54106" type="appears in" update="2013-03-21">
<name>RB-79C Ball Kaishuu-gata</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>133995.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54107" type="appears in" update="2013-03-21">
<name>MS-06F-2 Zaku II F2-gata</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>133996.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54108" type="appears in" update="2013-03-21">
<name>MS-09F/Trop Dom Tropen</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>133998.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54109" type="appears in" update="2013-03-21">
<name>YMS-16M Xamel</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>133999.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54110" type="appears in" update="2013-03-21">
<name>AMA-X2 Neue Ziel</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>134000.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54111" type="appears in" update="2013-03-21">
<name>MS-14F Gelgoog Marine</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>134001.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54112" type="appears in" update="2013-03-21">
<name>AGX-04 Gerbera Tetra</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>134003.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54113" type="appears in" update="2013-03-21">
<name>MA-06 Val Walo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>134004.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54114" type="appears in" update="2013-03-21">
<name>Birmingham</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>134007.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54115" type="appears in" update="2013-03-21">
<name>Magellan Kai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>134008.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54116" type="appears in" update="2013-03-21">
<name>Columbus Kai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>134009.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54117" type="appears in" update="2013-03-21">
<name>Peer Gynt</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>134011.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54118" type="appears in" update="2013-03-21">
<name>U-801</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>134013.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54119" type="appears in" update="2013-03-21">
<name>Lily Marrein</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>134012.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54120" type="appears in" update="2013-03-21">
<name>MS-14Fs Gelgoog Marine Shikikan-gata</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>134002.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54121" type="appears in" update="2013-03-21">
<name>Albion</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>134006.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="8043" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-05-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガンダム強奪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stolen Gundam</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gundam Goudatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8044" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-06-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">終わりなき追撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Endless Chase</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Owarinaki Tsuigeki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8052" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-08-22</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">出撃アルビオン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Into Battle, Albion!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shutsugeki Albion</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8053" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-09-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">熱砂の攻防戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Attack and Retreat on the Burning Sand</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nessa no Koubousen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8054" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-10-24</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガンダム, 星の海へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gundam, to the Sea of Stars</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gundam, Hoshi no Umi e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8055" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-11-21</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フォン・ブラウンの戦士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Warrior of Von Braun</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Von Braun no Senshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8056" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1992-02-20</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蒼く輝く炎で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">With Shining Blue Fire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aoku Kagayaku Honoo de</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8057" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1992-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">策謀の宙域</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Conspiracy Sector</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakubou no Chuuiki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8058" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1992-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ソロモンの悪夢</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Nightmare of Solomon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Solomon no Akumu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8059" update="2004-08-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1992-06-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">激突戦域</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Colliding War Zones</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitotsu Sen`iki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8060" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1992-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラビアンローズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">La Vie en Rose</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">La Vie en Rose</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8061" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1992-09-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">強襲, 阻止限界点</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Assault on the Point of No Return</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoushuu, Soshi Genkaiten</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8062" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1992-09-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">9.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">駆け抜ける嵐</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Storm Raging Through</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakenukeru Arashi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61931" update="2006-08-24">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">8.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61932" update="2006-08-24">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">8.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="61933" update="2006-08-24">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<rating votes="3">5.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙の蜉蝣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mayfly of Space</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu no Kagerou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93813" update="2008-10-25">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95200" update="2008-11-19">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175956" update="2020-03-31">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2016-01-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙の蜉蝣2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mayfly of Space 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu no Kagerou 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
