<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="718" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>50</episodecount>
<startdate>1985-03-02</startdate>
<enddate>1986-02-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kidou Senshi Z Gundam</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Z Gundam</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Zeta Gundam</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="synonym">Mobile Suit Zeta Gundam</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Kidou Senshi Zeta Gundam</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">机动战士Z高达</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">機動戦士Zガンダム</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Mobile Suit Zeta Gundam</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Mobile Suit Z Gundam</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="719" type="Sequel">Kidou Senshi Gundam ZZ</anime>
<anime id="717" type="Prequel">Kidou Senshi Gundam 0083: Stardust Memory</anime>
<anime id="2440" type="Same Setting">Gundam Neo Experience: 0087 - Green Divers</anime>
<anime id="4095" type="Alternative Setting">Kidou Senshi Z Gundam: A New Translation - Hoshi no Kodou wa Ai</anime>
<anime id="2187" type="Alternative Setting">Kidou Senshi Z Gundam: A New Translation - Hoshi o Tsugu Mono</anime>
<anime id="3969" type="Alternative Setting">Kidou Senshi Z Gundam: A New Translation - Koibito-tachi</anime>
<anime id="11207" type="Summary">Akai Shouzou: Char, Soshite Frontal e</anime>
<anime id="7454" type="Other">All That Gundam</anime>
<anime id="596" type="Other">Kidou Senshi SD Gundam</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="5">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="616461">Not as groundbreaking as its predecesor but it is still a solid gundam anime. Kinda slow and too many annoying characters making stupid decisions but the last 15 or so episodes are great. For fans.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="150297">second best space opera I ever see (after LOGH).
not just laser and blow, the story line also great.
IMO, it`s the only gundam series with deep storyline.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="256644">One of the best space opera/mecha series ever made. Make sure to watch the original `79 series as well so you can have full enjoyment of this classic.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.z-gundam.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="147" type="Original Work">Tomino Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="1352" type="Original Plan">Yatate Hajime</name>
<name id="147" type="Chief Direction">Tomino Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="5230" type="Character Design">Yasuhiko Yoshikazu</name>
<name id="919" type="Work">Sotsu Agency</name>
<name id="1433" type="Work">Nippon Sunrise</name>
<name id="1019" type="Work">Nagoya TV Housou</name>
<name id="7765" type="Music">Saegusa Shigeaki</name>
</creators>
<description>The year is Universal Century 0087. Seven years have passed since the end of the One Year War. In its zeal to stamp out any remaining opposition, the Earth Federation has organized the Titans, an elite fighting force. However, the Titans soon get out of hand, committing atrocities on par with the worst the Principality of Zeon had to offer during the war. In response, dissatisified citizens, former Zeon soldiers, and even members of the Earth Federal Forces form a resistance group known as the Anti-Earth Union Group, or AEUG. As the next war is brewing, a small AEUG group arrives at Side 7 to investigate the new Gundam Mk. II...</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1411">7.38</permanent>
<temporary count="1420">7.62</temporary>
<review count="3">8.27</review>
</ratings>
<picture>194006.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1381</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>85</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>834</identifier>
<identifier>qumsta</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.z-gundam.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Zeta_Gundam</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>機動戦士Ζガンダム</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89261</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>360</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="975" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-05">
<name>pessimist</name>
<description>This character has a tendency to take notice of the negative or unfavorable aspects of any given situation, or to take the gloomiest possible view.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2764" parentid="2627" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>space colony</name>
<description>The human race (or possibly some alien race) has mastered space travel and founded at least one colony either in space, on a moon or another planet. This usually also includes colony-life episodes that not only show the technical staff of professionals (astronauts, scientists, etc.), but also their families (i.e. children).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2867" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>politics</name>
<description>From commies to fat capitalist pigs, all the stuff done by the "guys with the power", mainly evil tactics for gaining more power over the masses.
Watching this title may remind you why CNN is boring.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3216" parentid="2626" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-25">
<name>Universal Century</name>
<description>Refers to the Universal Century timeline in Gundam anime. Gundam anime with this tag all belong in the same universe.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3267" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>everybody dies</name>
<description>Not necessarily everyone, but a good portion of the characters kick the bucket.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3269" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-11">
<name>genocide</name>
<description>The systematic killing of substantial numbers of people on the basis of ethnicity, religion, political opinion, social status, or other particularity.
Acts committed with intent to destroy, in whole or in part, a national, ethnic, racial or religious group.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3560" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-12-04">
<name>world government</name>
<description>When a whole planet (e.g. Earth or a fictional planet) has one single government.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3852" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-09">
<name>Bright slap</name>
<description>"You hit me! Not even my father ever hit me!" 
You are the commander of a spaceship, leader of a faction or a team and your best mecha pilot stops fighting and grows increasingly hysterical and angsty, while the enemy could strike you at any time. What are you going to do? 
You slap or punch him, preferably in the face, and back to his senses while delivering a heroic speech that would turn any wimp into a man of destiny.
Named after Bright Noa of Mobile Suit Gundam, a prominent user of this for-sure method.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3974" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>star-crossed lovers</name>
<description>Two lovers — usually teenagers — destined to be kept apart no matter how hard they struggle to be together. It may be fate or just feuding families, or even something as mundane as a few hundred miles, but something will always be in their way. Often, the two can only be together in death. The phrase is astrological in origin, stemming from the belief that the positions of the stars ruled over people`s fates. To describe a relationship as "star-crossed" is to say that it is "thwarted by a malign star", or that the stars are working against the relationship. Shakespeare`s Romeo and Juliet is the most famous example of this archetype but it dates back at least as far as the ancient Greeks.
"From forth the fatal loins of these two foes, / a pair of star-cross`d lovers, take their life."
- Romeo and Juliet, prologue</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4081" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space battles</name>
<description>There are space battles in this anime. Usually between Earth forces and some alien invader, but ship to ship skirmishes in deep space are just as common.</description>
<picurl>242377.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4404" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-28">
<name>real robot</name>
<description>A smaller form of mecha with no special abilities. They are mostly used by deploying them in battle just like modern tanks. They can be mass produced and their pilots (usually military officers or soldiers) are (mostly) interchangeable. Tanks are often a threat to them and they are more easily destroyed than their bigger counterparts.</description>
<picurl>42787.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4565" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-08-17">
<name>war-zone realities</name>
<description>War is hell. This tag is for when characters experience the hell of war... not just the exciting stuff blowing up part.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5929" parentid="2846" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>space opera</name>
<description>Space opera is a sub-genre of fiction that emphasizes romantic adventures in space. Space opera generally involves large-scale conflicts between opponents with powerful abilities and technology. The genre will often be melodramatic, sometimes playing music that can be nothing short of awesome. Warfare and a battle of wits are usually less emphasized, preferring romance (with exceptions, e.g. Ginga Eiyuu Densetsu). Some space operas tend to be formulaic and sometimes even prosaic, often employing very simple devices and somewhat obvious strategies. An example of this would be the infamous laws of physics in the Macross universe, in which the main male lead will hardly ever get hit in battle.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6327" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-30">
<name>chemical weapons</name>
<description>A chemical weapon is a device that uses chemicals formulated to inflict death or harm on human beings. The term may also be applied to any toxic chemical or its precursor that can cause death, injury, temporary incapacitation, or sensory irritation through its chemical action. Munitions or other delivery devices designed to deliver chemical weapons, whether filled or unfilled, are also considered weapons themselves. Under the Chemical Weapons Convention, there is a legally binding, worldwide ban on the production, stockpiling, and use of chemical weapons and their precursors. Notwithstanding, large stockpiles thereof continue to exist, usually justified as only a precaution against putative use by an aggressor.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2441" type="appears in" update="2009-01-15">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Earth Federation</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The unified world government that launched the space settlement program and now rules over both Earth and the space colonies. Its main decision-making body is the Earth Federation Assembly, which meets occasionally to pass new legislation.
Though not as cruel and aggressive as the Principality of Zeon`s leaders, the bureaucrats who rule over the Earth Federation are corrupt, weak-willed, and insensitive to the space colonists` desire for independence. After the One Year War, the Federation decides to concentrate its energies on reconstructing Earth instead of the space colonies, further increasing political tensions.</description>
<picture>17701.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2452" type="appears in" update="2009-01-15">
<name>Earth Federation Forces</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The military arm of the Earth Federation. The Federation Forces are divided into several branches, including land, sea, air, and space forces. Until mass production of the RGM-79 GM begins in the final weeks of the One Year War, the Federation Forces are forced to battle the Principality of Zeon`s mobile suits using conventional tanks, planes, and space fighters. Even in the postwar years, the Federation Forces are usually inferior to their opponents in terms of skill, morale, and equipment.</description>
<picture>1824.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="2680" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="13">4.63</rating>
<name>Bask Om</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The brutal field commander of the Titans. While the Titans are effectively a private army controlled by Admiral Jamitov Hymem, Bask is the organisation`s day-to-day leader, responsible for devising strategies and commanding operations. Bask considers his troops above the law and beyond the reach of the Earth Federation command structure, and doesn`t hesitate to take hostages or commit mass murder if it seems like the most effective way to crush dissent.</description>
<picture>85194.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2946" picture="23373.jpg">Gouri Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2681" type="appears in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="2">8.68</rating>
<name>Jamitov Hymem</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The sinister politician who controls the Titans from behind the scenes. From his perch at the pinnacle of the Earth Federation`s military command structure, Jamitov uses the Titans as a private army to further his own scheme for world domination. Cruel, devious, and utterly amoral, this evil genius will stop at nothing to impose his own brand of Earth-supremacist ideology on the suffering peoples of the space colonies.</description>
<picture>85193.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="261" picture="151648.jpg">Ikeda Masaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2715" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="43">8.95</rating>
<name>Haman Karn</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>After the fall of the Principality, a ragtag fleet of Zeon renegades makes its way to the asteroid belt, taking refuge at the asteroid base Axis. By U.C. 0083, the leadership of the this group has passed to a young woman named Haman Karn, the daughter of a Zeon admiral. Rallying the demoralized Axis renegades to the goal of an eventual triumphant return to the Earth sphere, Haman dispatches an advance fleet to aid Delaz in his master plan. Years later, the seeds of rebellion sown by Operation Stardust will be harvested by Haman and her Axis forces.</description>
<picture>85246.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="571" picture="172734.jpg">Sakakibara Yoshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2733" type="appears in" update="2013-06-25">
<name>Titans</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>An elite branch of the Federation Forces created in the aftermath of Operation Stardust. The Titans are charged with hunting down the renegade soldiers of the Principality of Zeon, and suppressing anti-Federation movements, but their overzealous actions soon create a new generation of resistance groups. The Titans are initially headquartered at the Gryps space colony, but as they gain control over the regular Federation Forces and form an alliance with the Republic of Zeon, they also take over Luna II and the Gate of Zedan.</description>
<picture>139051.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="3662" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="3">2.56</rating>
<name>Jerid Messa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The brash and arrogant Titan pilot who becomes Kamille Bidan`s would-be nemesis. One of the initial trio of Gundam Mk.II test pilots, Jerid first picks a fight with our juvenile hero, then demonstrates his piloting prowess by flying his Gundam straight into a police station. Jerid soon realises how unprepared he is for genuine combat, and his recurring humiliation at Kamille`s hands makes him determined to surpass his AEUG rival. His ambition becomes twisted into hatred and revenge as, one after another, his mentors and allies fall in battle against Kamille...</description>
<picture>85191.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3663" type="appears in" update="2012-04-05">
<name>Kacricon Cacooler</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kacricon, along with Jerid Messa and Emma Sheen, is a member of the Titans` initial trio of Gundam Mk.II test pilots. Forced to surrender his Gundam Mk.II during the AEUG`s raid on the Titan headquarters, Kacricon rejoins the battle against the rebels once they reach the moon, serving as a senior partner to the relatively hapless Jerid.</description>
<picture>85198.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3220" picture="24200.jpg">Totani Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3665" type="appears in" update="2012-04-04">
<rating votes="2">5.24</rating>
<name>Lila Milla Rira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An ace pilot of the regular Earth Federation Forces, assigned to the space cruiser Bosnia and stationed at the Luna II asteroid base. The tough, aggressive Lila is assigned to back up the Titans during their pursuit of the AEUG flagship Argama. Her initial rivalry with the arrogant Titan officers gives way to amused pity for the hapless Jerid Messa, and Lila takes it upon herself to give this so-called elite soldier a crash course in basic combat survival.</description>
<picture>85204.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="3666" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-04">
<rating votes="6">5.07</rating>
<name>Astonaige Medoz</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Astonaige Medoz is the Argama`s scruffy chief mechanic, whose hard-working crew somehow manages to keep the ship`s battered mobile suits in good working order. Astonaige and Kamille share a keen interest in mobile suit technology, and the pair collaborate on designing and upgrading the mighty Zeta Gundam.</description>
<picture>85165.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3219" picture="228523.jpg">Hiromori Shingo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3667" type="appears in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="1">7.93</rating>
<name>Blex Forer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The idealistic leader of the AEUG, who travels aboard the Argama during its initial tour of duty. Formerly a high-ranking officer in the Earth Federation Forces, Blex was outraged by the atrocities of the Titans, and used his political and business connections to organize a resistance group. Well-acquainted with his enemies Bask Om and Jamitov Hymem, Blex plots his counter-strategies against them with the calm intelligence of a veteran chess player.</description>
<picture>85185.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="3668" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-04">
<rating votes="3">3.15</rating>
<name>Henken Bekkener</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>This good-natured AEUG officer serves as the Argama`s first captain, and his even temper and jovial demeanor give the rebel flagship a more relaxed atmosphere than under Bright Noa`s command. Along with Blex Forer, Quattro Bajeena, and the junior officer Reccoa Londe, Henken forms part of the AEUG`s initial core leadership. After Bright takes charge of the Argama, Henken transfers to the battleship Radish, from which he continues his shy courtship of the frosty Emma Sheen.</description>
<picture>85173.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3669" type="main character in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="23">5.56</rating>
<name>Reccoa Londe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>This AEUG intelligence operative is a tough, daring spy with nerves of steel and a photographic memory. As warm and generous as she is tough and independent, Reccoa serves as a mentor to AEUG newcomers and a valued adviser to its core leadership. However, she has a streak of restlessness that causes her to seek out dangerous missions, such as scouting out the Federation`s Jaburo base in advance of the AEUG`s full-scale assault.</description>
<picture>85174.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1813" picture="172159.jpg">Katsuki Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3670" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="1">1.22</rating>
<name>Jamaican Daningan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>This arrogant Titan staff officer is one of Bask Om`s top henchmen. Assigned to pursue the AEUG flagship Argama after the rebels stage their daring raid on the Titan headquarters, Jamaican takes command of the cruiser Alexandria and chases the Argama back and forth across the Earth Sphere. While he`s an adequate strategist, Jamaican`s smug, condescending attitude quickly alienates the soldiers under his command.</description>
<picture>85200.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3255" picture="39572.jpg">Keaton Yamada</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3972" type="main character in" update="2012-04-04">
<rating votes="84">7.42</rating>
<name>Kamille Bidan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>This angry young man is destined to become the star pilot of the AEUG resistance group. A resident of the Green Noa 1 space colony, Kamille is the son of two Federation military engineers, and by entering junior mobile suit competitions he`s proven himself a talented engineer in his own right. He also has something of a complex about his feminine name and, as the story begins, Kamille is a budding juvenile delinquent with a hot temper and a hatred of authority figures. After clashing with the Titans he runs off with the rebel soldiers of the AEUG, and is soon invited to join their ranks as a mobile suit pilot. During his adventures, Kamille begins to outgrow his youthful anger and moodiness, and as his Newtype powers emerge he strives to understand the world around him and the people who fight by his side.</description>
<picture>85170.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3973" type="main character in" update="2012-04-04">
<rating votes="26">7.70</rating>
<name>Emma Sheen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Emma is a well-intentioned Titan pilot who switches her allegiance to the AEUG. Initially one of three junior officers chosen to test the Titans` Gundam Mk.II prototypes, Emma defects to the rebels after realizing the brutality of her leaders. Her military discipline and high-quality training make her an invaluable addition to the AEUG`s pilot roster, and when Kamille Bidan receives the Zeta Gundam, Emma inherits his Gundam Mk.II. Even as a rebel soldier, Emma retains her strict professional demeanour, which sometimes causes friction with her more casual comrades.</description>
<picture>85166.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="489" picture="43165.jpg">Okamoto Maya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3974" type="appears in" update="2012-04-10">
<rating votes="332">9.00</rating>
<name>Char Aznable</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Known as the "Red Comet" for his high-speed attack tactics, Char is the most famous of Zeon`s ace mobile suit pilots. He earned his nickname by destroying five Federation battleships during the Battle of Loum, and after the attack on Side 7, he becomes the dreaded nemesis of the White Base crew. However, defeating the Federation isn`t the only thing on Char`s mind, and his distinctive mask hides the face of a young man bent on his own personal quest for revenge. As the story continues, Char begins putting his own complicated schemes into motion, even as he becomes distracted by his growing rivalry with the Gundam`s pilot.
Source: Official Site</description>
<picture>85692.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="3975" type="main character in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="71">8.47</rating>
<name>Quattro Vageena</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Principality of Zeon`s infamous "Red Comet" has now become one of the heroes of the AEUG. After the end of the One Year War, Char infiltrated the ranks of the Earth Federation Forces, assuming the alias "Quattro Bajeena." Witnessing the growing tyranny of the Federation`s Titans faction, Char conspired with other dissident Federation officers to organise the secret resistance group known as the AEUG. However, Char has chosen to shirk the burden of command; while quietly advising his fellow AEUG leaders on matters of strategy, he hides behind his Quattro cover identity, insisting that he is merely an ordinary mobile suit pilot.</description>
<picture>85171.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="413" picture="151647.jpg">Ikeda Shuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3976" type="appears in" update="2012-04-04">
<rating votes="3">4.53</rating>
<name>Hilda Bidan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hilda Bidan is a Lieutenant working in the Research and Development department of the Titans along with her husband Franklin Bidan. An expert in metallurgy, she studies the various types of metals and compounds used to create the armour of mobile suits and weaponry.
Source: gundam.wikia.com</description>
<picture>85245.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="404" picture="151682.jpg">Takashima Gara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3977" type="appears in" update="2012-04-04">
<rating votes="2">1.88</rating>
<name>Franklin Bidan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Franklin Bidan is the principle designer of the RX-178 Gundam Mk-II developed for use by the Titans. Often absorbed into his work he neglects his own family, instead finding comfort in a mistress named Margarita. Taken aboard the Titans flagship Alexandria by Bask Om, he and his wife were used as hostages in negotiations for the return of the Gundam Mk. II`s captured by the AEUG.
Source: Official Site</description>
<picture>85248.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1416" picture="18579.jpg">Ishimori Takkou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4634" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-04">
<rating votes="18">4.73</rating>
<name>Fa Yuiry</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fa is one of Kamille Bidan`s schoolmates from the Green Noa 1 space colony, and more or less his girlfriend. Her parents are arrested by the Titans after Kamille joins the AEUG, while she herself escapes with the help of Bright Noa and makes it to safety aboard the rebel flagship Argama. Fa proceeds to join the ship`s crew, eventually undergoing pilot training so she`ll have something to do other than argue with Kamille.</description>
<picture>85172.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6696">Matsuoka Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4635" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-04">
<rating votes="2">5.35</rating>
<name>Kai Shiden</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A former White Base crew member during the One Year War, who was better known for his cynicism and sarcasm than for his prowess as a Guncannon pilot. Kai has grown up into a flamboyant freelance journalist, whose globe-trotting exploits give him ample opportunity to gather intelligence for the Karaba resistance group, and whose keen perceptions allow him to see right through Char Aznable`s "Quattro Bajeena" guise.
Source: Official Site</description>
<picture>85234.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2583" picture="23188.jpg">Furukawa Toshio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4636" type="appears in" update="2012-04-05">
<name>Roberto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of a pair of veteran Rick Dias pilots who serve as Char Aznable`s wingmen. Roberto is a reliable team player, experienced enough to handle almost any combat situation, and perhaps slightly more serious and diligent than his wisecracking comrade Apolly.</description>
<picture>85186.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2405" picture="23217.jpg">Shioya Kouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4637" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="9">4.88</rating>
<name>Apolly Bay</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Initially serving along with his comrade Roberto as one of Quattro Bajeena`s wingmen, Apolly later goes on to become the chief of the AEUG flagship Argama`s Rick Dias team. Like Quattro, Apolly is a veteran soldier who can handle almost any combat situation. This solid team player provides our heroes with not only valuable support in battle, but also a much-needed dose of sardonic wit.</description>
<picture>85175.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32415" picture="24430.jpg">Abe Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6650" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="1">9.23</rating>
<name>RX-178 Gundam Mk-II</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>This prototype mobile suit was developed by the Titans at the Gryps space colony. Based on the legendary RX-78 Gundam, the Mk.II inherits its predecessor`s high performance and remarkable potential, although it suffers from a few lingering design flaws - notably, its obsolete armour materials. On the other hand, the Mk.II also introduces the radical new movable frame design concept, giving it superb manoeuvrability. All three prototype units are captured by the AEUG resistance group during their raid on the Titans` headquarters. The rebels keep one in service, replacing its sinister Titans colours with a more heroic white and blue scheme, and eagerly dissect the other two in order to learn their technological secrets.</description>
<picture>24420.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6651" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<name>Rick Dias</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>This attack mobile suit, was jointly developed by the AEUG resistance group and their corporate sponsor Anaheim Electronics. Thanks to the participation of former Zeon engineers, its appearance is reminiscent of Zeon`s Rick Dom series. The Rick Dias is the first mobile suit armoured with lightweight Gundarium Gamma alloy, allowing it to carry a larger propellant supply without sacrificing speed or manoeuvrability, and this formidable machine becomes the weapon of choice for the AEUG`s veteran pilots. While the Rick Dias is initially produced in a black colour scheme, Quattro`s trademark red hues soon become its standard colours.</description>
<picture>24419.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6652" type="appears in" update="2009-05-04">
<rating votes="2">7.72</rating>
<name>Hyaku Shiki</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Hyaku Shiki is a prototype machine created as part of the AEUG`s secret "Zeta Project." Its name, which means "Type 100," reflects both its model number and the ambition of its designer Dr. Nagano that this mobile suit would last a hundred years. Originally designed as a transformable model, the Hyaku Shiki`s transformation mechanisms proved to be defective, and it was redesigned as a high-performance non-transformable mobile suit. The Hyaku Shiki`s beam-resistant coating gives it an eye-catching golden exterior, well suited for the use of the AEUG`s principal pilot.</description>
<picture>24421.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6653" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<name>Nemo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>This interceptor mobile suit is introduced as a replacement for the obsolete GM II, and soon becomes the backbone of the AEUG resistance group and its terrestrial Karaba allies. For cost reasons the Nemo is armoured with the older Gundarium Alpha alloy, which is identical to the Luna Titanium used during the One Year War. Nonetheless, it`s better protected than the GM II on which it`s based, and more manoeuvrable as well.</description>
<picture>24422.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6654" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<name>GM II</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The GM II is a minor revision of the mass-produced mobile suit used by the Earth Federation Forces during the One Year War. While it`s undergone modest improvements to its armour materials and sensor systems, and been fitted with the standard linear floating seat and panoramic screen, the GM II is no match for modern mobile suits. In the early stages of the Gryps Conflict, this obsolete machine is used by both the AEUG and the Earth Federation Forces, but it`s soon retired in favour of newer models.</description>
<picture>24423.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6655" type="appears in" update="2009-05-04">
<name>Argama</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The flagship of the AEUG, the Argama was constructed in secrecy at the space colony of Sweetwater, with generous funding from Anaheim Electronics. Its appearance - with its two catapult decks, retractable mega particle cannons, and extendable bridge - hearkens back to that of the legendary White Base. In place of its ancestor`s internal centrifuge, the Argama is equipped with two residential modules, which rotate around the ship to provide artificial gravity. While Henken Bekkener serves as captain during its maiden voyage, the Argama is transferred to Bright Noa`s command once the former White Base captain joins the rebel ranks.</description>
<picture>24424.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6656" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<name>Radish</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The Radish is one of the handful of Irish-class battleships which spearhead the AEUG`s space fleets. A development of the Argama, the Irish class is a more straightforward design with a greater emphasis on firepower. The jade-green Radish, commanded by former Argama captain Henken Bekkener, enjoys a status within the rebel fleet second only to the flagship Argama itself, and the two ships are often deployed together on particularly urgent missions. The Radish also serves as Quattro Bajeena`s base of operations when he`s away from the Argama.</description>
<picture>24425.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6657" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<name>Audhumla</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The Audhumla is one of a handful of Garuda-class transport planes constructed by the Earth Federation Forces. These enormous aircraft are pressed into service during the hurried evacuation of the Federation`s Jaburo base, and the AEUG soldiers seize two of them during their own escape. One of these, the Audhumla, eventually becomes a mobile headquarters for the Karaba resistance group. Able to transport ten to twenty mobile suits and an equivalent number of support sleds - and, incidentally, capable of launching Temptation-class space shuttles into orbit! - the Audhumla makes an excellent airborne carrier. Others of its class, like the Sudori and Melord, are similarly employed by the pursuing Titans.</description>
<picture>24426.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6659" type="appears in" update="2009-05-05">
<name>Gundam Mk-II</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>This prototype mobile suit was developed by the Titans at the Gryps space colony. Based on the legendary RX-78 Gundam, the Mk.II inherits its predecessor`s high performance and remarkable potential, although it suffers from a few lingering design flaws - notably, its obsolete armour materials. On the other hand, the Mk.II also introduces the radical new movable frame design concept, giving it superb manoeuvrability. All three prototype units are captured by the AEUG resistance group during their raid on the Titans` headquarters. The rebels keep one in service, replacing its sinister Titans colors with a more heroic white and blue scheme, and eagerly dissect the other two in order to learn their technological secrets.</description>
<picture>24431.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6660" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<name>Hizack</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Hizack is the first new model of mobile suit produced by the Earth Federation Forces after the One Year War. Based on Zeon`s versatile MS-06 Zaku II, the Hizack incorporates a mixture of Zeon and Federation technologies, but it`s essentially an improved Zaku rather than a genuinely new machine. New armour materials and a lightweight power generator make the Hizack lighter and more agile than its ancestor, and thanks to its ease of operation and maintenance it`s become the standard mobile suit of the regular Federation Forces and Titans alike. However, its inability to drive more than one type of beam weapon at a time means that the Hizack is often equipped with an obsolete machine gun rather than a beam rifle.</description>
<picture>24432.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6661" type="appears in" update="2009-05-04">
<name>Hizack Custom</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>This improved version of the Hizack was developed independently by the Titans. Its armour is reinforced with Gundarium alloy, vulnerable power cables have been relocated internally, and new verniers and stabilizers give it a modest performance boost. When equipped with a long-range beam launcher, the Hizack Custom serves as a capable sniper unit.</description>
<picture>24457.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6662" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<name>Marasai</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Marasai is an improved version of the Hizack, developed by Anaheim Electronics and offered to the Titans as a diplomatic gesture. Thanks to its lightweight Gundarium alloy armour, the Marasai has greater propellant capacity than the Hizack, and its improved rocket engines make it faster as well. Most importantly, its higher power output enables it to drive two types of beam weapons simultaneously. While it never fully replaces the Hizack in the Titans ranks, this versatile mobile suit is often assigned to novice pilots.</description>
<picture>24434.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6663" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<name>Barzam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>While the Titans` transformable mobile suits prove to be very effective in battle, their complexity and high performance make them unsuitable for the average pilot. As a result, the Titans develop this final mass production model, a non-transformable machine with better performance and cost-effectiveness than the AEUG`s Nemo. However, only limited numbers of these formidable mobile suits have reached the battlefield by the time the conflict ends.</description>
<picture>24435.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6664" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<name>Asshimar</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Unlike previous mobile suits, which could fight in mid-air only by making brief rocket-assisted jumps, this transformable mobile armour is capable of sustained atmospheric flight. The Asshimar`s transformation mechanisms are treated with performance-enhancing magnet coating, enabling it to switch from mobile suit to saucer-shaped mobile armour form within half a second, and thus making possible all kinds of novel aerial combat tactics. After proving its worth in the hands of test pilot Buran Blutarch of the Oakland Newtype Lab, the Asshimar enters full production and is posted to key areas like the Earth Federation capital in Dakar.</description>
<picture>24468.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6665" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<name>Asshimar</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>Unlike previous mobile suits, which could fight in mid-air only by making brief rocket-assisted jumps, this transformable mobile armour is capable of sustained atmospheric flight. The Asshimar`s transformation mechanisms are treated with performance-enhancing magnet coating, enabling it to switch from mobile suit to saucer-shaped mobile armour form within half a second, and thus making possible all kinds of novel aerial combat tactics. After proving its worth in the hands of test pilot Buran Blutarch of the Oakland Newtype Lab, the Asshimar enters full production and is posted to key areas like the Earth Federation capital in Dakar.</description>
<picture>24469.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6666" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<name>Gabthley</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Gabthley is a prototype transformable mobile suit designed by the brilliant Paptimus Scirocco. With its shoulder-mounted cannons and powerful fedayeen rifle, it excels at long-range bombardment, and its beam sabers and the grappling claws built into its legs make it dangerous in close combat as well. In its insect-like mobile armour form, the Gabthley exhibits remarkable agility thanks to its dozens of rocket engines and manoeuvring verniers, and this high-performance machine proves to be a worthy adversary for the AEUG`s Zeta Gundam.</description>
<picture>24470.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6667" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<name>Gabthley</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The Gabthley is a prototype transformable mobile suit designed by the brilliant Paptimus Scirocco. With its shoulder-mounted cannons and powerful fedayeen rifle, it excels at long-range bombardment, and its beam sabers and the grappling claws built into its legs make it dangerous in close combat as well. In its insect-like mobile armour form, the Gabthley exhibits remarkable agility thanks to its dozens of rocket engines and manoeuvring verniers, and this high-performance machine proves to be a worthy adversary for the AEUG`s Zeta Gundam.</description>
<picture>24471.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6668" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<name>Hambrabi</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Hambrabi is another prototype transformable mobile suit created by Paptimus Scirocco, whose simple design makes it more suitable for mass production. Although its generator power and thruster output are relatively low, the Hambrabi is very manoeuvrable, and - since it can use its hand weapons and forearm claws even in its mobile armour form - it has excellent melee combat capabilities. Yazan Gable and his wingmen use their trio of Hambrabis in closely coordinated team manoeuvres, employing electrical weapons like the "sea serpent" and "spider web" for tricky surprise attacks.</description>
<picture>24472.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6669" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<name>Hambrabi</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The Hambrabi is another prototype transformable mobile suit created by Paptimus Scirocco, whose simple design makes it more suitable for mass production. Although its generator power and thruster output are relatively low, the Hambrabi is very manoeuvrable, and - since it can use its hand weapons and forearm claws even in its mobile armour form - it has excellent melee combat capabilities. Yazan Gable and his wingmen use their trio of Hambrabis in closely coordinated team manoeuvres, employing electrical weapons like the "sea serpent" and "spider web" for tricky surprise attacks.</description>
<picture>24473.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6670" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<name>Byalant</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Developed at the Titans` Kilimanjaro base, this prototype mobile suit is designed for high-speed atmospheric flight. The Byalant`s thermonuclear jet engines let it accelerate rapidly and remain airborne for extended periods. To reduce its weight, the Byalant has mega particle cannons built into its forearms rather than an external beam rifle, but as a result its manipulator hands are fairly rudimentary and its melee combat capabilities relatively poor. Once its thrusters are replaced with standard rocket engines, the Byalant proves to be an effective space fighter as well.</description>
<picture>24458.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6671" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<name>Baund Doc</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>As the Gryps Conflict nears its end, Titan field commander Bask Om scrambles to organize an elite combat team made up of artificially-enhanced Cyber-Newtypes. The team`s members are equipped with this transformable mobile armour, whose eccentric appearance belies its surprising combat effectiveness and high performance. Armed with a beam sabre and oversized grappling claws, the Baund Doc has excellent close combat abilities even in its streamlined mobile armour form, as well as a devastating mega particle cannon. Three prototype units were produced, the first one a two-seater model with a monitoring station for Newtype researcher Loren Nakamoto.</description>
<picture>24459.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6672" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<name>Baund Doc</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>As the Gryps Conflict nears its end, Titan field commander Bask Om scrambles to organize an elite combat team made up of artificially-enhanced Cyber-Newtypes. The team`s members are equipped with this transformable mobile armour, whose eccentric appearance belies its surprising combat effectiveness and high performance. Armed with a beam sabre and oversized grappling claws, the Baund Doc has excellent close combat abilities even in its streamlined mobile armour form, as well as a devastating mega particle cannon. Three prototype units were produced, the first one a two-seater model with a monitoring station for Newtype researcher Loren Nakamoto.</description>
<picture>24460.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6673" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<name>Messala</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>This huge transformable mobile armour is a handmade creation of the brilliant Paptimus Scirocco, constructed aboard the transport ship Jupitris during its round trip to the outer reaches of the solar system. The Messala`s powerful engines are designed to counter the pull of Jupiter`s gravity, and its mega particle cannons and missile pods give it firepower comparable to that of a space warship. In its mobile suit form, the Messala`s beam sabres, forearm claws, and grenade launchers make it a formidable foe in close combat as well. As Scirocco continues his mobile suit development efforts, he hands this early work down to a succession of his loyal followers.</description>
<picture>24461.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6674" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<name>Messala</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>This huge transformable mobile armour is a handmade creation of the brilliant Paptimus Scirocco, constructed aboard the transport ship Jupitris during its round trip to the outer reaches of the solar system. The Messala`s powerful engines are designed to counter the pull of Jupiter`s gravity, and its mega particle cannons and missile pods give it firepower comparable to that of a space warship. In its mobile suit form, the Messala`s beam sabres, forearm claws, and grenade launchers make it a formidable foe in close combat as well. As Scirocco continues his mobile suit development efforts, he hands this early work down to a succession of his loyal followers.</description>
<picture>24462.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6675" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<name>Palace Athene</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>This elegant mobile suit is the second in Paptimus Scirocco`s series of handmade custom machines. Comparable in size to the transformable Messala, the Palace Athene is a heavy attack model, whose firepower is sufficient to destroy even the heavily-armoured warships of the modern era. Of course, it`s also formidable in close combat against enemy mobile suits.</description>
<picture>24446.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6676" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<name>Bolinoak Sammahn</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Bolinoak Sammahn is the third of the handmade mobile suits created by Paptimus Scirocco aboard the transport ship Jupitris. Equipped with a radome in its head and laser sensors in its left forearm, the Bolinoak is well-suited for patrol and reconnaissance missions. The shield integrated into its right arm - which houses a pair of multi-purpose beam sabres and a set of grappling claws - also gives it excellent close combat capabilities.</description>
<picture>24447.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6677" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<name>The O</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The fourth and last of Paptimus Scirocco`s handmade custom machines, designed expressly for Scirocco`s personal use. The O`s thick Gundarium armour renders it virtually indestructible but, thanks to its powerful thrusters and the fifty manoeuvring verniers which cover its exterior, this unique mobile suit is also supremely agile. For extra protection at close ranges, a pair of "hidden hands" - capable of wielding the mobile suit`s beam swords - unfold from its skirt armour. The O is also equipped with a psychic interface called the "bio-sensor," which allows its Newtype pilot to control the mobile suit via mental commands, further increasing the responsiveness and manoeuvrability of this remarkable machine.</description>
<picture>24463.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6678" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<name>MRX-009 Psyco Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>This huge transformable mobile armour, was developed by the Murasame Newtype Lab for use by their artificially-enhanced Cyber-Newtypes. The Murasame Lab`s original goal was simply to equip a Gundam with a psycommu system, the psychic interface developed by Zeon scientists during the One Year War. However, the sheer bulk of this device - and the addition of features like a Minovsky craft flotation system, a protective anti-beam barrier, and complex transformation mechanisms - resulted in the Psyco Gundam becoming a forty-metre monster. As well as its immense firepower, the Psyco Gundam houses a more subtle weapon... a combat system which overrides its pilot`s will and forces her to fight.</description>
<picture>24464.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6679" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="1">4.67</rating>
<name>MRX-009 Psyco Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>This huge transformable mobile armour, was developed by the Murasame Newtype Lab for use by their artificially-enhanced Cyber-Newtypes. The Murasame Lab`s original goal was simply to equip a Gundam with a psycommu system, the psychic interface developed by Zeon scientists during the One Year War. However, the sheer bulk of this device - and the addition of features like a Minovsky craft flotation system, a protective anti-beam barrier, and complex transformation mechanisms - resulted in the Psyco Gundam becoming a forty-metre monster. As well as its immense firepower, the Psyco Gundam houses a more subtle weapon... a combat system which overrides its pilot`s will and forces her to fight.</description>
<picture>24465.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6680" type="appears in" update="2009-05-05">
<name>MRX-010 Psyco Gundam Mk.II</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>This transformable mobile armour, an improved version of the original Psyco Gundam, is theoretically the most powerful mobile weapon in the entire Earth Sphere. However, the Psyco Gundam Mk.II enters battle in an incomplete state, unable to transform into its "mobile fortress" form or deploy its full range of fighting capabilities, and its performance is further hampered by the mental instability of its pilot. In theory, the Psyco Gundam Mk.II can deploy remote-controlled "reflector bits" to redirect its beam fire towards its targets, and the beam swords in its wire-guided detachable forearms make it equally dangerous in close combat.</description>
<picture>24466.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6681" type="appears in" update="2009-05-05">
<name>MRX-010 Psyco Gundam Mk.II</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>This transformable mobile armour, an improved version of the original Psyco Gundam, is theoretically the most powerful mobile weapon in the entire Earth Sphere. However, the Psyco Gundam Mk.II enters battle in an incomplete state, unable to transform into its "mobile fortress" form or deploy its full range of fighting capabilities, and its performance is further hampered by the mental instability of its pilot. In theory, the Psyco Gundam Mk.II can deploy remote-controlled "reflector bits" to redirect its beam fire towards its targets, and the beam swords in its wire-guided detachable forearms make it equally dangerous in close combat.</description>
<picture>24467.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6682" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<name>Dogosse Gier</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>This immense battleship, twice the size of cruisers like the Argama and Alexandria, was created to serve as the flagship of the Titan fleet. With a dozen mobile suit catapults and batteries of huge cannons, the Dogosse Gier is virtually a fleet unto itself. Although Char spies this ship under construction during the initial AEUG raid on the Titans` headquarters, it doesn`t enter battle until the Titans set out to capture the lunar city of Von Braun. The Dogosse Gier is initially entrusted to Paptimus Scirocco, but as the Titans` leaders become increasingly suspicious of their scheming underling, Bask Om decides to take charge of this mighty battleship himself.</description>
<picture>24449.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6683" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<name>Alexandria</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The Alexandria is the first in a new series of Earth Federation space cruisers specifically designed to serve as mobile suit carriers. While its modular construction is reminiscent of Zeon`s old Musai cruiser, an Alexandria-class vessel can carry an entire squadron of mobile suits, allowing a single ship to operate as an independent taskforce. The Titan fleet includes several of these cruisers, but the most familiar is the Alexandria itself, which is usually commanded by Jamaican Daninghan or Gady Kinsey.</description>
<picture>24450.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6684" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<name>Salamis Kai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The Salamis-class cruiser has been the workhorse of the Earth Federation Space Force since before the start of the One Year War, and these ships have remained in service for many years thanks to periodic upgrades. The most recent round of revisions has given the venerable Salamis a mobile suit launch deck, and a hangar with enough space for three or four machines. Both the AEUG and Titan space fleets are made up primarily of these standard Salamis cruisers, with the rebel ships painted in pale green and the Titan versions retaining their original blue-grey colours.</description>
<picture>24451.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6685" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<name>Jupitris</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>This 2000-metre-long transport ship is part of the Jupiter Fleet, whose vessels voyage out to the gas giant Jupiter to collect helium-3 fuel for the Earth Sphere`s fusion reactors. The Jupitris is propelled by a set of thermonuclear pulse engines, and equipped with a rotating ring which provides its crew with artificial gravity. This massive ship serves as Paptimus Scirocco`s home base; after he joins forces with the Titans he has the Jupitris parked in Earth orbit, and he returns here periodically to plan his schemes and work on his menagerie of handmade mobile suits.</description>
<picture>24452.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6686" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<name>Qubeley</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Qubeley is the crowning technological achievement of the renegade Zeons who took refuge at the asteroid base Axis. Essentially a compact, humanoid version of the mobile armour MAN-08 Elmeth, the Qubeley is equipped with a fully functional psycommu system and an array of tiny remote-controlled weapon pods called "funnels." Via the psycommu system, a Newtype pilot can use her thought waves to control both the Qubeley`s funnels and the mobile suit itself. However, the Axis forces have only one Newtype powerful enough to operate this amazing machine, and so the Qubeley has become the personal mobile suit of Axis leader Haman Karn.</description>
<picture>24453.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6687" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<name>Gaza C</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>After years of exile in the far reaches of the solar system, the renegade Zeons who inhabit the asteroid base Axis return to the Earth Sphere, bringing with them hundreds of these transforming mobile suits. The Gaza C is based not on the Zeon mobile suit of the One Year War era, but on the worker machines which the renegades used to construct their asteroid headquarters. Although it has the firepower and thruster output of a mobile armour, the Gaza C suffers from exceptionally poor manoeuvrability. Combined with the Axis forces` fondness for mass formation tactics, this renders it vulnerable to experienced enemy pilots.</description>
<picture>24454.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6688" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<name>Gwadan</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The Gwadan is the flagship of the Axis fleet, a massive battleship constructed in the distant reaches of the asteroid belt during the Zeon renegades` years of exile. Larger even than the Titan flagship Dogosse Gier, the Gwadan possesses enough firepower to disable the Titans` dreaded Colony Laser with a single volley from its main guns.</description>
<picture>24456.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6689" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<name>Gwanban</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>After the loss of the Axis flagship Gwadan, Haman Karn transfers her base of operations to the somewhat smaller battleship Gwanban. There appear to be other ships of this class, among them the Gwanzan, which served as the flagship of the Axis Advance Fleet that returned to the Earth Sphere during the Delaz Conflict of U.C.0083.</description>
<picture>24455.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6690" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="1">9.23</rating>
<name>MSZ-006 Zeta Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>This machine is the culmination of the AEUG`s secret "Zeta Project," whose goal was to create a transformable mobile suit capable of operating in every environment from weightless space to Earth`s gravity. By transforming into a streamlined Wave Rider form, the Zeta Gundam can ride the shockwaves of atmospheric re-entry and then cruise through Earth`s atmosphere. As a mobile suit, it combines the movable frame technology of the Gundam Mk.II with the lightweight Gundarium Gamma alloy of the Rick Dias, not to mention an extraordinary level of firepower. In the hands of the young Newtype pilot Kamille Bidan, one of its principal designers, the Zeta Gundam proves to be the most powerful weapon in the rebels` arsenal.</description>
<picture>24478.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6691" type="appears in" update="2015-02-08">
<name>MSZ-006 Zeta Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>This machine is the culmination of the AEUG`s secret "Zeta Project," whose goal was to create a transformable mobile suit capable of operating in every environment from weightless space to Earth`s gravity. By transforming into a streamlined Wave Rider form, the Zeta Gundam can ride the shockwaves of atmospheric re-entry and then cruise through Earth`s atmosphere. As a mobile suit, it combines the movable frame technology of the Gundam Mk.II with the lightweight Gundarium Gamma alloy of the Rick Dias, not to mention an extraordinary level of firepower. In the hands of the young Newtype pilot Kamille Bidan, one of its principal designers, the Zeta Gundam proves to be the most powerful weapon in the rebels` arsenal.</description>
<picture>24479.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="9127" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-04">
<rating votes="170">4.75</rating>
<name>Haro</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haro is the mechanical mascot of the Gundam science fiction anime metaseries, and is the only character that appears in more than one timeline.
The original Haro is a little robot companion built by the main character Amuro Ray. It is a cute testament to Amuro`s exceptional talent for machines. Haro`s features include a limited range of speech, and the ability to hover (in environments with atmosphere and low gravity) by flapping its ear-like appendage coverings. Haro can usually be found rolling behind Amuro`s next door neighbor Frau Bow. The ability to detect brain waves is also one of Haro`s functions; in one of the episodes, Haro actually claimed that the brain wave of Amuro was lowered/different.
In Zeta Gundam, a mass-produced Mk-II version of Haro ends up in the hands of that series` main protagonist Kamille Bidan, who initially suspects it to be the original. He repairs the robot, only to have it constantly address him as Amuro.
During the events of Char`s Counterattack, Amuro gives a "third-generation" Haro to Hathaway, the son of his captain Bright Noa.
Haro continues to permeate the Gundam franchise, having appeared in Gundam SEED as Lacus Clyne`s multi-colored horde of simple-speech robot pets, built for her by Athrun Zala. These Haros are roughly 1/4 the size of their Universal Century counterparts and are similar in function, however a few possess certain abilities such as unlocking doors. Lacus`s favorite Haro is a pink machine that she refers to as "Pink-Chan" (often translated as "Mr. Pink" or "Pinky"). Another notable Haro in Lacus`s collection is "Navy-Chan", a navy blue robot on which she paints a mustache bearing a distinct resemblance the facial ornament of the ∀ Gundam of the CC (正歴 Seireki) calendar system. The rest of Lacus` Haros have been seen in yellow, orange, blue, green, and black. The parody comic Mobile Suit Gundam SEED Club Yonkoma states that Athrun has built a total of 35 Haros for Lacus.
In Mobile Suit Gundam 00, Celestial Being had produced unknown numbers of Haros as an assistant of daily maintenance works. Currently at least 6 unique Haros have appeared in the animation production. The Haros in the series took much more maintenance and combat role than any other series` counterpart, usually seeing them operating with various machines, including mobile weapons.</description>
<picture>28615.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3947" picture="25762.jpg">Shou Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10951" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-05-06">
<rating votes="37">7.98</rating>
<name>Lalah Sune</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>This young woman is a test subject of the Flanagan Institute, a Zeon research organization created to investigate the gifted humans known as "newtypes." While the exploits of pilots like Char and Amuro have led to speculation that they may be newtypes, Lalah`s powers are obvious and undeniable, and accompanied by a profound spiritual awareness. However, despite her gentle nature, Lalah is fiercely loyal to the man who saved her life - Char Aznable, the scheming "Red Comet."</description>
<picture>87316.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13526" type="appears in" update="2009-12-03">
<name>Anaheim Electronics</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Anaheim Electronics is a fictional civilian manufacturing company that appeared in the Universal Century timeline of the Gundam anime metaseries. The company appeared first in Mobile Suit Zeta Gundam(aired in 1985) as the main funder, as well as the main military supplier and manufacturer of the faction AEUG. However, the company also design and manufacture weapons for both the Earth Federation, its elite faction Titans, enemy of the AEUG, and third party faction Axis Zeon, which in turn became the enemies of the AEUG later in the series until the end of the sequel, Mobile Suit Gundam ZZ(aired in 1986). The company continues its manufacturing contracts in Mobile Suit Gundam ZZ and Mobile Suit Gundam: Char`s Counterattack(aired in 1988), where its weapons are always seen in both sides of the conflicting factions. In the novel, Gundam Sentinel(serialized in 1989), which happens between the conflicts of the anime series Mobile Suit Zeta Gundam and Mobile suit Gundam ZZ, Anaheim Electronics became the main contractor of the Earth Federation of its new mass-production units like Nero and the Z Plus series for the Task Force alpha and also provided prototype units such as S Gundam as a testbed for the Federation. The Gundam Sentinel`s Model Graphix special edition, Gundam Wars III, the battle of real Gundam in turn gave a detail analysis of the company and retconned the production and testing history. The company`s earlier history was then told in the anime Mobile Suit Gundam 0083: Stardust Memory(OVA first released in 1991), where it first became the contract manufacturer of the Earth Federation. In December 2003, celebrating the 20th Anniversary of the Gundam metaseries, a book Anaheim Journal was released, disguised as a monthly magazine published by Anaheim Electronics in UC0100. The company also appeared in the comic Silhouette Formula 91, and later in the anime Mobile Suit V Gundam.
Based on the Moon, Anaheim Electronics originally produced a wide range of technological applications from consumer electronics to battleships and even space colonies. Their service do not end at electronic goods, according to Anaheim Journal, they also have departments providing cosmetics, vacation travelling plans (with their own resort space colonies) and credit cards, ultimately fitting the definition of a zaibatsu. Upon the end of the One Year War, Anaheim was able to acquire the assets and personnel of the Zeonic Corporation - a mobile suit manufacturing firm of the defeated Principality of Zeon. This merger enabled Anaheim Electronics to enter the lucrative business of mobile suit production. As such, the firm was contracted by the Earth Federation to become its principal mobile suit provider until the end of the second Neo Zeon movement.
Anaheim Electronics is known for its profit-oriented mindset - creating advanced mobile weapons for any faction that would be willing to pay, then selling the same technology to the former`s enemy. During the rise of the oppressive Titans taskforce, Anaheim funded the AEUG and gave it access to their technology and safe shelter as the Titans restricted their trading engagements, despite the Earth Federation Forces and the Titans being their primary customer. Later, the company would service contracts from the remnants of the Principality of Zeon such as Axis and Neo Zeon. According to GundamOfficials, this is due to the gigantic company structure. With several development departments, each departments can be contracted by different factions without needing to notify the main executive board. This policy is simply adopted to minimize the companies overall responsibility; after the main battle, they can always just apply the penalty on a single department`s head instead of making the whole company suffer.
In the story of Silhouette Formula 91, after U.C. 0123, Anaheim Electronics lost its contract bid with the EFF to SNRI`s new miniaturized mobile suit designs, which were cheaper, more versatile and higher in performance. Anaheim Electronics had to maintain its low profile until U.C. 0153, and financially supported League Militaire in secrecy defending Earth from Zanscare Empire.
According to the official timeline, Anaheim Electronics remains as the main manufacturer of mobile suits in the Earth Sphere until the Earth Federation itself was disbanded in the U.C. 0200s, although its monopoly in the field was literally obliterated since the second Universal Century with the entrance of the Federation-backed competitor SNRI.
Corporate Profile
Name: Anaheim Electronics, Inc.
Main Office: Anaheim, Moon
Chairman of the Board: Melanie Hue Carbine (as of U.C. 0087)
Known Factories:
Von Braun City
Granada
La Vie en Rose mobile factory/docking ship</description>
<picture>39669.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="16540" type="appears in" update="2018-08-16">
<rating votes="9">5.82</rating>
<name>Mineva Lao Zabi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>As the child heir to the Zabi dynasty, Mineva is the nominal leader of the Zeon renegades who took refuge at the asteroid base Axis. The daughter of Zeon admiral Dozle Zabi, Mineva was a mere infant when her people fled to the asteroid belt, and her whole life has been spent in preparation for her glorious destiny as the ruler of a revived Principality of Zeon. However, beneath the royal finery and behind the rehearsed speeches is a lonely little girl, starved of affection and longing for companionship.
Source: Official Site
She makes her first appearance as a new born in episode 34 of http://anidb.net/a715 [Mobile Suit Gundam]. She later appears in http://anidb.net/a719 [Zeta Gundam] and she is the female lead of http://anidb.net/a6517 [Gundam Unicorn], under the alias http://anidb.net/ch13499 [Audrey Burn].</description>
<picture>85677.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="229" picture="152363.jpg">Itou Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18913" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="8">4.69</rating>
<name>Paptimus Scirocco</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A sinister genius who joins forces with the Titans. Known as "the man from Jupiter," Scirocco is a member of the Federation`s Jupiter Fleet, whose huge transport ships collect helium fuel from the outer planets. Not only is he a gifted mobile suit designer, skilled pilot, and powerful Newtype, but Scirocco`s keen intellect and overwhelming charisma enable him to easily manipulate those around him - particularly women. Though his goals and ideology are utterly alien to those of the Titans, their leaders recruit Scirocco to bolster their fighting power, foolishly thinking that his oath of loyalty will protect them from this dangerous renegade.</description>
<picture>85196.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="199" picture="23218.jpg">Shimada Bin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18914" type="appears in" update="2012-04-04">
<rating votes="6">8.43</rating>
<name>Four Murasame</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The artificially enhanced cyber-Newtype who pilots the mighty Psyco Gundam. The fourth product of the Earth Federation`s Murasame Newtype Lab, Four is a war orphan with no memory of her past, whose masters have promised to restore her lost memories if she performs to their satisfaction. Four`s opportunity to prove herself in battle comes when she is assigned to aid the Titans in their pursuit of the rebel transport plane Audhumla. However, her priorities are thrown into question by her developing rapport with AEUG pilot Kamille Bidan.</description>
<picture>85203.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2055" picture="21393.jpg">Shimazu Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18915" type="appears in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="4">5.77</rating>
<name>Rosamia Badam</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An artificially enhanced Cyber-Newtype produced by the Earth Federation`s Augusta Newtype Lab. Traumatized by the sight of a falling space colony during the One Year War, Rosamia alternates between sadistic aggression and childlike terror, and her psychological instability is only worsened as her masters subject her to repeated reprogramming. Later in the story, she is dispatched to infiltrate the Argama crew, an undercover assignment which puts her on the path to complete mental disintegration.</description>
<picture>49827.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23578" picture="64914.jpg">Fujii Kayoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29813" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="2">1.20</rating>
<name>Katz Kobayashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Katz is one of the trio of war orphans who were adopted after the One Year War by White Base crewmembers Hayato Kobayashi and Fraw Bow. Katz now feels he`s old enough to follow in the footsteps of his childhood heroes, and after helping Amuro escape Federation surveillance and join the resistance fighters, Katz makes his way into space to fight alongside the AEUG. Like his foster father Hayato, Katz is impulsive and reckless, not to mention dangerously naive.
Source: Official Site</description>
<picture>85169.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3282" picture="24710.jpg">Nanba Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29814" type="appears in" update="2012-04-04">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Kikka Kobayashi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Adopted child of Hayato and Fraw Kobayashi</description>
<picture>85244.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3947" picture="25762.jpg">Shou Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29815" type="appears in" update="2012-04-04">
<name>Letz Kobayashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Adopted child of Hayato and Fraw Kobayashi</description>
<picture>85243.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4720" picture="27543.jpg">Tonguu Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29816" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-04">
<rating votes="5">2.22</rating>
<name>Hayato Kobayashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The former Guntank pilot has become a leader of the terrestrial Karaba resistance group, operating a secret command post from his aerospace museum at the Kennedy Space Center. After the AEUG`s Jaburo assault, Hayato takes charge of the captured transport plane Audhumla and turns it into a mobile headquarters for the rebel forces. Thanks to the leadership of "Director Hayato," Karaba`s small force proves to be a valuable complement to the AEUG`s space fleet.
Source: Official Site
After the events of Gundam 0079, Hayato marries Fraw Bow and they adopt Katz, Letz and Kikka.</description>
<picture>85187.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3243" picture="24223.jpg">Suzuki Kiyonobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29817" type="appears in" update="2012-04-04">
<rating votes="2">7.53</rating>
<name>Fraw Kobayashi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fraw Bow marries Hayato Kobayashi after the events of Gundam 0079 and together they adopt Katz, Letz and Kikka.</description>
<picture>85247.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4941" picture="222847.jpg">Ukai Rumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29818" type="appears in" update="2012-04-04">
<rating votes="4">8.10</rating>
<name>Mirai Noa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>After the One Year War, White Base navigator Mirai Yashima married the ship`s captain Bright Noa, and their family has since expanded to include their son Hathaway and daughter Cheimin. The Noa family live in a military residence at the Federation`s Jaburo base, effectively making them hostages to ensure Bright`s continued loyalty, but when Bright defects to the AEUG resistance group Mirai spirits their kids out of harm`s way and sets out to get them safely off the Earth.
Source: Official Site</description>
<picture>85241.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5637" picture="188452.jpg">Shiraishi Fuyumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29819" type="appears in" update="2011-03-11">
<name>Hathaway Noa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The son of Mirai Noa and Bright Noa.</description>
<picture>67520.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="29820" type="appears in" update="2011-03-11">
<name>Cheimin Noa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Daughter of Mirai Noa and Bright Noa. Sister of Hathaway Noa.</description>
<picture>67521.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1870" picture="186893.jpg">Mizutani Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29823" type="appears in" update="2012-04-04">
<rating votes="1">1.22</rating>
<name>Wong Lee</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>This domineering and foul-tempered fellow is an executive of the lunar corporation known as Anaheim Electronics, one of the primary sponsors of the AEUG, resistance group. As the personal representative of Anaheim chairman Melanie Hue Carbine, Wong feels perfectly entitled to meddle in the AEUG`s strategic planning or physically discipline ill-mannered recruits like Kamille Bidan.
Source: Official Site</description>
<picture>85238.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3361" picture="24391.jpg">Natori Yukimasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29824" type="appears in" update="2012-04-04">
<rating votes="9">5.63</rating>
<name>Beltorchika Irma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>This young Karaba operative first appears to guide the rebels` Audhumla carrier plane to a secret base, boldly flying her replica biplane through the thick of a mobile suit battle. Beltorchika immediately latches onto the famous Amuro Ray, and her strident defense of her hero`s interests alienates many of her comrades.
Source: Official Site</description>
<picture>85188.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2193" picture="21749.jpg">Kawamura Maria</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29825" type="appears in" update="2012-04-04">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Stephanie Luio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The outward face of the Luio family from Hong Kong, who has contacts that can get almost anything done.</description>
<picture>85239.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="29826" type="appears in" update="2012-04-04">
<name>Buran Blutarch</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Major Buran Blutarch, in charge of a squadron at one time including Rosamia Badan.</description>
<picture>85237.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="601" picture="165793.jpg">Nakamura Hidetoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29827" type="appears in" update="2012-04-04">
<name>Ben Wooder</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Captain Ben Wooder replaces Buran Blutarch as commander of the Sudori.</description>
<picture>85235.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3383" picture="24325.jpg">Oobayashi Ryuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29828" type="appears in" update="2012-04-04">
<name>Namicar Cornell</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Four Murasame`s nurse and superior.</description>
<picture>85240.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="29829" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-04">
<name>Torres</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Argama`s navigator, Torres is a spacenoid born and raised in the lunar city of Granada.</description>
<picture>85184.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32415" picture="24430.jpg">Abe Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29830" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-04">
<name>Saegusa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the communications officers on the Argama.</description>
<picture>85179.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2405" picture="23217.jpg">Shioya Kouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29831" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-04">
<rating votes="10">4.00</rating>
<name>Caesar</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the communications officers on the Argama.</description>
<picture>85182.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3297" picture="24321.jpg">Takamiya Shunsuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29832" type="appears in" update="2012-04-04">
<name>Samarn</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the communications officers on the Argama.</description>
<picture>85180.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2279" picture="23207.jpg">Satou Masaharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29833" type="appears in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="2">6.78</rating>
<name>Mouar Pharaoh</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>This female Titan pilot aids Jerid Messa during the evacuation of Jaburo and subsequently becomes his loyal sidekick. Her talents soon attract the attentions of Paptimus Scirocco, but she opts to stick with Jerid instead, and their partnership gradually deepens into romance.
Source: Official Site</description>
<picture>85201.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="571" picture="172734.jpg">Sakakibara Yoshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29834" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="8">5.96</rating>
<name>Sarah Zabiarov</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A naive young cadet trained at the Titans` private Newtype Lab, and assigned to Jerid Messa`s supervision for her first tour of combat duty. Despite her inexperience, Sarah is clever and resourceful. Her talents earn her the attention of the scheming Scirocco, and she soon becomes a devoted minion of her "Master Paptimus." Nonetheless, this young Newtype has a good heart and a troubled conscience, raising the hope that the entreaties of our heroes may yet overcome the evil influence of Scirocco`s charms.
Source: Official Site</description>
<picture>85189.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1870" picture="186893.jpg">Mizutani Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29835" type="appears in" update="2012-04-05">
<name>Gady Kinsey</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takes over the Alexandria after Jamaican`s death.</description>
<picture>85199.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3220" picture="24200.jpg">Totani Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29836" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-04">
<rating votes="2">2.03</rating>
<name>Yazan Gable</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Titan pilot distinguished by his superb fighting skills and sheer aggression. Yazan joins the crew of the Titan cruiser Alexandria around the time of the attack on Von Braun City and becomes the ship`s resident ace pilot, eclipsing the hapless Jerid Messa. Brutal and bloodthirsty, he lives for the thrill of the hunt, and despises cautious commanders who try to spoil his fun. He`s later joined by a pair of equally cunning and sadistic wingmen, Ensigns Dunkel Cooper and Ramsus Hasa.
Source: Official Site</description>
<picture>85197.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="297" picture="233915.jpg">Ootsuka Houchuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29837" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-04">
<rating votes="1">1.09</rating>
<name>Shinta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>When Char Aznable returns from a trip to the Earth Federation capital in Dakar, he brings with him a pair of orphaned children, who remain aboard the Argama as mascots and comic relief. For the most part, Shinta and Qum are entrusted to the care of their babysitter Fa Yuiry and their pet robot Haro, but when they`re really bored they`ll pester Kamille, Bright, or the kindly ship`s doctor Hasan for additional entertainment.
Source: Official Site</description>
<picture>85183.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="548" picture="186185.jpg">Sakamoto Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29838" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-04">
<rating votes="1">1.09</rating>
<name>Qum</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>When Char Aznable returns from a trip to the Earth Federation capital in Dakar, he brings with him a pair of orphaned children, who remain aboard the Argama as mascots and comic relief. For the most part, Shinta and Qum are entrusted to the care of their babysitter Fa Yuiry and their pet robot Haro, but when they`re really bored they`ll pester Kamille, Bright, or the kindly ship`s doctor Hasan for additional entertainment.
Source: Official Site</description>
<picture>85178.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3947" picture="25762.jpg">Shou Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29839" type="appears in" update="2012-05-26">
<name>Hasan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A military physician assigned to the assault landing ship Nahel Argama. Hasan is a veteran doctor who served aboard the original Argama during the Gryps War, and he has been with the Nahel Argama since the first Neo Zeon War.</description>
<picture>88449.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2279" picture="23207.jpg">Satou Masaharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29840" type="appears in" update="2011-03-11">
<name>Manack</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the crewmen of the Argama.</description>
<picture>5962.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="29841" type="appears in" update="2011-03-11">
<name>Botty</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lieutenant Botty is one of the Argama`s Rick Dias pilots.</description>
<picture>5963.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="468" picture="17383.jpg">Kikuchi Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43421" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-10">
<rating votes="8">7.00</rating>
<name>Amuro Ray</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The famous pilot of the original RX-78 Gundam remained in the Federation military after the end of the One Year War, but he`s been placed under virtual house arrest by a government that considers Newtypes to be dangerous rogue elements. Trapped in his luxury mansion, and deeply scarred by his traumatic wartime experiences, Amuro is initially content to leave the fighting to other people this time. However, his old friends eventually goad Amuro back into action, and he goes on to become the foremost ace of the Karaba resistance group.
Source: Official Site</description>
<picture>85678.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="454" picture="17354.jpg">Furuya Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43422" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-10">
<rating votes="13">5.59</rating>
<name>Bright Noa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The captain of the legendary White Base remained in the Federation military after the One Year War, but was regarded with suspicion by the repressive new regime, and as this story begins the famous captain has been relegated to commanding a space shuttle that ferries government VIPs back and forth. After witnessing the brutality of the Titans firsthand, Bright finally decides to cast his lot with the AEUG resistance group. Bright is swiftly installed as the captain of the rebel flagship Argama, and his charisma and keen judgement make him a remarkable asset to the AEUG.
Source: Official Site</description>
<picture>85685.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3136" picture="24121.jpg">Suzuoki Hirotaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43423" type="appears in" update="2012-04-10">
<rating votes="4">9.54</rating>
<name>Sayla Mass</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sayla has a brief cameo in Mobile Suit Zeta Gundam. She is shown listening by radio to Char`s speech at the Federation Assembly in Dakar and she makes a appearance in Mobile Suit Gundam ZZ as the person who saved Judau Ashta`s younger sister, Leina.
Source: gundam.wikia.com</description>
<picture>85688.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="45275" type="appears in" update="2012-05-27">
<name>MS-21C Dra-C</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>A mass production mobile suit developed during the Delaz Conflict. Thanks to upgrades such as a gatling gun on its right arm, and the engravings added all over its body, this mobile suit doesn`t look at all like an antique.</description>
<picture>88543.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="81850" type="appears in" update="2016-04-22">
<name>Loren Nakamoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63732.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2026" picture="21352.jpg">Yara Yuusaku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81851" type="appears in" update="2016-04-22">
<name>Gates Capa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63733.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="283" picture="17113.jpg">Yao Kazuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81852" type="appears in" update="2016-04-22">
<name>Ajis Aziba</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63734.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="283" picture="17113.jpg">Yao Kazuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81853" type="appears in" update="2016-04-22">
<name>Dunkel Cooper</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63735.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="468" picture="17383.jpg">Kikuchi Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81854" type="appears in" update="2016-04-22">
<name>Ramsus Hasa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63736.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3219" picture="228523.jpg">Hiromori Shingo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95606" type="appears in" update="2018-05-18">
<name>RMS-117 Galbaldy Beta</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>217709.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="8376" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-03-02</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒いガンダム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Black Gundam</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Sette anni dopo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuroi Gundam</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8377" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-03-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">旅立ち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Departure</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Fuga</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tabidachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8378" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-03-16</airdate>
<rating votes="6">9.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カプセルの中</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Within the Capsule</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Dentro la capsula</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Capsule no Naka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8379" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-03-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エマの脱走</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Emma`s Desertion</title>
<title xml:lang="it">LA decisione di Emma</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Emma no Dassou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8380" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-03-30</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">父と子と...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Father, Son and...</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Padre e figlio</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chichi to Ko to...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8381" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-04-06</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地球圏へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the Earth Sphere</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Sulla terra</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikyuu Ken e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11116" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-04-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サイド1の脱出</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Escape from Side 1</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Fuga da Side 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Side 1 no Dasshutsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14643" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-11-02</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キリマンジャロの嵐</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Storm Over Kilimanjaro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kilimanjaro no Arashi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14644" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-09-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シャアの帰還</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Char`s Return</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Char no Kikan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14645" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-02-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロザミアの中で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">From Rosamia`s Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rosamia no Naka de</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14646" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">月の裏側</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dark Side Of The Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il lato oscuro della Luna</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuki no Uragawa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14647" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-11-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">永遠のフォウ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Four To Infinity</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eien no Four</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14648" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-12-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さよならロザミィ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goodbye Rosamia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sayonara Rosamia</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14649" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-10-12</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">謎のモビルスーツ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mysterious Mobile Suits</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nazo no Mobile Suits</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14650" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-11-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">レコアの気配</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reccoa`s Sign</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Reccoa no Kehai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14651" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-08-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シロッコの眼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scirocco`s Vision</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Scirocco no Me</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14652" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-08-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コロニーが落ちる日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Day Of The Colony Drop</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Colony ga Ochiru Hi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14653" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-07-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">灼熱の脱出</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Fiery Escape</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shakunetsu no Dasshutsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14654" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-12-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">目覚め</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Awakening</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mezame</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14655" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-02-15</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">生命散って</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scattered Souls</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seimei Chitte</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14656" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-09-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サイド2の危機</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Side 2 Crisis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Side 2 no Kiki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14657" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-02-22</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙を駆ける</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Run Through The Cosmos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu o Kakeru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14658" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-09-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジュピトリス潜入</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jupitris Infiltration</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jupitris Sennyuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14659" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-10-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アクシズからの使者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Messenger From Axis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Axis Kara no Shisha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14660" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-12-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">グリプス始動</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gryps` Debut</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gryps Shidou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14661" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-01-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天から来るもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Celestial Body</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ten Kara Kuru Mono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14662" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-10-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙[そら]が呼ぶ声</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Call From Space</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sora ga Yobu Koe</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14663" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-01-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゼダンの門</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Gate Of Zedan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zedan no Mon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14664" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-07-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">とらわれたミライ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Captive Mirai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Torawareta Mirai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14665" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-07-13</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シンデレラ・フォウ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cinderella Four</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cinderella Four</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14666" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-02-01</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙の渦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Universal Maelstrom</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu no Uzu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14667" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ムーン・アタック</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Moon Attack</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moon Attack</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14668" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-06-01</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シャトル発進</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shuttle Launch</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il lancio dello shuttle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuttle Hasshin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14669" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-07-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゼータの鼓動</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Zeta`s Heartbeat</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zeta no Kodou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14670" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-11-30</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">湖畔</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lakeside</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kohan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14671" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-04-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新しい絆</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A New Bond</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Un nuovo legame</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atarashii Kizuna</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14672" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-08-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">反撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Counterattack</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hangeki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14673" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-06-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">白い闇を抜けて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Through The White Mist</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiroi yami o Nukete</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14674" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-09-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジェリド特攻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jerid`s Suicide Attack</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jerid Tokkou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14675" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-12-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハマーンの嘲笑</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Haman`s Sneer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haman no Choushou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14676" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-08-31</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジオンの亡霊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Spirit Of Zeon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zeon no Bourei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14677" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-06-08</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アムロ再び</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Amuro Again</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Amuro vola ancora</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Amuro Futatabi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14678" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-06-15</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カツの出撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Katz`s Sortie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Katz no Shutsugeki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14679" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-10-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハーフムーン・ラブ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Half-Moon Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Half-Moon Love</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14680" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジャブローの風</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Winds Of Jaburo</title>
<title xml:lang="it">I venti di Jaburo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jaburo no Kaze</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14681" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1986-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シロッコ立つ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scirocco Steps Forward</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Scirocco Tatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14682" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-05-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大気圏突入</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Into The Atmosphere</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Entrando nell`atmosfera</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taikiken Totsunyuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14683" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-05-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">再会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reunion</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Riunione</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14684" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-11-16</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダカールの日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dakar`s Day</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dakar no Hi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14685" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1985-06-29</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ホンコン・シティ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hong Kong City</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hong Kong City</title>
</episode>
<episode id="87741" update="2010-05-10">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1985-03-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="87742" update="2010-05-10">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1985-08-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="87743" update="2010-05-10">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>1985-03-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="87744" update="2010-05-10">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>1985-11-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
