<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7187" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-01-09</startdate>
<enddate>2010-03-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kaitou Reinya</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Таинственный похититель Лена</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Неуловимая воровка Рейня</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">怪盗丽娅</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">怪盗レーニャ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Phantom Thief Reinya</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">怪盗丽奈</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.reinya.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="10858" type="Chief Direction">Something Yoshimatsu</name>
<name id="16957" type="Original Plan">Up-Front Style</name>
<name id="54575" type="Work">Stingray</name>
<name id="54576" type="Direction">Iwami Hideaki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the "nonsensical comedy" 4-koma manga by the same name.
Tanaka Reina, a member of Hello Project`s girl band Morning Musume, serves as the inspiration for the main character Reinya, a thief that is the stuff of urban legends.
Tanaka (Onegai My Melody Kirara`s title character) will play Reinya, a girl who wears a signboard for the Faminya convenience store near a police station by day. By night, she is a whimsical thief chased by bumbling police officers, led by the handsome Keiji-san ("Detective," Okano Kousuke) and the cool Keibu-san ("Inspector," Youki Sou). Joining Reinya on her escapades is her trusty assistant, the mouse Chuutarou (Okano).</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="164">3.08</permanent>
<temporary count="166">5.14</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>80683.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11166</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7561</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>18375</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4583</identifier>
<identifier>sfoevh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.reinya.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>怪盗レーニャ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1938</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>335485</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12402</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>怪盗丽娅</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>phantom-thief-reinya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2805" parentid="2798" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>4-koma manga</name>
<description>Yonkoma manga (4コマ漫画, four cell manga, or 4-koma for short), a comic-strip format, generally consists of gag comic strips within four panels of equal size ordered from top to bottom. (They also sometimes run right-to-left horizontally or use a hybrid 2x2 style, depending on the layout requirements of the publication in which they appear.) Though the word yonkoma comes from the Japanese, the style also exists outside of Japan in other Asian countries as well as in the English-speaking market.</description>
<picurl>70558.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3515" parentid="2898" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-10">
<name>shinsengumi</name>
<description>The Shinsengumi were a special police force of the late shogunate period.</description>
<picurl>191098.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4170" parentid="5626" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-08-08">
<name>police are useless</name>
<description>The civilian law enforcement representatives do not seem to be of much use, when trying to take on the usually vastly superior foes.
The "helpless" and often clumsy antics of the police can be used as a comedy element.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4200" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>flash animation</name>
<description>Made in Adobe Flash (formerly known as Macromedia Flash), a software package for rich multimedia and Web animations and applications. Very popular on amateur fanproductions (like the ones found in places such as YouTube)
Sadly, Flash has also earned a bad reputation among the animation purists because it leads to cheap low-quality animation jobs, since anyone with a hint of creativity and a "idea" on its head can easily learn how to produce an animated feature in Flash... and sell it to the masses.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4223" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>running gag</name>
<description>(Bit) character(s) play out a short skit several times during the course of the anime. The skit may or may not be exactly the same but does tend to have the same theme throughout.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4516" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>animal abuse</name>
<description>Violence against animals. The humane society will not like this.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5626" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>adults are useless</name>
<description>For when adults can`t do anything right.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5834" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>show within a show</name>
<description>A fictional TV (or radio, or stage) show that takes place within an actual TV show; or, occasionally, a fictional instalment or incarnation of an actual show. Many comedies have short one-off gags where they parody existing shows.
Example: A large part of Martian Successor Nadesico is centred around the fictional popular anime Gekigangar III, which is being watched by several characters of the Nadesico crew.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5980" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-24">
<name>live-action imagery</name>
<description>This anime incorporates still images and/or video footage of real-world objects and locations into the animation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6248" parentid="2872" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>thievery</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="13352" type="main character in" update="2012-07-01">
<rating votes="2">4.20</rating>
<name>Kaitou Reinya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4353.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="10995" picture="39480.jpg">Tanaka Reina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13354" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-30">
<rating votes="1">1.45</rating>
<name>Chuutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2835.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="389" picture="56097.jpg">Okano Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13355" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-30">
<rating votes="1">2.70</rating>
<name>Keiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2836.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="389" picture="56097.jpg">Okano Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46518" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-01">
<rating votes="1">1.45</rating>
<name>Keibu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4365.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="36864" picture="135594.jpg">Youki Sou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46523" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-01">
<rating votes="1">6.59</rating>
<name>Fukei Notti</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4383.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="31277" picture="83931.jpg">Noto Arisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46526" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-01">
<rating votes="1">9.12</rating>
<name>Senpuuki</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4390.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2903" picture="23287.jpg">Misawa Sachika</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="112936" update="2020-02-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2010-03-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらばレーニャ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goodbye Reinya!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saraba Reinya!</title>
<summary>Deep in the holy mountains, Reinya trains with the old master to gain the strength to defeat the invaders who beat her once. One day, the master introduces Reinya to Black Reinya and her sidekick Black Chutaro. The appearance of new rivals sets Reinya and Chutaro`s fighting spirits aflame, but the two do not stand a chance against Black Reinya`s incredible strength.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>539994</identifier>
<identifier>phantom-thief-reinya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="112937" update="2020-02-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2010-03-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">浮気はゆるさぁーん!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`ll Never Forgive This Affair!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uwaki wa Yurusaan!</title>
<summary>Reinya gets excited about true love of Akemi and Tatsuhiko while watching her favorite soap opera "Love in Space: From the Magellanic Clouds with Love" when Tatsuhiko walks into Faminya with his real girlfriend. Unable to distinguish between fiction and reality, the furious Reinya follows the couple. When Reinya pulls out a gun-shaped object, Chutaro begins to worry.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>539876</identifier>
<identifier>phantom-thief-reinya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="112938" update="2020-02-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2010-03-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あ~ん, レーニャ初敗北の巻!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Oh, No... Reinya Is Finally Beaten!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aan, Reinya Hatsu Haiboku no Maki!</title>
<summary>In her heat induced delirium, Reinya drinks what she thinks is a can of juice brought to her by a balloon. When she finally comes to, she realizes she just stole some juice from a little girl, who runs off to report the incident to her father, the Captain. That night, the Captain and his daughter read Reinya`s letter. His daughter unsettles him when she makes him promise he will catch Reinya this time. At that moment, Reinya makes her appearance.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>539798</identifier>
<identifier>phantom-thief-reinya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="112939" update="2020-02-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2010-03-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新撰組はじめましたぁ~!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Organize the Shinsengumi Troops!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinsengumi Hajimemashitaa!</title>
<summary>Policewoman Nocchi is so absorbed in the Oedo Police Department`s Brain Analyzer, she doe not notice when the electric fan blows her skirt up. Just when the Captain shows up, Nocchi suddenly shouts, "90% of Reinya is Shinsengumi!" and leaves the police department while muttering something under her breath. Meanwhile, Reinya returns to her hideout with the golden dark soy sauce with Nocchi hidden inside. Reinya uses her Kitty Eyes to discover Nocchi is Isami Kondo, leader of the Shinsengumi.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>539658</identifier>
<identifier>phantom-thief-reinya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="112940" update="2020-02-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2010-02-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エヘッ? レーニャのデート大作戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mission Impossible: Reinya`s Date!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ehe? Reinya no Date Daisakusen!</title>
<summary>Reinya invites the Detective on a picnic as Faminya`s clerk Reina, making the obsessive Detective`s imagination run wild has he fantasizes about marrying her. However, Reinya cares nothing for the Detective`s feelings and desires only to get information about the golden macadamia chocolate. On the day of the picnic, Reinya is enjoying the Detective`s homemade sandwiches when suddenly, her face turns blue. The sandwiches contain natto, Reinya`s forbidden food, causing her to break into many small Reinyas which are swept away in a river.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>539608</identifier>
<identifier>phantom-thief-reinya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="112941" update="2020-02-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2010-02-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">うそっ! レーニャが呪われたぁ~!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">No Way! Reinya Is Cursed!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uso! Reinya ga Norowaretaa!</title>
<summary>Reinya snatches a golden witch from the billionaire`s mansion, but for some reason, he is relieved to see it go. Strange things begin happening to Reinya. Mysterious carnivorous plants take over her hideout, and she finds a hole in her favorite socks. The golden witch turns out to be a cursed object bringing bad luck to Reinya`s hideout. When Chutaro is eaten by the carnivorous plant, he advices her to throw the statue away, and Reinya is forced to choose between her love for gold and her love for her sock.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>539472</identifier>
<identifier>phantom-thief-reinya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="112942" update="2020-02-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2010-02-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">忍者になりたぁ~い!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Wanna Be a Ninja!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ninja ni Naritaai!</title>
<summary>Wanting to leave her name in history, Phantom Thief Reinya tries to come up with a memorable special ability. Inspired by the book "How to be a Ninja", she begins training in ninja techniques. However, the electric fan of her "Hidden Leaf Technique" leaves her in a mess, and she nearly drowns when a dragonfly perches the straw of her "Hidden Water Technique." Realizing the plastic straw is too thin for the "Hidden Water Technique," she replaces it with a bamboo tube just as a sparrow approaches.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>539430</identifier>
<identifier>phantom-thief-reinya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="112943" update="2020-02-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2010-02-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">え~ん! ワナにかかったぁ~!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shoot! Reinya Is Trapped!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Een! Wana ni Kakattaa!</title>
<summary>While fleeing the scene in her flying balloon swing, Reinya drops her shoe. Chutaro warns her the police might perform a DNA analysis on some hair attached to her shoe, but Reinya merely fusses over the pimple on her neck and her refusal to eat natto. Finally, Reinya decides to sneak into the Oedo Police Department and finds her shoe on a table. She approaches without caution, only to be caught in the Captain`s secret weapon designed specifically to thwart Reinya, the "Phantom Thief Sticky Glue."
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>539386</identifier>
<identifier>phantom-thief-reinya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="112944" update="2020-02-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2010-01-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">うそっ! 命狙われた~!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">No Way! Someone`s Got It In for Me!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uso! Inochi Nerawareta!</title>
<summary>Reinya`s favorite soap opera “Stolen Love in Space: From the Magellanic Clouds with Love” is on the air. The show`s love triangle between a mollusk-shaped and rock-shaped alien brings tears to her eyes when a package from Feline Express sets off her hideout`s alarm system. Reinya takes the package to the idiots of the Oedo Police Department who take it to the Hazardous Material Management Facility to be examined.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>539326</identifier>
<identifier>phantom-thief-reinya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="112945" update="2020-02-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2010-01-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スペ~ス略奪愛!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stolen Love in Space?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Space Ryakudatsu Ai!?</title>
<summary>A message from Reinya arrives at the Oedo Police Department announcing her plans to steal the Golden Kid`s Meal. The thee idiots arrive at the scene of the crime to secure the area. On her way to the Golden Kid`s Meal, Reinya activates her “Kitty Mode,” transforming her eyes into lamps and giving her superhuman speed. Reinya is a kitty-person, a cat-human hybrid.
Meanwhile, the Captain and Nocchi play cards while waiting for Reinya, but the thief does not make an appearance.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>538956</identifier>
<identifier>phantom-thief-reinya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="112946" update="2020-02-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2010-01-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナイショの話ィ~!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tete-a-Tete</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Naisho no Hanashii!</title>
<summary>While reading reading her favorite “Monthly Thief Magazine,” Reinya spots a fortune telling her to steal something that drives married women wild for good luck and begins planning her next burglary.
Up above in the convenience store, the three idiot police arrive. Too busy reading to deal with customers, Reinya sends Chutaro to deal with them, and his apathy drives her crazy. Reinya reluctantly heads to the register, driving the Detective into his world of delusion as he expresses his love for Reina with exaggerated gestures.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>538954</identifier>
<identifier>phantom-thief-reinya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="112947" update="2020-02-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2010-01-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">怪盗レ~ニャ参上やん!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Here Comes Phantom Thief Reinya!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaitou Reinya Sanjou yan!</title>
<summary>Reinya works as the poster girl for convenience store Faminya by day and steals golden treasures as Phantom Theif Reinya by night. With her sidekick Chutaro, Reinya plays a slapstick game of cat-and-mouse with the perverted Captain, the delusional Detective, and Nocchi of the Oedo Police Department.
The Golden Umakabai, a solid gold statue of a local instant noodle brand, is scheduled to go on display at the Hakata Museum. Following her motto “nothing is greater than gold,” Reinya decides to snatch this golden treasure. However, the Captain, the Detective, and Nocchi are on full alert for Reinya at the museum.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>538952</identifier>
<identifier>phantom-thief-reinya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="149628" update="2020-02-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2010-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Pilot</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
