<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7208" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-04-24</startdate>
<enddate>2010-04-24</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Trigun: Badlands Rumble</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">劇場版トライガン</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">트라이건: 배드랜즈 럼블</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">trigun movie</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">TRIGUN BADLANDS RUMBLE</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Trigun: Badlands Rumble</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Trigun - Badlands Rumble</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Trigun: Rachot v Badlands</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="53" type="Parent Story">Trigun</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="219" approval="38" total="46">Cowboy Bebop: Tengoku no Tobira</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="6">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="26239">If you liked the series, you will like this as well.  If you`ve never seen the series, its not necessary, but you might get all of the characters` quirks.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="82150">Although made mainly for fans, it can be watched without prior knowledge of the series and be caught in its setting and unforgettable main character. Being a side story, don`t expect anything new in relation to the anime, as a matter of fact, it`s closer to the original manga than its anime counterpart. 
Nevertheless, you will find it nostalgic and extremely enjoyable to see these characters again, after so long.
A treat for Trigun fans, and while not being a brilliant film, it does its job good enough to be worth another look at Planet Gunsmoke and the Humanoid Typhoon.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="54199">One of The best! :D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="199638">Must see for fans.
For the rest - currently the best scifi wild west in anime. Awesome settings, nicely done guns &amp; gunfights, very cool vehicles.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="248393">One of the finest animes that i watched recently.. A very well made side story of my favorite anime,
even if you didn`t see the series you can watch this masterpiece.
Vash &amp; Wolfwood are the best</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.trigun-movie.com</url>
<creators>
<name id="3630" type="Character Design">Yoshimatsu Takahiro</name>
<name id="9055" type="Original Work">Naitou Yasuhiro</name>
<name id="7168" type="Direction">Nishimura Satoshi</name>
<name id="4547" type="Music">Imahori Tsuneo</name>
<name id="9269" type="Chief Direction">Inoue Hideki</name>
<name id="3630" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yoshimatsu Takahiro</name>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a seinen manga by http://anidb.net/cr9055 [Naitou Yasuhiro], serialised in YK Comics.
In Macca, a town surrounded by quicksand: with rumours spreading that the legendary robber Gasback has his sights set on the town, mayor Kepler has brought together bounty hunters to protect the town. These bounty hunters have been following Gasback from town to town in hopes of bagging the prize. http://anidb.net/ch9909 [Meryl] and http://anidb.net/ch9910 [Milly] have come to town to assess the situation as insurance agents, but are shocked by this turn of events. Moreover, http://anidb.net/ch4423 [Vash the Stampede] is also in town, along with the female bounty hunter http://anidb.net/ch26345 [Amelia] and http://anidb.net/ch9911 [Nicholas D. Wolfwood].</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2604">7.93</permanent>
<temporary count="2619">7.94</temporary>
<review count="3">6.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>55347.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9499</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4106</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.trigun-movie.com</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Trigun:_Badlands_Rumble</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>トライガン</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>335748</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11855</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="201" parentid="2872" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-01">
<name>bounty hunter</name>
<description>A bounty hunter is one who hunts and captures targets (be it people, animals, etc.) for monetary gain, preferably without killing/destroying their target. Despite being illegal in most of the world today, it is a legal profession in the United States and Philippines (a former commonwealth of the US), who are known as "bail enforcement agents".
If they are only and constantly hired to kill, they are likely an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="760" parentid="2274" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>robot helper</name>
<description>In a http://anidb.net/t2846 [science fiction] setting, the robot helper is, in a comedic sense, pretty much equivalent to what the "cute comic relief http://anidb.net/t1835 [animal sidekick]" is in a fantasy setting. The usually small machine has artificial intelligence, enabling it to support their owner / master with advice or help with menial tasks.
http://anidb.net/t1278 [Androids] should not be considered robot helpers since these are far more complex; use the android tag instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1179" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-21">
<name>indecisive</name>
<description>This character has trouble taking their own decisions, and may rely on others to do that instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2180" parentid="2636" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-24">
<name>cyborg</name>
<description>A cyborg is a cybernetic organism (i.e. an organism that has both artificial and natural systems). The term was coined in 1960 when Manfred Clynes and Nathan Kline used it in an article about the advantages of self-regulating human-machine systems in outer space. D. S. Halacy`s Cyborg: Evolution of the Superman in 1965 featured an introduction which spoke of a "new frontier" that was "not merely space, but more profoundly the relationship between `inner space` to `outer space` -a bridge...between mind and matter." The cyborg is often seen today merely as an organism that has enhanced abilities due to technology, but this perhaps oversimplifies the category of feedback.
Fictional cyborgs are portrayed as a synthesis of organic and synthetic parts, and frequently pose the question of difference between human and machine as one concerned with morality, free will, and empathy. Fictional cyborgs may be represented as visibly mechanical (e.g. the Cybermen in the Doctor Who franchise or The Borg from Star Trek); or as almost indistinguishable from humans (e.g. the "Human" Cylons from the re-imagining of Battlestar Galactica). The 1970s television series The Six Million Dollar Man featured one of the most famous fictional cyborgs. Cyborgs in fiction often play up a human contempt for over-dependence on technology, particularly when used for war, and when used in ways that seem to threaten free will. Cyborgs are also often portrayed with physical or mental abilities far exceeding a human counterpart (military forms may have inbuilt weapons, among other things).
Real (as opposed to fictional) cyborgs are more frequently people who use cybernetic technology to repair or overcome the physical and mental constraints of their bodies. While cyborgs are commonly thought of as mammals, they can be any kind of organism.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42022.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2461" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>domestic cat</name>
<description>The cat (Felis catus or Felis silvestris catus), also known as the domestic cat to distinguish it from other felines and felids, is a small, usually furry, domesticated, and carnivorous mammal. Cats are valued by humans for companionship and their ability to hunt vermin and household pests, and are often kept as indoor pets, in which case they are also called housecats; they have been associated with humans for at least 9,500 years and are currently the most popular pet in the world, being found almost everywhere on Earth.
Cats are similar in anatomy to the other felids, with light, strong and flexible bodies, excellent hearing, sense of smell, and near darkness eyesight, quick reflexes, sharp retractable claws, and teeth adapted to killing small prey. They are skilled predators and hunt over 1,000 species for food. Despite being solitary hunters, cats are a social species, with communication means that include pheromones, body language and a variety of vocalizations, such as meowing, purring, trilling, hissing, growling and grunting.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>41283.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2629" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-16">
<name>desert</name>
<description>Setting with vast amounts of sand, merciless high temperatures, and very little water.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2847" parentid="2611" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-22">
<name>Western</name>
<description>The setting and/or world are pretty much like in Western films depicting the American Old West, with cowboys, Indians, deserts, small towns, bounty hunters, and lots of revolvers.
Just think John Wayne, Clint Eastwood, and Sergio Leonne`s The Good, The Bad and The Ugly, or A Fistful of Dollars.</description>
<picurl>220675.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3053" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-23">
<name>allergy to potential love interests</name>
<description>A character will be found responding to potential love interests, usually of the opposite gender, as if allergic to them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3432" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>pacifism</name>
<description>The belief and following of principles stating all and any conflict has a peaceful solution without use of violence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4073" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-15">
<name>unusual weapons -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This anime tag is set to be split into multiple character tags. If you are sure of what existing tag to use, please apply it to the relevant characters and remove this one from the anime. On the other hand, if you know why this tag is applied and either expect a new tag will be necessary or don`t know how to handle the retagging, simply remove it from the anime and explain the case to the mod.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4521" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>lost technology</name>
<description>Any advanced technology or science-related knowledge that was lost for some reason fits the description. This could be technology from a time before a post-apocalyptic cataclysm, knowledge gained a long time ago but forgotten, or the relics of an old alien civilization only recently discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6480" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-26">
<name>gun - TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This character uses at least one type of gun, or this anime has one character that uses at least one type of gun. Please tag the characters with the appropriate gun type tags (e.g. pistol, revolver, assault rifle, etc) and remove this tag from them or their corresponding anime afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="4423" type="main character in" update="2009-06-27">
<rating votes="371">8.99</rating>
<name>Vash the Stampede</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Known as "The Humanoid Typhoon" due to the destruction which surrounds him. He is initially discovered by Meryl and Milly, representatives from an insurance agency investigating claims made due to damages caused by the mysterious "Humanoid Typhoon". The pair find Vash while he is being chased by bandits who want to collect the bounty on "The $$60,000,000,000 (sixty billion double dollar) Man".</description>
<picture>20489.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="183" picture="16992.jpg">Onosaka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9909" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-25">
<rating votes="85">6.72</rating>
<name>Meryl Stryfe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Meryl Stryfe AKA "Derringer Meryl" and her junior coworker, Milly, are agents of the Bernardelli Insurance Society sent to evaluate claims regarding Vash the Stampede. She`s hotheaded and strong willed. Initially, she finds Vash to be a nuisance and dismisses the idea that he is the legendary Humanoid Typhoon. As time passes, she realizes that Vash isn`t the villain that he is made out to be nor the buffoon that he presents himself to be. Gradually, she comes to respect Vash and love him deeply, though in the anime her love is more romantic than in the manga. Although she doesn`t often fight alongside Vash, she hides many derringer-style "throwaway" pistols under her coat. In the manga she becomes petrified of Vash after she witnesses his Plant-like nature and sees through his eyes the destruction of July City. After Bernardelli shuts down while Knives is ravaging the planet, she and Milly assume support roles along with Brad and Luida to help combat Knives. At the end of the manga`s story, the two become investigative reporters for the planet`s first television broadcasting channel, continuing to follow Vash wherever he goes.</description>
<picture>29996.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3058" picture="23960.jpg">Tsuru Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9910" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-25">
<rating votes="81">5.14</rating>
<name>Milly Thompson</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Milly Thompson is a fellow Bernardelli agent, and friend and assistant to Meryl. Despite physically towering over Meryl, Milly looks up to her and always refers to her in a respectful manner. She appears rather simple, but has a kind heart and also reveals a strength of character and genuine optimism. Milly comes from a very large family, and writes huge masses of letters to them constantly (known as "The Milly Monthly"). Milly manages to hide a very heavy concussion gun, referred to as a "stun-gun", under her coat. The shots, which pop out into the shape of an X-shaped claw, are so powerful they can even knock over trucks. Although she does not have a relationship with Wolfwood in the manga, events after his death indicate that she might have had a romantic interest in him. Her reaction to Wolfwood`s loss in the anime is considerably greater compared to the manga. The manga version of Milly has blond hair whereas the anime depiction has browner-colored hair.</description>
<picture>29997.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="271" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9911" type="main character in" update="2009-06-25">
<rating votes="137">8.23</rating>
<name>Nicholas D. Wolfwood</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nicholas D. Wolfwood, also known as Nicholas the Punisher. Nicholas is a traveling preacher, but contrary to his job as a man of God he`s quite devious and violent, a foil to his companion Vash`s peaceful and goofy nature. Wolfwood often criticizes Vash`s philosophy of not killing, stating that one day he`s going to have to. Despite this, he adopts Vash`s non-lethal style though he still kills when he feels it`s needed. Wolfwood carries a special, large cross-shaped gun called the Punisher, which contains a large machine gun in its bottom section and a rocket launcher at its top. In the anime the sides hold several Colt handguns. Wolfwood`s background and development are almost completely different between the manga and anime versions of the character.</description>
<picture>29999.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27" picture="26123.jpg">Hayami Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19377" type="main character in" update="2010-07-05">
<rating votes="12">6.97</rating>
<name>Gasback</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50692.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="560" picture="41051.jpg">Isobe Tsutomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26345" type="main character in" update="2016-02-17">
<rating votes="19">6.79</rating>
<name>Amelia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Amelia is a female bounty hunter. She initially meets Vash the Stampede aboard a sand steamer where he comes to her aid while she is being accosted by thugs. Vash attempts to win her over with flattery and fanciful tales of them being destined to meet, but she shrugs him off. Amelia shows a peculiar and often humorous allergic reaction to being touched by men which causes her to break out and itch. She is strong and capable as a bounty hunter, but often show signs of youth and innocence especially when it comes to her low tolerance for alcohol. She is initially little more than irritated by Vash and later brought to anger by his actions, but she gradually comes to accept his outlook on life.
 Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>183090.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="227" picture="205854.jpg">Sakamoto Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="113509" update="2018-08-16">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>90</length>
<airdate>2010-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
<summary>Twenty years ago, Vash the Stampede allowed an infamous outlaw named Gasback to escape final justice. Now, on the streets of Macca City, Vash is about to learn a hard truth about consequences - and he might end up paying for the lesson with his life.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="126286" update="2010-12-19">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2010-04-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126287" update="2010-12-19">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2010-04-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221317" update="2019-09-11">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>75</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">スタッフインタビュー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Staff Interview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221318" update="2019-09-11">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">アフレコ風景</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Post-recording</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221319" update="2019-09-11">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>50</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">シネマサンシャイン池袋 舞台挨拶ダイジェスト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cinema Sunshine Ikebukuro: Stage Greeting Digest</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
