<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7224" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-07-03</startdate>
<enddate>2010-09-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Mitsudomoe</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Three Way Struggle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Mitsudomoe 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">MDOM</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">みつどもえ</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">超元气三姐妹</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7948" type="Sequel">Mitsudomoe Zouryouchuu!</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4241" approval="68" total="79">Kyou no Go no Ni</anime>
<anime id="5029" approval="52" total="93">Kodomo no Jikan (2007)</anime>
<anime id="6646" approval="32" total="58">Hanamaru Youchien</anime>
<anime id="4309" approval="17" total="24">Minami-ke</anime>
<anime id="2787" approval="15" total="27">Ichigo Marshmallow</anime>
<anime id="6054" approval="8" total="12">Kyou no Go no Ni (2008)</anime>
<anime id="12957" approval="5" total="11">Mitsuboshi Colors</anime>
<anime id="106" approval="4" total="13">Azumanga Daiou The Animation (2002)</anime>
<anime id="9722" approval="3" total="17">Non Non Biyori</anime>
<anime id="14156" approval="0" total="3">Watashi ni Tenshi ga Maiorita!</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="20">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="264691">first i thought it wouldn`t be that good but i was wrong. it`s fu**ing hilarious and really enjoyable.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="379712">While it may be funny, there isn`t much that sets it apart from Kodomo no Jikan and Hanamaru Kindergarten. 

All three are about new teachers who have just embarked on their very first class. 

All three have very similar looking main character teachers.

All three have the main teacher in love with a big breasted co-worker (before a fellow teacher, the gym teacher and now a nurse)

All three have three main loli`s with very similar personalities to their counterparts. 

If you liked either Kodomo no Jikan or Hanamaru Kindergarten you may like this but the similarities are a little ... annoying in my opinion. Like I said there isnt much that sets this apart from the other two so ... : /</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="40905">Agree completely with Yoru-chan. So I`m dropping at the half of the first episode. I`ve already watched Hanamaru and Kodomo, so no copies for me. Btw the one that I really like is Kodomo no Jinkan.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="330374">While i watched i felt like i was forcing myself in doing so. But still was fun to watch and relaxing? Have a lot of funny and ass hurting moments. Picked it since i was bored, time well spent. :D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="261766">One of the funniest and cutest shows I`ve seen.
The jokes tend to be a "bit" dirty so I hope you don`t mind it getting weird.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="379737">its funny as hell xD</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="806168">Mature mixed with very immature content.
Overall very ecchi anima with loads of references to panties and boobs.
The first 2 episodes might stretch your limit with dragging a joke for 4 minutes and more the later episodes speed up the joke delivery.

If you are looking for cute and moe, nothing to see here.

Many times you can see where the joke is going and watch it crawl towards it`s target.
Overuse of the trope "sustained misunderstanding".

I agree with the nurse Aiko the whole class seems perverted.
It`s only half the class tho, the rest is mostly misinterpreted.

Wish they brought out Miku mom more.
I feel very sorry for Marui Soujirou he has a tough life raising these 3 girls.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="34912">This is a very fun and silly anime with a unique art style.  And it gets funnier as the show progresses.  Highly recommend! :-)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="426261">Judging by the first episode, it will be more akin to South Park than Kodomo no Jikan.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="277195">If you are a person who LOVE comedy, then you have to watch this serie!
There is NO ending laught!
This is a must see serie!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="56620">Funny as all hell!!! I laughed so much it literally hurt!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="301049">I hope this anime goes on for a bazillion seasons. Mitsudomoe was the funniest anime I`ve seen since azumanga. You have to watch this.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="403713">its story is about elementary school students funny misunderstandings. very funny and a very must see</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="516692">comedy from misunderstanding :)
funny, hilarious, silly anime
don`t be fooled with elementary school setting
watch this and you won`t regret :D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="604679">hilarious. not for kids.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="325333">Don`t get discouraged by the visuals or elementary school setting. Anime could hardly get any funnier than this imo.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="349866">This is truly one of the best comedies out there today. I watched the first episode and just couldn`t stop. A breath of fresh air when compared to some comedies which just seem forced. Characters are interesting and show a little development as time goes on. And you just have to feel for their father!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="299976">So inappropriate that you have to see it! Great show that will surely make you laugh. Funny art makes it even more special!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.mitsudomoe-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="14625" type="Original Work">Sakurai Norio</name>
<name id="7852" type="Direction">Oota Masahiko</name>
<name id="9160" type="Character Design">Ookuma Takaharu</name>
<name id="6742" type="Series Composition">Aoshima Takashi</name>
<name id="9160" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ookuma Takaharu</name>
<name id="7802" type="Music">Misawa Yasuhiro</name>
<name id="24618" type="Animation Work">Bridge</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the gag manga by http://anidb.net/cr14625 [Sakurai Norio], serialised in http://anidb.net/cr28562 [Weekly Shounen Champion].
The somewhat precocious and sadistic girl http://anidb.net/ch15428 [Mitsuba] (oldest), the somewhat lecherous muscle girl http://anidb.net/ch15429 [Futaba], and the somewhat mysterious girl http://anidb.net/ch15430 [Hitoha] (youngest). Better known as the mischievous Marui Sisters these triplets go about their days in class 6-3 with their cute yet wild antics.
Source: Manga-Updates
Note: The first and second episodes were aired during a special event on Sunday, June 20, 2010 in a school gymnasium in Tokyo. Participants were chosen through an e-mail lottery held until Wednesday, June 16. The regular television broadcast started on July 3.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2016">6.61</permanent>
<temporary count="2024">7.37</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>50722.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11180</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9396</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>7627</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4718</identifier>
<identifier>sxrzjl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.mitsudomoe-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Mitsudomoe_(manga)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>みつどもえ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1970</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>335749</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12860</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2608</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2010/mitsudomoe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mitsudomoe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="997" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>association football</name>
<description>Football is a sport that involves kicking a ball in order to score a goal, while the other team tries to stop you by kicking the ball in the other direction to score a goal of their own. In the United States, this sport is known as soccer; the inappropriately titled "American" football (which in fact is played with the egg-shaped "ball" being carried around) is some kind of rugby for babies.</description>
<picurl>40031.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1063" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-11">
<name>elementary school</name>
<description>The term elementary school is used in some countries for schools where children from the age of about five receive primary education.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2566" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-31">
<name>loli</name>
<description>Lolita (often also just abbreviated to loli) refers originally to a novel by Vladimir Nabokov. The book is internationally famous for its controversial subject: the narrator and protagonist, middle aged Humbert Humbert, becomes obsessed and sexually involved with a 12-year-old girl named Dolores Haze.
Nowadays the name "Lolita" describes a sexually precocious young girl.
Related to this is http://anidb.net/t2415 [lolicon], the Japanese abbreviation of the English phrase "Lolita Complex". Sometimes written as "roricon" or "rorikon" due to the inexact mapping between Japanese and English phonemes. This is the term used to describe the fetish/fascination some mature people have for underage girls. There is an entire industry in Japan devoted to providing legal but schoolgirl-themed pornography, taking advantage of the cute childlike appearance some Japanese women maintain well into their twenties.
Because the characters in anime are often young by convention, many fans think that a character can only be Lolicon if she is twelve or younger. Exceptions are granted if the other character in the relationship is a lot older.
One particular device used to skirt the boundaries of taste and legality is the exotic being (alien, creature of magic, robot or the like) which takes the form of an underage human girl, but is in fact for all other practical purposes an adult.
Another reason why lolicon is fetishized by people may be because some of them just view it as a substitute for their fetish for flat-chested, but otherwise well-developed, women.
Source: Wikipedia / TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2665" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>school sports festival</name>
<description>To show off the students in sports clothing — in ecchi anime the female students in particular — a sports festival (or athletic meet) is quite popular in your typical anime with school setting. Here the protagonists can show their skills in diverse athletic competitions.
Note: This festival may also, though very rarely, take place at a kindergarten or preschool.</description>
<picurl>161025.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2711" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-25">
<name>urination</name>
<description>Urination, also known as micturition, voiding, peeing, weeing, pissing, and more rarely, emiction, is the ejection of urine from the urinary bladder through the urethra to the outside of the body. In healthy humans the process of urination is under voluntary control. In infants, some elderly individuals, and those with neurological injury or extreme psychological problems, urination may occur as an involuntary reflex. In other animals, in addition to expelling waste material, urination can mark territory or express submissiveness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2761" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>dodgeball</name>
<description>Dodgeball is any of a variety of games in which players try to hit other players on the opposing team with their own balls while avoiding being hit themselves. 
Don`t try this at home, kids.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2822" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>skirt flipping</name>
<description>Naughty characters — usually boys — flip the skirts of female protagonists to ascertain what panties they are wearing (also see Pantsu category).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3107" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-10-12">
<name>unfoundedly feared character</name>
<description>Due to some strange misunderstanding, or some other unfounded reason the character in the anime is feared by his contemporaries.
Example: A male student with an "evil eye" is mistaken for a delinquent, and thus feared by the students in his class.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3824" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-01-05">
<name>sentai</name>
<description>In Japanese, sentai is a military unit, and may be translated as "squadron", "task force", "group" or "wing". In the anime fandom, however, it usually refers to the Super Sentai Series, a long-running superhero team franchise of http://anidb.net/t5000 [tokusatsu] shows featuring live action characters and colorful special effects, and other similar shows. A prominent characteristic of such shows is that the colour- and elemental-coded heroes, usually numbering around five or more, fight to save the world from the evil that terrorizes the area, which may even span the entire universe.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4669" parentid="6249" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-27">
<name>parenting</name>
<description>This anime is about parenting and its many challenges.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5790" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-30">
<name>family without mother</name>
<description>For some reason, the protagonist`s mother is no longer among the living. The much-too-early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime, and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family. For example: the grief-stricken father and children barely function as humans; the oldest daughter has an extra burden of raising the other children, additional emphasis is given to the only female child in the family, i.e. with bishounen brother and dad in a shoujo setting.
In rare cases the mother may still be alive, just not living with the rest of the family presently, i.e. on some quest or job and gone for a long time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5834" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>show within a show</name>
<description>A fictional TV (or radio, or stage) show that takes place within an actual TV show; or, occasionally, a fictional instalment or incarnation of an actual show. Many comedies have short one-off gags where they parody existing shows.
Example: A large part of Martian Successor Nadesico is centred around the fictional popular anime Gekigangar III, which is being watched by several characters of the Nadesico crew.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5843" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>sibling yin yang</name>
<description>In real life, siblings hardly ever act the same. Fiction sometimes takes this to an extreme.
Enter Sibling Yin Yang, the occurrence of siblings that are nearly polar opposites. If he`s cool and reckless, she`s responsible and thoughtful. If she`s a spiky-haired hooligan, he`s the nerdy wimpy one. If he`s an immature brat, she`s... well, you get the picture.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5943" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-14">
<name>misunderstanding</name>
<description>Suggests that a large portion of storyline revolves around a rather large misunderstanding between two or more characters, usually forming long lasting situations of separation or hostility between all those involved.
A large portion of the story may be dedicated to gradually working all parties into a mutual understanding to true intentions or changes of heart.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6046" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>pool episode</name>
<description>An episode playing at the pool, mostly in school, sometimes outside of it when the cast does not have a chance for a beach episode.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version of the http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode].
Other variants are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160904.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="15428" type="main character in" update="2013-12-09">
<rating votes="78">8.09</rating>
<name>Marui Mitsuba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Marui Mitsuba is the eldest of the Marui triplets, enjoys causing mischief and is aptly described as a "precocious sadist".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>48600.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="411" picture="17475.jpg">Takagaki Ayahi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15429" type="main character in" update="2010-05-26">
<rating votes="61">7.60</rating>
<name>Marui Futaba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48601.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1511" picture="173601.jpg">Akesaka Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15430" type="main character in" update="2010-05-26">
<rating votes="152">9.10</rating>
<name>Marui Hitoha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48602.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18110" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-26">
<rating votes="36">6.81</rating>
<name>Sugisaki Miku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48587.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18111" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-26">
<rating votes="24">4.57</rating>
<name>Yoshioka Yuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48588.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18112" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-17">
<rating votes="29">6.46</rating>
<name>Miyashita</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48589.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1437" picture="18823.jpg">Oohara Momoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18113" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-26">
<rating votes="19">4.59</rating>
<name>Matsuoka Sakiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48590.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9124" picture="186845.jpg">Hayama Ikumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18114" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-26">
<rating votes="24">4.43</rating>
<name>Yabe Satoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48591.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18115" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-26">
<rating votes="29">3.45</rating>
<name>Kuriyama Aiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48592.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="476" picture="23579.jpg">Saitou Momoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18116" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-26">
<rating votes="13">5.09</rating>
<name>Satou Shin`ya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48593.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="81" picture="41282.jpg">Sanpei Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18117" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-26">
<rating votes="24">6.58</rating>
<name>Chiba Yuudai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48594.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10380" picture="38227.jpg">Yamamoto Kazutomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18118" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-26">
<rating votes="9">3.87</rating>
<name>Ogata Airi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48595.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="245" picture="46862.jpg">Chihara Minori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18119" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-26">
<rating votes="14">4.00</rating>
<name>Itou Shiori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48596.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18120" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-26">
<rating votes="13">3.49</rating>
<name>Katou Mayumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48597.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1614" picture="148394.jpg">Uchida Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18121" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-26">
<rating votes="37">7.95</rating>
<name>Marui Soujirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48598.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1942" picture="50629.jpg">Amada Masuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18122" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-26">
<rating votes="11">6.08</rating>
<name>Chikubi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48599.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="476" picture="23579.jpg">Saitou Momoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21568" type="appears in" update="2010-09-12">
<rating votes="12">3.72</rating>
<name>Sugisaki Ryuuta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54907.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12323" picture="171959.jpg">Takayama Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21735" type="appears in" update="2010-09-19">
<rating votes="30">7.99</rating>
<name>Sugisaki Marina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55210.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29374" type="appears in" update="2011-03-01">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Gachi Blue</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66808.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="174" picture="41158.jpg">Kakihara Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29375" type="appears in" update="2011-03-01">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Gachi Yellow</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66809.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1442" picture="18829.jpg">Kaida Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29376" type="appears in" update="2011-03-01">
<rating votes="2">5.25</rating>
<name>Gachi Black</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66817.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12623" picture="151646.jpg">Iguchi Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29394" type="appears in" update="2011-03-01">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Noda-kouchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66834.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6942" picture="41078.jpg">Takaoka Binbin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29395" type="appears in" update="2011-03-01">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Koganei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66836.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3712" picture="240126.jpg">Tamura Mutsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94834" type="appears in" update="2018-03-26">
<name>Youmuin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215491.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3797" picture="65487.jpg">Matsuo Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94836" type="appears in" update="2018-03-26">
<name>Ten`in</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215489.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="595" picture="17993.jpg">Kimoto Orie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94847" type="appears in" update="2018-03-28">
<name>Inuragon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215551.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6942" picture="41078.jpg">Takaoka Binbin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94851" type="appears in" update="2018-03-28">
<name>Kazuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215563.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23312" picture="205591.jpg">Takamori Natsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94852" type="appears in" update="2018-03-28">
<name>Hahaoya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215564.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33607" picture="223565.jpg">Yamakawa Tomomi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="118772" update="2010-06-09">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-06-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>568862</identifier>
<identifier>mitsudomoe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="118776" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-20</airdate>
<rating votes="18">5.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">丸井家! 良い子 悪い子 恐ろしい子!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Marui Family! The Good, the Bad, and the Fearsome!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Marui-ke! Ii Ko Warui Ko Osoroshii Ko!!</title>
<summary>Hello!
I`m the new teacher, Yabe Satoshi!
Today we`re playing "Fruit Basket Turnover" to celebrate my becoming the teacher for class 6-3.
I`ve prepared myself for all the situations I expected to encounter in an elementary school, 
but this particular class is home to three problem children.
The Marui sisters,
Mitsuba-chan, Futaba-chan and Hitoha-chan.
I wanted our Fruit Basket Turnover game to be fun, but it ended up being horrible beyond imagination.
How the heck am I supposed to survive this...?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543890</identifier>
<identifier>mitsudomoe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="118984" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-20</airdate>
<rating votes="17">2.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">三つ子がとまらない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Those Three Girls Won`t Stop!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mitsugo ga Tomoranai</title>
<summary>HWAACHOO! Oh, it sure is wa...wa...warm today.
Huh?  What`s my "character", Micchan?
Eew, my nose won`t stop running...
I`m gonna drown in my own snot...
Oh no, I`m out of tissues!  They`ve abandonned me!  My fate is sealed...
Haa...HWACHOO!  Agh!  Now I`m glued to Yabecchi with my super-sticky snot!
I gotta do something!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543888</identifier>
<identifier>mitsudomoe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="119561" update="2010-07-05">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119589" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="13">6.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">不審者がいっぱい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Full of Strangers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fushinsha ga Ippai</title>
<summary>Time to gradate to more adult books, I suppose...huh?
The youngest one`s book...HOOOOOOOOLLLLLLLY COW!
I have to see more!  Please, please!  Let me see!
N-No?  I`m begging you!  Even just a tiny little peek!
Crap!  She won`t even let me near it...I`m just gonna have to take it by force!
Oh, hey Satou...you heard that?  Hmm?  That`s illegal?  I shouldn`t do it!
It`s not fair!  Forget you, I`m not listening to some goody-goody who`s not into girls at all! XXX
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543886</identifier>
<identifier>mitsudomoe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="119638" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">乳と白パンツと小生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Milk and White Pants and Yours Truly</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chichi to Shiro Pantsu to Shousei</title>
<summary>Sensei.
You`re underestimating Futaba`s breast obsession.
It`s totally abnormal.  You can`t underestimate it...
Normally she just goofs around all the time
but breasts are the one thing that she gets deadly serious about. She`s a breast artisan,
tirelessly seeking to create the perfect representation of her ideal.
Sometimes she gets so hard on herself she`ll roam around aimlessly.
Her refined breast creations are masterpieces, beautiful...And sexy!
Look! Look at the dedication on her face!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543788</identifier>
<identifier>mitsudomoe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="120018" update="2010-07-18">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120019" update="2010-07-18">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120379" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-07</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">帽子とパンツはかぶるためにある!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hats and Underwear Go on Your Head!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boushi to Pantsu wa Kaburu Tame ni Aru!?</title>
<summary>Tomorrow`s field day!  I`m at school practicing the night before!
Huh?  Daddy?  Where`d you come from?  The house?
I`m not supposed to go out on my own at night?  I`m sorry...
But I just couldn`t sit still knowing tomorrow`s field dat!
I thought I`d do a rehearsal!
Will you help too daddy?  Great!  We`ll start with the opening parade!
Then the obstacle course!
Then the tug-of-war, the piggyback battle, and the relay!
Mmm...first place...zzzzz...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543880</identifier>
<identifier>mitsudomoe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="120380" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブラ! ブラ! ブタ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bra! Bra! Pig!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bura! Bura! Buta!</title>
<summary>I`ll need to buy a bra soon, too.
I-It`s not `cause they told me to!
I was really thinking of buying one.
But I tried to sneak off and buy it, and this retarded old hag clings along!
Huh?! They don`t sell boobs!
Geez, I`m just buying it and going home. Umm, is there anything cute and cheap...
Huh? My size? Uh, maybe this big? N-No? Size depends on the size of your chest?
Screw it all!!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543874</identifier>
<identifier>mitsudomoe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="120501" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-23</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">RUNNER</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Runner</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Runner</title>
<summary>Ack, It`s Futaba!  I`ll have to sacrifice Hitoha to escape!
Hey wait, why`re you chasing me!  Argh, enough!  How long are you gonna chase me?
I`ll just have to hide in the equipment shed!
I`ll hide inside the hurdle blocks...
Get out, get out.  Good, she`s gone!
Uh...uh oh!  I`m STUCK!  Why?!  Someone help!
Oh...Hitoha...umm...help?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543884</identifier>
<identifier>mitsudomoe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="120502" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-16</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガチで愛してしょうがない!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Can`t Help Being in Love!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gachi de Koishite Shouganai!?</title>
<summary>Live-action superheroes...How insipid.
Wow...
I...I never knew there was such an awesome show on TV!
Hoo...
I wanna tell them how awesome the Gachi Rangers were.
I want them to understand.
But...wait, other people in the class like Gachi Rangers too?
U-U...Umm...I, umm...I saw...I saw it too...
No...no, wait! Not a ghost or a ghoul or a poltergeist!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543882</identifier>
<identifier>mitsudomoe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="120929" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-06</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ちぢょになる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We`re Gonna Be *******</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chijo ni Naru</title>
<summary>Today we`re having recess with the first graders...hey, Hitoha!
None of the kids are playing with me because you`re here!
Ah well, kids are pains in the neck anyways so it`s just as well.  I wish this class would just end already.
Hey, what`s wrong?  Your RC Helicopter`s stuck in a tree?
I suppose it`s up to me to come to the rescue then!
But you`ll have to be extra polite, call me "-sama" and be my footstool for a d-
What do you mean, "clam it?!"
Snotty little brat...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543878</identifier>
<identifier>mitsudomoe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="120930" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-13</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マジで変する5秒前</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Things Get WEIRD in 5 Seconds</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maji de Hen Suru Go Byou Mae</title>
<summary>I can`t focus...probably because I skipped breakfast...
Stupid Futaba, she says grabbing my stomach`s like grabbing an I-cup!
Hmm...?  Th-The "Vibe-Shape Belt," it makes you skinny just by wearing it!
What a wonderful device....It`s so expensive, but I want it so bad!
Huh?  Hey, it`s Sugisaki`s cell phone...
H-Holy cow!  If I put this on my stomach...
Aah...my abs...my abs...they`re getting tighter...What an amazing discovery!
Mitsu: I`ll use dad`s phone when I get home.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>544204</identifier>
<identifier>mitsudomoe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="120931" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-30</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">変人はサンタクロース</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Santa Claus Is My Sweetheart</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Henjin wa Santa Claus</title>
<summary>KHACKACKACK!  COUGH!  KUGH!  It`s Christmas Eve...
What a time to be sick...KHACKACKACK!
Futaba is expecing Santa Claus (me) to come tonight...!
But I can`t...give Futaba her present...when I`m so sick...!
What do I do...?  I know...I got something nice for you, Hitoha...
That...that bag...
...There`s a Santa suit inside.  It`s all...up to you...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543876</identifier>
<identifier>mitsudomoe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="121251" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-19</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">君に届かない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Can`t Reach You</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi ni Todokanai</title>
<summary>Hmm?  Youngest?
Whatcha doing?  Oh, you`re changing the light?
You can`t reach it, huh...here, you can ride on my shoulders.  Upsy-daisy...
What?  What`s wrong?  You wanna get down?  But you didn`t change the light!
Huh?!  Youngest hates me now!
What happened?  Did I do something weird?  No...I just lifted her up like normal...
Maybe she thinks I`m a freak like everyone else in this class and she shouldn`t hang out with me.
No...I`m not like them!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>544206</identifier>
<identifier>mitsudomoe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="121864" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-26</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">丸井さんの家庭の日常</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Day at the Marui House</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Marui-san no Katei no Nichijou</title>
<summary>Daddy, we found a stray kitty!  Can we bring him home?
But it even said "Meow, I wanna live with the Maruis!"
Really?  We can keep it?!  Yippee!  We did it, Hitoha!
Let`s go get it now!  Huh?  It`s gone...
I`m sure a really nice, kind person picked it up.
Uh oh, Hitoha`s in shock...can`t we do something, Micchan?
Ah ha, I`LL be the kitty!  Meoooooow!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>544208</identifier>
<identifier>mitsudomoe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="128367" update="2011-02-27">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-02-23</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">OPPAI IPPAI ママ元気</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lots of Breasts, Mama`s Alright</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oppai Ippai Mama Genki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128882" update="2011-03-17">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">8.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130858" recap="true" update="2011-06-12">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-03-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">傑作選(3)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Masterpiece selection 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130859" recap="true" update="2011-06-12">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-03-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">傑作選(2)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Masterpiece selection 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130860" recap="true" update="2011-06-12">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-03-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">傑作選(1)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Masterpiece selection 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
