<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7231" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-02-18</startdate>
<enddate>2010-02-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Uchuu Show e Youkoso</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="synonym">Willkommen zur SPACE SHOW</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Добро пожаловать на космическое шоу!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">宇宙ショーへようこそ Welcome to THE SPACE SHOW</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Welcome to the Space Show</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Welcome to the Space Show</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Benvenuti allo Show dello Spazio</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="6249" approval="4" total="13">Summer Wars</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="232613">Very lovely movie, reminds me a lot of older movies from Ghibli when they where at the best! Really an must see anime.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.uchushow.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3754" type="Character Design">Ishihama Masashi</name>
<name id="3016" type="Direction">Masunari Kouji</name>
<name id="11042" type="Original Work">Besame Mucho</name>
<name id="1303" type="Work">A-1 Pictures</name>
<name id="4410" type="Music">Ike Yoshihiro</name>
</creators>
<description>A tiny mountain village in a remote woodland region. Five primary school kids have come together in this idyllic spot in order to spend their summer holidays at a camp. At first the children enjoy carefree days amidst unspoiled nature far away from adult supervision. But their life changes dramatically when they come across what they believe to be a small dog, badly in need of help. The creature - known as Pochi - turns out not to be a dog at all but an alien on an important mission. It seems there is a mysterious substance on earth that is coveted throughout the universe. Pochi had almost found it but was so badly injured during a fight that he had to give up his search. Thanks to the children`s help, the alien survives - and decides to reward them generously. "Where would you most like to travel?" is the question Pochi puts to his rescuers. Their answer is prompt, if vague: "As far as possible!" Pochi suggests they try the moon first of all, and so, the alien whisks away the kids to the satellite next door. This marks the beginning of an absolutely amazing adventure. During the course of their travels they discover that the substance coveted throughout the universe is in fact also integral to Japanese cuisine - and it just so happens that one of the kids has some of this mysterious substance in his pocket.
Source: Berlin Film Festival site
Note: The movie got a premiere screening at Berlin Film Festival (11-21.02.2010).</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="652">7.27</permanent>
<temporary count="656">7.38</temporary>
<review count="1">5.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>62443.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9174</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8115</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.uchushow.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Welcome_to_the_Space_Show</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>宇宙ショーへようこそ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1963</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>336088</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12767</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2622</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1999" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-29">
<name>tomboy</name>
<description>A girl who acts and dresses like a boy and enjoys rough, noisy activities traditionally associated with boys.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2406" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-13">
<name>talking animal</name>
<description>Talking animals are a common theme in mythology and folk tales, as well as children`s literature. Fictional talking creatures often are anthropomorphic, possessing human-like qualities but appearing as a creature. An animal that only knows how to say its name (for example, 99.9% of all http://anidb.net/t2493 [Pokemon]), are not talking animals.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2616" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>mina</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word mina refers to a broad audience, which can be said to be "the entire family", from the grumpy grandpa to the newborn baby. In Japanese, the word means simply "everyone", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic. Mina works are deliberately targeted at a range of people as wide as possible, and are commonly associated with high-budget releases that require a very large audience to be financially viable. They usually bring mildly philosophical themes so that the adults can be interested, but do so without bringing objectionable content so that the children can be allowed to watch, and indeed also feature content specifically geared to spark their interest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2659" parentid="2660" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Moon</name>
<description>The Moon is an astronomical body that orbits planet Earth, being Earth`s only permanent natural satellite. It is the fifth-largest natural satellite in the Solar System, and the largest among planetary satellites relative to the size of the planet that it orbits.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214385.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2662" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>school excursion</name>
<description>True for almost all anime with school setting, there will be a school excursion or field trip. Tokyo and Kyoto seem to be particularly popular as sightseeing destinations. So are hiking excursions into the local mountains. This also is a good excuse to present the prefecture`s / city`s food specialities.
Potential for ecchi moments: Obviously the "boys" will get all sorts of ideas with the "girls" sleeping so close by.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2667" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>university</name>
<description>Since college/university students are typically at least eighteen years old, with stories covering mature everyday life topics, you will find the college setting quite often in seinen and josei anime.
Topics that can now be covered - as compared to High School settings - are higher education (i.e. coping with higher intellectual stress), the more adult party life (i.e. alcohol, smoking, sex), the issues of daily life vs. studying - especially when having to work to pay for bills, and finally the possible friction between those in and out of college.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3062" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-02">
<name>unidentified flying object</name>
<description>An unidentified flying object, or UFO, is in its strictest definition any apparent object in the sky that is not identifiable as a known object or phenomenon. However, the term is widely used in popular culture to refer more specifically to supposed observations of craft of extraterrestrial origin.
Most UFOs are later identified as conventional objects or phenomena (e.g., aircraft, weather balloons, clouds). Some of them are not identified, either because of lack of evidence or because no conventional explanation can be found despite extensive evidence. Some people consider the latter cases as possible observations of extraterrestrial space craft.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="13566" type="main character in" update="2011-04-19">
<rating votes="1">3.97</rating>
<name>Satou Kiyoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The oldest of the group — being in sixth grade — Kiyoshi has leadership qualities: a strong sense of responsibility, honesty, trustworthiness, and kindness.</description>
<picture>39744.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16803" picture="45970.jpg">Uzawa Shoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13567" type="main character in" update="2011-02-16">
<rating votes="3">6.44</rating>
<name>Nishimura Noriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Despite being a very timid fourth grader, Noriko always acts like her dream is to be an idol star.</description>
<picture>39745.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="635" picture="18162.jpg">Matsumoto Tamaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13568" type="main character in" update="2011-02-16">
<rating votes="2">8.43</rating>
<name>Suzuki Amane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The youngest of the five main characters, Amane is Natsuki`s cousin and in second grade. She is an amiable and reliable person who has a totally honest and gently personality.</description>
<picture>39746.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23669" picture="5823.png">Ikezuki Honoka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13569" type="main character in" update="2011-04-11">
<rating votes="1">3.97</rating>
<name>Harada Kouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kouji wears glasses and is an avid bookworm brimming with curiosity about everything. He loves anything to do with UFOs, aliens, and the occult.</description>
<picture>39747.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16805" picture="45972.jpg">Yoshinaga Takuto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13570" type="main character in" update="2011-02-16">
<rating votes="2">5.94</rating>
<name>Koyama Natsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A fifth grade student who recently moved from town, the energetic Natsuki longs to be a heroine.</description>
<picture>39748.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16804" picture="224734.jpg">Kurosawa Tomoyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16556" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-21">
<rating votes="1">1.81</rating>
<name>Neppo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92757.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3149" picture="132209.jpg">Nakao Ryuusei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16557" type="main character in" update="2012-09-05">
<rating votes="4">8.37</rating>
<name>Pochi Lickman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Looking like an ordinary dog at first glance, Pochi is actually an alien from the planet Wan. The five schoolmates helped him after they found him injured. As a reward he invited them to the Moon.</description>
<picture>93482.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28778" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-16">
<rating votes="5">9.04</rating>
<name>Ink</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ink is a friendly alien who makes friends with Harada Kouji and lends a big help to the group...</description>
<picture>65893.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10041" picture="39859.jpg">Iino Mayu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47983" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-21">
<name>Goba</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92753.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2782" picture="23189.jpg">Ginga Banjou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47984" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-21">
<name>Taro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92760.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4690" picture="246059.jpg">Itou Kazuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47985" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-21">
<name>Tony</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92761.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47986" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-21">
<name>Hanako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92754.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="268" picture="17093.jpg">Hidaka Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47987" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-21">
<name>Heston</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92755.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4196" picture="26343.jpg">Takeda Masanori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47988" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-21">
<name>Bogner</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92752.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="183" picture="16992.jpg">Onosaka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47989" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-21">
<name>Marie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92756.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="693" picture="226546.jpg">Igarashi Rei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47990" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-21">
<name>Rubin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92759.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1987" picture="225435.jpg">Egawa Hisao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47991" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-21">
<name>Robby</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92758.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="398" picture="17243.jpg">Miyamoto Mitsuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47993" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-21">
<name>Pet Daiou</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92764.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47994" type="appears in" update="2012-08-21">
<name>Satou Mitsuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kiyoshi`s mother.</description>
<picture>92771.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="229" picture="152363.jpg">Itou Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47995" type="appears in" update="2012-08-21">
<name>Harada Osamu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kouji`s father.</description>
<picture>92769.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5021" picture="188516.jpg">Taki Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47996" type="appears in" update="2012-08-21">
<name>Harada Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kouji`s mother.</description>
<picture>92770.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="447" picture="224407.jpg">Tsunematsu Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47997" type="appears in" update="2012-08-21">
<name>Koyama Ken`ichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Natsuki`s father.</description>
<picture>92768.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19121" picture="156854.jpg">Oda Toshimitsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47998" type="appears in" update="2012-08-21">
<name>Koyama Shimizu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Natsuki`s mother.</description>
<picture>92767.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="271" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47999" type="appears in" update="2012-08-21">
<name>Nishimura Hiroto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Noriko`s younger brother.</description>
<picture>92773.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33923" picture="93435.jpg">Hayashi Roi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48000" type="appears in" update="2012-08-21">
<name>Nishimura Nobuhiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Noriko`s grandfather.</description>
<picture>92772.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6011" picture="223622.jpg">Juku Ikkyuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48001" type="appears in" update="2012-08-21">
<name>Suzuki Megumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Amane`s mother.</description>
<picture>92765.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3006" picture="226210.jpg">Hirata Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48002" type="appears in" update="2012-08-21">
<name>Suzuki Toushirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Grandfather of Natsuki and Amane.</description>
<picture>92766.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="599" picture="226547.jpg">Naya Rokurou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="116460" update="2018-05-24">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>140</length>
<airdate>2010-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
<summary>A group of kids are whisked away to a space colony on the dark side of the moon, an interstellar melting pot with a non-stop parade of alien creatures, jellyfish spaceships, and dragon trains, marking for a glorious and wondrous adventure.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="128175" update="2011-02-11">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="180254" update="2016-10-05">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Special preview</title>
<summary>Special preview on Tokyo MX</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
