<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="724" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>3</episodecount>
<startdate>2000-06-23</startdate>
<enddate>2000-10-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Refrain Blue</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">リフレインブルー</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">RB</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">Refrain Blue</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Refrain Blue</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.pinkpineapple.co.jp/refrain/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="4511" type="Character Design">Watanabe Mayumi</name>
<name id="5902" type="Direction">Kashima Norio</name>
<name id="41074" type="Animation Work">PP Project</name>
<name id="4511" type="Chief Animation Direction">Watanabe Mayumi</name>
<name id="878" type="Original Work">Elf</name>
<name id="3730" type="Series Composition">Yoshioka Takao</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the game by http://anidb.net/cr878 [Elf] with the same title. Consists of three chapters which all take place on the Toyo Gakuen`s summer school, on seashore.
The first chapter, Recollection, tells about the recollection of Yoshihiro`s past about various events of summer school, of the fate where encounter and separation are interwoven with each other, as Yoshiro and Matsunaga will pass the Toyo Gakuen and will arrive at summer school at seashore. A mysterious girl smiles as she watches Yoshiro who stands still at the seashore dusk.
The second chapter focuses on another character, Matsunaga, who was caught by the feeling of the past but cannot be betrayed.
On the last chapter, Matsunaga meets the girl of mystery from the first chapter.
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="270">4.46</permanent>
<temporary count="272">6.33</temporary>
<review count="2">7.91</review>
</ratings>
<picture>2461.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1129</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>676</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>929</identifier>
<identifier>joeeeg</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.pinkpineapple.co.jp/refrain/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1021</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>160291</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4202</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>203</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2019" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-16">
<name>suicidal</name>
<description>The character has suicidal tendencies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2829" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-21">
<name>shower scene</name>
<description>The anime contains a shower scene, obligatory for ecchi anime. The person under the shower will most likely be female — providing "fanservice".</description>
<picurl>208635.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2865" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>summer festival</name>
<description>The summer festival is used to show off the female protagonists in traditional Japanese clothing — the yukata — a casual form of kimono.
The festivities include food stalls (cotton candy, candy apples, choco bananas, taiyaki), various games (scoop goldfishes), and a fireworks display.</description>
<picurl>161023.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3806" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-13">
<name>tanabata</name>
<description>Tanabata (七夕, meaning "Evening of the seventh") is a Japanese star festival, originating from the Chinese Qixi Festival.
It celebrates the meeting of the deities Orihime and Hikoboshi (represented by the stars Vega and Altair respectively). According to legend, the Milky Way separates these lovers, and they are allowed to meet only once a year on the seventh day of the seventh lunar month of the lunisolar calendar. The date of Tanabata varies by region of the country, but the first festivities begin on July 7 of the Gregorian calendar. The celebration is held at various days between July and August.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160813.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="53036" type="appears in" update="2013-02-20">
<rating votes="2">7.85</rating>
<name>Morisawa Nao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132417.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6815" picture="31498.jpg">Kikuchi Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53037" type="appears in" update="2013-02-20">
<rating votes="2">5.83</rating>
<name>Iwasaki Chinatsu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132418.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2091" picture="151645.jpg">Ishikawa Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53038" type="appears in" update="2013-02-20">
<rating votes="1">5.58</rating>
<name>Hayase Shizuku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132419.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4957" picture="91922.jpg">Uchikawa Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53039" type="appears in" update="2013-02-20">
<rating votes="1">5.58</rating>
<name>Kawana Yuori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132420.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6685" picture="31329.jpg">Asano Ruri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53040" type="appears in" update="2013-02-20">
<rating votes="1">7.62</rating>
<name>Nazo no Shoujo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132421.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7102" picture="17145.jpg">Sonozaki Mie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53041" type="appears in" update="2013-02-20">
<rating votes="1">5.58</rating>
<name>Tsugashima Tsugumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132422.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4101" picture="26184.jpg">Adachi Mari</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="7651" update="2010-05-13">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-06-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">緋色の追憶</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scarlet Remembrance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hiiro no Tsuioku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7652" update="2018-05-06">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-08-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">月影の下で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beneath the Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Getsuei no Moto de</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7653" update="2010-05-13">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2000-10-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">碧波の永遠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eternal Blue Waves</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hekiha no Eien</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
