<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7242" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-01-05</startdate>
<enddate>2010-06-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Masuda Kousuke Gekijou Gag Manga Biyori +</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Gyagu Manga Biyori +</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Gag Manga Biyori Plus</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">gag manga4</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">増田こうすけ劇場 ギャグマンガ日和+</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">搞笑漫画日和+</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5774" type="Prequel">Masuda Kousuke Gekijou Gag Manga Biyori 3</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://jumpsq.shueisha.co.jp/contents/gag10th/anime.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="730" type="Animation Work">Studio Deen</name>
<name id="8578" type="Original Work">Masuda Kousuke</name>
<name id="1423" type="Direction">Daichi Akitarou</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a shounen gag manga by http://anidb.net/cr8578 [Masuda Kousuke] serialised in Monthly Shounen Jump.
The fourth season of Masuda`s hyperactive, random, and nonsensical anime turned gag manga.
Note: Mixed in with new episodes were re-runs of episode from the previous seasons. There were a total of 12 new episodes and 14 re-run episodes.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="41">6.49</permanent>
<temporary count="41">6.47</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>40174.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11194</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7761</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4615</identifier>
<identifier>ydbipd</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://jumpsq.shueisha.co.jp/contents/gag10th/anime.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Gag_Manga_Biyori</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>増田こうすけ劇場_ギャグマンガ日和</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1839</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>335592</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12324</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1283" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-24">
<name>tsukkomi</name>
<description>A tsukkomi is a comedy duo stock character in a traditional Japanese slapstick stand-up comedy style known as manzai. Tsukkomi characters are the smart, reasonable, and down-to-earth half of the unit; their simple-minded counterparts are the http://anidb.net/t1399 [boke] characters. As a result of their boke counterparts` simple mistakes and gross exaggerations, tsukkomi berate and abuse them both verbally and physically; a very common example of tsukkomi physical abuse is a paper fan slap, which is generally accompanied by a sound effect. Their approximate equivalent in Western culture is the comedy role of straight man.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="112355" update="2010-01-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2010-01-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルノアールVSセザンヌ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Renoir VS Cezanne</title>
</episode>
<episode id="113154" update="2018-02-28">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2010-01-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">銭湯に行こう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s go to the bath-house</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116316" update="2018-02-28">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2010-02-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">新撰組 / 松尾芭蕉ショート</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shinsengumi -Ikedaya Case- / The Narrow Road to the Deep North Middle of the Journey (Short Story)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116474" update="2018-02-28">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2010-02-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">巨重戦士メンタリオン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hefty Warrior Mentallion</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116518" update="2018-02-28">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2010-03-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">親友は狼男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Best Friend is a Werewolf</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116952" update="2018-02-28">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2010-03-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">メカマツオ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mecha Matsuo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117340" update="2018-02-28">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2010-04-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋のラブソングを君に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Love Song of Love for You</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117343" update="2018-02-28">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2010-05-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">なめられペリー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Teasing Perry</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117345" update="2018-02-28">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2010-05-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">凶暴エイリアン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Frenzied Alien</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoubou Alien</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118307" update="2018-02-28">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2010-06-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">富士山</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mt. Fuji</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuji-san</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118647" update="2018-02-28">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2010-06-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">名探偵なので! うさみちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Because She`s a Famous Detective! Usami-chan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118649" update="2018-02-28">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2010-06-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">陰陽師物語</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Onmyouji Story</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onmyouji Monogatari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="179209" update="2018-09-21">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>2010-07-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">10th Year Anniversary Special</title>
<summary>Celebrating the 10th year anniversary of the original manga, a special aired on TV that included interviews with the crew, "Making of" GMB, and an in-studio tour</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
