<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7247" restricted="false">
<type>TV Special</type>
<episodecount>10</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-12-21</startdate>
<enddate>2009-12-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hipira-kun</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Hipira: The Little Vampire</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ヒピラくん</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.hipira.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="7827" type="Direction">Kimura Shinji</name>
<name id="726" type="Work">Sunrise</name>
<name id="149" type="Original Work">Ootomo Katsuhiro</name>
<name id="7827" type="Original Work">Kimura Shinji</name>
<name id="4221" type="Music">Conisch</name>
<name id="726" type="Animation Work">Sunrise</name>
</creators>
<description>The story follows a young vampire boy named Hipira who lives in Salta, an eternally dark city of vampires. He goes on a series of adventures with the rest of the town`s residents.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="222">4.50</permanent>
<temporary count="223">5.87</temporary>
<review count="1">6.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>132123.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11205</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22983</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>7723</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4602</identifier>
<identifier>hwxwgi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.hipira.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Hipira:_The_Little_Vampire</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ヒピラくん</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2849</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>335913</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1409" parentid="1152" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-20">
<name>vampire</name>
<description>A vampire is a mythological or folkloric nocturnal undead. Vampires use long fangs to penetrate the necks of people, usually young females, to drink their blood, both as a form of nourishment and to turn the targets into slaves.
In the classic vampire stories, they are thought to have no reflection in mirrors, are able to shapeshift into bats (sometimes also wolves or some form of fog), have unlimited lifespan and superhuman strength, reflexes and senses, and may only be killed by silver bullets, silver blades, a stake through the heart, fire, or exposure to sunlight; on the other hand, they cannot tolerate garlic, holy water, or Christian crosses (sometimes expanded to religious symbols in general).
In modern anime, these limitations are usually dropped, and they become far more powerful and fearsome opponents than usual. A human bitten, or sometimes even scratched, by a vampire typically becomes a slave, eventually dying as if poisoned, and becoming a vampire, ghoul, zombie, or other form of undead after death, often staying under the command of the vampire who originally bit them.</description>
<picurl>231496.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1846" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>kodomo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word kodomo refers to a children`s audience roughly for the ages 12 and younger. In Japanese, the word means simply "child", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2257" parentid="1152" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-12">
<name>zombie</name>
<description>A zombie is asserted to be a reanimated corpse, or a human who is being controlled by someone else by use of magic with some media renditions using a pandemic illness to explain their existence.
Stories of zombies originated in the West African spiritual belief system of voodoo, which told of the people being controlled as laborers by a powerful wizard.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3805" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-13">
<name>European stylised</name>
<description>The anime`s setting is crafted in some classic European style. Imagine an architectural and cultural mix of London, Paris, Rome, Berlin, Prague, and other cities as they were at any point in the 19th century or earlier.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4465" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-08">
<name>stereoscopic imaging</name>
<description>This anime was shown in cinema rooms with stereoscopic 3D capabilities, released on Blu-ray 3D, or available for other stereoscopic 3D capable devices like the Nintendo 3DS or the Sharp AQUOS "NERV Edition" SH-06D smartphone. It was either produced in stereo 3D (e.g. "Baby Princess 3D Paradise Love") or produced in 2D and later converted from 2D to 3D (e.g. "Koukaku Kidoutai Stand Alone Complex: Solid State Society"). At any rate, it was at some point officially available with stereoscopic 3D depth effect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="52877" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-12">
<name>Elena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132084.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52878" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-12">
<name>George</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132080.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="444" picture="17329.jpg">Suzuki Chihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52879" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-12">
<name>Derucha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132081.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3833" picture="25459.jpg">Shibahara Chiyako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52880" type="main character in" update="2013-02-12">
<name>Hipira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132079.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="320" picture="66660.jpg">Kobayashi Yumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52881" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-12">
<name>Malena-sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132083.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3240" picture="45305.jpg">Yokoo Mari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52882" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-12">
<name>Yanis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132082.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52884" type="appears in" update="2013-02-12">
<name>Kaeru Ouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132088.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52885" type="appears in" update="2013-02-12">
<name>Goblin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132096.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52886" type="appears in" update="2013-02-12">
<name>Sara</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132092.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="643" picture="228609.jpg">Kojima Sachiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52888" type="appears in" update="2013-02-12">
<name>Sand</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132090.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="493" picture="65381.jpg">Itou Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52889" type="main character in" update="2013-02-12">
<name>Soul-kun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132095.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52890" type="appears in" update="2013-02-12">
<name>Zombie</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132086.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12658" picture="130581.jpg">Yoshimoto Genki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52891" type="appears in" update="2013-02-12">
<name>Dirt</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132089.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="52892" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-12">
<name>Chourou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132085.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="199" picture="23218.jpg">Shimada Bin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52893" type="appears in" update="2013-02-12">
<name>Vacuum</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132093.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31" picture="65365.jpg">Ueda Youji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52894" type="appears in" update="2013-02-12">
<name>Rose</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132094.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52895" type="appears in" update="2013-02-12">
<name>Rock</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132091.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12658" picture="130581.jpg">Yoshimoto Genki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52896" type="appears in" update="2013-02-12">
<name>Okaasan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hipira`s mother.</description>
<picture>132097.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2735" picture="69014.jpg">Horikoshi Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52944" type="appears in" update="2013-02-14">
<name>Bend / Doll</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132166.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31" picture="65365.jpg">Ueda Youji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53100" type="appears in" update="2013-02-22">
<name>Kaijuu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132523.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12658" picture="130581.jpg">Yoshimoto Genki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="112249" update="2009-12-25">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ウィッチ・スケッチの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Witch Sketch</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Witch Sketch no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112250" update="2009-12-25">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-12-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地底世界の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Underground World</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chitei Sekai no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112251" update="2009-12-25">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-12-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あたらしい友だちの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">New Friends</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atarashii Tomodachi no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112252" update="2009-12-25">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サルタ最後の日?の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Last Day of Salta?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Salta Saigo no Hi? no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112253" update="2009-12-25">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">学校はたのしいの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">School Is Fun</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gakkou wa Tanoshii no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112254" update="2009-12-25">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カエル王子の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Frog Prince</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaeru Ouji no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112255" update="2009-12-25">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">野バラの精の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Wild Rose Fairy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nobara no Sei no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112256" update="2009-12-25">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コケコッコーの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cock a doodle doo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokekokkoo no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112257" update="2009-12-25">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-12-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ソウルくん誕生の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Birth of Soul</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soul-kun Tanjou no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112258" update="2009-12-25">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2009-12-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヒピラくん登場の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hipira is Introduced</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hipira-kun Toujou no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147625" update="2018-08-15">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<rating votes="2">3.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">赤い部屋の秘密の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Red Room`s Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akai Heya no Himitsu no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147626" update="2018-08-15">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<rating votes="2">3.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恐怖! ムンカー館の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scary! Munker`s Mansion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoufu! Munker-kan no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154302" update="2018-08-15">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2014-01-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ソウルくんピンチ!の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Soul-kun`s in a Pinch!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soul-kun Pinch! no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="167905" update="2015-04-15">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
