<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7276" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>25</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-12-29</startdate>
<enddate>2010-04-09</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Yutori-chan</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ゆとりちゃん</title>
</titles>
<url>http://yutori-chan.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="6241" type="Character Design">Nishio Kimitake</name>
<name id="1038" type="Work">Actas</name>
<name id="1038" type="Original Work">Actas</name>
<name id="6763" type="Series Composition">Asakawa Miya</name>
<name id="6090" type="Direction">Kawaguchi Keiichirou</name>
<name id="6241" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nishio Kimitake</name>
<name id="20085" type="Music">Kasamatsu Miki</name>
</creators>
<description>The story centres around http://anidb.net/ch15719 [Yutori-chan], a high school girl assigned to a part-time job in the marketing team of a medium-sized toy company called Popuu. There, she deal with the generation gaps that separate her from http://anidb.net/ch15718 [Tsumekomi-chan] (another part-time worker and a student at Japanese`s most prestigious university, T Dai) and http://anidb.net/ch15717 [Dankai-san] (the regular employee who oversees Yutori-chan).
Note: Biglobe claims that this is the first anime to be distributed by email, although what will actually be sent in each email message from the fictional character Yutori-chan to users is a URL address to a video. There was a limited free preview of the first four episodes that was distributed from December 29 to December 31.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="245">3.94</permanent>
<temporary count="248">5.88</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>40505.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11219</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7770</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4641</identifier>
<identifier>leqpsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://yutori-chan.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ゆとりちゃん</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2063</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>336271</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12712</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2378" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-02">
<name>hard-working</name>
<description>Describes someone, who is constantly, regularly, or habitually active or occupied.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2603" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-25">
<name>office lady</name>
<description>An office lady, often abbreviated OL, is a female office worker in Japan who performs generally pink collar tasks such as serving tea and secretarial or clerical work. Like many unmarried Japanese, OLs often live with their parents well into early adulthood. Office ladies are usually full-time permanent staff, although the jobs they do usually have little opportunity for promotion, and there is usually the tacit expectation that they leave their jobs once they get married.
OL stock characters are frequently found in josei manga and anime, often portrayed as attractive, clever, and wistful individuals bored with their jobs, over-pressured by their families, and facing psychological issues.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3012" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-02">
<name>pillow fight</name>
<description>A fight involving the use of pillows, as weapons, in a melee or projectile capacity. Usually they do not inflict harm but in the arms of certain individuals they are deadly weapons which, unlike real life pillow fights, can involve fatal injuries.</description>
<picurl>167002.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3444" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>hot springs visit</name>
<description>An onsen is a term for hot springs in the Japanese language, though the term is often used to describe the bathing facilities and inns around the hot springs. Often the cast of a show somehow ends up going to an onsen because of various reasons, such as winning a lottery ticket. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters nude and raise the DVD sales.
Another cheap variant is the http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160784.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3622" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>merchandising show</name>
<description>The bane of the parent`s wallet; this show usually has only a single reason for existence: to advertise the toy line it is based upon to the intended target audience. The variety of toys can range from accessories for girls and boys, to cards and figures or models. Most often the ability of the toys will be exaggerated or invokes magic to work in the anime. The toys`s names will also be continuously repeated in the anime, often accompanied by flashy effects and loud shouting. Combined with an intricate story that typically involves an adventure or a tournament of sorts, it makes for an effective commercial.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5805" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-06-11">
<name>post-credits scene</name>
<description>A little bit of the story is found after the credit titles. A little bonus for those patient enough!
This applies regardless of if the credits play over an ED sequence, or over the "regular episode" that continues to air into the credits.
A sequence at the end of an episode, showing what will happen in the next episode, is NOT a post-credits scene; that is a preview.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="15717" type="main character in" update="2010-03-11">
<rating votes="4">7.34</rating>
<name>Dankai Reiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44468.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15718" type="main character in" update="2010-03-11">
<rating votes="2">4.25</rating>
<name>Tsumekomi Shiori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44467.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15719" type="main character in" update="2010-03-11">
<rating votes="4">4.18</rating>
<name>Tanaka Yutori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44466.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15720" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-05">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Iyashi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Iyashi is a full-time employee in Popuu.</description>
<picture>1649.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="347" picture="41555.jpg">Nonaka Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15721" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-05">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Otsumen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Otsumen is a full-time employee in Popuu.</description>
<picture>1644.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3787" picture="25815.jpg">Miyazaki Hiromu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15722" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-05">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Kakarichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chief clerk in Popuu.</description>
<picture>1656.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3337" picture="211147.jpg">Ogino Seirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15723" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-05">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Kachou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Manager in Popuu.</description>
<picture>1654.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2067" picture="186243.jpg">Hoshino Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39319" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-24">
<rating votes="1">1.78</rating>
<name>Ayanokouji Baburuisu Kanamori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>169361.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="340" picture="17176.jpg">Yabe Masahito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39341" type="appears in" update="2011-12-04">
<name>Yutori Mama</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yutori`s mother.</description>
<picture>1660.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39342" type="appears in" update="2011-12-04">
<name>Shiwada Rumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shiwada Rumi is a lady around 40 years old.</description>
<picture>78041.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39343" type="appears in" update="2011-12-04">
<name>Shiwada Rumi (Magical Jukujo)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shiwada Rumi after the transformation.</description>
<picture>78042.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39344" type="appears in" update="2011-12-04">
<name>Rarittora</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Merchandise from Popuu.</description>
<picture>1661.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39345" type="appears in" update="2011-12-04">
<name>Soko Soko V</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Merchandise from Popuu.</description>
<picture>1666.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="39384" type="appears in" update="2011-12-05">
<name>Kangoshi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nurse in the hospital.</description>
<picture>78073.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39385" type="appears in" update="2011-12-05">
<name>Roujin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Old man in the hospital.</description>
<picture>78074.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3787" picture="25815.jpg">Miyazaki Hiromu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39386" type="appears in" update="2011-12-05">
<name>Shikai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Moderator of morning children`s show Morning Burning.</description>
<picture>78075.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2798" picture="22836.jpg">Oki Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="113056" update="2011-12-06">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<rating votes="1">9.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゆとりちゃん登場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Enter Yutori-chan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yutori-chan Toujou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="113058" update="2011-12-06">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<rating votes="1">7.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">電話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Telephone</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Denwa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="113059" update="2011-12-06">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<rating votes="1">3.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">説教</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lecture</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sekkyou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="113060" update="2011-12-06">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<rating votes="1">5.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サプライズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Surprise</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Surprise</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117031" update="2011-12-06">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>4</length>
<rating votes="1">3.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">予定表</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Schedules</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yoteihyou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117032" update="2011-12-06">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<rating votes="1">7.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ご機嫌予報</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mood Forecast</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gokigen Yohou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117062" update="2011-12-06">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>4</length>
<rating votes="1">3.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">じゃんけん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rock, Paper, Scissors</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Janken</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117067" update="2010-03-23">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>3</length>
<rating votes="1">2.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バブルくん登場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Enter Bubble-kun</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bubble-kun Toujou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117091" update="2011-12-06">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>4</length>
<rating votes="1">7.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新商品</title>
<title xml:lang="en">New Product</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shin Shouhin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117505" update="2011-12-06">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">社員旅行</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Company Trip</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shain Ryokou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117506" update="2011-12-06">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋愛観</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Philosophy of Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ren`aikan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117507" update="2011-12-06">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">セーブ?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Safe?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Save?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117508" update="2011-12-06">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">バブルくん再び</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bubble-kun Again</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bubble-kun Futatabi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117509" update="2011-12-06">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゆとりママ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yutori Mama</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yutori Mama</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117510" update="2011-12-06">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">イベント</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Event</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Event</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117511" update="2011-12-06">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">異義あり!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Objection!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Igiari!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117512" update="2011-12-06">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">乙女の夢</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Maiden`s Dream</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otome no Yume</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117513" update="2011-12-06">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">うわさ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rumors</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uwasa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117514" update="2011-12-06">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">火事</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaji</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117515" update="2011-12-06">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">お見舞い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Visiting</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omimai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117516" update="2011-12-06">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">錯乱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Confusion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakuran</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117552" update="2010-04-08">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>3</length>
<rating votes="1">3.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">きれいにしてね</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pretty It Up</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kirei ni Shite ne</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117637" update="2011-12-06">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">仕様</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Specification</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiyou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117638" update="2011-12-06">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">緊張</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tension</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kinchou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117639" update="2011-12-06">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">リサーチ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Research</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Research</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122106" update="2010-09-11">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
