<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7280" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-07-03</startdate>
<enddate>2010-09-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shukufuku no Campanella</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="synonym">La Campanella Della Benedizione</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="synonym">祝福的鐘聲</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="synonym">祝福之鐘</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Campanella</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">祝福のカンパネラ -la campanella della benedizione-</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Blessing of the Campanella</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">祝福的钟声</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8243" type="Side Story">Shukufuku no Campanella (2011)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8834" approval="22" total="30">Shining Hearts: Shiawase no Pan</anime>
<anime id="9741" approval="16" total="18">Zettai Bouei Leviathan</anime>
<anime id="10241" approval="14" total="15">Escha &amp; Logy no Atelier: Tasogare no Sora no Renkinjutsushi</anime>
<anime id="13779" approval="2" total="4">Last Period: Owarinaki Rasen no Monogatari</anime>
<anime id="13912" approval="2" total="2">Bermuda Triangle: Colorful Pastorale</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://www.marv.jp/special/campanella/</url>
<creators>
<name id="6028" type="Character Design">Fujita Mariko</name>
<name id="3644" type="Chief Animation Direction">Koga Makoto</name>
<name id="3894" type="Music">Elements Garden</name>
<name id="732" type="Work">AIC</name>
<name id="10737" type="Original Work">Windmill</name>
<name id="11255" type="Direction">Ushiro Shinji</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the Shukufuku no Campanella —la campanella della benedizione— adult game by http://anidb.net/cr10737 [Windmill].
Ert`Aria, a city known as the "Treasury of the World" is preparing for a harvest festival. http://anidb.net/ch16158 [Leicester Maycraft], a young item technician of the Oasis clan, encounters a shooting star near a party he is attending. Upon finding it, a girl appears before Leicester calling him her father.
Source: Wikipedia
Note: The first episode was screened as part of a one hour long promotional event held on Saturday, June 26, 2010 in Akihabara Theatre, Tokyo. Participants were chosen through an e-mail lottery held until Friday, June 18. The earliest television airing started on July 3.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="839">2.84</permanent>
<temporary count="853">5.67</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>231817.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11225</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9167</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>6979</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4667</identifier>
<identifier>ewyhpr</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.marv.jp/special/campanella/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Shukufuku_no_Campanella</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>祝福のカンパネラ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1971</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>337147</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12805</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2607</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1337</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2010/campanella</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11746</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>11880</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="520" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-14">
<name>nopan</name>
<description>The character foregoes underwear.</description>
<picurl>162753.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2396" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-08">
<name>swimsuit</name>
<description>A swimsuit is one of several kinds of garments designed to be worn by people engaging in water-based activities or sports or during certain activities under sunlight. Most kinds of swimsuit reveal a large portion of the body surface area, but exceptions exist. The more revealing kinds may also be worn as undergarment in sports that require wetsuits, or when there is a need to display the body, as in the case of beauty pageants or bodybuilding contests.
There is a very wide range of styles of modern swimsuits, which vary in relation to body coverage and materials. The choice of style of swimsuit is dependent on current fashions, community standards of modesty, and plain personal preference. Swimsuits for men usually expose the chest, while those for women do not usually do so; however, many women prefer to engage in water or sun activities with their torso uncovered, in a practice commonly described as toplessness or topfreedom. Since the early twentieth century a naturist movement has developed in western countries that seeks a return to non-sexual nakedness when swimming and during other appropriate activities; in some places around the world, nude beaches have been set aside for people who choose to engage in normal beach activities in the nude, and such beaches may or may not enforce nudity onto their goers.
In anime, it is common for at least one episode to feature the characters in swimsuits, usually as an excuse for gratuitous fanservice; when that happens, the episode is usually labeled a pool or beach episode, after the place the characters went to. Swimsuits, and in particular one-piece swimsuits, are a very common fetish in Japan; while the reason for that is uncertain, a common folk explanation is the fact that boys throughout their entire adolescence are commonly exposed to their female classmates wearing them, in what might be called an experiment in sexual discovery waiting to happen.</description>
<picurl>149786.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2640" parentid="2625" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-06-02">
<name>alternative past</name>
<description>An anime that takes place in an alternative past is an anime that clearly does not belong to the future or the present, and isn`t tied particularly closely to our history, or has ties to our history but only as a premise: there are too many things that don`t make sense for the time-period. In some cases there is futuristic technology present, but the overall setting still feels that of the past. However the setting must still take place on Earth, since we can not know if the history of a fantasy world is an alternate one or not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2830" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>furo scene</name>
<description>Furo (polite: Ofuro) is Japanese for bath, specifically a type of bath which originated as a short, steep-sided wooden bathtub. Baths of this type are found all over Japan in houses, apartments and traditional Japanese inns (Ryokans).
Furo are part of the Japanese ritual of bathing, not used for washing but for relaxing and warming oneself. Washing is carried out separately outside the furo, and only when completely clean does the bather enter the water. Generally Japanese bathrooms are small, so the bathroom is set up much like a walk-in shower area but containing the ofuro.
The cheapest and shortest way to show naked skin on TV, at least as much as allowed. It usually only takes up few minutes at most and as such it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales while still maintaining a "non-filler" episode.
Compare to the big brothers http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode] and http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160785.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2865" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>summer festival</name>
<description>The summer festival is used to show off the female protagonists in traditional Japanese clothing — the yukata — a casual form of kimono.
The festivities include food stalls (cotton candy, candy apples, choco bananas, taiyaki), various games (scoop goldfishes), and a fireworks display.</description>
<picurl>161023.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3202" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-04">
<name>adoring fan club</name>
<description>A character, group or characters, or an organisation is considered so awesome that a adoring fan club is formed to idolise them. Not only do they have notable admirers, but their fans become organised in such a fashion to have a following that could only be guaranteed in real life by precise and long increments of paparazzi-like stalking.
If the character is sufficiently cool, an instant fan club may happen practically overnight (i.e., within a few episodes of them being introduced), although the subject of admiration typically has mixed feelings about the entire affair.</description>
<picurl>48684.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3233" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-09-13">
<name>cooking curry</name>
<description>Japanese curry, usually eaten as curry rice, and often pickled vegetables, served on the same plate and eaten with a spoon, is one of the most popular dishes in Japan, where people eat it 125 times a year according to a survey made in 2005.
As such Japanese series will often devote a whole episode to the characters cooking and eating curry dishes.</description>
<picurl>160828.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3444" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>hot springs visit</name>
<description>An onsen is a term for hot springs in the Japanese language, though the term is often used to describe the bathing facilities and inns around the hot springs. Often the cast of a show somehow ends up going to an onsen because of various reasons, such as winning a lottery ticket. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters nude and raise the DVD sales.
Another cheap variant is the http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160784.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3896" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-23">
<name>bloodless wounds</name>
<description>No matter what weapon is used in what way to attack, hurt or kill somebody, there won`t be blood. You may see ripped clothes and smoke coming from the deadly wounds, but that`s it.
So if you have an aversion towards the red liquid but still love some action going on - this is the anime for you!</description>
<picurl>39189.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4150" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-01">
<name>everybody is nice</name>
<description>All characters are nice in their own way; nobody has ill intentions to others. Even if a secondary character appears to be bad at the beginning, they will redeem themselves or become tamed/pacified/neutralized swiftly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4465" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-08">
<name>stereoscopic imaging</name>
<description>This anime was shown in cinema rooms with stereoscopic 3D capabilities, released on Blu-ray 3D, or available for other stereoscopic 3D capable devices like the Nintendo 3DS or the Sharp AQUOS "NERV Edition" SH-06D smartphone. It was either produced in stereo 3D (e.g. "Baby Princess 3D Paradise Love") or produced in 2D and later converted from 2D to 3D (e.g. "Koukaku Kidoutai Stand Alone Complex: Solid State Society"). At any rate, it was at some point officially available with stereoscopic 3D depth effect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4521" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>lost technology</name>
<description>Any advanced technology or science-related knowledge that was lost for some reason fits the description. This could be technology from a time before a post-apocalyptic cataclysm, knowledge gained a long time ago but forgotten, or the relics of an old alien civilization only recently discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5843" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>sibling yin yang</name>
<description>In real life, siblings hardly ever act the same. Fiction sometimes takes this to an extreme.
Enter Sibling Yin Yang, the occurrence of siblings that are nearly polar opposites. If he`s cool and reckless, she`s responsible and thoughtful. If she`s a spiky-haired hooligan, he`s the nerdy wimpy one. If he`s an immature brat, she`s... well, you get the picture.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6137" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-09">
<name>catchphrase</name>
<description>A catchphrase is a sound, word or phrase commonly used by a person. That may be simply out of habit, or in an attempt to deliver some form of image, like that of cuteness. In fiction, characters often use catchphrases as a way to deliver specific personality traits. Examples include Otohime Mutsumi`s "ara ara" in Love Hina, Yang Wenli`s "yare yare" in Legend of the Galactic Heroes, Misuzu`s "gao" in AIR, Sakura`s "hoe" in Card Captor Sakura, Suiseiseki`s "desu" in Rozen Maiden, and Ayu`s "uguu" in Kanon (as well as several other characters in the same show).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7222" parentid="7220" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-30">
<name>groping</name>
<description>Groping is the act of subjecting another person to unwanted sexual touching.</description>
<picurl>68310.png</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="16086" type="main character in" update="2010-08-03">
<rating votes="14">6.87</rating>
<name>Agnes Boulange</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Agnes is an puppeteer, and holds traveling Circus act, involving many automata puppets.
Agnes also has a huge appetite and she loves desserts.</description>
<picture>45302.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="591" picture="226209.jpg">Mizuhashi Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16087" type="main character in" update="2010-08-03">
<rating votes="19">7.86</rating>
<name>Carina Verritti</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Carina is Leicester`s childhood friend, and her parents are grand duke in the city.
She is also a mage herself using a paddle like object to fly around town.
She lives in a mansion near the sea.</description>
<picture>45300.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="546" picture="17760.jpg">Koyama Kimiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16088" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-27">
<rating votes="14">7.52</rating>
<name>Salsa Tortilla</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45303.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18413" picture="48519.jpg">Yunohara Ari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16089" type="main character in" update="2010-08-03">
<rating votes="24">7.26</rating>
<name>Chelsea Arcot</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chelsea is one of the Holy Knights.
She has a horrible sense of direction.</description>
<picture>45301.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4715" picture="223209.jpg">Imai Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16090" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-26">
<rating votes="15">5.32</rating>
<name>Nina Lindberg</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45215.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="243" picture="17061.jpg">Yuimoto Michiru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16091" type="main character in" update="2010-08-09">
<rating votes="14">6.35</rating>
<name>Minette</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She was awoken by a meteor, and immediately considered Leicester to be her papa, due to him being the first man she saw.
She is a automata puppet made by Mise Altoise.</description>
<picture>45299.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15655" picture="44791.jpg">Kadowaki Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16092" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-03">
<rating votes="23">8.75</rating>
<name>Ritos Tortilla</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ritos acts clueless a lot. She always leaves her sister Salsa, to take the blame, fall for traps, or an attack from an enemy, while Ritos escape just in time.
She also ignores her sister, and often leaves her out of any plan she has, and withholds important information from her sister, until the last second.</description>
<picture>45304.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1671" picture="19766.jpg">Gotou Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16158" type="main character in" update="2010-03-27">
<rating votes="15">7.29</rating>
<name>Leicester Maycraft</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45298.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18064" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-20">
<rating votes="7">5.68</rating>
<name>Aberdeen Roland</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53637.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="221" picture="17039.jpg">Sugiyama Noriaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18065" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-18">
<rating votes="14">5.79</rating>
<name>Avril</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52533.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18066" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-03">
<rating votes="14">5.64</rating>
<name>Erin Garnet</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is a dragons avatar, who helps Leicester when her powers are split into two, making a shadow dragon.</description>
<picture>51935.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4713" picture="186249.jpg">Hasegawa Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18067" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-31">
<rating votes="2">7.45</rating>
<name>Golem</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>52252.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18068" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-03">
<rating votes="12">7.86</rating>
<name>Shelley Maycraft</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mother of Leicester Maycraft and act affectionately toward him.</description>
<picture>51668.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="488" picture="138714.jpg">Takano Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18069" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-07">
<rating votes="2">6.94</rating>
<name>Tango</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52366.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="556" picture="17848.jpg">Koorogi Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18070" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-03">
<rating votes="3">5.33</rating>
<name>Nagan Maycraft</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is Leicester`s father.</description>
<picture>52253.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18071" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-31">
<rating votes="6">4.79</rating>
<name>Nick La`juck</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51934.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18073" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-31">
<rating votes="5">4.34</rating>
<name>Fabious Verritti</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52251.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2729" picture="186723.jpg">Ishimaru Hiroya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18074" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-01">
<rating votes="13">5.81</rating>
<name>Fiore Verritti</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52365.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="556" picture="17848.jpg">Koorogi Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18075" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-20">
<rating votes="10">5.13</rating>
<name>Mise Altoise</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53636.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3006" picture="226210.jpg">Hirata Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18076" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-09">
<rating votes="10">4.85</rating>
<name>Miriam</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is Minette`s new friend in episode 5 and she is polite and shy.</description>
<picture>53062.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2204" picture="23065.jpg">Ichimura Oma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18077" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-01">
<rating votes="1">7.75</rating>
<name>Montecchia</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>52367.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3006" picture="226210.jpg">Hirata Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20341" type="appears in" update="2010-08-08">
<rating votes="1">7.75</rating>
<name>Clan Avventuriero Oasis</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>53024.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="21426" type="appears in" update="2019-03-30">
<rating votes="2">6.09</rating>
<name>Tortilla Company</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Tortilla Company is a rival clan of Oasis from Ert`Aria, consisting of the Tortilla sisters and their automaton Golem.</description>
<picture>231814.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="118670" update="2019-03-30">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-03</airdate>
<rating votes="13">2.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">流星群の夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Night of the Meteor Shower</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryuuseigun no Yoru</title>
<summary>In the city of Ert`Aria lives the young inventor Leicester Maycraft. He is part of a small adventuring clan called Oasis led by Carina Verritti, the daughter of the Archduke who rules over the city. Later that evening there is to be a regular meteor shower that comes once every seven years, and the clan is preparing a party. They meet a young puppeteer named Agnes Boulange who makes an impressive show of her magical automata puppets in the square. They also meet a young knight named Chelsea Arcot and the sisters Ritos and Salsa who run the Tortilla shop in front of their clan hall.
The clan holds their little party at the roof of the city`s cathedral, and a great meteor comes their way. It is not a physical meteor, but a cluster of Ale, the magical energy used in that world. It strikes a tower near where they are, and Leicester goes to investigate. In the tower finds a bed where what appears to be a young girl is lying down. When the others reach him, the girl awakens, and calls Leicester `Papa`.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="118771" update="2010-06-09">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-06-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Trailer</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview Video</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119437" update="2015-10-09">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">祝福のカンパネラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blessing of the Campanella</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shukufuku no Campanella</title>
<summary>Oasis and Aberdeen and Avril arrive at the mine, and are attacked by a horde of crystal monsters. Aberdeen and Avril remain nearby to repel as many of the monsters as they can as Oasis goes ahead. They appear before a great tower where the Waterwheel of the Heavens is. They are attacked by yet more monsters as they ascend the tower, so Nick and Garnet remain behind to keep the monsters from following.
They arrive at the top of the tower and see the Waterwheel of the Heavens, and see Mise Altoise in its centre. She tells them to leave, but they refuse, saying that they came all that way to attempt to repair the Waterwheel, but she tells them that it is impossible, as it was built with lost technology that no one today understands, and any mistake in attempting to repair it could lead to the permanent disappearance of the Ale energy in the whole world, and along with it everything that depends on it, such as automata like Minette and Miriam. Altoise says that they can try, but to do that will require to relinquish her hold on the Waterwheel and cause the Ale to go even more unstable until they can repair it.
Leicester and Minette go to work on repairing the Waterwheel while the rest of Oasis attempts to prevent the unstable Ale, which takes the form of serpentine monsters, from interfering with them. Against all odds they manage to succeed, and the resulting stabilisation of the Ale flow in the world causes most of the crystal monsters to stop attacking, and leads to Miriam`s eventual recovery.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119438" update="2015-10-09">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それぞれの思い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Differing Thoughts</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sorezore no Omoi</title>
<summary>Leicester and the rest of Oasis search the city to try to find Minette. Carina and Leicester are the first to find Aberdeen`s home. They are attacked by Avril, but Carina uses a spell to send Leicester ahead to the house while she fights Avril. He confronts Aberdeen and they do battle, and after Leicester makes his weapon produce an explosion that sends both of them reeling convinces him that there has to be another way, a way to save Miriam without needing to sacrifice Minette.
The Tortilla sisters return to Ert`Aria to report their findings to Oasis, of how there was a great explosion of light at the mountain and many crystal monsters suddenly appeared and began to attack. The Waterwheel of the Heavens must be nearby they reason, and they realise that if something is not done soon to stabilise the flow of Ale there will be a cataclysm of apocalyptic proportions. Oasis, Aberdeen, and Avril make their way there while the Tortillas remain to help the Archduke and Nagan to defend the city from the approaching wave of crystal monsters.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119439" update="2015-10-09">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-04</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミネットの選択</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Minette`s Choice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Minette no Sentaku</title>
<summary>Before leaving, Aberdeen says that he wants the Minette`s core, the Anima Pearl, to save Miriam, whose own automaton core is being badly affected by the instability of Ale flow in the world. This leaves Minette conflicted, as she wants to save Minette but her own passing would leave many unhappy, Miriam first of all. Oasis then goes about attempting to find Aberdeen and protect Minette from him, while at the research into the Ale instability left to the Tortilla sisters, who find that the strange phenomena are concentrated around the old mine where they had found the chamber with the large crystal.
That evening, Minette resolves to give herself up to Aberdeen to save Miriam, leaving the bells they had made with Leicester at everyone`s door. She meets Shelley at the Cathedral who speaks to her briefly about her decision. Leicester awakens and realises that Minette has left, and he goes to find her.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119440" update="2015-10-03">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">異変の予兆</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Unusual Omen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ihen no Yochou</title>
<summary>Nagan, Leicester`s father, explains about how the meteor shower activity that year is rather unusual, and how the previous shower was similar, and that Altoise had been aware of this and trying to investigate it. The letter she left for Agnes mentioned something called the `Waterwheel of the Heavens`, and how it was related to the mysterious meteor shower activity. Carina and Agnes research this mysterious artefact, but find nothing new.
Meanwhile, Minette meets with her friend Miriam again, and she says that she wants to give a present to her cat. Leicester suggests they give it a bell that uses an Ale Crystal. The two of them help Leicester make these bells, but as they are finishing Miriam collapses just as a meteor shower falls on the city. It is seen that Miriam is an automaton, and Aberdeen`s sister. He arrives with Avril to take her home.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119441" update="2015-10-03">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">8話だよ! 全員集合!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Eighth Episode! Everyone Gets Together!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">8-wa Da yo! Zen`in Shuugou!</title>
<summary>It is the Ert`Aria harvest festival, and to let Minette enjoy herself during the festivities, someone has to accompany her in case Aberdeen strikes again. The Tortilla sisters accompany her through most of the festival, and they see Agnes at her puppet show, Chelsea at the Knights` Cafe, and Carina at the cathedral looking over the artefacts. The Tortillas obtain an item from Leicester they need for the fireworks display that evening. Leicester brings Salsa back to Oasis to obtain an item from Nina, and is invited to join the rest of Oasis to watch the fireworks at the cathedral roof but instead opts to join Ritos to do the fireworks.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119442" update="2015-09-30">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-14</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人形の森</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Forest of Dolls</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ningyou no Mori</title>
<summary>It has been some time but apparently the Ale meteor shower is still going on. This concerns the Archduke so he sends Oasis on a new quest to investigate the phenomenon. They are asked to visit the forest home of Mise Altoise, Agnes`s teacher for possible clues. Agnes is familiar with the area and knows how to get through the maze of magical traps her teacher had set, but notices that they have been changed in subtle ways, so she expects Mise to be there, and is disappointed to find that she is not there. Oasis searches the house and finds a note for Agnes hidden in a secret compartment. Meanwhile, Nick, standing guard outside the house is attacked by a girl who proves to have exceptional fighting ability. The girl is recognised by Agnes, who calls her Avril, and she is shocked to see her. Avril`s partner, Aberdeen Roland, appears, also much to Agnes`s shock, as they were both apprentices with Mise in the past. He says that his goal is to obtain Minette`s core, and they have a fight with Oasis, but he decides to withdraw after the fight does not seem to progress.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119443" update="2015-09-30">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-07</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">パーティーの夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Night of the Party</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Party no Yoru</title>
<summary>The Archduke has organised a party to honour the Knights for their service to the city. Leicester and Nick have been given guard duty for that night over the artefacts at the cathedral which the Knights are supposed to protect. Leicester sees a great sword known as the Sacred Celestine and feels particularly attracted to it, fascinated in its construction by the ancients. The Tortillas have been given guard duty outside the Archduke`s palace, and as the party is going on, they are attacked by a crystal monster that seems to have the shape of a serpent. It can move so quickly when it attacks that its movements cannot be seen, so much so that no one can hit it. Minette summons Garnet who is sent to call for Leicester at the cathedral, and when he finally arrives he realises that the monster is attracted by light, so he uses a strong crystal-powered lamp to attract it and allow Chelsea to destroy it. How or why the monster could have appeared in the middle of the city is a mystery.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119444" update="2015-09-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Oasisの休日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Day Off for Oasis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oasis no Kyuujitsu</title>
<summary>Oasis has no quests assigned, but everyone is very busy, so no one is around to play with Minette, except Garnet, who suddenly materialises as she was getting bored in the dragon world. Nina asks Minette to buy the ingredients for the night`s dinner, which she happily does, considering it as her own personal quest for the day. The Tortilla sisters have also been asked to silently watch her and make sure that she is all right. Minette and Garnet go around town trying to collect everything from Nina`s list, and see the various members of Oasis about their duties, Agnes doing her puppet show in the square, Carina at the cathedral, and Chelsea wandering around lost. Garnet leaves to assist Chelsea in getting to her meeting with the knights at the cathedral, and Minette has to get to the butcher`s by herself. Along the way she meets with a girl named Miriam and they quickly become friends, and she shows Minette a short cut to the butcher`s. Along the way they see a cat stuck at the top of a high ledge, and Minette tries to rescue it and falls, but Leicester is there to catch her. They return the cat to its owner, who is grateful.
Minette returns to the clan house, without the meat from the butcher`s shop. However, the cat Minette rescued actually belonged to the butcher, so he asked the Tortillas to bring them a premium cut of meat as thanks for saving his pet.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119445" update="2015-09-18">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">闇の中</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Within the Darkness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yami no Naka</title>
<summary>The clan is going on another quest from an old woman who is one of Agnes`s most avid fans. They are to obtain a supply of hot spring crystals and go to an abandoned mine to obtain some. While mining these crystals they happen upon a hidden chamber with a large crystal in its centre, which has a complex flow of Ale energy emanating from it. Before they can examine it further the mine experiences subsidence due to the rains, and the ceiling cracks, and they try to get out, but Agnes and Leicester are separated from the others by a cave-in. The two of them manage to find another way out, and see a rainbow at the exit, and rejoin the others.
When they return to the clan house, they use the extra hot spring crystals to heat water for the bath, and Leicester is encouraged by his mother Shelley to go ahead. She has however also told the same thing to Agnes and the two of them bump into each other. They hide in a corner while the other girls get inside, and Leicester manages to get away without them realising he was there.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119446" update="2015-09-17">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絆の杖</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Staff of Bonds</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kizuna no Tsue</title>
<summary>Agnes and Leicester are planning something secretly, and later they propose that the clan take on a quest to recover some rainbow flowers that absorb all the light surrounding them. They grow in a certain forest which is growing darker and more dangerous as they flourish. Carina accepts, and they travel to that forest, and Carina and Leicester use her staff Montecchia to survey the area and tell the rest of the clan where to go. Their aerial survey discovers the spot where the flowers grow, and they direct everyone else where it is, while the two of them investigate ahead. As Carina tries to reach for one of the flowers they are attacked by a crystal monster, and she uses her staff to fly to a safe distance so she can use her magic on it while Leicester tries to fend it off, but she suddenly loses magical energy and falls on top of him, and the two of them are tangled in vines in a compromising position when the rest of the clan arrives and defeats the monster, recovering its crystal.
They return to town with the flowers, and Agnes and Leicester say that they wanted to go on the quest so they could obtain a crystal powerful enough for them to modify Montecchia so it can talk. After some false starts Leicester eventually succeeds with Carina`s help.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119447" update="2015-09-10">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">竜の世界</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The World of Dragons</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryuu no Sekai</title>
<summary>The young girl calls Leicester "Papa", which scandalises Carina, but it turns out that the girl, named Minette, is actually a highly sophisticated automaton created by Agnes`s mentor, Mize Altowirz, activated by the burst of Ale energy from the meteor, and bonded with him as he was the first person she saw.
The next morning, Carina`s father, the Archduke Fabious Verritti, along with Chelsea, comes by and informs them that the meteor shower has caused some trouble in the underground treasury. The Ale energies from the meteor shower may have been absorbed by some of the treasures and created a crystal monster, and he asks the clan to investigate. At the advice of the Archduke they bring Minette along with them. They find the strange energies emanating from a magical door that leads into the dragon world, and they encounter a shadow dragon with a crystal on its head. None of their attacks work, but a strange woman speaks to Minette and tells her to use her powers to ease the dragon`s troubled feelings. She does this, using her Anima Pearl, and the dragon disappears, leaving a jewel in its wake. The strange woman, named Garnet, is actually a dragon and the monster they just fought was her shadow. She gives the jewel to Minette, saying that she can summon her by using it.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119818" update="2011-05-19">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-07-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119819" update="2011-03-11">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-07-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121852" update="2011-03-11">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-08-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121853" update="2011-03-11">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-08-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121854" update="2011-03-11">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-09-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121940" update="2010-09-07">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-08-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122679" update="2015-11-01">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="5">9.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Issho ni Bath Time: Carina version</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124724" update="2010-10-29">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="4">4.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Issho ni Bath Time: Minette version</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125582" update="2010-11-28">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="4">6.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Issho ni Bath Time: Chelsea version</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126375" update="2010-12-25">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="4">8.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Issho ni Bath Time: Agnes version</title>
</episode>
<episode id="127833" update="2011-01-30">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="3">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Issho ni Bath Time: Ritos &amp; Salsa version</title>
</episode>
<episode id="127834" update="2011-03-12">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-08-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128362" update="2011-02-25">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">9.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Issho ni Bath Time: All together version</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
