<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7286" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-04-02</startdate>
<enddate>2010-06-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">B Gata H Kei</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">B-Type H-Style</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">B-cup H-group</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">B-type H-persona</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">B-Type H-Group</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">B-группа H-персона</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Второй размер, интим предлагать</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">B-Gata H-Kei</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">B型H系</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">BGata</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">BGHK</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">B型H系</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">B Gata H Kei: Yamada`s First Time</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Yamada : Ma première fois</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">B型H系</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="7978" approval="29" total="55">Onii-chan no Koto Nanka Zenzen Suki ja Naindakara ne!!</anime>
<anime id="12554" approval="9" total="10">Hajimete no Gal</anime>
<anime id="4067" approval="5" total="7">Joshikousei: Girl`s High</anime>
<anime id="10395" approval="2" total="10">Soredemo Sekai wa Utsukushii</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="22">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="271998">Laught a lot. Perfectly what I`am expecting from this genre.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="192886">surprisingly great anime
rofled every episode</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="319333">If you like School comedy`s with a touch of ecchi this is something you should watch, it`s a little whacky but the leadcharacter is nuts which makes this anime enjoyable. Not the best I`ve seen so far, but I would still recommend it. :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="409786">funny funny funny</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="312687">This one is hilarious. Pretty coherent, but definitely watch it for the laughs.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="502713">I actually LOL`d quite a few times, it`s very funny in places, hilarious even, there are a few pacing issues, some episodes seemed pointless, others didn`t continue (like the camping one), there were barely any cliche characters, but of course by typical japanese fashion the story doesn`t reach home base, but it got a lot further than most anime and further than i would have thought, but there always has to be something stupid and contrived to stop the goal from being reached otherwise the story would finish and they wouldn`t be able to milk it to death.
I loved how they showed each sides point of view, that`s rarely done, there`s a lot to learn from that. An R rated DVD only episode or two could have brung a nice solid conclusion to this anime, but we don`t live in a world were that can happen (yet). It can get a little annoying at times, but this underrated anime is definitely recommended. (7/10)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="81544">Funny female character and very decent situation twists , worth the watching time .</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="338795">I was gagging of laughter watching this series for it`s one of my favourite Comedy/Ecchi animes out there and for a change a perverted virgin school girl is leading the parade.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="564519">ecchi/comedy fans are gonna be really satisfied with this. even if im not an ecchi fan it was really funny and sort of cute.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="403846">Not your average ecchi. What surprises in this show is that it actually have a story and a decent one at that (as decent as it can get for ecchi/comedy genres). In addition to that the comedy is just too much, it make you cry all the time (from LoLing). Definitely a must see for everyone.

p.s. Dont Judge it by the rating,  7 is a way underrated.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="712992">I did not expect to enjoy it as much as I did. from the premise it looked like typical fan service anime, where girls are as dirty minded as guys hope them to be. and for the most part, it is that anime, full of fan service.
but the Jokes work. the situations are hilarious, and not in contrived way. while watching it I never felt creepy. so that`s good enough for me. and the jokes did literally mode me LOL.

on more analytical note, if the gender roles were reversed, it would have been considered very rapy. So its very nice socially commentary the show makes behind the scenes, whether intentionally or not.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="426409">This is definitely one of the most funny anime I`ve ever seen. It`s quite ecchi, but then surprisingly modest in time. Well, they are all shy in the end...
Best is the noise that little figure makes when Kosuda gets an er.....
You`ll see what I mean ;-)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="467556">its it the first anime I have saw. 
and it was really funny, and had everything a serie normal need to have :D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="333240">Whatever you are expecting this is...it isn`t..xD
I laughed pretty hard sometimes; this is funny has hell! Definitely recommend it to ecchi and comedy fans.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="456383">Definetly one of the best series I`ve watched... This story really kept me going crazy as to how it will unfold. It reminded me of all the akwardness involved in your first time(sex). It is really fun and cute too. A must watch for anyone that have lost their virginities.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="758779">Extremely fun echi anime. The cast is extremely strong while exagerated as all Hell. To go along with that it was just great to see the antics they always got into, even when I was able to predict what would basically happen at the beginnig of each episode.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="188597">this is a fantastic anime! one of the best school-comedy-romance animes i´ve ever seen. and trust me i´ve seen a lot. ^^ the story is really great and believable. the charas and the animation are great as well. and the ecchi part is right at the spot. not to much.
short and sweet: a must see.

ps: sad there is no 2nd seasson.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="421806">This was great. rofl every episode.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.bgata-hkei.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3661" type="Series Composition">Nishizono Satoru</name>
<name id="6520" type="Direction">Yamamoto Yuusuke</name>
<name id="8149" type="Music">Fujima Hitoshi</name>
<name id="4672" type="Music">Fujita Junpei</name>
<name id="13979" type="Character Design">Yahiro Yuuko</name>
<name id="13979" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yahiro Yuuko</name>
<name id="754" type="Animation Work">Hal Film Maker</name>
<name id="10623" type="Chief Animation Direction">Abe Tomoyuki</name>
<name id="11268" type="Original Work">Sanri Youko</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a seinen 4-koma manga by http://anidb.net/cr11268 [Sanri Youko], serialised in http://anidb.net/ch32180 [Weekly Young Jump].
The sexually inexperienced http://anidb.net/ch13815 [schoolgirl] is aiming to get 100 sex-friends after entering high school. But she always freaks out, because she thinks she would be laughed at for her virginity. That is why she searches for a virgin-guy, since he would be inexperienced as well, and would not look down on her. One day, quite by chance, she literally bumps into such a http://anidb.net/ch15168 [guy], later realizing that he actually sits right next to her at school! Fate?
And so her seduction attempts begin...</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="4199">5.28</permanent>
<temporary count="4239">6.99</temporary>
<review count="6">5.96</review>
</ratings>
<picture>43375.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11199</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7817</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4668</identifier>
<identifier>gbggel</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.bgata-hkei.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B_Gata_H_Kei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B型H系</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1886</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>336312</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12528</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11648</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1471" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-19">
<name>bad cooking</name>
<description>The character is hopelessly terrible at cooking, and any attempts he or she makes at making even the simplest dishes are spectacular failures.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1651" parentid="2883" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>photography</name>
<description>Photography is the art or process of producing images by the action of radiant energy and especially light on a sensitive surface (such as film or an optical sensor).
Source: Merriam-Webster</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2491" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-09-09">
<name>nurse</name>
<description>For hentai shows, it`s enough if a http://anidb.net/t884 [nurse costume] is worn without the female character actually working as a nurse.
For ecchi shows, the nurse profession must play a big enough part in the overall setting.
Almost completely exclusive to hentai animations.</description>
<picurl>160445.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2679" parentid="2672" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Kyoto</name>
<description>Kyoto Prefecture is a prefecture of Japan in the Kansai region of the island of Honshu. The capital is the city of Kyoto.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214383.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2706" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>masturbation</name>
<description>Manual erotic stimulation of the genitals or other erogenous regions, often to orgasm, either by oneself or a partner.</description>
<picurl>210612.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2779" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>multiple couples</name>
<description>More than one couple is developed in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2784" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>sudden girlfriend appearance</name>
<description>Sudden Girlfriend Appearance anime involve a sudden change in the main character`s life where (s)he suddenly gets confronted with an individual (s)he`s sexually attracted to, the two of them inevitably becoming a couple.</description>
<picurl>210066.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2805" parentid="2798" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>4-koma manga</name>
<description>Yonkoma manga (4コマ漫画, four cell manga, or 4-koma for short), a comic-strip format, generally consists of gag comic strips within four panels of equal size ordered from top to bottom. (They also sometimes run right-to-left horizontally or use a hybrid 2x2 style, depending on the layout requirements of the publication in which they appear.) Though the word yonkoma comes from the Japanese, the style also exists outside of Japan in other Asian countries as well as in the English-speaking market.</description>
<picurl>70558.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2816" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sexual fantasies</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime let their imaginations run wild thinking about another character.
Yes, they are thinking about sex, and in an ecchi anime these thoughts are often perverted, leading to a nosebleed. But it may also be romanticising simply being husband and wife, and everything that implies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2820" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>wardrobe malfunction</name>
<description>A euphemistic term for an embarrassing display of a body part when clothing droops, falls, or is torn. Wikipedia: "Super Bowl XXXVIII half-time show" for more details.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3721" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-07">
<name>RPG elements</name>
<description>The anime shows elements of a `R`ole `P`laying `G`ame, either as part of a parody or because the anime is actually based on an RPG.
Typical elements: When collecting items, beating opponents, or levelling up a distinct (often childishly sounding) sound cue is played. A HUD (`H`eads `U`p `D`isplay) may also be presenting in combat, showing vital player and "enemy" statistics.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3751" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-02">
<name>grandiose displays of wealth</name>
<description>Some of the characters in this anime come from very wealthy families. A huge estate with large mansion or castle, a flotilla of expensive cars, private jets or islands, and many servants will impress the viewer profoundly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4030" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-13">
<name>mental cinema</name>
<description>The ability to imagine all kinds of things, as if they were real.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5485" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-28">
<name>penis jokes</name>
<description>A penis or other phallic object is used as a device to elicit laughter from the viewer. This also includes indirect references to such objects provided the intent is clearly the same.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5518" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-03">
<name>flat chest jokes</name>
<description>Jokes about the (supposedly or actually) flat chest of a character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5843" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>sibling yin yang</name>
<description>In real life, siblings hardly ever act the same. Fiction sometimes takes this to an extreme.
Enter Sibling Yin Yang, the occurrence of siblings that are nearly polar opposites. If he`s cool and reckless, she`s responsible and thoughtful. If she`s a spiky-haired hooligan, he`s the nerdy wimpy one. If he`s an immature brat, she`s... well, you get the picture.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5875" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>jealousy</name>
<description>A character is jealous of another character either due to love, or power, or wealth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5915" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>French kiss</name>
<description>A kiss in which the tongue enters the partner`s mouth.</description>
<picurl>238326.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5944" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-28">
<name>i got a crush on you</name>
<description>It happens when a person develops an interest in someone that seems mysterious, smart, sexy, cute, fun, etc. Basically just someone you would like to spend more time with. Crushes are usually one sided and they happen more frequently among middle and high school students.
A person with a crush usually has a hard time expressing or conveying his/her feelings to that other person. That other person is usually clueless of the situation. Sometimes that person knows about the crush, but feels annoyed or embarrassed by it for some reason.
Having a crush on someone does not mean you are in love with that person, at least not yet. Depending on the situation crushes could develop differently (for better or worse):
1) Larger scale interactions (love).
2) Dating relationships.
3) Scary obsession or stalker type situations.
4) Disappear over time or distance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6083" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>master-servant relationship</name>
<description>To some genres, this would suggest a genuine pairing where one person exists to serve another person, such as in some action/dramas where the pair becomes united by destiny as partners — fighting or battles between different pairs/partners will usually be a dominant part of the story.
In other genres, this suggests a relationship where one person may be occupied as or even forcefully treated as a servant or slave to the other who designates themself the master — these services usually apply anywhere from tsundere/romantic-comedies to ecchi or to the more extreme in hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6349" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>multi-segment episodes</name>
<description>Multi-segment episodes are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes], which are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length (up to and including 10 minutes).
Also not to be confused with an OVA or music video with multiple (otherwise unrelated) full-length http://anidb.net/t7241 [bundled episodes] consolidated into a single episode video track.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="13815" type="main character in" update="2011-04-24">
<rating votes="73">6.62</rating>
<name>Yamada</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yamada is a third year high-school girl. Although she is a virgin, in her mind she had over 100 sexual encounters already.
One day she falls in love with http://anidb.net/ch15168 [Kosuda Takashi], a plain-looking guy at her school. Unexperienced in love as she is, she tries her best to make him notice her.</description>
<picture>70493.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15165" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-01">
<rating votes="9">5.89</rating>
<name>Yamada no Erogami-sama</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45510.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2038" picture="49098.jpg">Shishido Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15166" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-01">
<rating votes="17">3.52</rating>
<name>Misato Mami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45517.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13791" picture="151660.jpg">Iwasaki Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15167" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-01">
<rating votes="30">6.02</rating>
<name>Miyano Mayu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45513.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15168" type="main character in" update="2010-04-01">
<rating votes="32">3.20</rating>
<name>Kosuda Takashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45514.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="545" picture="188506.jpg">Abe Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15169" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-01">
<rating votes="21">7.09</rating>
<name>Kosuda Kazuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45515.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15170" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-01">
<rating votes="23">6.25</rating>
<name>Yamada Chika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45511.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1735" picture="31933.jpg">Shimoda Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15171" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-01">
<rating votes="19">4.87</rating>
<name>Katase Aoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45518.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4929" picture="41385.jpg">Kitta Izumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15172" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-01">
<rating votes="31">6.68</rating>
<name>Takeshita Miharu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45512.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15173" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-01">
<rating votes="17">6.76</rating>
<name>Akai-sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45509.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2228" picture="21776.jpg">Gibu Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15174" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-01">
<rating votes="23">3.97</rating>
<name>Kanejou Kyouka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45516.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16587" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-24">
<rating votes="12">4.47</rating>
<name>Matsuo Daisuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Matsuo Daisuke is the boyfriend of http://anidb.net/ch15172 [Takeshita Miharu]. He works part-time in a bookshop, and is interested in classical literature (Dostoevsky, Tolstoy, etc.).</description>
<picture>70492.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1510" picture="49914.jpg">Koizumi Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18605" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-24">
<rating votes="9">1.48</rating>
<name>Kanejou Keiichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kyoka`s brother. He is unaware of his sister`s brother complex. He starts chasing after Yamada, right after she swiftly rejects him.</description>
<picture>70491.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="612" picture="79531.jpg">Maeno Tomoaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18606" type="appears in" update="2010-06-08">
<rating votes="5">5.72</rating>
<name>Ichihara-san</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kyoka`s housemaid.</description>
<picture>49322.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18698" picture="49321.jpg">Nakane Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18607" type="appears in" update="2010-06-08">
<rating votes="5">4.41</rating>
<name>Kobayashi Maki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yamada`s friend.</description>
<picture>49323.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10422" picture="223562.jpg">Kusunoki Hiroko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18608" type="appears in" update="2010-06-08">
<rating votes="3">2.77</rating>
<name>Kosuda Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takashi`s mother.</description>
<picture>49324.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18698" picture="49321.jpg">Nakane Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18609" type="appears in" update="2010-06-08">
<rating votes="2">2.65</rating>
<name>Miyano Mahiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mayu`s brother.</description>
<picture>49326.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="19346" type="appears in" update="2011-03-12">
<rating votes="2">2.65</rating>
<name>Akimoto Kouta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kosuda`s bad friend. He is also a classmate of Kosuda and Yamada and is one of her groupies.</description>
<picture>67671.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11041" picture="82436.jpg">Ooshita Kouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19347" type="appears in" update="2011-03-20">
<rating votes="3">2.77</rating>
<name>Kurokawa Futoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kurokawa Futoshi is another of Kosuda`s friends and classmates.</description>
<picture>68146.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20022" picture="51304.jpg">Matsui Fumihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19348" type="appears in" update="2011-03-12">
<rating votes="3">5.97</rating>
<name>Sakai Kaori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakai Kaori is another of Yamada`s friends. She is the tsukkomi to Kobayashi`s boke.</description>
<picture>67674.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19122" picture="222832.jpg">Hase Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19349" type="appears in" update="2011-03-12">
<rating votes="2">2.65</rating>
<name>Kudou Shun`ichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kudou Shun`ichi is another of Kosuda`s friends and classmates.</description>
<picture>67675.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1510" picture="49914.jpg">Koizumi Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19382" type="appears in" update="2011-03-12">
<rating votes="3">3.34</rating>
<name>Kosuda Takashi no Erogami-sama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67672.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="545" picture="188506.jpg">Abe Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19383" type="appears in" update="2011-03-12">
<rating votes="3">5.30</rating>
<name>Miyano Mayu no Erogami-sama</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67673.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19384" type="appears in" update="2011-10-28">
<rating votes="3">7.17</rating>
<name>Kanejou Kyouka no Erogami-sama</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74577.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="117311" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-02</airdate>
<rating votes="24">6.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぼーい♂みーつ♀がーる あなたの『初めて』私にちょうだい!! / 放課後大作戦! とりあえずキスしましょ?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Boy Meets Girl. Let Me Have Your "First Time"! - Big Gambit After School! Why Don`t We Start With a Kiss?</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Boy Meets Girl Voglio essere la"Prima"!! - Strategia del Dopo-Scuola! Cominciamo con un bacio?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boy Meets Girl Anata no "Hajimete" Watashi ni Choudai!! / Houkago Daisakusen! Toriaezu Kiss Shimasho?</title>
<summary>Yamada is the cutest girl in the whole school, and she wants to have her way with 100 different boys before the final bell rings. There’s just one problem: she’s never even been kissed!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="117347" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-18</airdate>
<rating votes="14">7.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">僕らのために世界は回る さよなら... B型H系 / 天使になった山田! さらば! B型H系!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The World Revolves for Us! Goodbye... B Gata H Kei! - Yamada Turns Into an Angel! Farewell! B Gata H Kei!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bokura no Tame ni Sekai wa Mawaru Sayonara... B Gata H Kei / Tenshi ni Natta Yamada! Saraba! B Gata H Kei!!</title>
<summary>As the New Year approaches, Yamada and Kosuda slip out of their clothes and into a bed at the local love motel! Lust is in the air, but it’s kind of hard to make out over the sound of that ambulance!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="117348" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-11</airdate>
<rating votes="15">9.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">2年H組のクリスマス・イブ あたしをベッドにつれてって♡ / 金城さんが見てる!? 限界ギリギリ『生』放送!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Year 2 Class H`s Christmas Eve! Take Me to Bed! - Kanejo Is Watching?! A "Live" Broadcast That Pushes the Limits!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">2-nen H-gumi no Christmas. Atashi o Bed ni Tsuretette. / Kanejou-san ga Miteru!? Genkai Girigiri "Nama" Housou!</title>
<summary>A luxurious Christmas party provides the perfect opportunity for Yamada and Kosuda to take their relationship to the next level! Too bad someone’s watching their every move on a hidden camera!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="117349" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-04</airdate>
<rating votes="14">6.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">金城家の一族 セレブな兄のキラキラな秘密! / 恋する途中?私の男(コスダ)に手を出すな!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Kanejo Family! Richy Brother`s Sparkling Secret! - On My Way to Love? Don`t Hit on My Kosuda!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanejou Ie no Ichizoku. Celeb na Ani no Kirakira na Himitsu! / Koi Suru Tochuu? Watashi no Otoko (Kosuda) ni Te o Dasuna!!</title>
<summary>When Kanejou’s brother confesses his interest in Yamada, his stunning little sister takes aim at Kosuda! Will Yamada stick with her ordinary virgin - or go after the hunk and get stuck between siblings?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="117350" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そんな! みんなの見てる前で... 嫌いなんて言ってないじゃん...秋 / 体育祭にかけろ! 好きにすればいいじゃん...秋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Oh No! In Front of Everyone... I Never Said I Don`t Like You... Autumn. - Put Your Hopes in Field Day! Suit Yourself... Autumn.</title>
<title xml:lang="it">No! Non Così, di Fronte a Tutti... Non ho Mai Detto che ti Odio... Autunno - Scommettiamo sul Festival dello Sport! Fa` pure quello che vuoi... Autunno</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sonna! Minna no Miteru Mae de... Kirai Nante Ittenai jan... Aki / Taiikusai ni Kakero! Suki ni Sureba Ii jan... Aki</title>
<summary>Kosuda’s public confession of love leaves Yamada feeling flustered. And that’s before a super-handsome stranger sees her in a cheerleading outfit! Will Kosuda be shunned in the wake of this hunky new arrival?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="117351" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">わーい, 修学旅行だ! 二人っきりになれなくて... / 俺, 山田のことが, す...すったもんだの珍道中</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yay! It`s a School Trip! No Chance to Be Alone... - I Have to Tell You That I L... The Trip Causes a Great Fuss!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Evvai! Siamo in Gita Scolastica! Non riusciremo a stare da soli...- Yamada, io ti a... Un Sacco di Storie, Un Viaggio Eccitante</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Waai! Shuugakuryokou Da! Futarikkiri ni Narenakute ... / Ore, Yamada no Koto ga, Su ... Suttamonda no Chindouchuu</title>
<summary>It’s school field trip time, which means the girls talk about guys, the guys talk about girls, and they both try desperately to summon the courage to actually talk to each other!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="117352" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-14</airdate>
<rating votes="12">4.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スク水で大決闘! アンタにだけは絶対負けない! / 夏の日の思いで...山田, 野生に帰る!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Major Duel in School Swimsuits! I`m Not Gonna Lose Against You! - Memories of a Summer Day... Yamada Returns to the Wild!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La Grande Sfida in Costume da Bagno! Non Perderò Mai Contro di Te! - Giornate Estive da Ricordare... Yamada Ritorna Selvaggia!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">School-Mizu de Daikettou! Anta ni Dake wa Zettai Makenai! / Natsu no Hi no Omoide... Yamada, Yasei ni Kaeru!</title>
<summary>Swimsuits are the story of the hour as Yamada puts her looks to the ultimate test in a scandalous showdown with Kanejou. Next up, camping, toy weapons, and a moonlit photo shoot - clothing optional!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="117353" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-07</airdate>
<rating votes="12">4.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">金城さんが来る! あのキラキラが許せない! / バラ色の笑顔の裏に...金城の黒い秘密!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kanejo Is Coming! I Can`t Stand That Sparkle! - Behind That Rosy Smile Is... Kanejo`s Dark Secret!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Arriva Kanejou-san! Non sopporto che sia così brillante!- Dietro quello splendido sorriso... si nasconde l`oscuro segreto di Kanejou!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanejou-san ga Kuru! Ano Kirakira ga Yurusenai! / Barairo no Egao no Ura ni... Kanejou no Kuroi Himitsu!!</title>
<summary>Yamada is disturbed by the arrival of a stunning new student from across the sea. The new girl quickly becomes the center of attention and sets her sights on stealing Yamada’s man!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="117354" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-30</airdate>
<rating votes="14">5.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">汗と涙のバレンタインヤマダより愛? をこめて! / 磨けエロパワー! こんな感覚, 初めてなの...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yamada`s Level Increased! She Learned How to Deep Kiss! - Work on Your Naughty Power! I`ve Never Felt a Sensation Like This Before...</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Un San Valentino fatto di Sudore e Lacrime! Con Più "Amore" di Yamada - Aumenta il tuo Ero-Power! E` la Prima Volta che provo questa Sensazione...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ase to Namida no Valentine Yamada Yori Ai ? o Komete! Migake Ero Power! Konna Kankaku, Hajimete na no...</title>
<summary>When Valentine’s Day rolls around, Yamada tries to seduce Kosuda with homemade chocolates. If that doesn’t work, she can always stop wearing panties!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="117355" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="16">7.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ときめく聖夜 ファーストキスって, なんの味? / このままじゃ帰れない! いちゃラブ公園に行こうよ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Romantic Christmas Eve! What Does the First Kiss Taste Like? - I Can`t Go Back Empty-Handed! Let`s Go to the Make-Out Park!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Un`Eccitante Vigilia di Natale Com`è il sapore del primo bacio? - Non posso tornare a casa così! Andiamo al parco degli innamorati!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokimeku Seiya First Kiss-tte, Nan no Aji? / Kono Mama ja Kaerenai! Icha Love Kouen ni Ikou yo!</title>
<summary>The holidays have arrived, and lust is in the air! Kosuda and Yamada are ready to get busy on a special Christmas Eve date, but the park is full of perverts!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="117356" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="14">5.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暗室で急接近! ちょっとキケンな部活動!? / 燃える文化祭! 学園の女王はこの山田(わたし)!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Suddenly So Close in the Darkroom! Kinda Dangerous Club Activities?! - Passionate School Festival! I, Yamada, Will Be the School`s Queen!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Approccio Improvviso nella Camera Oscura! Un`Attività del Club Leggermente Pericolosa?! - Un Eccitante Festival Scolasticol! Io, Yamada, sono la Regina della Scuola!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anshitsu de Kyuusekkin! Chotto Kiken na Bukatsu!? / Moeru Bunkasai! Gakuen no Joou wa Kono Watashi!!</title>
<summary>In the private confines of the darkroom, Yamada sheds her top and makes a move on Kosuda! Later, she enters a school beauty contest to show the boy exactly what he’s missing!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="117357" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="20">5.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そうだ! プールに行こう 私の水着, 見たいよねっ! / ライバル出現 誰よ? あのFカップ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Oh, Yeah! Let`s Go to a Pool! You Wanna See Me in a Swimsuit, Right?! - Here Comes the Rival! Who`s That F-Cup Girl?!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Giusto, andiamo in piscina! - Vuoi vedermi in costume, vero? ~ E` comparsa una rivale! - Chi è questa maledetta Coppa F?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sou da! Pool ni Ikou Watashi no Mizugi, Mitai yo ne! / Rival Shutsugen Dare yo? Ano F-Cup!?</title>
<summary>Yamada takes her mission of seduction to the next level by slipping into a sexy swimsuit and inviting Kosuda to the local waterpark! But when the splashing subsides, a busty, bespectacled rival enters the picture!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="117413" update="2011-01-04">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-04-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117414" update="2011-01-04">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-04-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117415" update="2018-02-25">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1 (0:15)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128808" update="2018-02-25">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">BD/DVD CM 3 (0:30)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128809" update="2018-02-25">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">BD/DVD CM 2 (0:30)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128810" update="2018-02-25">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">BD/DVD CM 1 (0:15)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128811" update="2018-02-25">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 2 (0:15)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
