<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7307" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-04-07</startdate>
<enddate>2010-09-15</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">K-On!!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Легкая музыка!!</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Hafif Müzik Kulübü!!</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Клуб легкої музики!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">k-on2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">k-on 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">keion 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">けいおん!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">K-On! Season 2</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">K-ON!!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">轻音少女 第二季</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6257" type="Prequel">K-On!</anime>
<anime id="8280" type="Side Story">Eiga K-On!</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="6783" approval="10" total="24">Sora no Oto</anime>
<anime id="9077" approval="6" total="14">Tari Tari</anime>
<anime id="10134" approval="2" total="8">SoniAni: Super Sonico The Animation</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="10">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="14283">If you liked the first season, you will like this one, its bascially the same.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="306544">Second season is basically the same as first, but with much better animation and quality. Great combination of comedy and music makes it light and worth to watch^^</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="179886">if you like comedy, moe and music, you`ll definitely will love k-on!! No deep story, but fun to watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="652565">To me, this thing is awesome !!! it just had a lot of sweet moment, great animation, voice acting that gonna make your heart melt, and really you will enjoy every second of watching this show. Unfortunately though, this show is not for everyone, some people may find this to contain a lot of cringe and the cuteness is overacted, so just watch the first couple of eps and judge for yourself (as they are pretty representative of the content for the entire show)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="420280">I watched the first season without even skipping OP or ED and enjoyed it. 
K-on!! Is still quite good, but not as enjoyable as season one. And I really don`t like the opening song xD</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="403522">Season 2 is very similar to the first season. If you enjoyed the first season than definitely watch the second season.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="99271">K-On is just great, I was moved because it feels like you`re really there. The songs are pretty sweet too. It`s trivial but it`s soo real, and the parting was so sad, because it was like I was saying farewell with them. Maybe it was so good because it`s all about things we can relate to!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="319333">In the beginning I  thought this show was pretty slow, but the intro and endingsong was just pure awesome.. but the 2nd endingsong beats every song I`ve heard from this anime so far. I can`t wait until their live with those songs which I hope they`ll be playing. Anyways the show gets better each episode. This is a MUST watch :).</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="555526">It`s just... I don`t know how to put in in words. I felt like i was having fun with them, being with them. I struggled a lot to even finish this anime, because i didn`t wanted it to end. I never had such an intense post-anime depression to be honest...</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/k-on/</url>
<creators>
<name id="736" type="Animation Work">Kyoto Animation</name>
<name id="1790" type="Series Composition">Yoshida Reiko</name>
<name id="528" type="Character Design">Horiguchi Yukiko</name>
<name id="1507" type="Original Work">Kakifly</name>
<name id="1791" type="Direction">Yamada Naoko</name>
<name id="528" type="Chief Animation Direction">Horiguchi Yukiko</name>
<name id="2424" type="Music">Hyakkoku Hajime</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr1507 [Kakifly]`s seinen 4-koma manga series K-ON!, serialised in Manga Time Kirara since 2007.
It is the final year of high school for http://anidb.net/ch4424 [Hirasawa Yui] (guitar), http://anidb.net/ch4426 [Tainaka Ritsu] (drums), http://anidb.net/ch4425 [Akiyama Mio] (bass), and http://anidb.net/ch4427 [Kotobuki Tsumugi] (keyboard); the founding members of the Light Music Club. Together with their junior member http://anidb.net/ch7124 [Nakano Azusa] (guitar), they spend their days after school in the music room enjoying tea and sweets, and practising music. Amidst band practice, preparations for the new student orientation performance, scouting for new members, and student responsibilities they still have time for After School Tea Time.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="4802">7.62</permanent>
<temporary count="4835">7.87</temporary>
<review count="3">7.49</review>
</ratings>
<picture>224014.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11262</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9203</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>7791</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>9734</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4689</identifier>
<identifier>dcxbal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/k-on/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>K-On!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>けいおん!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1882</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>336379</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12601</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2010/k_on2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11696</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>15069</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>15489</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1262" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-11-07">
<name>naive</name>
<description>A naive (also spelled naïve, keeping its French diacritic) person lacks worldly knowledge, experience, wisdom, understanding, or judgement.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1279" parentid="2869" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-18">
<name>all-girls school</name>
<description>This school is only for female students. There may be a few male teachers though.</description>
<picurl>70853.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1446" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-15">
<name>energetic</name>
<description>An energetic character, often also called a genki character, shows great, often excessive levels of activity or vitality, and seems to always be doing everything extra fast. Genki characters are often slightly, or sometimes very, eccentric, and are filled with confidence and determination, regardless of whether they are competent or not; in fact, they often have little to no actual competence at whatever they generally do. Although genki characters are usually played exclusively for comedy effect, sometimes they may slow down for a serious or introspective moment. The most common genki character archetype is the genki schoolgirl, who will often be late to school and run with a toast in her mouth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1662" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-22">
<name>weaponized paper fan</name>
<description>Harisen (ハリセン meaning "slapping fan" in Japanese) is a giant paper fan, usually made in a closed fashion, It is used in Japanese comedy shows as a form of physical comedy (this is what is usually seen in anime when a character smacks another on the head with a paper fan).</description>
<picurl>47539.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1876" parentid="2794" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>musical band</name>
<description>A musical ensemble also known as a music(al) group or music(al) band is a group of people who perform instrumental or vocal music, typically known by a distinct name.</description>
<picurl>10249.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2396" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-08">
<name>swimsuit</name>
<description>A swimsuit is one of several kinds of garments designed to be worn by people engaging in water-based activities or sports or during certain activities under sunlight. Most kinds of swimsuit reveal a large portion of the body surface area, but exceptions exist. The more revealing kinds may also be worn as undergarment in sports that require wetsuits, or when there is a need to display the body, as in the case of beauty pageants or bodybuilding contests.
There is a very wide range of styles of modern swimsuits, which vary in relation to body coverage and materials. The choice of style of swimsuit is dependent on current fashions, community standards of modesty, and plain personal preference. Swimsuits for men usually expose the chest, while those for women do not usually do so; however, many women prefer to engage in water or sun activities with their torso uncovered, in a practice commonly described as toplessness or topfreedom. Since the early twentieth century a naturist movement has developed in western countries that seeks a return to non-sexual nakedness when swimming and during other appropriate activities; in some places around the world, nude beaches have been set aside for people who choose to engage in normal beach activities in the nude, and such beaches may or may not enforce nudity onto their goers.
In anime, it is common for at least one episode to feature the characters in swimsuits, usually as an excuse for gratuitous fanservice; when that happens, the episode is usually labeled a pool or beach episode, after the place the characters went to. Swimsuits, and in particular one-piece swimsuits, are a very common fetish in Japan; while the reason for that is uncertain, a common folk explanation is the fact that boys throughout their entire adolescence are commonly exposed to their female classmates wearing them, in what might be called an experiment in sexual discovery waiting to happen.</description>
<picurl>149786.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2520" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>school swimsuit</name>
<description>A school swimsuit (also known as sukumizu, shorthand for school mizugi) is a standardised navy blue one-piece swimsuit worn by schoolgirls. Typically they also have a name tag on the front. Sukumizu can also be black or white.
Normally worn at schools though sometimes also worn at beaches when the character feels this to be easier, forgot to buy a normal swimsuit of their own or wants to give some fan service to those that like school swimsuits better than regular swimsuits.
In http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] anime, a swimsuit of this type sometimes serves censoring purposes when characters take a bath. If there is a group of female characters donning swimsuits, you can expect the youngest or youngest-looking girl to wear one of these.</description>
<picurl>52174.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2662" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>school excursion</name>
<description>True for almost all anime with school setting, there will be a school excursion or field trip. Tokyo and Kyoto seem to be particularly popular as sightseeing destinations. So are hiking excursions into the local mountains. This also is a good excuse to present the prefecture`s / city`s food specialities.
Potential for ecchi moments: Obviously the "boys" will get all sorts of ideas with the "girls" sleeping so close by.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2670" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>school festival - TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>THIS TAG NEEDS TO BE SPLIT:
into http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=tag&amp;tagid=6119&amp;reltb=eptb [school culture festival]
and http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=tag&amp;tagid=2665&amp;reltb=eptb [school sports festival]
The obligatory school festival (or cultural fair) with cosplay cafe, haunted house, theatre performance, and food booths cannot be missing in any school setting.
For good measure there may also be an athletics or sports festival in this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2679" parentid="2672" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Kyoto</name>
<description>Kyoto Prefecture is a prefecture of Japan in the Kansai region of the island of Honshu. The capital is the city of Kyoto.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214383.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2805" parentid="2798" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>4-koma manga</name>
<description>Yonkoma manga (4コマ漫画, four cell manga, or 4-koma for short), a comic-strip format, generally consists of gag comic strips within four panels of equal size ordered from top to bottom. (They also sometimes run right-to-left horizontally or use a hybrid 2x2 style, depending on the layout requirements of the publication in which they appear.) Though the word yonkoma comes from the Japanese, the style also exists outside of Japan in other Asian countries as well as in the English-speaking market.</description>
<picurl>70558.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2830" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>furo scene</name>
<description>Furo (polite: Ofuro) is Japanese for bath, specifically a type of bath which originated as a short, steep-sided wooden bathtub. Baths of this type are found all over Japan in houses, apartments and traditional Japanese inns (Ryokans).
Furo are part of the Japanese ritual of bathing, not used for washing but for relaxing and warming oneself. Washing is carried out separately outside the furo, and only when completely clean does the bather enter the water. Generally Japanese bathrooms are small, so the bathroom is set up much like a walk-in shower area but containing the ofuro.
The cheapest and shortest way to show naked skin on TV, at least as much as allowed. It usually only takes up few minutes at most and as such it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales while still maintaining a "non-filler" episode.
Compare to the big brothers http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode] and http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160785.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2873" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>Valentine`s Day</name>
<description>Valentine`s Day is a festive day celebrated every February 14.
In Japan, South Korea, Taiwan, and China, Valentine`s Day is one month before http://anidb.net/t3147 [White Day], a celebration unique to those countries.
In the rest of the world:
On Valentine`s Day, both males and females will express their feelings of affection towards their loved ones, by exchanging gifts (such as cards, candies, and chocolates), going on dates, and other signs and actions of affection. Some people also take the opportunity to confess and propose for marriage. In Western countries, it is generally expected of the male to offer gifts to the significant other.
In many countries, friends and co-workers also exchange small gifts to show their friendship towards each other.
In Japan, South Korea, Taiwan, and China:
On Valentine`s Day, many women feel obliged to give chocolates to all male co-workers, except when the day falls on a Sunday, a holiday. This is known as giri choco (義理チョコ, "obligation chocolate"), with unpopular co-workers receiving only chougiri choco (超義理チョコ, "ultra-obligatory chocolate") cheap chocolate.
This contrasts with honmei choco (本命チョコ, "love chocolate"), chocolate given to a loved one.
Friends, especially girls, may exchange chocolate referred to as tomo choco (友チョコ, "friend chocolate").
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>160891.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3758" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-28">
<name>concert</name>
<description>The main characters play one or more live music performances during the show. This mostly happens for anime with the main focus on music.</description>
<picurl>169133.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4116" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-13">
<name>eternal blush</name>
<description>It is no ordinary blush it is a blush that does not disappear.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4323" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-04">
<name>spacing out</name>
<description>A comedy element: The character starts to daydream or fantasize about some topic. The typical complete lack of reality makes the spacing out funny. Especially when the protagonist mumbles to himself / herself and friends hear this. Promptly teasing the possibly lovestruck and very embarrassed protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4386" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-19">
<name>eating Pocky</name>
<description>Pocky (ポッキー) is a Japanese snack food produced by the Ezaki Glico Company of Japan. Pocky was first sold in 1966, and consists of a biscuit stick coated with chocolate. It was named after the Japanese onomatopoetic word for the sound Pocky makes when bitten, pokkin (ポッキン). The original was followed by "Almond Pocky" in 1971, with an almond coating, and "Strawberry Pocky" in 1977. Today, the product line includes such variations as milk, mousse, green tea, honey, banana and coconut flavored coatings, and themed products such as "Decorer Pocky," with colourful decorative stripes in the coating, and "Men`s Pocky," a dark (bittersweet) chocolate and "mature" version.
Source: Wikipedia
It`s marketed in Germany under the name Mikado (Note: NOT the game, the snack).</description>
<picurl>73630.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5084" parentid="2794" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>heavy metal music</name>
<description>Heavy metal (or simply metal) is a genre of rock music that developed in the late 1960s and early 1970s, largely in the United Kingdom and the United States. With roots in blues rock and psychedelic rock, the bands that created heavy metal developed a thick, massive sound, characterized by highly amplified distortion, extended guitar solos, emphatic beats, and overall loudness. Heavy metal lyrics and performance styles are often associated with masculinity, aggression, and machismo.
Heavy metal is traditionally characterized by loud distorted guitars, emphatic rhythms, dense bass-and-drum sound, and vigorous vocals. Metal subgenres variously emphasize, alter, or omit one or more of these attributes.
The anime features a theme revolving around metal music or generally features metal music.</description>
<picurl>10251.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5725" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-15">
<name>purikura</name>
<description>A standard on a date in a school setting, to remember the moment with the "loved one".
In Japan, purikura (プリクラ) refers to a photo sticker booth or the product of such a photo booth. The name is a shortened form of the registered trademark Purinto Kurabu (プリント倶楽部). The term derives from the English print club.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5843" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>sibling yin yang</name>
<description>In real life, siblings hardly ever act the same. Fiction sometimes takes this to an extreme.
Enter Sibling Yin Yang, the occurrence of siblings that are nearly polar opposites. If he`s cool and reckless, she`s responsible and thoughtful. If she`s a spiky-haired hooligan, he`s the nerdy wimpy one. If he`s an immature brat, she`s... well, you get the picture.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6046" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>pool episode</name>
<description>An episode playing at the pool, mostly in school, sometimes outside of it when the cast does not have a chance for a beach episode.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version of the http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode].
Other variants are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160904.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6137" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-09">
<name>catchphrase</name>
<description>A catchphrase is a sound, word or phrase commonly used by a person. That may be simply out of habit, or in an attempt to deliver some form of image, like that of cuteness. In fiction, characters often use catchphrases as a way to deliver specific personality traits. Examples include Otohime Mutsumi`s "ara ara" in Love Hina, Yang Wenli`s "yare yare" in Legend of the Galactic Heroes, Misuzu`s "gao" in AIR, Sakura`s "hoe" in Card Captor Sakura, Suiseiseki`s "desu" in Rozen Maiden, and Ayu`s "uguu" in Kanon (as well as several other characters in the same show).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7146" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-14">
<name>cute girls doing cute things</name>
<description>Cute girls doing cute things with each other (CGDCT): when girls are super friendly with each other and do all sorts of http://anidb.net/t798 [cute/moe] things with each other, but there is no yuri or shoujo ai subtext -- more specifically, there is no romantic subtext.

* CGDCT applies where the main focus is on moe/cute girls and their interactions with each other. Good examples include http://anidb.net/a9722 [Non Non Biyori] (600 weight / 3.0 stars) and http://anidb.net/a9579 [Kin`iro Mosaic] (600 weight / 3.0 stars).
* Generally, CGDCT is applicable only if the anime is also tagged predominantly female cast or all female cast.
* CGDCT does not apply if girls doing cute things is incidental to a larger motive/theme/meta. For example, in http://anidb.net/a8168 [Nichijou] the focus is comedy, using cute girls; the tag would not apply.

CGDCT is often mistaken as low level yuri or shoujo ai. If there is also actual romantic subtext, use the http://anidb.net/t2695 [yuri (18+)] and http://anidb.net/t2782 [shoujo ai] tags as well. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>223153.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="4424" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="618">7.69</rating>
<name>Hirasawa Yui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hirasawa Yui is the main character of K-On!. She is one of the members of the http://anidb.net/ch6218 [light music club] and plays a Heritage Cherry Sunburst Gibson Les Paul Standard electric guitar that she nicknames "Giita" (ギー太). She does not get good grades in school (though when properly coached, she can achieve astounding results) and is easily distracted by trivialities (mainly those deemed cute and adorable). Yui is clumsy and easily spaces out most of the time. She takes a huge liking for any kind of food (she practically never gains weight, which is greatly envied by Mugi, Mio, and Sawako). She has her younger sister Ui, who is the very mature and down-to-earth opposite of Yui, to take care of her and keep herself in line. Yui works extremely hard to get better at playing guitar, which is shown in later chapters. During performances, Yui plays with amazing energy and joy, which usually results in great response from the audience.
Yui is the band`s main vocalist and has perfect pitch — she can tune her guitar perfectly without a tuner, which greatly impresses Azusa, who has played the guitar much longer than Yui. She has a very easy-going nature, but has incredible concentration when hyped, though this is only limited to one subject at a time. She will totally neglect any other things in the process to the point of forgetting anything she has learned beforehand. Despite all of this, Yui is still devoted to her band and will always practice hard enough for the club. At school, she has become quite admired for her great voice. However, she is known to forget her lyrics in mid-performance as well as overdoing things, making her unable to perform sometimes. Mio was the lead vocalist at first, since Yui could not play the guitar and sing at the same time. Yui is also known to write childish lyrics as Ui has assisted her in creating them.
Her surname is taken from P-Model guitarist Susumu Hirasawa.</description>
<picture>20554.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4425" type="main character in" update="2010-05-28">
<rating votes="870">8.70</rating>
<name>Akiyama Mio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akiyama Mio is a shy girl who is in the light music club and plays a left-handed, 3-Color Sunburst Fender Jazz Bass with a tortoiseshell pickguard, though is shown playing a Fender Precision Bass in the first manga volume. She originally intended to join the literary club, but is forced into the http://anidb.net/ch6218 [light music club] by her childhood friend and the club`s president/drummer, http://anidb.net/ch4426 [Ritsu]. She gets excellent grades in school, but is bad with listening to stories involving macabre experiences, and cowers whenever something gross is brought up. While she can be mature and strict sometimes, she gets embarrassed easily, and is often subject to teasing from Ritsu and Sawako, their club adviser and eventual third-year homeroom teacher. She cites that she chose bass since it is not the center of attention in the band, unlike the guitarist. Mio is more technical when it comes to music, and Yui often comes to her when she is in need of more guitar tutorials.
She is the band`s backing vocalist and usually takes over lead vocals whenever Yui is incapable of singing or forgets the lyrics. She writes most of the songs, although they usually feature some odd and overly girlish lyrics like "Light and Fluffy Time". As she is left-handed, she becomes entranced whenever she sees left-handed instruments. Due to an unexpected accident in one of their live performances (and partly due to her attractive appearances), she acquired a huge amount of popularity, and even a fan club for her is formed (much to her dismay considering the circumstances surrounding it), whose founding member is the former student council president who also stalks Mio. Due to this, most of her classmates voted her to play as Romeo in their class play. Mio is seemingly a fan of Lomography, as she is often seen with a camera strongly resembling the Lomo LC-A during her summer training. Her surname is taken from former P-Model bassist and keyboardist Katsuhiko Akiyama.</description>
<picture>20555.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4426" type="main character in" update="2011-01-15">
<rating votes="393">6.89</rating>
<name>Tainaka Ritsu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ritsu is the president of the light music club. She has an ambiguous personality, and often has trouble with forgetting about important club activities and announcements. She says she chose to play the drums because they are "cool", but she has trouble playing instruments which involve intricate finger movements. Her surname is taken from former P-Model drummer Sadatoshi Tainaka.</description>
<picture>20556.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="162" picture="23208.jpg">Satou Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4427" type="main character in" update="2011-01-15">
<rating votes="416">6.71</rating>
<name>Kotobuki Tsumugi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsumugi is a girl with a gentle personality who plays the keyboard in the light music club. She has played piano since she was four years old, and has experience in winning piano contests. She is the daughter of a company president, and her family has several villas in various places around Japan. When Yui goes to buy her guitar, Tsumugi is successfully able to drive down the price in the shop her father owns. She often brings confectionery to the club room, along with a tea set which is kept in the room. She originally intended to join the chorus club, but joined the light music club after receiving an invitation and encouragement from Mio and Ritsu. Her surname is taken from former P-Model keyboardist Hikaru Kotobuki.</description>
<picture>20557.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1798" picture="20493.jpg">Kotobuki Minako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5521" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-15">
<rating votes="136">5.68</rating>
<name>Manabe Nodoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Manabe Nodoka is http://anidb.net/ch4424 [Yui]`s childhood friend and a member of the student council. Her surname is taken from Yoshiaki Manabe, lead guitarist for http://anidb.net/cr4828 [The Pillows].</description>
<picture>22313.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2416" picture="180631.jpg">Fujitou Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5522" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-15">
<rating votes="185">6.98</rating>
<name>Hirasawa Ui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hirasawa Ui is http://anidb.net/ch4424 [Yui]`s younger sister. However, unlike her older sister she is a more polite person, handles household chores easily and excels in studying, making her seem more like the older sister of the two. She likes her older sister however very much and tends to look after her. Like Yui, her surname is taken from Susumu Hirasawa.</description>
<picture>23504.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1961" picture="222838.jpg">Yonezawa Madoka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5523" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-02">
<rating votes="185">6.59</rating>
<name>Yamanaka Sawako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A popular and beautiful teacher at school, who is adored by most female students. She does not only teach music but is also the advisor for the wind instruments club.
Since she does not want people to know she wanted to be in a heavy metal band in the past, she becomes the advisor of the light music club, though it is unknown whether she stopped being the adviser for the wind instrument club as well. She enjoys cosplaying in the light music club. Her surname is taken from Sawao Yamanaka, the lead vocalist and rhythm guitarist for The Pillows.</description>
<picture>25012.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="359" picture="65537.jpg">Sanada Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6218" type="appears in" update="2009-04-18">
<rating votes="34">8.60</rating>
<name>Keionbu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The club where the main characters gather to do moe stuff and (try to) make music.</description>
<picture>23506.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6903" type="appears in" update="2009-05-16">
<rating votes="31">7.85</rating>
<name>Hirasawa Yui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>25009.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6904" type="appears in" update="2009-05-16">
<rating votes="11">5.33</rating>
<name>Hirasawa Ui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>25010.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7124" type="main character in" update="2011-01-19">
<rating votes="566">7.94</rating>
<name>Nakano Azusa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nakano Azusa is a new student who joins the http://anidb.net/ch6218 [light music club], a self-proclaimed novice guitarist who has been playing the guitar since the fourth grade and whose parents are working in a jazz band. She often finds herself bewildered by the tea parties and cosplaying aspects of the club, when she would rather just practice, although she also has a weakness for cakes. She could be described in part as a tsundere.
Furthermore she is referred to as "Azunyan" by Yui and the others since the day she wore a pair of fake catears (nekomimi).</description>
<picture>26457.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16455" type="appears in" update="2010-04-22">
<rating votes="22">6.36</rating>
<name>Kawakami-san</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46724.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="234" picture="244740.jpg">Nakamura Chie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16456" type="appears in" update="2011-01-15">
<rating votes="29">5.73</rating>
<name>Suzuki Jun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Suzuki Jun is http://anidb.net/ch7124 [Azusa]`s and http://anidb.net/ch5522 [Ui]`s classmate who often hangs out with the latter. Ui tries to get her to join the light music club but ultimately fails due to a strange visit to the club room. However, she starts to regret it when she hears about all the activities the club does. She has a pet cat.</description>
<picture>46278.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4010" picture="25938.jpg">Nagata Yoriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16685" type="appears in" update="2020-03-24">
<rating votes="16">6.48</rating>
<name>Sokabe Megumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sokabe Megumi was the president of the student council before http://anidb.net/ch5521 [Nodoka] succeeded her in her third year, and she is also the president of http://anidb.net/ch4425 [Mio]`s fan club, who is later succeeded by Nodoka. She stalks Mio during her last few days in high school because she wanted to see Mio one more time. The band offers her a song as a graduation gift. Although her position on the student council and in Mio`s fan club is only brought up in the manga version, she can be seen in episodes six and eleven of the anime.</description>
<picture>68708.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="5031" picture="28718.jpg">Kodama Asumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16777" type="appears in" update="2010-07-22">
<rating votes="8">5.07</rating>
<name>Ton-chan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46421.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="16947" type="appears in" update="2010-04-22">
<rating votes="12">4.98</rating>
<name>Manabe Nodoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46721.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2416" picture="180631.jpg">Fujitou Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16949" type="appears in" update="2010-04-22">
<rating votes="17">4.75</rating>
<name>Tainaka Satoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46722.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="69" picture="171155.jpg">Itou Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18149" type="appears in" update="2010-05-28">
<rating votes="4">5.10</rating>
<name>Akiyama Mio Fanclub</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Due to an unexpected accident in one of the light music club`s live performances (and partly due to her attractive appearances), Mio acquired a huge amount of popularity, and even a fan club for her is formed (much to her dismay considering the circumstances surrounding it), whose founding member is the former student council president, http://anidb.net/ch16685 [Sokabe Megumi], who also stalks Mio. Yui`s childhood friend and Mio`s classmember and friend http://anidb.net/ch5521 [Manabe Nodoka] later becomes its president after Megumi graduates from school.</description>
<picture>48684.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="18946" type="appears in" update="2010-06-18">
<rating votes="11">5.17</rating>
<name>Seitokai-kaikei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49932.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2505" picture="141583.jpg">Makiguchi Mayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18947" type="appears in" update="2010-06-18">
<rating votes="15">6.11</rating>
<name>Kawaguchi Norimi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kawaguchi Norimi is Sawako`s friend and band mate, named `Death Devil`.</description>
<picture>49934.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="82" picture="216596.jpg">Asakawa Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19980" type="appears in" update="2010-07-24">
<rating votes="4">3.24</rating>
<name>Ichimonji Tomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51854.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12580" picture="222815.jpg">Chijimatsu Sachiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20960" type="appears in" update="2010-08-20">
<rating votes="7">3.16</rating>
<name>Horikomi-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53654.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17988" picture="170364.jpg">Kanaya Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47497" type="appears in" update="2012-08-02">
<rating votes="2">7.83</rating>
<name>Death Devil</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Heavy metal band of former Light music club</description>
<picture>91849.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="113370" update="2019-06-02">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="20">6.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">整頓!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Clean-up!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Aufräumen!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seiton!</title>
<summary>The Light Music Club decides to clean up the disorganized Music Preparation Room. The room has become a storage space for miscellaneous items, mostly stuff that Yui collected from who knows where, as well as other personal belongings.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="113371" update="2019-06-02">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="24">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">高3!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seniors!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">3. Klasse!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Третий класс!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kou 3!</title>
<summary>Yui Hirasawa, Mio Akiyama, Ritsu Tainaka, and Tsumugi Kotobuki from the Light Music Club enter their third and final year of high school. It`s recruiting season again, and the members set off to find new members along with second-year Azusa Nakano, who joined after the previous year`s new student welcome ceremony.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="113372" update="2010-01-30">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">2.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode T1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117518" update="2019-06-02">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-30</airdate>
<rating votes="13">6.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">残暑見舞い!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Late Summer Postcard!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Spätsommergrüsse!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zanshomimai!</title>
<summary>Yui and the other senior Light Music Club members study in the library in preparation for university entrance exams. Being the only second-year, Azusa is at home with a lot of time on her hands. Just as Azusa is thinking she wants to make the most of summer break, Ui comes to visit.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="117519" update="2019-06-02">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-23</airdate>
<rating votes="14">6.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏フェス!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summerfest!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Open Air!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu Fesu!</title>
<summary>Sakuragaoka High School has entered summer break. This will be the last summer break for the seniors, and Yui suggests that they have a training camp.
Although hesitant at first, Mio decides to organize a camp when talk of a summer music festival pops up.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="117520" update="2019-06-02">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-16</airdate>
<rating votes="14">4.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暑い!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hot!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">So heiss!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atsui!</title>
<summary>The Light Music Club practices on a hot summer day, but the sweltering heat is affecting their concentration. The members try all sorts of things to cool down, but finally turn to their advisor Sawako for suggestions.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="117521" update="2019-06-02">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-09</airdate>
<rating votes="16">8.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">先生!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Teacher!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Lehrerin!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sensei!</title>
<summary>On her way to school one morning, Tsumugi happens to see Sawako having a nervous conversation with someone in a car. What`s more, Sawako receives a suspicious phone call after school in the music room, and the Light Music Club members decide to investigate.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="117522" update="2019-06-02">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-02</airdate>
<rating votes="14">5.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">期末試験!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Finals!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Semesterabschlussprüfungen!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimatsushiken!</title>
<summary>Finals are coming up, and the Light Music Club seniors aren`t in their usual music room, spending their time after school studying in the library instead.
Unlike Mio and Tsumugi who buckle down to study, Yui and Ritsu have trouble concentrating as usual.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="117523" update="2019-06-02">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="13">5.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">進路!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Career!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Laufbahn!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinro!</title>
<summary>Nodoka is surprised that Yui still hasn`t figured out her plans for after high school.
Ritsu also writes "undecided" on her life plans questionnaire and Sawako summons the two girls to the staff room.
Worried about the two of them, Nodoka and Mio share some childhood memories with Tsumugi.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="117524" update="2019-06-02">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-19</airdate>
<rating votes="20">4.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お茶会!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tea Party!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Teegesellschaft!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ochakai!</title>
<summary>As they walk down the hall, Yui notices that Mio is acting strange. When asked, Mio replies that she thinks someone has been watching her all morning.
With the exception of a concerned Azusa, the Light Music Club members all poke fun at Mio for being a scaredy-cat.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="117525" update="2019-06-02">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-12</airdate>
<rating votes="15">6.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">梅雨!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rainy Season!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Regenzeit!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuyu!</title>
<summary>It`s the rainy season, and it`s been raining all morning. Yui tries to get to school without getting Geeta wet, but has a tough time on the way. Yui arrives at the classroom soaked, and is the center of everyone`s attention.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="117526" update="2019-06-02">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-05</airdate>
<rating votes="17">7.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お留守番!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Staying Behind!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Zu Hause geblieben!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Orusuban!</title>
<summary>Yui sends Ui and Azusa photos of all the fun she`s having on her field trip.
With the seniors gone, Azusa and Jun try to cheer up Ui, who misses her beloved sister, and school feels a little different.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="117527" update="2019-06-02">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="19">6.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">修学旅行!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Field Trip!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Klassenfahrt!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuugakuryokou!</title>
<summary>The Sakuragaoka High School seniors set off for a field trip to Kyoto. Since the students must go around in groups of at least four, the Light Music Club members form their own group, but Yui and Ritsu are already so hyped up on riding the bullet train there that Mio is filled with trepidation.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="117528" update="2019-06-02">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-21</airdate>
<rating votes="20">4.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドラマー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Drummer!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Schlagzeugerin!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Drummer!</title>
<summary>The Light Music Club is captivated by Ton-chan, their newest member (?).
It`s another normal day for the club when Ritsu suddenly kicks up a fuss after viewing something on a laptop. Having seen photos from the club activity records, Ritsu realizes that she doesn`t stand out enough.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="117733" update="2013-07-05">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117734" update="2013-07-05">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118665" update="2010-06-10">
<epno type="5">P1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Funsub of Episode 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119334" update="2019-06-02">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-14</airdate>
<rating votes="16">5.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マラソン大会!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Marathon Tournament!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Marathonlauf!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Marathon Taikai!</title>
<summary>Summer break is over, the second term has begun, and with the school festival just around the corner Azusa can`t contain her excitement. However, Yui is feeling down about the upcoming school-wide marathon. The girls each do what they can to prepare for the run.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119335" update="2019-06-02">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="15">6.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏期講習!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summer Training!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Sommerkurs!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsuki Koushuu!</title>
<summary>After the ever-studious Mio refuses to hang out with her, Ritsu is alone near the station when she spots Tsumugi, who is out planning to buy some summer prep course materials. Ritsu then asks Tsumugi to hang out with her.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119336" update="2019-06-02">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="16">6.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">先輩!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Upperclassmen!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Senpai!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senpai!</title>
<summary>Azusa`s classmate Jun asks about the Light Music Club`s daily activities, and Azusa suddenly realizes that she`s grown accustomed to the seniors` lax attitude. She tries to motivate herself, hoping to restore the discipline she had when she first joined the club.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119337" update="2019-06-02">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-28</airdate>
<rating votes="15">7.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">部室がない!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">No Club Room!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kein Klubraum!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bushitsu ga Nai!</title>
<summary>Because of a water leak from the ceiling in the room directly below, the Light Music Club`s club room is out of commission. With less than a month until the school festival, the members go hunting for another practice venue.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119338" update="2019-06-02">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-04</airdate>
<rating votes="15">5.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">主役!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Leading Role!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Hauptrolle!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuyaku!</title>
<summary>All the Light Music Club seniors are going to be in a production of "Romeo and Juliet" as part of the Class 3-2 presentation for the school festival. The class votes to have Mio play Romeo and Ritsu play Juliet. Practice begins that very day after school, but things
don`t seem to be working out.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119339" update="2019-06-02">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-11</airdate>
<rating votes="14">6.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロミジュリ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Romeo &amp; Juliet!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Romeo und Julia!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">RomeJuli!</title>
<summary>It`s the first day of the school festival and there is a flurry of activity at Sakuragaoka High School. Class 3-2 is working hard to prepare for their class play, "Romeo and Juliet." Finally, the show opens to a big crowd.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119340" update="2019-06-02">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-18</airdate>
<rating votes="22">9.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">またまた学園祭!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yet Another School Festival!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Und wieder ein Schulfest!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Matamata Gakuensai!</title>
<summary>It`s the second day of the school festival, and the students start preparing early in the morning. Yui and the others are pumped up trom a practice session the night before. At long last, After-school Teatime starts their school festival performance on the auditorium stage.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119341" update="2019-06-02">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-25</airdate>
<rating votes="15">5.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">卒業アルバム!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Graduation Yearbook!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Abschlussalbum!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sotsugyou Album!</title>
<summary>It`s almost graduation photo time and Yui tries all kinds of hairstyles, unable to decide on a look. The following day during Light Music Club activities, the members try taking practice individual shots.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119342" update="2019-06-02">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-01</airdate>
<rating votes="14">6.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">受験!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Entrance Exam!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Aufnahmeprüfung!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Juken!</title>
<summary>Yui and the other seniors are facing entrance exams soon, and spend their days studying in the clubroom. Being the only second-year, Azusa hatches a secret plan to give them all chocolates for Valentine`s Day, something she`s never done before.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119343" update="2019-06-02">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-08</airdate>
<rating votes="14">6.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">放課後!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">After School!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Nach der Schule!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Houkago!</title>
<summary>Yui and the other seniors have no more classes, and decide to all come in the morning to hang out in the clubroom. Everything is laid back as usual when they start talking about unfinished business they might have before graduation.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119344" update="2019-06-02">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-15</airdate>
<rating votes="17">9.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">卒業式!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Graduation Ceremony!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Abschlussfeier!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sotsugyoushiki!</title>
<summary>At long last, it`s graduation day for the four seniors in the Light Music Club. They all decide to meet up and go to school together for their big day, but when the time comes Yui is nowhere to be seen. Ritsu texts Yui`s phone, and gets a hasty response...</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119345" update="2019-06-02">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-22</airdate>
<rating votes="14">6.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">企画会議!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Planning Discussion!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikaku Kaigi!</title>
<summary>Azusa randomly stumbles upon last year`s new student recruitment video, made by Yui and the other seniors. Mio had been so embarrassed by the video that she had hidden it away in a cookie tin. Azusa is then inspired to make a recruitment video of her own.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119894" update="2010-07-14">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119895" update="2010-07-14">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121297" update="2011-05-18">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-09-15</airdate>
<rating votes="5">1.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">きょうだいほしい みおとムギ / ゆい / あずさわこ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Want Siblings: Mio &amp; Mugi / Yui / AzuSawako</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoudai Hoshii: Mio to Mugi / Yui / AzuSawako</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121298" update="2011-05-18">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-08-18</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おみやげ話 定番 / それぞれの. / お題です</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Souvenir Stories: Popular Items / To Each Her Own. / A Request</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omiyage Hanashi: Teiban / Sorezore no. / Onegai Desu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121299" update="2011-05-18">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2010-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">みんなで占い 夢占い / 占いのけっかは? / ゆいの前世</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fortune Telling for Everyone: Dream Reading / Outcome of the Reading? / Yui`s Former Life</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Minna de Uranai: Yumeuranai / Uranai no Kekka wa? / Yui no Zense</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121300" update="2011-05-18">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="5">1.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">子どものコロのゆめ ゆいのゆめ / のどかりつみおつむぎ / さわこのゆめ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Childhood Memories: Yui`s Dream / Nodoka, Ritsu, Mio, Tsumugi / Sawako`s Dream</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kodomo no Koro no Yume: Yui no Yume / Nodoka Ritsu Mio Tsumugi / Sawako no Yume</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121450" update="2019-06-02">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-29</airdate>
<rating votes="13">8.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">訪問!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Visiting!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Houmon!</title>
<summary>The seniors are done with classes, but still come to school to hang out in the club room over tea.
Yui is strangely restless, stating that something "very important" is going to be delivered. Then, Nodoka visits the club room.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="125473" update="2011-05-18">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2010-11-17</airdate>
<rating votes="4">1.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">MCグランプリ 提案 / というわけで. / すて身で / ヒーローはおくれて.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">MC Grand Prix: Idea / After That. / All Out / The Hero That Arrives Late.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">MC Grand Prix: Teian / To Iu Wake de. / Sute Mi de / Hero wa Okurete.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125482" update="2011-05-19">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2011-01-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">桜が丘かげき団 けいおんぶらしく...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakuragaoka Musical Company: In the Style of the Light Music Club...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakuragaoka Gekidan Keionbu-rashiku...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125483" update="2011-05-18">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">うらおん! 3分クッキング なかの先生 / たいなか先生 / 山中先生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Uraon! 3-Minute Meals: Nakano-sensei / Tainaka-sensei / Yamanaka-sensei</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uraon! 3-bun Cooking: Nakano-sensei / Tainaka-sensei / Yamanaka-sensei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128487" update="2011-05-19">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2011-02-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">むかしばなし あずとゆいギリス / ゆいスズメ / あずたろう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fairy Tale: Azu and Yuihopper / Yuisparrow / Azutarou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mukashibanashi: Azu to Yuigirisu / Yui Suzume / Azutarou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128891" update="2019-06-02">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-03-16</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">計画!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Plan!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Keikaku!</title>
<summary>Yui receives a gift Tsumugi got for her during an overseas trip and wishes she could go somewhere, too. This gets the girls talking, and the Light Music Club decides to go on a graduation trip once entrance exams are over. The five of them including Azusa discuss where they might want to go.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="129100" update="2013-05-10">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2011-03-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おたすけ! ゆいちゃんマン シール / あんこ / ちちんぷい / おまけ けいおんぶラップ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the Rescue! Yui-chanman: Sticker / Sweet Bean Paste / Pain No More / Extra: Light Music Club Rap</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otasuke! Yui-chanman: Seal / Anko / Chichinpui / Omake: Keionbu Rap</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
