<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="732" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2003-05-08</startdate>
<enddate>2003-07-31</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Submarine Super 99</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">SS99</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">サブマリン スーパー99</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Submarine Super 99</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Submarine 99</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Súper Submarino 99</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="725" type="Other">Uchuu Kaizoku Captain Harlock</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8913" approval="2" total="2">Ozuma</anime>
<anime id="5037" approval="1" total="2">Marine Snow no Densetsu</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://www.leiji-matsumoto.ne.jp/ss99/</url>
<creators>
<name id="773" type="Unknown Relation">Vega Entertainment</name>
<name id="7443" type="Character Design">Shimazu Ikuo</name>
<name id="4537" type="Series Composition">Fujikawa Keisuke</name>
<name id="6781" type="Direction">Matano Hiromichi</name>
<name id="1107" type="Original Work">Matsumoto Reiji</name>
<name id="773" type="Animation Work">Vega Entertainment</name>
<name id="7443" type="Chief Animation Direction">Shimazu Ikuo</name>
<name id="1107" type="Chief Designer">Matsumoto Reiji</name>
</creators>
<description>In the year 20XX AD, mysterious shipwrecks have been continuing to occur near Japan. Oki Juzo and Itsuro disappears to investigate these incidents. Just before they left, they came by a key engraved with the letters "SS-99" in the underground lab where Juzou`s grandchild and Itsuro`s younger brother, a senior high student Oki Shinji, had been improving various "99 Shikipo Heichu" rifles.
As the two progresses in their investigation, the two get caught when they sneak into a laboratory and are lead to a workshop underground. There, one never seen before huge submarine rests.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="45">5.36</permanent>
<temporary count="47">6.61</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>378.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6039</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1713</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1213</identifier>
<identifier>hbyqqb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.leiji-matsumoto.ne.jp/ss99/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>潜水艦スーパー99#アニメ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>65</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>241168</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6065</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="635" parentid="36" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-30">
<name>navy</name>
</tag>
<tag id="898" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-04-17">
<name>submarine</name>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="14565" update="2007-02-23">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">深海調査艇, 消滅!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Deep Sea Explorer Disappeared!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le bathyscaphe a disparu !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinkai Chousaitei, Shoumetsu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27613" update="2007-02-23">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">超潜水艦, スクランブル!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scramble, the Super Submarine!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le super sous-marin appareille !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chou Sensuikan, Scramble!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27614" update="2007-02-23">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">深度一万二千の死闘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle at 39600 Feet Deep!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Duel à 12000 mètres !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shindo Ichiman Nisen no Shitou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27615" update="2007-02-23">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらば, 名将!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell, the Great General!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Adieu, illustre amiral !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saraba, Meishou!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27616" update="2007-02-23">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">美しい海へ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Embark to A New Ocean!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Vers un nouvel océan !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Utsukushii Umi e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27617" update="2007-02-23">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">若き戦士の挑戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Challenge of A Young Warrior</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le défi du jeune guerrier !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakaki Senshi no Chousen!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27618" update="2007-02-23">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">海洋帝国爆破!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blast the Ocean Empire!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Destruction de l`Empire !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaiyou Teikoku Bakuha!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27619" update="2007-02-23">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ホールドアップ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hold-Up</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les mains en l`air !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hold Up!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27620" update="2007-02-23">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">我, 奇襲に成功せり!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ambush Achieved Great Success!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un raid réussi !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Waga, Kishuu ni Seikou Seri!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27621" update="2007-02-23">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">罠!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Booby Trap!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le traquenard !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wana!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67603" update="2011-06-30">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">名将の決断!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Decision of A Great General</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La décision d`un illustre amiral !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meishou no Ketsudan!</title>
<summary>Submarine Super 99 heads for the Ocean Empire. Captain Oyama uses Dr. Oki ` s visual sonar to prepare for battle. Hell sends out a new fleet to attack 99 and tells General Zelbert to get rid of Dr. Oki and Goro. However, Zelbert realizes that he no longer wishes to help Hell.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="67605" update="2007-02-23">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">皇帝即位宣言!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Coronation of Emperor Is Declared!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le couronnement de l`Empereur !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koutei Sokui Sengen!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67606" update="2007-02-23">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Decisive Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le combat final !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102623" update="2009-05-18">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102624" update="2009-05-18">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
