<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7323" restricted="false">
<type>Other</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-07-30</startdate>
<enddate>2008-07-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Inuyasha: Kuroi Tessaiga</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Inuyasha: Black Tetsusaiga</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">InuYasha - Black Tessaiga</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">It`s a Rumic World: InuYasha</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Inuyasha: Kuroi Tetsusaiga</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">犬夜叉 黒い鉄砕牙</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">犬夜叉 黑色鐵碎牙</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">犬夜叉 黑色铁碎牙</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="144" type="Parent Story">Inuyasha</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="3412" type="Character Design">Hishinuma Yoshihito</name>
<name id="2703" type="Music">Wada Kaoru</name>
<name id="726" type="Work">Sunrise</name>
<name id="5680" type="Direction">Aoki Yasunao</name>
<name id="3412" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hishinuma Yoshihito</name>
<name id="818" type="Original Work">Takahashi Rumiko</name>
</creators>
<description>This special was originally exclusively screened during the "It`s a Rumic World" art exhibit held in Tokyo`s Ginza district from July 30 - August 11, 2008 together with two other specials for http://anidb.net/a7322 [Urusei Yatsura] and http://anidb.net/a6141 [Ranma 1/2].
On January 29, 2010 a limited edition "It`s a Rumic World Special Anime Box" DVD collection was released which contains all three specials.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="251">5.92</permanent>
<temporary count="251">6.89</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>57878.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15225</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4886</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2640" parentid="2625" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-06-02">
<name>alternative past</name>
<description>An anime that takes place in an alternative past is an anime that clearly does not belong to the future or the present, and isn`t tied particularly closely to our history, or has ties to our history but only as a premise: there are too many things that don`t make sense for the time-period. In some cases there is futuristic technology present, but the overall setting still feels that of the past. However the setting must still take place on Earth, since we can not know if the history of a fantasy world is an alternate one or not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3955" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>DESCRIPTION MISSING</name>
<description>The description for this entry is missing. e.g plot, biography...
Please help by adding it, and remove this tag afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7245" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="411">7.31</rating>
<name>Inuyasha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>InuYasha is a hanyou (half-demon), the product of an inu-youkai (犬妖怪, dog demon) and a human. He wields Tetsusaiga, a supernatural sword made from one of his deceased father`s fangs. When properly wielded, the sword can destroy one hundred demons with a single swing. InuYasha can quickly recover from injuries that would be fatal to a human, largely due to his demonic blood. During the first night of each lunar month (new moon), InuYasha changes into a normal human with black hair and black eyes and loses his demonic powers.
InuYasha was bound to Goshinboku by Kikyo`s arrow for fifty years until Kagome freed him. InuYasha wears a special bead necklace that forces him to respond to Kagome`s command "Osuwari!", which translates to "Sit!" in English. In the English-dubbed version, "InuYasha, sit!" or "Sit, boy!" are sometimes used instead. Following the command, InuYasha is thrown to the ground. Kaede had placed the necklace upon InuYasha because he had threatened to kill Kagome if she refused to give the Jewel of Four Souls to him. As the series goes on, he begins to like Kagome more and more, shown when he will leave a battle to save her from being hurt.</description>
<picture>36855.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7246" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="314">5.44</rating>
<name>Higurashi Kagome</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Higurashi Kagome is one of the main protagonists of the series. Born in modern Japan as the reincarnation of the priestess Kikyo, Kagome has the Shikon Jewel unknowingly hidden inside her body until 1997, when a demon pulls her into the Bone Eater`s Well and 500 years back through time. They emerge in the Feudal Era about 50 years after Kikyo`s death, where the demon extracts the jewel from Kagome. When another demon seizes the jewel, Kagome shoots it with a bow and arrow.
While trying to protect the jewel using a bow and arrow, she accidentally shatters it into numerous shards that disperse throughout the country. She agrees to help find them, as she can sense the presence of nearby shards. As the series progresses, she falls in love with InuYasha, and finds herself competing with the revived Kikyo for his affections. During the search for the jewel, Kagome`s own spiritual powers and archery skills continue to improve.
At the end of the series, Kagome returns to her own time for three years. She is then able to return to the Feudal era where she and InuYasha acknowledge their love for one another and she chooses to remain there with him.</description>
<picture>36854.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="271" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7247" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-06-28">
<rating votes="295">8.00</rating>
<name>Saotome Ranma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ranma, the only son of Genma and Nodoka Saotome, was taken from his home by his father when approximately 2 years old, to begin a 13-14-year training trip to perfect his skills in the martial arts.
Later, near the end of the trip, Genma took Ranma to a training ground in China named Jusenkyo that few people used, due to the springs being cursed. Falling into them would transform a person into whatever first fell in. Not knowing this, and not having the patience to listen to a warning from the local guide, Genma attempted to train with Ranma atop the bamboo poles which jutted up out of the pools. When Ranma knocked Genma into Shonmaoniichuan/"Spring of `Drowned` Panda", he was surprised to watch a panda emerge from the pond and leap onto one of the poles. Genma, now cursed, was able to hit a surprised Ranma into Nyannichuan, or the "Spring of `Drowned` Girl". Thus he turns into a female version of his original form when splashed with cold water, which is only temporarily reversible through contact with hot water.</description>
<picture>30262.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7449" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-05-27">
<rating votes="404">8.31</rating>
<name>Saotome Ranma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He turns into a female version of his original form when splashed with cold water, which is only (temporarily) reversible through contact with hot water.</description>
<picture>26086.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="9099" type="cameo appearance in" update="2019-01-14">
<rating votes="550">8.23</rating>
<name>Lum</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lum (also referred to in some Western versions as Lamu - since her name in Japanese is technically pronounced "Ramu") is the second main protagonist of the series. She is a beautiful Oni alien who is capable of flying and generating electrical shocks and even lightning. She is extremely popular and is famous for ending her sentences with ~daccha (loosely translated as "yes?" or "you know?"). Except when in her school girl`s uniform, she usually wears a sexy outfit consisting of a tiger-striped bikini and knee-high go-go boots. While generally good-natured, sweet, faithful, and innocent, Lum also has a very hot temper and she is extremely jealous. Her dream in life is to live in a "Sweet Home with Darling" in which she keeps house and raises babies while Ataru, her "Darling," works a job. Unfortunately, Lum`s idea of "cooking" is to take very spicy ingredients like jalapenos, cayenne peppers and Tabasco sauce and irradiate them with an alien energy bazooka until they carbonize into inedible, crystallized nuggets. As an alien she has access to many bizarre gadgets whose use she really doesn`t understand all that well, leading to comic results. Differences between human and "Invader" physiology also drive many stories, like the time Lum`s horns begin to grow larger after she is bitten by a cow, or the time she becomes drunk by eating pickled plums.
(Source: Wikipedia.com)</description>
<picture>28639.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="9101" type="cameo appearance in" update="2019-01-14">
<rating votes="209">8.40</rating>
<name>Moroboshi Ataru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A student at Tomobiki High School, Class 2-4, Ataru suffers from an incredible amount of bad luck, having been born on the unluckiest day of the Bhuddist calendar. He is very lecherous, stupid, and lazy. Though he often tries to escape from Lum and flirts with other women, he really does have feelings for her. Ataru`s main goal in life is to live in the center of a harem composed of exotic and beautiful women (including Lum and most of her alien friends). His pick-up techniques would creep out most stalkers. Usually, he just walks up to a woman he`s never met before and asks for her name, phone number, and address. Once he decides to go after a particular female, virtually no force on Earth (or from outer space) can stop him. He refused to admit it but, deep down, he proved in the later episodes that it was Lum that he truly loved.
(source:Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>28589.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="10477" type="main character in" update="2010-02-09">
<rating votes="591">8.49</rating>
<name>Sesshoumaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sesshoumaru is InuYasha`s older half-brother. Like their father, he is the Lord of the Western Lands, although Sesshoumaru maintains no permanent home. As a full-blooded Inu-yokai, he is a very powerful demon and nearly unequalled in raw power, but is unable to defeat Naraku in volume twenty-three of the manga. He has no interest in possessing even one shard of the Shikon Jewel to enhance his powers, since he is already supremely confident of his own strength.</description>
<picture>36856.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="387" picture="17233.jpg">Narita Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11091" type="appears in" update="2017-07-10">
<rating votes="60">5.80</rating>
<name>Naraku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Naraku is the series` primary antagonist. Naraku is responsible for most of the characters` misfortunes, including the death of http://anidb.net/ch10909 [Kikyou], the sealing of http://anidb.net/ch7245 [Inuyasha] to the sacred tree, http://anidb.net/ch12161 [Miroku]`s curse, and the death of http://anidb.net/ch12162 [Sango]`s family. Naraku was born from the fusion of http://anidb.net/ch72625 [Onigumo], a crippled human bandit tended by Kikyou, and a horde of weak demons. Driven by frustrated lust for Kikyou, Onigumo made a bargain with the demons: His soul would allow the demons to combine into one entity and he would become part of that new body. However the resulting half-demon promptly caused Kikyou`s death in an attempt to corrupt and possess the Shikon Jewel.
Naraku is driven by three goals: To become a full demon, to possess a fully-corrupted Shikon Jewel, and to possess Kikyou. The third goal was a result of the fact that Onigumo`s heart remained a vital part of Naraku`s body, causing an obsession with Kikyou that prevents him from killing her. He attempts to rid himself of Onigumo`s heart multiple times, eventually succeeding in separating it into The Infant. With his heart freed from his obsession, he is able to later kill Kikyou. At the end of the manga, however, he expressed regret at not being able to have her for his own.
Throughout the series, Naraku creates many subordinate beings from his own body to aid his goal of killing his opponents and reuniting the shards of the Shikon Jewel, whose corrupted form he hopes to use to gain ultimate power.</description>
<picture>36852.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12156" type="appears in" update="2012-02-27">
<rating votes="23">7.44</rating>
<name>Toutousai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A youkai (probably) swordsmith. He forged both Inuyasha`s Tessaiga and Sesshoumaru`s Tenseiga. Toutousai generally appears with his flying, three-eyed cow.</description>
<picture>36861.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12160" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-07">
<rating votes="90">3.82</rating>
<name>Shippou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shippou is an orphaned young fox demon who attempts to steal the Shikon Jewel from Kagome and InuYasha, wanting to become stronger and avenge his father`s death. Though his plan fails, Kagome and InuYasha aid him after hearing his story, and he becomes their companion for the rest of the series.
Shippou normally appears to be a young boy with certain fox-like features: his legs, feet, ears, and tail. He can shape-shift, but his other forms (such as a large pink flying balloon) are temporary and often ineffective, usually given away by his lingering fox tail. He can also create illusory duplicates of himself, as well as weak fox-fire magic and toy-based tricks such as his giant spinning top attack. Naively observant, he often directs cheeky comments to InuYasha, earning a smack on the head. InuYasha and Kagome serve as older sibling figures to Shippou. Because of his small size, Shippou often rides on Kirara or the shoulders of others. His actual age is never stated in the series; according to the official InuYasha guide by Takahashi Rumiko, his appearance is equivalent to that of a seven year old boy.</description>
<picture>36876.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12161" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-07">
<rating votes="135">6.04</rating>
<name>Miroku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miroku is a Buddhist monk who travels the countryside performing services such as exorcisms and demon exterminations, although sometimes he deliberately falsifies these to earn comfortable rewards. Miroku can attack enemies with his holy staff and sutra scrolls, but his greatest weapon, the Wind Tunnel embedded in the palm of his hand, is also a hereditary curse originally inflicted by Naraku upon Miroku`s grandfather Miyatsu. The Wind Tunnel sucks in almost anything in its path and is a powerful weapon against demons; however, it grows larger with increasing use, so that Miroku`s grandfather and father were eventually consumed by their own Wind Tunnels. Miroku hopes to break the curse by killing Naraku.
Miroku first meets InuYasha by stealing the Shikon Jewel, causing them to fight one another until Kagome leaps between them. After Miroku explains his situation, InuYasha allows him to join their group as a valuable ally. Miroku`s lechery is a recurrent habit, usually manifesting as shameless flattery, semi-surreptitious groping, and asking random women to bear him a child; he learned these bad habits from the monk Mushin who raised him, but he also has the more serious motive of wanting an heir to follow him if he dies without defeating Naraku.</description>
<picture>36866.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12162" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-01-11">
<rating votes="186">7.10</rating>
<name>Sango</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sango is a demon slayer who hails from a village of professional demon slayers. Naraku wipes out her entire family and village, then causes Sango to blame InuYasha and try to kill him. When the plot fails, Naraku revives Sango`s little brother Kohaku, controlling him as a pawn to manipulate Sango`s emotions and attack the rest of InuYasha`s group. Sango seeks vengeance against Naraku, but her primary goal is to rescue Kohaku from Naraku`s influence and save his life.
Of her broad repertoire of tools and tricks for fighting demons, her most powerful weapon is the Hiraikotsu, a massive boomerang made of purified demon bones. She is accompanied by the demon cat Kirara. Sango is often the victim of Miroku`s lecherous tendencies and slaps him for it.
She has three kids with Miroku by the end of the series, twin girls and a boy.</description>
<picture>36867.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12163" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-11">
<rating votes="92">3.99</rating>
<name>Jaken</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jaken is a small green imp-like youkai who is extremely loyal to Sesshomaru, often praising his master`s greatness although Sesshomaru usually ignores him. Jaken himself is not especially powerful, despite bearing a weapon known as the Staff of Two Heads. He seldom engages in battle and is actually killed by Kaijinbo with Toukijin, but Sesshomaru resurrects him with Tenseiga.</description>
<picture>46124.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12164" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-11-11">
<rating votes="97">7.25</rating>
<name>Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rin is an orphan girl who finds http://anidb.net/ch10477 [Sesshomaru] in the woods after he is badly injured by InuYasha. Although Sesshomaru snubs her, she visits him regularly and attempts to take care of him, even stealing fish from the village for him until she learns that he doesn`t eat human food. The villagers beat her for the theft, but when Sesshomaru idly inquires about her injuries, she seems strangely happy about his interest in her welfare. During this time, she never speaks, only communicating with hand gestures and smiles.
Later, the wolf-demon http://anidb.net/ch12169 [Kouga] chases a thief to her village, then lets his wolves kill and eat the villagers. Rin flees through the forest towards Sesshomaru, but the wolves catch up to her. Recovered from his wounds, Sesshomaru is leaving when he catches Rin`s scent and follows it to her mauled corpse. Remembering her smile, he retests Tenseiga by using it to resurrect her. After setting Rin on her feet again, Sesshomaru walks away, leaving the dumbfounded http://anidb.net/ch12163 [Jaken] and a wide-eyed Rin standing on the path. After a moment, they both follow. The next time Rin appears, she is clean, wearing a new, colourful kimono, and talking and acting more like a typical child. Throughout the series, she continues to follow "Lord Sesshomaru", as she calls him; when he is away on dangerous tasks, she waits for him with Jaken and a two-headed dragon which she names "Ah-Un".
Though Sesshomaru never states any feelings for her, he displays a strong protective instinct and Rin is obviously devoted to him.</description>
<picture>36875.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12166" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-07">
<rating votes="23">4.06</rating>
<name>Kohaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kohaku is Sango`s younger brother. Disguised as the young nobleman Kagewaki Hitomi, Naraku summons Sango`s family and companions to slay a false demon, then controls Kohaku with a Shikon shard and makes him kill all of the other demon slayers (Sango survives solely by sheer luck). Castle guards also kill Kohaku that night.
Naraku resurrects him as an amnesiac puppet, but after several encounters with Sango and her friends, Kohaku begins to recover his painful memories. Kagura helps him escape from Naraku, who kills her for the defection. Hoping to redeem himself, Kohaku travels with Kikyou until she tells him he must leave her to keep his shard pure. He later joins Sesshomaru`s group and becomes Rin`s friend and co-protector.</description>
<picture>36872.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12192" type="appears in" update="2009-10-08">
<rating votes="7">4.79</rating>
<name>Byakuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Naraku`s ninth and final detachment, meant to replace Kagura. His main purpose is to observe InuYasha and Mouryoumaru`s growing powers and report back to Naraku. He has an incredible power to create illusions, but has many other powers as well: he can possess people with paper soldiers, summon vines to entrap his enemies, teleport others to different dimensions, detach organs from his body, and erect barriers. He travels on a giant origami paper crane.</description>
<picture>36909.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12194" type="appears in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="12">4.29</rating>
<name>A-Un</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A two-headed dragon demon and Sesshomaru`s beast of burden. He is one of two youkai in the series who is explicitly stated to be an herbivore. Despite travelling with Sesshomaru for centuries, he has no name until Rin gives him one, calling the right head "A" and the left head "Un". A-Un can fire youkai energy from both mouths. The right head shoots blue beams of lightning, while the left shoots green lightning that can control clouds and possibly the weather. A grey cloud-like gas trails from his legs in flight, similar to Kirara`s flames.</description>
<picture>36911.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="113322" update="2011-08-22">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2008-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Special</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
