<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7382" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-06-27</startdate>
<enddate>2010-09-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gakuen Mokushiroku: High School of the Dead</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Highschool of the Dead</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Школа Мёртвых</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Gyvųjų Numirėlių Mokykla</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Гимназията на мъртвите</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Школа мерців</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Старша школа мерців</title>
<title xml:lang="mn" type="synonym">Үхэгсдийн Ахлах Сургууль</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">HOTD</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">HSOTD</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">HOTDTV</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">HSOTDTV</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">学園黙示録 HIGH SCHOOL OF THE DEAD</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">High School of the Dead</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Highschool of the Dead</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">High School of the Dead</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Highschool of the Dead</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Apocalipsis en el instituto</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">학원묵시록</title>
<title xml:lang="sk" type="official">Stredná škola mŕtvych</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">学園黙示録</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">学园黙示録</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7953" type="Side Story">Gakuen Mokushiroku: High School of the Dead - Drifters of the Dead</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="6108" approval="27" total="57">Biohazard: Degeneration</anime>
<anime id="8660" approval="21" total="45">High School DxD</anime>
<anime id="10697" approval="11" total="22">Gakkougurashi!</anime>
<anime id="7900" approval="8" total="28">Freezing</anime>
<anime id="8315" approval="6" total="18">Gyo</anime>
<anime id="4799" approval="6" total="16">Tokyo Majin Gakuen Kenpuchou Tou</anime>
<anime id="7902" approval="3" total="26">Deadman Wonderland</anime>
<anime id="5587" approval="2" total="24">Detroit Metal City</anime>
<anime id="10951" approval="1" total="8">Koutetsujou no Kabaneri</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="44">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="302120">for fans of zombies and adventures this is the perfect anime! reallly splatter and a bit violent yeah!!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="158874">This anime gains fanbase on fanservice and not story. I for one thought it would be better, I mean everybody loves zombies!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="505867">Here is the bottom line. It`s got boobs, guns, and love triangles. After watching it and finishing it......

*(Spoiler)*-------------------------------------------------The story just ends....at a shopping center. I don`t get why, I guess it`s not over yet?? Anyways ending is bad but the rest is ok. The story is somewhat plastered on like it was made in a rush. Enjoy the boobs but don`t stay for the ending.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="326975">If you like boobs and gore, this show is for you. If you don`t, stay away from it, because there is nothing else in this series.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="90416">Typical shounen, but more fanservice, and more clichés than ever.
Also, the main characters are more stupid than any other sounen, and the story is slower than any other shounen, otherwise the setting could have been really great.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="300757">Zombies and ecchi normally don`t mix well, and this anime makes no exception at this rule for me. The plot starts with the classic argument of a "zombie infection" on a big city, and the disease expanding at abnormally fast speeds. The ecchi part is somewhat out of place.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="473022">This Series is so good!! You gotta watch this, even if you dont like zombies!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="279674">A good mix of zombies and tits in one show. However, I hope the show won`t switch completely to ecchi episodes.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="138124">Really great anime, having a lot of fun watching it :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="178631">For those who love contrast of blood-spill, tits &amp; panty-flash.
Quite decent action too and zombies are popular these days. Decent watch</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="210547">Blood,guts and hard core zombie style. SPLENDID</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="425228">This series was excellent. I recommend it to everybody, specially zombie lovers.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="264318">Wow~~ nice story and great fan service ^_^
if only there is HOTD 2.... it`s going to be a HIT ! luv u</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="16938">The first episode is one of the best single episodes of anime ever created in my opinion, the ending scene of it, on the rooftop, is just mindblowing.
The overall series is also very good, but it turns very ecchi half-way through, which may turn some people off. The music also needs mention as it contains tributes to zombie movies such as 28 Weeks/days later, and is very VERY good.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="319333">Seen 2 eps so far and it seems very promising, it grabs you on the very first episode! A definite must watch! I hope the story continues this way :) *Don`t Screw this up please* ^^</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="456383">This anime is really good. It hooked me up since episode 1. I`m not really into zombies, but I mainly watched for the relationship among the characters. Good plot, music and fairly enough action. I hope a second season is released.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="420280">Decent!
It`s almost a must see, if it weren`t for the excessive, ill-timed, fan service.
It gives it a pleasant unconventional feel though :P Other than that: Awesome²</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="232613">Good Anime for plot and action, the fan service however ruins the mood of the show. Without it it would been an true Zombie Anime, something Anime is lacking overall. Still very good zombie action!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="341304">Dude, it`s got zombies. Watch it!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="473348">a really entertaining horror gore fest with bundles of humour and ecchi. doesnt take itself too seriously which saves it from being yet another horror flop.  watch if u enjoy lighthearted slash/gore fun</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="338163">Zombies, boobs, action, character development, and a sense of helplessness... This anime does successfully what so many recent zombie flicks wish they could attain.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="364898">Now if only the manga came off hiatus...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="291829">Looking for something, not necessarily with a well thought-out plot ... well look no further ... you`ve come to the right place ...
Personal opinion: Rather relaxing, but at the same time entertaining. Might not be with the best plot or the deepest story, but still made me think about some things ... well 12 episodes - 4 hours ... you decide if it`s too much for you ...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="308099">Zombies, gore, boobs and ecchi. What else could you possibly want?

Well putting that aside I think this could be a top anime if they actually put more thought into the story line. I mean it just lack story telling. I surely hope for a second season. Maybe a bit less ecchi wouldn`t hurt and mroe gore.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="442226">This is a rather interesting show to watch. I find that the ecchi elements don`t hold  back the quality of the whole story. To be honest, this is like an anime version of Resident Evil, with high school students.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="241161">Wow, I haven`t been this hooked on an anime in a longgg time. I usually watch the anime and never look over the manga, but after seeing the 9th episode, I`m gonna reconsider.

This anime is a total blast to watch and the humor is great!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="414904">Simply stunning! Prepare to be sucked in the scenario starting 2nd minute of first episode till the end of series. This is definitely a must watch!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="162764">Good style and drawings - definitly worth Full HD, plus Gore, Zomby Action and ZR.. what more can you ask for!? ;)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="264498">It`s my first time seeing this combination in anime... fan service or not fan service, if u are truly an anime watcher you will apreciate it. action, gore, comedy, ecchi and a drop of romance blended with the zombies it leave`s u the impression that u want more of it. it`s damn funny. must see</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="562257">Boobs, guns and zombies.... What more is there to say? A definate must see!! Cant wait for season 2!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="81165">This series is incredible.
A bit to much fanservice, but one of the best `life after zombies` stories I`ve ever seen in any form.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="266839">Wow. The opening sequence is just great. Great animation. It should have another 12 or 40 episodes! You can say it is the anime version of RED DAWN but wayyyy cooler.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="492032">OF cource! One of ny favorite animes. Hot babes + zombies = I`m happy. I recomend this to everyone who like Ecchi and horror. From the first episode I was hooked. You`ll like it! MUST SEE!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="86398">Definitely a v.good show top 10 this year in my ranking a must see for those that are reading the manga.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="51585">Tits, asses, pantsu, guns, gore and zombies. What else do you need?

It`s awesome entertainment with few(several) beers and among male friends.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="366535">This anime is very good with the action and mental parts, but the ecchi parts don`t combine with the post-apocalyptical tension...but even with this in the anime is very good and is good to watch, and if you love ecchi you definitely MUST SEE</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="260880">Would you like to be scared ?Then watch it.It is possibly capable of scaring you more than "dawn of the dead"</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.geneonuniversal.jp/rondorobe/anime/hotd/</url>
<creators>
<name id="9383" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ochiai Hitomi</name>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="2210" type="Character Design">Tanaka Masayoshi</name>
<name id="1572" type="Series Composition">Kuroda Yousuke</name>
<name id="1523" type="Direction">Araki Tetsurou</name>
<name id="18474" type="Music">Wada Takafumi</name>
<name id="12663" type="Original Work">Satou Shouji</name>
<name id="12662" type="Original Work">Satou Daisuke</name>
<name id="2210" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tanaka Masayoshi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the manga written by http://anidb.net/cr12662 [Satou Daisuke], illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr12663 [Satou Shouji].
The world is ravaged by a deadly disease that turns humans into zombies. In Japan, several students of Fujimi High School, and the school nurse, band together to survive this apocalypse. http://anidb.net/ch16778 [Komuro Takashi] is one of the students who survived the initial outbreak.
Note: The first episode received an early screening on June 27, 2010 in Tokyo`s Theater Tsutaya, in front of selected viewers who were chosen from a nationwide postcard lottery held until June 14. The earliest television broadcast started on July 5.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="7664">5.76</permanent>
<temporary count="7762">7.23</temporary>
<review count="9">6.23</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221584.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11271</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8074</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4715</identifier>
<identifier>msqdvf</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.geneonuniversal.jp/rondorobe/anime/hotd/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Highschool_of_the_Dead</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>学園黙示録_HIGHSCHOOL_OF_THE_DEAD</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1968</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>337150</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12864</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2010/gakuenmokushiroku</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1221" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-28">
<name>scooter</name>
<description>A scooter is a type of motorcycle with a step-through frame and a platform for the rider`s feet.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>218044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2257" parentid="1152" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-12">
<name>zombie</name>
<description>A zombie is asserted to be a reanimated corpse, or a human who is being controlled by someone else by use of magic with some media renditions using a pandemic illness to explain their existence.
Stories of zombies originated in the West African spiritual belief system of voodoo, which told of the people being controlled as laborers by a powerful wizard.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2259" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-30">
<name>naked apron</name>
<description>A character wearing nothing but an apron appears in the show.</description>
<picurl>162045.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2621" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>bullet time</name>
<description>Bullet time refers to a simulation of variable speed (i.e. slow motion, time-lapse, …) and is characterized both by its extreme transformation of time and space to show normally imperceptible and un-filmable events, such as flying bullets.
Most infamous scene using this technique, Neo dodging bullets in The Matrix film.</description>
<picurl>211279.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2715" parentid="7220" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-11">
<name>rape</name>
<description>Rape means to force someone to engage in sexual interaction without their consent. If the rape is not successfully executed (both fellatio and penetration did not occur), tag with http://anidb.net/t7238 [attempted rape] instead.</description>
<picurl>212186.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2893" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>female teacher</name>
<description>Any kind of female teacher will do, even if she only does home visits. Female teachers imply mature women (even if they sometimes look like schoolgirls) dressed in what women would typically wear when doing official business (like a blouse, pinstripe dress with side front slit), but of course, not limited to that. Furthermore, school nurses also count as female teachers unless they`re actually wearing a nurse outfit, which they almost never are.
Almost completely exclusive to hentai animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2894" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>female student</name>
<description>Pretty much exclusive to hentai shows only unless an ecchi show has implied sex and/or a strong indicator of nudity. A character is considered a student if she goes to school, doesn`t matter if it`s high school, college or homeschooling, but she should be of appropriate age for a student; a housewife going to college should not get this category.</description>
<picurl>210611.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3075" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2013-02-27">
<name>nervous breakdown</name>
<description>A character sees his entire world being destroyed around him, and his brain can`t take it anymore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3267" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>everybody dies</name>
<description>Not necessarily everyone, but a good portion of the characters kick the bucket.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3395" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-18">
<name>promise</name>
<description>A dramatically-made promise that serves as foreshadowing. The promise will eventually be called in and action will be required.
Whether they succeed, fail or refuse to keep their promise depends almost entirely on the idealism-level of the story. Other factors, such as whether they were told what they had to do, or if it was a Leonine Contract, may come into play. Even Releasing from the Promise is usually a scene of high drama.
Source: TVTropes</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4170" parentid="5626" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-08-08">
<name>police are useless</name>
<description>The civilian law enforcement representatives do not seem to be of much use, when trying to take on the usually vastly superior foes.
The "helpless" and often clumsy antics of the police can be used as a comedy element.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4228" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-09">
<name>subtle OP ED sequence change</name>
<description>A (small) part of the opening or ending sequence changes after a certain episode, usually to reflect a plot milestone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4246" parentid="3395" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-01">
<name>childhood promise</name>
<description>Sweet childhood promises... who remembers them other than the Japanese anime characters?
It keeps the main characters obsessed with promises that they made when they were children, mostly related to love, with lines like "I will always protect you" or "I will marry you when we grow up".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4257" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>survival</name>
<description>The theme/genre of survival typically depicts the act or process of continuing to live, generally in a hostile, possibly post-apocalyptic environment. Survival-centered media tends to be dark, set most commonly in a contemporary context, and generally leads either to small groups of people forming closely knit and functional units or to individuals turning against their fellows in a return to the survival of the fittest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4277" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-30">
<name>nuclear weapons</name>
<description>A nuclear weapon is an explosive device that derives its destructive force from nuclear reactions, which release vast quantities of energy from relatively small amounts of matter. Nuclear weapons are considered weapons of mass destruction, and their use and control have been a major focus of international relations policy since their debut.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4340" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-26">
<name>suicide</name>
<description>One or several characters in this anime commit suicide.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5466" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-17">
<name>epidemic</name>
<description>A rapid spread or increase of something (e.g. a disease) affecting many persons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5626" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>adults are useless</name>
<description>For when adults can`t do anything right.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5762" parentid="3842" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>violence censoring</name>
<description>Describes TV shows, where parts of the scenes considered as too violent are blackened, blurred, changed to other static screen, or cut out completely.
While TV censoring is normally used to boost the BD/DVD sales, this is done under the mantle of being "for the healthy development of youth" or similar excuses. In the long run, it`s just the same.
Examples: Deadman Wonderland, Fate/Zero, and Mirai Nikki.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5952" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-25">
<name>end of the world</name>
<description>The imminent end of the world may range from the total destruction of the planet Earth, to the destruction of Earth`s surface, or to the point where human life on the planet is no longer possible, aka the end of humanity.
In any case it looks grim, and the protagonists battle to preserve what they can.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5981" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-10-12">
<name>seeking protagonist</name>
<description>The main character has a main objective that is referenced to through the whole series; he is in search of something, or someone
Should it be treasure, friends, money, power or all of the above nothing will stop our lead character in his quest to find his passion</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6480" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-26">
<name>gun - TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This character uses at least one type of gun, or this anime has one character that uses at least one type of gun. Please tag the characters with the appropriate gun type tags (e.g. pistol, revolver, assault rifle, etc) and remove this tag from them or their corresponding anime afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7222" parentid="7220" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-30">
<name>groping</name>
<description>Groping is the act of subjecting another person to unwanted sexual touching.</description>
<picurl>68310.png</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="16778" type="main character in" update="2010-04-17">
<rating votes="109">6.95</rating>
<name>Komuro Takashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Komuro Takashi is a 17 year old sophomore high school student, Takashi is in the same class as Rei whom he has been friends with since childhood. He`s loved her ever since she made a childhood promise to marry him when they were older. However it was his hesitance and ignorance about her feelings that caused tension in their friendship which led to her starting to date his friend Hisashi. He was one of the first people to notice that something was wrong in the school and quickly took action to escape with his friends. His relationship with Rei was shaken further when he was forced to kill her boyfriend after he was bitten and had turned into a zombie. Soon afterwards their relationship was amended. His resolve to protect Rei at all costs and everyone else in the group earned him their respect and admiration as a leader despite his own feelings of inadequacy. He often acts brash and will go out to risk his life to save or protect someone on a whim. Similar to Saeko, Takashi confessed that he`s found an exhilaration in killing "them".
Though initially depicted as a poor student who often skips class, he`s proven to be a very reliable person that all the characters can count on. Saya Takagi has once mentioned that he and Kohta are the most likely to snap if things keep going the way they are. Like the rest of the group, Takashi is determined to find his parents and to make sure that they`re safe.</description>
<picture>46423.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="5878" picture="45926.jpg">Harada Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16779" type="main character in" update="2010-07-06">
<rating votes="136">4.79</rating>
<name>Miyamoto Rei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miyamoto Rei is a classmate and childhood friend of Takashi, they`ve known each other since kindergarten. When they were little she promised that one day she would marry him. Despite liking Takashi, their relationship was at odds at the beginning due to his indecisiveness. It was then that she started dating one of his friends, Hisashi, since he wouldn`t make a move. As the story progressed they ended up reconciling their relationship. She doesn`t find it above herself to reprimand Takashi for acting carelessly. She worries about his well-being yet admits that his selfless nature is one reason why she fell in love with him. Headstrong and reliable, Rei has proven to be a skilled combatant and strong asset to the group.
Initially in the same year as Saeko, Rei was held back despite being an excellent student. Her father - a police detective - had been investigating the corruption behind the father of Shido, one of the teachers at her school. As a result of this he held her back purposefully. Rei bears a lasting grudge against him and feels uneasy whenever he`s around.
After having escaped the high school and resting at the family mansion of Saya, she and the group are in search of their parents.</description>
<picture>46424.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16780" type="main character in" update="2010-04-17">
<rating votes="309">8.55</rating>
<name>Busujima Saeko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Busujima Saeko is a high school senior and president of the school`s kendo club, she is extremely skilled with a bokken and close combat. Calm and collected with a sense of pride in her skills and those that she`s with, Saeko is among the most reliable of the group. Everyone can count on her combat skills to pull them through a tough spot if need be. She has shown fondness towards Takashi and believes in his abilities to get them through the crisis. Not much is known about her family except for her father who had traveled abroad on a self-defense conference before the advent of the Outbreak. Saya`s father Souichirou Takagi tells Saeko that her father gave him some guidance once so in gratitude he gives her a unique sword.
Four years prior to the start of the story, a man had attempted to assault her. Armed with her bokken, she easily disposed of the would-be assailant, breaking several of his bones before the police came. This experience revealed her sadistic tendencies; she enjoyed holding the power to inflict pain on another human being. In addition to her reliance on killing the undead in order to survive, Saeko continually struggles with this part of her self, which causes momentary weaknesses in her otherwise strong demeanor. After telling Takashi her story and encountering a group of undead afterwards, for a second Saeko considers letting herself get taken away. She is stopped by Takashi who restores her confidence and resolve. After this she accepts herself and promises to continue fighting with Takashi whom she now counts on to be responsible for her actions. After Saya Takagi mentions that Takashi and Kohta are the most likely to "lose it and become a danger to themselves" if things keep going the way they are. It is Saeko that mentions that she will be there for them and that she is of the female sex.</description>
<picture>46425.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16781" type="main character in" update="2011-05-02">
<rating votes="116">5.78</rating>
<name>Takagi Saya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takagi Saya is first making her escape with fellow classmate Kohta Hirano, she is the daughter of an influential Uyoku dantai politician and her family is deeply involved in Japan`s politics. A self-proclaimed genius, Saya`s knowledge and deductive capabilities have allowed the group to escape from harm. She was among the first to conclude that "they" were attracted to only sound. Despite coming from a prestigious family she despises her parents whom she thought had given up on her in this crisis. It was before their escape from the mansion that she managed to makeup with her parents. Other than Rei, she is the only one who has a history with Takashi Komuro since they were children and is hinted to having deeper feelings for him.
Slightly self-conscious, she detests the fact that people neither address her by her first name nor look her in the eyes while speaking. The only exception to this is Kohta with whom she has a strange friendship. Saya`s grown very attached to Alice and acts like a mother figure in this time of crisis. She does her best to keep intact Alice`s innocence and will severely scold anyone who would dare attempt to tarnish that to the any degree.</description>
<picture>46426.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16782" type="main character in" update="2010-04-17">
<rating votes="94">6.92</rating>
<name>Hirano Kouta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hirano Kouta is a 16-year old sophomore student who was often bullied in school, Kouta is a gun otaku and knows the ins and outs of the firearms and any military-related equipment that the group may comes across. At the beginning of the story he helped Takagi Saya escape danger, though only did so by following her orders. His skills as a marksman has proven to be an invaluable asset to keeping everyone alive. On a one-month trip to America he was trained by the US military contractor Blackwater USA which furthered his obsession over weapons.
His crush on Saya is one-sided as he on occasion tries to ask her out only to be rejected, but she has shown to care about him. His crush has since then, ended, and he had now developed deep feelings for police officer; Nakaoka Asami, in the most recent arc. With both parties holding mutual feelings, both expressed the love for the other, and Kouta managed to convince Asami to join the group in their escape. Before leaving the family mansion of Saya, her father entrusted her safety to him and Takashi. Takagi Saya has once mentioned that he and Takashi are the most likely to snap if things keep going the way they are. He`s grown very attached to Alice with whom he is often around playing with.
His character may have been based on the http://anidb.net/cr3564 [mangaka of the same name] as the two look similar.</description>
<picture>46427.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16783" type="main character in" update="2019-11-20">
<rating votes="128">5.06</rating>
<name>Marikawa Shizuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Marikawa Shizuka is the school nurse at Fujimi High School, she is rather ditsy as compared to the rest of girls in the group. Her large bust size is often used as a comical element in the story. A 27 year old bachelorette she lives with Rika Minami, a sniper of Japan`s Special Assault Team. Her home was used as a safe haven for the group once they escaped the high school. As a nurse she is responsible for the health and care of everyone in the group and is efficient at doing so.
Despite being the only adult in the group, she is emotionally fragile and doesn`t know what will become of her life since the Outbreak started. Like the rest of the main characters, Shizuka worries that she will never see her family or friends again.</description>
<picture>46428.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="80" picture="228656.jpg">Fukui Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17779" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-01">
<rating votes="22">3.29</rating>
<name>Igou Hisashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Igou Hisashi is Rei`s classmate and boyfriend. He, Takashi, and Rei were among the first to try and escape the rampage at the school. On their way out of class, he was bitten by an infected teacher and subsequently turned into one of "them" afterwards. Aware of his fate, he instructed Takashi to kill him before he turned, but died before Takashi could do so, and rose back up as one of "them". Takashi then gathers himself together and takes down Hisashi permanently. A brief bitterness between Rei and Takashi occurred as a result from his death. Hisashi was responsible for "naming" the zombies as "them".
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>50711.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="255" picture="40713.jpg">Miyano Mamoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17780" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-02">
<rating votes="75">7.13</rating>
<name>Minami Rika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Minami Rika is the chief of first squadron in the prefecture police and an expert sniper in the Special Assault Team sent to clear the nearby airport of any zombie stragglers. She is friends with Shizuka, and has the desire to go and save her from the outbreak of zombies. Unknown to her, they had stayed at her residence and have fled in her Humvee. She has been held up in the same airport alongside surviving passengers who were supposed to fly out with surviving Special Assault Team and Special Security Team operatives alongside airport security guards, customs officers, and firefighters in clearing the airport of any stragglers by reducing the zombie strength.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>52468.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="302" picture="17134.jpg">Takeuchi Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17781" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="62">3.90</rating>
<name>Maresato Alice</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Only 7 years old she was saved from being attacked by several undead by Takashi after her father was killed by members of a household who wouldn`t allow them safety. Innocent and passive, Alice is the only member of the group that maintains a cheerful attitude despite all their troubles and the loss of her parents. Looking up to everyone in the group as a bigger brother and sister, she is unwilling to leave them even if it`s for her own safety.</description>
<picture>52548.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17782" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-01">
<rating votes="37">1.11</rating>
<name>Shidou Kouichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shidou Kouichi is the teacher of Class 3A. Rei Miyamoto is afraid and is disgusted by him and Saeko Busujima says his name with a scowl, showing that he apparently is a sadistic and villainous character. Both girls have good reasons to do so as we see him leaving behind a student who has sprained his ankle and even kicking him back towards a group of zombies chasing them. He then makes a speech about how weaklings do not deserve to exist. It was implied by Hirano that Shidou allowed bullies to beat him up as he watched with glee. It is assumed that the former`s story is true because Hirano pointed the nail gun at Shidou without blinking or hesitating to shoot a nail at his face.
He has a desire to be a leader, and some of the characters have theorized that he is trying to build a new religion with him on top as leader. Shidou is an apparent coward in the face of extreme danger, as seen when being threatened by a grazing head shot with a nail gun on Hirano`s part, but nonetheless, proves to be a manipulative, villainous and sadistic character.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>51588.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="181" picture="171560.jpg">Taniyama Kishou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19385" type="appears in" update="2011-07-01">
<rating votes="11">4.18</rating>
<name>Hayashi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Teacher, second victim of zombie outbreak in Fujimi High School.</description>
<picture>50705.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="449" picture="17341.jpg">Honna Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19386" type="appears in" update="2010-07-05">
<rating votes="5">2.75</rating>
<name>Tejima</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50706.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="76" picture="16684.jpg">Maeda Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19387" type="appears in" update="2010-07-05">
<rating votes="5">2.23</rating>
<name>Wakisaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50707.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6942" picture="41078.jpg">Takaoka Binbin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19388" type="appears in" update="2010-07-05">
<rating votes="8">2.95</rating>
<name>Misuzu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50708.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19568" picture="50821.jpg">Seto Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19389" type="appears in" update="2010-07-05">
<rating votes="6">2.56</rating>
<name>Toshimi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50710.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56" picture="16651.jpg">Shimizu Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19842" type="appears in" update="2010-07-20">
<rating votes="5">2.45</rating>
<name>Ishii</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51586.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6126" picture="37816.jpg">Hamazoe Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19843" type="appears in" update="2010-07-20">
<rating votes="5">3.24</rating>
<name>Takuzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51591.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19844" type="appears in" update="2010-07-20">
<rating votes="7">2.33</rating>
<name>Naomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51590.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2038" picture="49098.jpg">Shishido Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20293" type="appears in" update="2010-08-02">
<rating votes="7">4.45</rating>
<name>Tajima</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52470.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="99" picture="139554.jpg">Hirakawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20294" type="appears in" update="2011-04-12">
<rating votes="10">1.86</rating>
<name>Yuuki Miku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69702.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8812" picture="33246.jpg">Sakuno Airi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20599" type="appears in" update="2010-09-08">
<rating votes="10">3.86</rating>
<name>Zeke</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54689.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5878" picture="45926.jpg">Harada Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21428" type="appears in" update="2010-09-08">
<rating votes="12">6.53</rating>
<name>Takagi Souichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leader of a radical Uyoku dantai group in the Tokonosu district, he is an extreme right-winger who showed his leadership to the survivors when he rallies them to kill the zombies in order to save Japanese society from collapsing. He added a rather pointed illustration by killing his zombified subordinate. Later on, he insists that Kohta give up his weapons. However, Kouta`s friends (including Saya) rallied for Kouta and supported him. It is implied that he was impressed by their willingness to challenge him and allows Kouta to maintain the weapons he took from Rika`s house.
It is also shown that Saya hates her father more than her mother because he didn`t ensure her safety when the outbreak started in Japan. Souichirou seems to be a sword expert and is sceptical about Hirano`s reasons of keeping his guns until he`s confronted by everyone in the main group except for Marikawa, who defends his reasons for protecting his daughter. It is currently shown that he and his followers are preparing to leave the estate in two days time and is told by Takashi if he and his friends are not back with their parents by then, they should leave without waiting for them. However, when the zombies manage to enter the estate due to a gap from one of the barrier`s inadvertently created by Shidou, the Takagis, their followers, and the remaining survivors fight to hold off the invading horde until they could go to other areas of the neighbourhood that were not breached. Before Takashi &amp; his entourage leave the estate, Kouta and Takashi swore to Saya`s father to protect her and Saya tells her parents that she loves them before they attempt their escape. Souichirou and his wife were last seen fighting against the horde with rest of the estate survivors while saying that they were proud of their daughter and the friends she made. Their fate is currently unknown.</description>
<picture>54695.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21429" type="appears in" update="2010-09-08">
<rating votes="31">6.26</rating>
<name>Takagi Yuriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Souichirou`s wife and Saya`s mother. Yuriko was once a New York Stock Broker who later married her future husband after she was impressed with his charisma and political skills. Thanks to her business connections, the Takagi family fortune rises significantly. She is very faithful to her husband and loves her daughter very much. She was last seen with her husband and other survivors fighting against the horde that breach their estate.</description>
<picture>54697.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="571" picture="172734.jpg">Sakakibara Yoshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21470" type="appears in" update="2010-09-08">
<rating votes="6">4.16</rating>
<name>Alice no Chichioya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54685.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21471" type="appears in" update="2010-09-08">
<rating votes="7">2.88</rating>
<name>Doi Tetsutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54699.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20422" picture="156870.jpg">Koshiba Daishi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21774" type="appears in" update="2010-09-20">
<rating votes="9">3.45</rating>
<name>Matsushita</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Asami`s senior officer from the local police station. She is briefly shown at the end of the anime`s episode 12.</description>
<picture>55280.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="21782" type="appears in" update="2011-04-12">
<rating votes="3">5.22</rating>
<name>Yoshioka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69701.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="371" picture="166173.jpg">Kuroda Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21783" type="appears in" update="2011-04-23">
<rating votes="5">4.34</rating>
<name>Matsudo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68581.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="373" picture="191382.jpg">Hamada Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21784" type="appears in" update="2010-09-21">
<rating votes="6">3.45</rating>
<name>Yamada</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A teen that is concerned for his family; he is one of the only ones who hasn`t been brainwashed by Shindo. His concern is noted when Shindo notices he didn`t take part in the orgy in chapter 11. The others teens, now finally able to do what they want, don`t like the idea of their families being in danger. Shindo persuades others that Yamada`s been corrupted and suggests that, for the sake of the new world, they toos him off. The other teens do so and drive off, leaving him to die, even waving as he pleads to be let back on. The boy is shown one last time as a zombie lunges for his head. This scene shows how corrupt the kids have gotten. It is not shown if Yamada is officially dead, or if he escaped his attacker.</description>
<picture>55297.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20422" picture="156870.jpg">Koshiba Daishi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21785" type="appears in" update="2010-09-21">
<rating votes="7">1.88</rating>
<name>Shidou Ichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shidou Kouichi`s father and an influential politician. It was him that made Kouichi hold back Rei for a year to put pressure on her father, a police officer, who was investigating against him.</description>
<picture>55298.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="66" picture="216211.jpg">Bifu Hitoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="118584" update="2010-06-02">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-03-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118639" update="2018-06-30">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-26</airdate>
<rating votes="31">3.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Running in the DEAD</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Running in the Dead</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tomber sur les morts-vivants</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Correndo da Morte</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Running in the Dead</title>
<summary>The population grows desperate and chaos runs wild in the streets. Crossing any bridge presents a world of problems for Komuro and Rei, while dissension among the ranks splits the bus group in two.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="118640" update="2018-06-30">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-19</airdate>
<rating votes="32">6.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Democracy under the DEAD</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Democracy Under the Dead</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Démocratie sous les morts-vivants</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Democracia sobre os Mortos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Democracy Under the Dead</title>
<summary>The enemy`s weak points are discovered and exploited. The human condition is put to the test, and everyone`s base survival instincts kick in. Tensions rise as more people swell the ranks, and one survivor refuses to continue with the group.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="118641" update="2018-06-30">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-12</airdate>
<rating votes="36">6.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Escape from the DEAD</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Escape from the Dead</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Fuite des morts-vivants</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Fugindo dos Mortos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Escape from the Dead</title>
<summary>As the entire school quickly spirals into chaos, more players just into the fight, handmade weapons at the ready. New enemy traits are discovered, and the survivors realize the situation that they`re really in. 
Source: IMDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="118642" update="2018-06-30">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-27</airdate>
<rating votes="43">8.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Spring of the DEAD</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Spring of the Dead</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le printemps des morts-vivants</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Primavera dos Mortos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Spring of the Dead</title>
<summary>A deadly virus is turning the world`s population into walking corpses. While the world erupts into chaos around them, Takashi Komuro and his friends frantically search for a way to break free from the living dead.
Source: IMDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119524" update="2012-05-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-07-05</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119525" update="2010-07-05">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-07-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119739" update="2018-06-30">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="21">7.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">All DEAD`S attack.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">All Dead`s Attack</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">O Ataque de todos os Mortos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">All Dead`s Attack</title>
<summary>After an EMP wave shuts down all electronic equipment in a wide radius, Komuro and his friends must defend the mansion or risk losing everything that matters to them.
Source: IMDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119740" update="2018-06-30">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-13</airdate>
<rating votes="23">4.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">DEAD storm rising</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dead Storm Rising</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Tempestade da Morte Avançando</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dead Storm Rising</title>
<summary>Tempers flare in the House of Saya Takagi. Decisions must be made, and a leader must be chosen. Honor, love, devotion and mercy are put to the test; and a man from the group`s past makes an unexpected return.
Source: IMDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119741" update="2018-06-30">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-06</airdate>
<rating votes="24">3.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">The DEAD`S house rules</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dead`s House Rules</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">As Regras das casas dos Mortos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Dead`s House Rules</title>
<summary>The group reunites at Takagi`s house, an impenetrable fortress run by her parents and their army of workers. After surviving this long on their own, being absorbed into a larger group becomes a huge concern.
Source: IMDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119742" update="2018-06-30">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-30</airdate>
<rating votes="31">6.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">The sword and DEAD</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sword and Dead</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le sabre et les morts</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">A Espada e os Mortos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Sword and Dead</title>
<summary>After narrowly escaping with their lives, Komuro and Saeko must make their way alone and rendezvous with the others. Saeko`s true nature is revealed, and it begs the question: Is her beauty only skin deep?
Source: IMDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119743" update="2018-06-30">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-23</airdate>
<rating votes="29">4.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">The DEAD Way Home</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dead Way Home</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La morte route vers le foyer</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">O Caminho Morto pra Casa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Dead Way Home</title>
<summary>An animal is said to be the most dangerous when cornered. After crossing the river, the group takes a wrong turn and becomes trapped. With no help in sight and a wall of the living dead surrounding them, how many waves can they fight off before they`re overwhelmed?
Source: IMDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119744" update="2018-06-30">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-16</airdate>
<rating votes="28">5.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">DEAD night and the DEAD ruck</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dead Night and the Dead Ruck</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Nuit des morts, groupe des morts</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">A Noite Morta e uma Multidão Morta</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dead Night and the Dead Ruck</title>
<summary>Fully rested and armed to the teeth, the group looks on as people are eaten alive in the streets below, and learn a valuable lesson: you can`t save them all. However, in the zombie apocalypse, there are always exceptions.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119745" update="2018-06-30">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-09</airdate>
<rating votes="30">4.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">In the DEAD of the night</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In the Dead of the Night</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Au milieu de la nuit</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Na Noite Morta</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">In the Dead of the Night</title>
<summary>With no help coming from headquarters, the police are ordered to use deadly force to maintain order at the blockade. Safe for the time being, the group relaxes and prepares themselves by gathering supplies for the chaos that awaits them outside.
Source: IMDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119746" update="2018-06-30">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-02</airdate>
<rating votes="31">5.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Streets of the DEAD</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Streets of the Dead</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les rues des morts-vivants</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Ruas dos Mortos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Streets of the Dead</title>
<summary>The population grows desperate and chaos runs wild in the streets. Crossing any bridge presents a world of problems for Komuro and Rei, while dissension among the ranks splits the bus group in two.
Source: IMDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119915" update="2010-07-14">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-07-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120027" update="2010-07-19">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-07-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120482" update="2010-07-29">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-07-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120617" update="2010-08-02">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-08-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121128" update="2010-08-10">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-08-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121335" update="2010-08-19">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-08-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121513" update="2010-08-27">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-08-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121597" update="2010-08-30">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-08-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121943" update="2010-09-07">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-09-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122423" update="2010-09-16">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-09-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122552" update="2010-09-20">
<epno type="3">C13</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 12</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
