<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7412" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-04-01</startdate>
<enddate>2010-09-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Heroman</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ヒーローマン</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Человек-герой</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Хиромен</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">الرجل البطل / هيرومان</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">HEROMAN</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">HEROMAN</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="6">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="122889">a nice serie that gives me the same feeling that I got with old hero programs like power rangers. Main difference has a storyline. And is better made.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="129620">Old school comic book action mixed with japanese flair</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="285275">very american i agree but not suprisingly for stan lee.i recommended for : animation &amp; nice fight scenes...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="112916">Now that the series ended, i can without a doubt recommend it.

It begins with a pretty cliche plot, but after the first arc ends the plot just blooms and develops at a pretty good pace right until it explodes in the ending, while keeping the story fresh.

The animation is absolutely superb, as one would expect from Studio Bones, and the story is well thought.

Shamefully, the ending feels a little "cut short" as many characters are left with fate unknown, but the classic "to be continued?" teaser is waved at the viewers.

Definetely one of the sleeper hits of the year, and personally, i can`t wait to see a second season of the show.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://wdshe.jp/heroman/</url>
<creators>
<name id="755" type="Animation Work">Bones</name>
<name id="7676" type="Character Design">Koyama Shigeto</name>
<name id="3467" type="Series Composition">Yamatoya Akatsuki</name>
<name id="662" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kawamoto Toshihiro</name>
<name id="10765" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tomioka Takashi</name>
<name id="14788" type="Original Work">Stan Lee</name>
<name id="5732" type="Direction">Nanba Hitoshi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on an original idea by American comic book writer http://anidb.net/cr14788 [Stan Lee], creator of Spider-Man and The Fantastic Four.
An American kid named http://anidb.net/ch15967 [Joey] lives in an urban city and has always wanted to become a hero. Unfortunately he is just an orphan working part time to support his grandma and himself. After watching a toy commercial on a new robot action figure, Joey comes to believe that he will gain strength once he obtains one of those. But the only robot toy he can get his hands on is a broken one that was abandoned by a rich school bully. Feeling pity for the trashed action figure, Joey takes the toy home to repair it. Little did he know, that once he repairs the toy, it will make his hero dream become reality.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="788">3.73</permanent>
<temporary count="798">6.11</temporary>
<review count="4">6.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>44278.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11266</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9121</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>4334</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4709</identifier>
<identifier>ddcijy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://disney-studio.jp/heroman/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.bones.co.jp/heroman</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Heroman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>HEROMAN</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1908</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>336385</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12598</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>heroman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2812" parentid="2832" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>United States</name>
<description>The United States of America (commonly referred to as the United States, the U.S., the USA, or America) is a federal constitutional republic comprising fifty states and a federal district. The country is situated mostly in central North America, where its forty-eight contiguous states and Washington, D.C., the capital district, lie between the Pacific and Atlantic Oceans, bordered by Canada to the north and Mexico to the south. The state of Alaska is in the north-west of the continent, with Canada to the east and Russia to the west across the Bering Strait. The state of Hawaii is an archipelago in the mid-Pacific. The country also possesses several territories in the Caribbean and Pacific.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>45504.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2832" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Americas</name>
<description>The Americas, also collectively called America, encompass the totality of the continents of North America and South America. Together they make up most of Earth`s western hemisphere and comprise the New World.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192247.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2863" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>proxy battles</name>
<description>In our terms, a proxy battle is a battle where humans use creatures/robots to do the fighting for them, either by commanding those creatures/robots or by simply evolving them/changing them into battle mode. Often the training aspect is also involved, or in some cases the proxies are nothing more than holographic representatives of some other variation of competition (like for example a card game). While many popular shounen anime fit under this category, it`s not limited to shounen anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3159" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-11-27">
<name>emotions awaken superpowers</name>
<description>During an extreme emotional state — rage, love, hate, angst, sadness, compassion — something inside the character will "click" that will increase greatly his/her power or a new superpower awakes, that surpasses anything achieved by him/her until then.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3516" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-28">
<name>insects of doom</name>
<description>Concerns insects, be them biological, magical or robotic in nature, that are either the bane, or a major stepping stone in the way of the main character(s) of the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4128" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-29">
<name>zero to hero</name>
<description>With his first appearance, this character is getting his ass kicked by nearly everyone, but as the plot continues, through training (mental or physical) or instant power-up, he changes into a killing/fighting/winning machine.
The best example: Makunouchi Ippo from Hajime no Ippo series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4198" parentid="5604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-14">
<name>hard work and guts</name>
<description>One of the character`s motto in the anime. Because there is nothing that cannot be achieved by hard work and guts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="15967" type="main character in" update="2010-03-19">
<rating votes="7">6.69</rating>
<name>Joey</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44920.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16085" picture="178446.jpg">Komatsu Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15968" type="main character in" update="2010-03-19">
<rating votes="2">7.00</rating>
<name>Heroman</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44921.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="15969" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-19">
<rating votes="2">5.78</rating>
<name>Psy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44922.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2225" picture="192115.jpg">Kimura Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15970" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-25">
<rating votes="9">7.91</rating>
<name>Lina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44923.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16089" picture="45161.jpg">Obata Mayu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15971" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-19">
<rating votes="3">5.16</rating>
<name>Denton</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44924.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="694" picture="52187.jpg">Choo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15972" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-19">
<rating votes="5">6.43</rating>
<name>Vera</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44925.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="252" picture="149852.jpg">Shindou Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15973" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-19">
<rating votes="2">2.87</rating>
<name>Will</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44926.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="68" picture="16675.jpg">Yasumura Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15974" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-19">
<rating votes="3">1.99</rating>
<name>Nick</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44927.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="399" picture="17244.jpg">Suyama Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15975" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-19">
<rating votes="2">3.96</rating>
<name>Gogorr</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44928.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16303" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-08">
<rating votes="2">5.15</rating>
<name>Obaa-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47563.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16594" picture="187282.jpg">Sakai Sumie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16304" type="appears in" update="2010-04-01">
<name>Sam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="10750" picture="186166.jpg">Takeuchi Ryouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16305" type="appears in" update="2012-04-25">
<name>Jean</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2888" picture="200816.jpg">Inoue Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16306" type="appears in" update="2010-04-10">
<rating votes="1">9.98</rating>
<name>Stan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Stan is actually Stan Lee, the creator of Heroman, appearing as a character in the show.</description>
<picture>46111.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5293" picture="186241.jpg">Ii Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16307" type="appears in" update="2010-05-08">
<name>Hilly</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Owner of the restaurant "EAT AT HILLY`S", where http://anidb.net/ch15967 [Joey] works at.</description>
<picture>47561.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3102" picture="24178.jpg">Chou Katsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16308" type="appears in" update="2010-05-08">
<rating votes="1">7.75</rating>
<name>Lina no Papa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47560.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="67" picture="25195.jpg">Ishii Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17504" type="appears in" update="2010-05-09">
<name>Pilot</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47603.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2888" picture="200816.jpg">Inoue Gou</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="235" picture="17053.jpg">Saizen Tadahisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17505" type="appears in" update="2010-05-09">
<name>Daitouryou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47604.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5321" picture="29433.jpg">Sasaki Bin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18131" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-27">
<rating votes="3">2.47</rating>
<name>Doctor Minami</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48651.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="455" picture="17356.jpg">Matsumoto Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18132" type="appears in" update="2010-05-27">
<rating votes="1">7.75</rating>
<name>Amanorich</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48652.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2002" picture="21307.jpg">Katsu Anri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18133" type="appears in" update="2010-05-27">
<name>Stallion</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48653.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2586" picture="233442.jpg">Kimura Masafumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18134" type="appears in" update="2010-05-27">
<rating votes="1">6.28</rating>
<name>Veronica</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48654.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19415" picture="50423.jpg">Gi Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19147" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-24">
<rating votes="6">7.56</rating>
<name>Holly Jones</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50267.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="457" picture="61775.jpg">Ogasawara Arisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19148" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-24">
<rating votes="3">6.77</rating>
<name>Axel Hughes</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50268.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="451" picture="17347.jpg">Touchi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="116869" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>539986</identifier>
<identifier>heroman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117296" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-01</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ビギニング</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beginning</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Beginning</title>
<summary>Center City, West Coast, USA. Joey loves heroes, and lives together in the city with his grandmother. While working a part-time job to support himself, he enjoys his life surrounded by Psy, his sarcastic lone-wolf friend, and Lina, a bright, cheerful girl from a well-to-do family. One day, Joey picks up a toy that was thrown away, repairs it, and names it "Heroman." But just then, a bolt of lightning strikes the toy! To Joey`s surprise, a giant-sized "Heroman" is born before his eyes!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>539930</identifier>
<identifier>heroman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117297" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-08</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エンカウンター</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Encounter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Encounter</title>
<summary>Seeing Heroman`s power before his own eyes, Joey wasn`t able to hide his happiness or bewilderment. He worries about what he should do with this power and what Heroman really is. Meanwhile, the mysterious life forms called "The Skrugg" have begun their Earth invasion. When Joey hears of it, he runs to tell Prof. Denton who was broadcasting to them of the imminent danger. However, the Skrugg appear there with weapons in hand! And Lina encounters them as well!?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>539932</identifier>
<identifier>heroman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117559" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">インヴェイジョン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Invasion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Invasion</title>
<summary>The giant saucer that appeared in the skies of Center City begins sending tons of Skrugg down to the ground. Even with the military in wait, they were no match for the onslaught, and the people could do nothing but escape. After Joey stands in shock watching the neighborhoods being destroyed, he and Psy head to Joey`s grandmother`s house. However, the Skrugg show up and get in their way. Joey steels his determination, activates Heroman, and stands up, ready to face the enemy himself.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>539934</identifier>
<identifier>heroman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117610" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">タマ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bullet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tama</title>
<summary>Will thinks that he should be the hero, and drags Nick along with him to infiltrate the enemy`s base and steal some of their weapons. At the same time Joey, having successfully dropped off his grandmother at the shelter, heads toward Professor Denton`s place to get more information. On the other hand, Kogorr starts attacking with a giant sphere. And what`s more, it`s started rolling straight toward the shelter where Grandma and Lina are! Joey and Heroman head out to face it and stop its advance somehow.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>539936</identifier>
<identifier>heroman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117611" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アサシンズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Assassins</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Assassins</title>
<summary>Against the rolling sphere that continues to destroy the city, Joey and the others could do nothing but barely hold its progress. Joey is determined to not leave the Skrugg alone, and leaps into the fray again even without a plan, while Prof. Denton gives a guitar weapon to Psy that he created using the Skrugg`s weapon. Joey and Psy head into the city with the weapon in hand, and they come up with a new plan to go up against the huge number of Skrugg. But before them a new threat comes calling...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>539938</identifier>
<identifier>heroman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117612" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バックラッシュ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Backlash</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Backlash</title>
<summary>Joey`s group is forced to retreat from the new enemies that suddenly appear in front of them. Meanwhile, Prof. Denton has analyzed the Skrugg and determined that the five spheres are heading toward different important world cities. One of them is the White House itself. At first thought to just be rolling spheres, it seems the Skrugg studied humanity well on how exactly to destroy the entire world. Realizing this, everyone is shocked and itching to do something about it, and as the time limit approaches, Joey and his friends become determined to head toward the enemy`s base.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>539940</identifier>
<identifier>heroman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="118172" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">レジスタンス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Resistance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Resistance</title>
<summary>Faced with the extinction of the human race, the President is coming closer to deciding to use nuclear weapons. But before him appears the mad scientist, " Dr. Minami." He claims to be able to stop the sphere without using a nuclear attack. Back in Center City, Joey and the others are infiltrating the Skrugg`s base, and in order to cause a diversion they split into two groups. The newly re-brainwashed Will and Nick appear before them. Joey has a plan to undo the brainwashing, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>539942</identifier>
<identifier>heroman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="118274" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コンバット</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Combat</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Combat</title>
<summary>In order to destroy the controls for the spheres, Denton and Psy infiltrate the Skrugg`s base, but they are quickly surrounded by the enemy and even with the guitar weapon can`t progress any further. Then the Skrugg`s leader, Kogorr, putting them in a desperate situation. But Joey and Heroman run in just in the nick of time to save them. It`s time for the battle between the two powerhouses, Kogorr and Heroman, to get started!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>539944</identifier>
<identifier>heroman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="118275" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アライブ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Alive</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Alive</title>
<summary>Joey can`t stand after taking a serious hit from Kogorr. Heroman, seeing Joey in such a state, unleashes a power that hasn`t been seen before. It`s the power of him going out of control. Dr. Minami stands ready to stop the sphere, seemingly confident. But his aim isn`t really to stop the sphere, that`s just step one. With all the peoples of the world`s fate on the line, humanity`s battle with the Skrugg reaches its conclusion!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>539946</identifier>
<identifier>heroman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="118276" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アプローチ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Approach</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Approach</title>
<summary>Three months after the battle with the Skrugg, peace has returned to Center City. Joey`s busy with his part-time work having doubled, and everyone is happily working on the reconstruction. Everyone except Lina, who lost her smile after having to part for eternity with her brother Will. Lina tries to get over her sadness by asking Joey out on a date. But just as it`s hard for her to express her feelings, some people end up getting in the way!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>539948</identifier>
<identifier>heroman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="118661" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">メナス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Menace</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Menace</title>
<summary>The United States government fears that the "Ghost" which is helping the reconstruction of Center City in the shadows has something to do with the Skrugg. Special Agent Hughes of the NIA, an agency that reports directly to the President, tries to come up with a way to meet this Ghost in person. Joey and Heroman are slowly being tracked down... About that time, a mysterious girl wielding a base shows up on Joey`s doorstep. It has been a while since Joey has seen her, and it is the start of his nightmare...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>539950</identifier>
<identifier>heroman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="118780" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ストーカーズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stalkers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Stalkers</title>
<summary>Joey and Lina are on that all important "first date." Both are young and innocent, and they have fun going shopping and playing on the beach. But from underneath that smooth surface lies a bunch up to no good. Psy, Denton, plus Joey`s sister Holly who came to break up the date, all hang over the proceedings like dark clouds. Joey does his best to get through the various difficulties and let Lina have a good time on their date, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>539952</identifier>
<identifier>heroman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="118852" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">リヴォルト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Revolt</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Revolt</title>
<summary>Joey is escaping alone in the forest, separated from his friends, and before him appears Hughes, the regular from Hilly`s coffee shop.  When he reveals his true identity, he asks Joey to talk. Joey is cautious at first, but his sincerity begins to... At the same time, Minami is seaching for Heroman, and starts going wild with the MR-1 to settle his grudge. With the attack headed toward Joey, finally the fated battle between Minami and Heroman begins!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543006</identifier>
<identifier>heroman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="118853" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ビリーガー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beleaguer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Beleaguer</title>
<summary>Joey and the gang successfully escaped from Center City, and continue heading to an acquaintance of Prof. Denton`s in Nevada. Heroman should be a hero that saved the world, but instead is being chased by the United States government, and Joey is worried. Joey ends up contacting Lina, but that gives away their location to Hughes and they are cornered. Without any place left to run, the others volunteer to stand up in order to protect Joey and Heroman...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543004</identifier>
<identifier>heroman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="118854" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゲッタウェイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Getaway</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Getaway</title>
<summary>Joey fully enjoyed himself on his date with Lina. But that blissful time was overturned in an instant with an emergency evacuation call from Prof. Denton. Joey hurries to meet up with Psy and Denton, where he learns that the government has officially labeled Heroman as a remnant of the Skrugg. The way that the truth has been bent and distorted is nearly unbearable for them. At the same time, they decide to make a break for it away from Center City while it`s being completely staked out by checkpoints...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>542850</identifier>
<identifier>heroman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="119660" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">デシジョン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Decision</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Decision</title>
<summary>Dr. Minami stubbornly continues to attack Heroman, and over the long battle Heroman and Joey`s stamina begins to fade. The fierce battle ends up at a dam, but Minami continues his attack, and begins to destroy it. The battle becomes extremely difficult for Heroman as he tries to fight while protecting the dam at the same time. Heroman continues to use his own body as a shield in the face of Minami`s indiscriminate attacks, until...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543008</identifier>
<identifier>heroman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="119959" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">レガシー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Legacy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Legacy</title>
<summary>Lately a number of research labs have been attacked in a series of incidents. Denton tells Joey and Psy that he believes the one thing that connects them all is the Skrugg. While feeling the dread of having to deal with the Skrugg again, they come up with a plan to lure out the culprit.  Fully prepared, Joey waits for the attack, when they suddenly appear with a bang! Who shows up but someone entirely unexpected! What is their true identity? What is their motive?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543010</identifier>
<identifier>heroman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="120109" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">セパレーション</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Separation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Separation</title>
<summary>Hughes arranges for Joey and the gang to go to a government owned, uninhabited island. Without any prying eyes, Heroman and the others spend a pleasant summer vacation. When night falls, they start telling ghost stories, of course, and according to Psy, the island is cursed by a demon. While he`s telling the story, strange things matching the story happen one after another... Joey and the others may be about to experience a true fright while trapped on the island!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543012</identifier>
<identifier>heroman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="120274" update="2010-07-23">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-06-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120275" update="2010-07-23">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-04-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120276" update="2010-07-23">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-06-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120277" update="2010-07-23">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-04-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120461" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サバイバル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Survival</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Survival</title>
<summary>The island that Joey and the others are visiting is being overrun with a mysterious life form! Joey and Lina begin to search deep into the jungle to find Heroman and the rest of the gang, and they come across Heroman who`s been caught by the life form and can`t move! Joey`s always been saved by Heroman before, but this time it`s his turn to do the saving, and then to find the origin of this creature and face it down!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543014</identifier>
<identifier>heroman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="120702" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミッシング</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Missing</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Missing</title>
<summary>Professor Denton is investigating a string of abductions that have been occurring in Center City for the past month, from cows to dogs and now even humans! After announcing he`s figured something out he goes missing as well, so Joey and Psy start to look for him.  Unfortunately, Holly decides to tag along and ends up taking over the entire investigation... Will they find out the true identity of the culprit behind the abductions, or just get dragged around by Holly as she plays around?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543016</identifier>
<identifier>heroman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="121153" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エモーション</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Emotion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Emotion</title>
<summary>With Professor Denton missing, and now Holly kidnapped, Joey and Psy turn to the NIA for help finding the identity of the abductor. But Joey can`t help feeling he seemed an awful lot like Will... With the prospect of having to fight Lina`s brother looming, Joey and Psy head off in search of their friends, but the truth they find is even more disturbing...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543018</identifier>
<identifier>heroman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="121334" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">メモリーズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Memories</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Memories</title>
<summary>After Psy is injured, Joey tries to search for answers about what being a hero really means. He always looked up to his dad, who sacrificed himself in a coal mining accident to save a great number of people, and everyone in the town holds Brian Carter Jones as a hero to be looked up to. Except for Holly, that is. Holly asks Joey to answer the question "What is a hero?" and Joey tries to find the answer. Meanwhile, Will pays a visit to Lina, and warns her to stay away from Joey...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543020</identifier>
<identifier>heroman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="121393" update="2010-08-23">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Third War Arc Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121448" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ソルティ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sortie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sortie</title>
<summary>It`s discovered that the recent incidents are all connected to the legacy of the Skrugg, so Joey and the others immediately start looking into the existence of the Skrugg remnants. However, the Skrugg`s secret plan has already started, and they reveal themselves to mankind, by attacking the White House! Faced with mysterious plant-like creatures spreading destruction surrounding the White House, Joey and the gang prepare to fight, knowing that the fate of the world hangs in the balance.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543022</identifier>
<identifier>heroman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="121698" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">リザレクション</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Resurrection</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Resurrection</title>
<summary>A fierce battle unfolds as Joey and Heroman make their way into the heart of the Skrugg`s territory. With the government unable to mount an all-out attack while the President`s safety is still in question, they`re putting all their hopes on those two`s battle. Just then, Keisha`s news helicopter appears and starts broadcasting the situation to the world. The image of Heroman and a single boy fighting alongside him... Then, at the epicenter of the enemy`s stronghold, the greatest foe Joey has ever faced is reborn...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543024</identifier>
<identifier>heroman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="122047" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クライシス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crisis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Crisis</title>
<summary>The Skrugg`s real aim was to resurrect their leader, Kogorr. Joey and Heroman bravely stand up before their greatest foe, reborn once again. But the rebirth of Kogorr is merely a prologue to the crisis that befalls them. At the same time, Denton and the others head toward the White House in the MR-1. With all the friends gathering together, Joey and Heroman put everything on the line to break through this worst possible situation, but... The story rushes toward its climax!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543026</identifier>
<identifier>heroman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="122428" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フェイス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Faith</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Faith</title>
<summary>A boy who looked up to heroes met "Heroman" and overcame countless battles and crises. As the world heads toward its end, a single boy, this "Joey Jones", stands up against mankind`s greatest foe, Kogorr. To protect the world, and his friends, Joey makes a firm decision. Does his fierce gaze peer toward a sparkling future, or something else... Now is when a true hero is born!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543028</identifier>
<identifier>heroman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="125050" update="2010-11-15">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2010-09-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">短篇1 ポーテント</title>
<title xml:lang="en">EX-1 Portent</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tanpen 1: Portent</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126382" update="2010-12-27">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2010-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">短篇2 プロミス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">EX-2 Promise</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tanpen 2: Promise</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129103" update="2011-05-17">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2011-03-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">短篇3 モノローグ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">EX-3 Monologue</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tanpen 3: Monologue</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130153" update="2011-05-14">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video "Boku no Te wa Kimi no Tame ni"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130154" update="2011-05-14">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video "Missing"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130155" update="2011-05-14">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video "Calling"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130156" update="2011-05-14">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video "Joey and Heroman"</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
