<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7413" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>51</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-04-04</startdate>
<enddate>2011-03-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Himechan! Otogitic Idol Lil`Pri</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Hime Chen! Otogi Chikku Idol Lilpri</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">变身!公主偶像</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ひめチェン! おとぎちっくアイドル リルぷりっ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Spellbound! Magical Princess Lil`Pri</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">变身! 偶像公主</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="102" approval="1" total="5">Cardcaptor Sakura</anime>
<anime id="2859" approval="1" total="3">Otogi-Juushi Akazukin (2006)</anime>
<anime id="13309" approval="1" total="3">Marchen Madchen</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>https://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/lilpri/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1178" type="Original Work">Sega</name>
<name id="1082" type="Original Work">Shogakukan</name>
<name id="3012" type="Character Design">Watanabe Atsuko</name>
<name id="2178" type="Series Composition">Yamada Yuka</name>
<name id="900" type="Animation Work">Telecom Animation Film</name>
<name id="4496" type="Direction">Moriwaki Makoto</name>
<name id="3012" type="Chief Animation Direction">Watanabe Atsuko</name>
<name id="38896" type="Music">Muramatsu Takatsugu</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on Lilpri: Yubi Puru Hime Chen! trading card arcade game.
Various reports of irregularities are flooding in from all corners of Fairytale Kingdom. The truth is, Fairytale Kingdom is on the verge of destruction! This is because the happiness within peoples` hearts, the "Happiness Tone", is disappearing. The only ones who can restore the Happiness Tone are the legendary Princesses...
The queen dispatches three "Magic Pets" to the human world. Upon arrival, at a concert held by the popular idol, Wish, the Magic Pets meet three young girls who have within them the power to become Princesses.
~ translated and adapted from the official Japanese site by Cranston</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="118">3.53</permanent>
<temporary count="119">5.62</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>234357.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11249</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8206</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4665</identifier>
<identifier>xpywfm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/lilpri/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>リルぷりっ#.E3.83.86.E3.83.AC.E3.83.93.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1910</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>336373</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12599</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2566</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2010/lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11662</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="157" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-15">
<name>playing violin</name>
<description>The violin is a string instrument, usually with four strings tuned in perfect fifths. It is the smallest, highest-pitched member of the violin family of string instruments, which includes the viola and cello.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1063" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-11">
<name>elementary school</name>
<description>The term elementary school is used in some countries for schools where children from the age of about five receive primary education.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1155" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-28">
<name>mermaid</name>
<description>A creature that is half-human (usually the upper body) and half-fish (usually the lower body). A male mermaid is called merman (but they can appear under many different names). Since mermaids are often confused with Sirens in media, they may posses special abilities akin to Sirens such as enchanting voice (on the other hand Sirens are often being portrayed as mermaids). Some mermaids might be able to transform their whole body into human (which is not surprising since mermaids are often associated with the "want to become human" theme) and that should not disqualify them from getting this tag.</description>
<picurl>209970.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1835" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-17">
<name>animal sidekick</name>
<description>Every mahou shoujo anime needs them, the cute little critters that are supposed to help the protagonists but in reality are nothing but useless bystanders most often abused for gags. Kids love them but they can also often turn into an annoyance.</description>
<picurl>227760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1846" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>kodomo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word kodomo refers to a children`s audience roughly for the ages 12 and younger. In Japanese, the word means simply "child", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1876" parentid="2794" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>musical band</name>
<description>A musical ensemble also known as a music(al) group or music(al) band is a group of people who perform instrumental or vocal music, typically known by a distinct name.</description>
<picurl>10249.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2343" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-17">
<name>ojou-sama laugh</name>
<description>A type of haughty laughter typical of rich young girls, as well as older rich women. Generally sounds like a high-pitched "OHOHOHOHOHOHO".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2406" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-13">
<name>talking animal</name>
<description>Talking animals are a common theme in mythology and folk tales, as well as children`s literature. Fictional talking creatures often are anthropomorphic, possessing human-like qualities but appearing as a creature. An animal that only knows how to say its name (for example, 99.9% of all http://anidb.net/t2493 [Pokemon]), are not talking animals.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3055" parentid="3876" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>fairy tale</name>
<description>This anime is either based on or contains parts of fairy tales. Usually those parts are highly modified or twisted when compared with the original source.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3170" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-10">
<name>occupation and career</name>
<description>The kind of anime which shows the career of a character, usually from the beginning.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3233" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-09-13">
<name>cooking curry</name>
<description>Japanese curry, usually eaten as curry rice, and often pickled vegetables, served on the same plate and eaten with a spoon, is one of the most popular dishes in Japan, where people eat it 125 times a year according to a survey made in 2005.
As such Japanese series will often devote a whole episode to the characters cooking and eating curry dishes.</description>
<picurl>160828.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3876" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>folklore</name>
<description>Folklore, or simply Lore, are the traditions of a culture, subculture, or group, in the form of legends, music, proverbs, jokes, popular beliefs, fairy tales, stories, tall tales and customs. In usage, there is a continuum between folklore and mythology.
Folklore is generally divided into four areas of study: physical artifacts, transmissible entities and stories, culture and technologies, and behaviors and rituals.
[From Wikipedia]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3971" parentid="3170" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-07-04">
<name>entertainment industry</name>
<description>The show depicts how the entertainment industry works and how the main protagonists strive to cope with the sudden change to fame. At times this can be a very ugly sight indeed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4057" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-19">
<name>magical creatures</name>
<description>Magical creatures are beings associated with a fantasy setting, thus do not exist in reality. Apparently they were "created of" or "powered by" magic. An incantation may have brought them into existence.
Examples: A legendary creature, a mythological or folkloric creature, a fairy or demon, ...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5768" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>intact family</name>
<description>The main character`s family is a so-called "nuclear family". Wherein both parents are alive and present in his or her life. This is actually relatively rare for anime, where "parental abandonment" is the norm.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5882" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>secret identity</name>
<description>The (usually main) protagonist has a secret identity that he or she desperately tries to keep secret.
This can lead to all sorts of amusing misunderstandings, thus is used as comedy element in some anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6078" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-23">
<name>gotta catch them all</name>
<description>A typical plot or sub-plot for many shows. Either the cast or somebody else, that being often the main antagonist, embarks on a quest to collect things, shiny things. Things that are said to grant simple wishes or even do miracles like bringing people back to life, destroying the whole world, galaxy, universe and in rare cases turning the hero into the greatest Pokemon Master. Those things can be weapons, lost technology, magical artefacts, pieces of a giant magical artefact and in some cases even people or little critters.
The point is, there`s stuff to collect!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6137" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-09">
<name>catchphrase</name>
<description>A catchphrase is a sound, word or phrase commonly used by a person. That may be simply out of habit, or in an attempt to deliver some form of image, like that of cuteness. In fiction, characters often use catchphrases as a way to deliver specific personality traits. Examples include Otohime Mutsumi`s "ara ara" in Love Hina, Yang Wenli`s "yare yare" in Legend of the Galactic Heroes, Misuzu`s "gao" in AIR, Sakura`s "hoe" in Card Captor Sakura, Suiseiseki`s "desu" in Rozen Maiden, and Ayu`s "uguu" in Kanon (as well as several other characters in the same show).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="16559" type="main character in" update="2011-10-20">
<rating votes="2">3.76</rating>
<name>Yukimori Ringo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70957.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10880" picture="39048.jpg">Wada Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16560" type="main character in" update="2011-10-20">
<rating votes="2">3.76</rating>
<name>Takashiru Reira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70960.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10881" picture="41032.jpg">Maeda Yuuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16561" type="main character in" update="2011-10-20">
<rating votes="2">3.76</rating>
<name>Sasahara Natsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70962.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10879" picture="39046.jpg">Fukuda Kanon</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18575" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-29">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Sei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68658.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1436" picture="18822.jpg">Takagi Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18576" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-29">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Dai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68659.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11035" picture="39690.jpg">Nakatsukasa Yuuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18577" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-29">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Ryoku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68660.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42" picture="155105.jpg">Hayamizu Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18578" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-13">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Chris</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68661.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="174" picture="41158.jpg">Kakihara Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18579" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-11">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Wish</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53224.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="174" picture="41158.jpg">Kakihara Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18580" type="appears in" update="2011-04-12">
<name>Kawabe Tsugumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69661.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="357" picture="32000.jpg">Shintani Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18581" type="appears in" update="2011-04-12">
<name>Oka Masaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69704.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18582" type="appears in" update="2011-04-12">
<name>Saotome Koutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69706.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3794" picture="38865.jpg">Kumai Motoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18583" type="appears in" update="2010-10-11">
<name>Kobayashi Yukie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="542" picture="60897.jpg">Doi Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18584" type="appears in" update="2010-10-11">
<name>Yuuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3198" picture="160468.jpg">Shimamura Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18585" type="appears in" update="2010-06-07">
<name>Mike</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="19121" picture="156854.jpg">Oda Toshimitsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18586" type="appears in" update="2010-06-07">
<name>Hayata</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="320" picture="66660.jpg">Kobayashi Yumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18587" type="appears in" update="2011-04-12">
<name>Kakeru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69663.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4762" picture="201584.jpg">Kodaira Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18588" type="appears in" update="2010-10-11">
<name>Ayane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="12352" picture="130106.jpg">Hirata Mana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18589" type="appears in" update="2011-04-12">
<name>Ran</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69703.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3198" picture="160468.jpg">Shimamura Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18590" type="appears in" update="2011-04-12">
<name>Hikaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69705.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19121" picture="156854.jpg">Oda Toshimitsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18591" type="appears in" update="2011-04-03">
<name>Atsui Tarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68949.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18592" type="appears in" update="2011-04-12">
<name>Mamoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69662.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="690" picture="187038.jpg">Higa Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18593" type="appears in" update="2010-10-11">
<name>Takeshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="9599" picture="222797.jpg">Aoyama Touko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37901" type="main character in" update="2011-10-20">
<rating votes="2">3.76</rating>
<name>Shirayukihime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70952.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10880" picture="39048.jpg">Wada Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37902" type="main character in" update="2011-10-20">
<rating votes="2">3.26</rating>
<name>Cinderella-hime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70959.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10881" picture="41032.jpg">Maeda Yuuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37903" type="main character in" update="2011-10-20">
<rating votes="2">3.76</rating>
<name>Kaguya-hime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70961.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10879" picture="39046.jpg">Fukuda Kanon</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="117429" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">プリンセスみーつけた☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Found The Princesses Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Princess Miitsuketa Pri!</title>
<summary>Yukimori Ringo is an energetic elementary school girl. Today she is helping her father sell apple pies at the concert hall where Wish’s concert is being held. Ringo adores Wish. As Ringo could not get a ticket, she tries to bring a gift apple pie to Wish, but the security personnel through her out. Despite all that, she still manages to get in somehow and meets Sasahara Natsuki and Takashiro Leila. Then three strange animals appear…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>542474</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117430" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔ペット大失敗☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ma-pets` Big Mistake Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ma Pet Daishippai Pri!</title>
<summary>Ringo’s family runs a super popular apple pie store. The apple pies Ringo’s father makes are so delicious that they quickly sell out. Today, they out in a flash again, so her father starts preparing for the next day. Meanwhile, Ringo, Leila, Natsuki, the Ma-Pets Sei, Dai, and Ryoku are discussing the events from the day before. After finishing some of the work, Sei goes in the kitchen to get a drink of water. Nobody is in the kitchen, but the many apple pies for tomorrow are there. Sei tries his best to hold back his desire to devour them, but the smell and sight is quite overwhelming…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>542524</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117560" update="2010-04-09">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-04-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117561" update="2010-11-30">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-04-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117636" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひめさまは忘れんぼ☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Princess is Forgetful Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hime-sama wa Wasurenbo Pri!</title>
<summary>Atsui Tarou is Ringo’s teacher. Today he’s already very intense from the beginning and suggests “Making something that will be the class’s trademark for tomorrow’s excursion!” However, none of the students pay attention to him. But he does not give up. His next suggestion is to stitch all of their handkerchiefs together to make a flag. However, all the students just leave their handkerchiefs and go home. After seeing that, Ringo, Leila, and Natsuki offer their help, but he insists that he has been “entrusted with their hearts” and begins to sew the handkerchiefs together. After a while, Leila goes back to the class room to pick something up she forgot. That’s when she sees the flag Mr. Atsui has made; it’s in tatters, about to fall apart on its own, so Leila decides to take it home to fix it, but…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>542526</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117832" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お師匠さまがやってきた☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Master Arrives Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oshishou-sama ga Yattekita Pri!</title>
<summary>Ringo and Leila visit Natsuki’s house and run into Natsuki’s grandfather and grandmother. Apparently they both have to leave on sudden business. Natsuki’s grandmother tells her that a master of dance will come by to pick up some fabric. Natsuki is the daughter of a dry goods merchant, and her parents are working abroad. That’s why Natsuki is living with her grandparents. While Natsuki is telling this story, someone calls at the front door. When Natsuki rushes to the front door, the master of dance, Kobayashi Sachie, is waiting there. Even though Natsuki properly greets her, she is met with a “Hah!” and a lesson in manners!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>542616</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117960" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">まいごで大さわぎ☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lost and in Big Trouble! Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maigo de Oosawagi Pri!</title>
<summary>Ringo, Leila, and Natsuki are at the department store. They came to see Wish’s giant poster. The Ma-pets Sei, Dai, and Ryoku are apparently in awe during their first visit to a department store. But suddenly Ryoku cries out! When everybody turns around, they see an energetic boy waving Ryoku around by his tail! Natsuki rushes to safe Ryoku. The boy’s name is Hayata, and it looks like he is lost. Since they can’t find his mother in the vicinity, the girls take him to the Lost Children Center. But when they try to give him up, they realize that he has disappeared again…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>542618</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="118060" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">プリンセス修行だよヨ☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Princess Training! Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Princess Shuugyou da yo yo Pri!</title>
<summary>The queen of Fairyland looks up at the sky with a sad expression. She is worried that collecting Happiness Tones is not going that well. Still, the queen is confident that Lil’Pri is doing their best and smiles. Meanwhile, Ringo, Leila, and Natsuki are busy watching a comedy show on TV. When a commercial with Wish comes on, they lose themselves. Even the Ma-pets who are supposed to watch over them are totally relaxed. That’s when the girl’s wands start glowing. The Ma-pets realize that they have more important business, namely “Making people happy and saving Fairyland!” The Ma-pets are full of passion and tell the girls that they have to undergo training to up their princess powers!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>542620</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="118246" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おケイコやーめた☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Quit Training! Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Okeiko Yameta Pri!</title>
<summary>Ringo’s class mate, Saotome Koutarou, missed a day of school because of a cold. However, rumor has it that he stayed home to practice for a violin recital. On their way home, Ringo and her friends keep talking about Saotome. When someone mentions that he’s aiming to become a pro, they get in a frenzy and say “He’ll be a celebrity!” and “We should get autographs while we still can!”. But soon they realize that an unfamiliar voice has joined the conversation. The mysterious rabbit who had helped them before was back. His name is “Chris”. Chris says that he’s come from Fairy Land, and that he will help Lil’Pri gather Happiness Tones. Then Chris pulls something out from a bush and gives it to Ringo. That something was a violin case with the name “Saotome” on it.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>542622</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="118366" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">五七五でラブラブ☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lovey-Dovey in Haiku Form! Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Go-shichi-go de Love-love Pri!</title>
<summary>The Ma-pet Sei is in love with the canary Ran. Sei tries everything in his repertoire to make Ran fall for him, but for some reason she is not receptive. Ringo and her friends watch over his efforts. They were also curious about the old man who kept sighing. His name is Oka Masaki and he runs a Haiku club in the neighborhood. Apparently the reason that Ran is so cold is because of him. The truth is that Oka is having trouble coming up with a good Haiku. According to him, Ran sings with her beautiful voice when you recite a good Haiku to her, but that hasn’t happened in some time…  In order to cheer him up, Ringo and her friends decide to help him come up with a Haiku. Will they ever hear Ran sing again? And what about Sei’s love?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>542516</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="118367" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぷりぷりサッカー☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PriPri Soccer! Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Puripuri Soccer Pri!</title>
<summary>One day, Natsuki’s friend Takeshi asks her to help out his soccer team, the “Hanasaki Kickers”, by playing in a match for them. Apparently his team has never won a game. On top of that, they will disband the team after this next match, so they don’t want to lose under any circumstances. Even then, Natsumi tries to refuse by saying that “It’s none of my business”. But when the other players laugh at the prospect of having a girl help them out, she unleashes her athletic prowess and takes the boys down a notch. And she ends up agreeing to help out… The day of the match is already near; however, one of the players, Mamoru, asks Natsuki to withdraw from the match.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>542514</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="118368" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-05-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Wishをおいかけろ☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chase After Wish! Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wish o Oikakero Pri!</title>
<summary>Ringo and her friends have a face-off with Tsugumi, another Wish fan, in front of a CD store. The reason for this incident is that neither could get the last handshake ticket for Wish. A heated argument ensues: “It’s your fault that I can’t meet Wish!” “That’s our line!”. The argument derails and they end up starting a competition to see who can get Wish’s autograph first. They all try different methods to get his autograph, however, it’s not as easy as they think. Depressed, Tsugumi sighs: “Wish…  I only have two more days…”. Apparently Tsugumi has a reason why she absolutely has to get Wish’s autograph…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>542624</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="118710" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ビッグなシンデレラ☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Big Cinderella! Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Big na Cinderella Pri!</title>
<summary>A female neighborhood friend of Leila has decided to get married. Leila was obviously invited to the wedding, but she also wanted Ringo and Natsuki to come to the ceremony. “Why us?” is their first reaction, but then the reason becomes apparent: the groom’s their teacher Mr. Atsui! He wants Ringo and Natsuki to be the bride’s veil girls and entrusted Leila with the important task of delivering the bride’s present. What kind of present is it? To answer that, Mr. Atsui shows the girls a picture of him and a giant shoe. The shoe is so big that the girls are blown away. But he says that it fits the bride perfectly…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>542518</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="118855" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おとぎの国にきちゃった☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We`ve Come to Fairyland Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otogi no Kuni ni Kichatta Pri!</title>
<summary>The three princesses used their last card and came to Fairy Land. They look on with desolate faces as the Ma-Pets confess to the Queen that they`ve run out of cards.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>542852</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="118856" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さいごのひめチェン? ☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Final Princess Change? Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo no Himechan? Pri!</title>
<summary>Lil’Pri are known as the mysterious stars. Ringo, Leila, and Natsuki are surprised by the unexpected attention but agree to “Try even harder to make everybody happy”. Sei, Dai, and Ryoku seem to be happy about the decision. But then they realize that only one of the princess change cards crucial for the transformation is left! Ringo and her friends are worried that they can only do the princess change one more time. That’s when Chris appears and delivers them a message from Wish. The message states that he wants them to appear on his show once again. The girls only have one card left, so Ringo and her friends get psyched to use the last card to amass a wealth of happiness tones and save Fairy Land in one last concerted effort, but…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>542522</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="118857" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">世界一のアップルパイ☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The World`s Best Apple Pie Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sekaiichi no Apple Pie Pri!</title>
<summary>Ringo and Saotome are having an argument. When Ringo says that “My father’s apple pies are the best in the world”, Saotome replies that being the best is not that easy. Ringo counters by saying that her father ‘s are still the best, so Saotome ups the ante by saying that he will accept her claim if her father wins the apple pie contest. After Ringo gets back, she immediately asks her father to participate in the apple pie contest. However, no matter how many times she implores him, he won’t agree to participate. On the next day, when Ringo tells her friends that her father won’t compete, Saotome shows up and starts another argument. He claims that Ringo’s father had no confidence and ran. So Ringo can’t help herself and says that her “Father will definitely compete!”.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>542520</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="119528" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">マジ? まじマジック☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Really? Is it Magic Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maji? Maji Magic Pri!</title>
<summary>The girls` classmate, Tenko Okamoto, is a big fan of magic. She leaves to go see a world-famous magician and hijinks ensue,
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>542854</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="119845" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">マーメイド・リリちゃん☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mermaid-Lili Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mermain Lili-chan Pri!</title>
<summary>Ringo, Leila, and Natsuki are on their way to the beach until they are surprised by Lili who is a mermaid that appears before their eyes.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>542858</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="119846" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハッピーシューズで発表会☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Happy Shoes and the Release Event Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Happy Shoes de Happyoukai Pri!</title>
<summary>Ringo and the girls attend a release party at Crystal Shoes, the store where Leila`s father works. Kumi Ochiai takes the girls in where they witness Wish in mid-rehearsal.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>542856</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="120368" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おかえり, レイラパパ☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome Home, Leila`s Dad Pri!</title>
<summary>Leila`s father, Marco Paparoncino, runs the Crystal Shoes store. He comes back from overseas. He needs Lil` Pri`s help to find the model in a poster for a new pair of boots.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>542860</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="120552" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏の思い出とんじゃビー! ☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Off We Go! Summer Memories Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu no Omoide Pri!</title>
<summary>Summer vacation is almost over. Ringo and the girls are discussing the homework that Mr. Atsui issued. They were told to create "hot and intense memories." As the three princesses discuss what to do to achieve this, a classmate shows up. She`s a fashionable girl named Momoka Hoshino.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543058</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="120553" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひめさまがおかあさま☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Princess is the Mother Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hime-sama ga Okaa-sama Pri!</title>
<summary>Ringo`s mother has to look after Ai, the daughter of her good friend, Tomoko. Ringo is so happy that she gets to play big sister with such a cute baby.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543056</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="120554" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">思いだせ! 魔ペット☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Remember! Ma-Pets Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omoidase! Ma Pet Pri!</title>
<summary>Today is the concern with Wish. Ringo and the girls are gleefully practicing singing in the park. The Ma-Pets are really getting into supporting the princesses, when...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543054</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="120555" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">きもだめしだゾーッ☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Test of Courage Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimodameshida Zoutsu Pri!</title>
<summary>Nighttime during summer break. The girls head to school for a test of courage. They end up doing it together, all 5 of them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543042</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="121537" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おとぎの国の王子さま☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Prince of Fairy Land Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otogi no Kuni no Ouji-sama Pri!</title>
<summary>The girls flee and make it back to Fairlyland. They reunite with the Queen, but then...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543066</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="121538" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひみつがバレちゃった☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Secret`s Out Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Himitsu ga Bare Chatta Pri!</title>
<summary>Ringo, Leila, and Mizuki are practicing their song at Wish`s stage at night.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543064</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="121539" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">モテモテかぐやひめ☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Popular Princess Kaguya Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Motemote Kaguya Hime Pri!</title>
<summary>Ringo and Leila are invited to a party at Natsuki`s house. This party has a long tradition where someone`s groom is decided for them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543062</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="121540" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おかしの家が落ちてきた☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Gingerbread House Fell From The Sky Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Okashi no ie ga Ochi Tekita Pri!</title>
<summary>During the night a mysterious house appears to fall from the sky, investigating the house the girls believe the owner to be a witch!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543060</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="122716" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-10-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">一寸法師でござるよ☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The One-Inch Boy Pri!</title>
<summary>Ringo and the others are having a picnic in the park when a tear drops the One-Inch Boy and his wife Momiji from Fairy Land.
On their way down, the two begin quarreling.
The quarrel worsens and the girls are unable to do anything. 
The cause of this is One-Inch Boy seems to have become a complete slacker. 
Once always practicing his sword, he now just idles.
As a result, he`s become fat and can`t ride his bowl boat.
On top of that, he always has a comeback to whatever is said.
Momiji can no longer take it and having reached her limit, explodes in anger!
The girls are shocked by this when the Magic Mallet comes tumbling down...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>560140</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="122717" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-10-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">委員長はだれがいーんでちょう☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Who`s a Good Fit For The Student Body Prez Pri!</title>
<summary>The girls` class has to decide on a class representative for the second semester. The first semester class representative, Tachibana Mamiko, instantly raises her hand as a candidate. However, the entire class is in a state of unease. The reason? Mamiko is a quick to nag and really strict class representative who is feared and called Nag-iko.  Everyone thinks her continuing as class representative spells trouble.  Suddenly, Saotome nominates Ringo for class representative; a move that surprises Ringo. Ringo claims her being class rep is impossible, but the class is so excited that they won`t listen to her.   Seeing the situation, Mr. Atsui proposes to let Ringo be class rep for three days as a test.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>560126</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="122718" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-10-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">いたずら魔ペット, ビビでち☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bibi, the Prankster Ma-Pet Arrives Pri!</title>
<summary>A talking cat appears before Chris. Its name is Vivi. It`s a Ma-Pet from Fairy Land. People are on edge about what Vivi will, but when he pulls out a card, nothing really happens...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>560116</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="122719" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-10-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゆめときぼうのオムライス☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Omelet Rice of Hopes and Dreams Pri!</title>
<summary>Wish greets the girls as they return from Fairy Land. Both the girls and Wish are happy to see the other safe and sound. They end up asking questions and hear Wish`s reason for becoming an idol.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>560112</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="122720" update="2010-09-26">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-09-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122721" update="2010-11-30">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-09-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124564" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔法カードで Oh!たいへん☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Oh No! Trouble With the Magic Card Pri!</title>
<summary>To return Prince Chris to his former self, Vivi uses her cards of fortune.  The cards end up showing Vivi`s mistress, the Keeper of the Jewels. Thinking the Ultimate Shine is at her mistress`, she returns to the house and, just as the fortune says, finds a card that is shining.  Vivi returns to the human world and heads straight for Chris.  However, the card she is holding suddenly glows and flies away saying "Liar, liar."  What Vivi was actually holding was the Liar Liar card which forces whatever it is attached to to lie. Vivi chases after the card to catch it, but the card runs through the entire town forcing people to tell lies. Finally, it attaches itself to Natsuki, who hates lies...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>560152</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="124565" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひめさまげきじょう☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Princess Play Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hime-sama Gekijou Pri!</title>
<summary>The girls` class decides to do a play for the school arts festival. However, when discussing what kind of play they want to do, the class is split and unable to come to a consensus. Suddenly, Saotome stands up and says they should do a play where he is the lead role.  The title is "Go Go Hero Saotome" and the last scene has the hero, Saotome, and the heroine kissing.  Among the class`s displeasure, Leila is having fun thinking up the costumes for the hero and heroine. Meanwhile, the class continues and finally gets to the point of deciding on who will play the heroine, the role which nobody wants to take. Out of nowhere, Leila raises her hand and says she will do it, surprising everybody. It turns out she had mistakenly thought they were deciding on who would make the costumes. Now unable to turn it down, Leila has to be the heroine...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>560132</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="124566" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぷりぷりキューピッド ☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pri-Pri Cupid, Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pri-Pri Cupid, Pri!</title>
<summary>Youichi has been trying to give a love letter to his middle school classmate Sayaka, but always fails.  Ringo and the girls see this and want to help make his confession a success. However, Ringo and Natsuki get into a fight over how to help him.  Natsuki dislikes Ringo`s method of trying to teach him how to be more popular with girls, using her favorite girl`s comics as an example. As hard as Leila tries to stop the fighting, Ringo and Natsuki won`t make up and things only gets worse.  Even Chris warns them that if their feelings cannot become one, they cannot become Lil` Pri and can`t save Fairy Land. Will Ringo and Natsuki be able to make up?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>560158</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="124567" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とどけ, リルぷりっの歌☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Resound, Lilpris` Song Pri!</title>
<summary>Wish has invited Ringo, Leila and Natsuki to be on a live TV music program.  The girls are excited to see Wish and other performers who they`ve only seen on TV rehearse right before them.  Wish`s rehearsal finishes and it`s Lil` Pri turn.  The girls take the stage as Wish watches from a corner.  As they finally start singing, the studio lights suddenly go out leaving them in the dark.  After a short time, the lights come back on and a woman faces and walks toward Lil` Pri.  Her name is Yuuko Nakajou, an important figure known as the Princess of Enka.  Yuuko approaches with an incredible aura, the intensity of which has the girls completely frightened.  What Yuuko wants with the girls is...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>560150</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="124568" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-10-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">小さな魔女みつけたでち☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Spy a Tiny Witch Pri!</title>
<summary>On their way home from school, the girls run into their classmate Natsume Mahiru and her little sister Manatsu.
At close glance, Manatsu looks kinda like a witch.  
It turns out, they are going to be participating in the costume festival.
Everyone dresses up how they want and parades through the Hanasaki District.
Of course, Manatsu is going as a witch.  Mahiru is going dressed as her favorite, a vampire.
Hearing this, Ringo and the others decide to join in since it sounds fun. 
However, Mahiru is not very good at making costumes.
Ringo proposes that they all make the costumes together while learning from Leila, who is good at sewing.
They all gather at Leila`s house and get to work making costumes.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>560144</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="125572" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-12-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おとぎの国の大パーティー☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Huge Party in Fairy Land Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otogi no Kuni no Dai Party Pri!</title>
<summary>Ringo and the others have come to Fairy Land. However, something seems different from normal. It turns out there is a Countdown Party at the Queen`s Castle today. In Fairy Land, they hold a giant party to welcome to the new year as it only begins after Ikkuru and Kukkuru, the fairy of the year past and the fairy of the coming year, join hands. After greeting the girls, the Queen takes them to visit Ikkuru. Upon arriving at Ikkuru`s room, the girls are shocked. The furnishings in Ikkuru`s room are strewn everywhere and it is littered with junk while Ikkuru is sprawled out and looking bored. It seems the state of the room is causing Ikkuru to sulk. The Queen tells the girls that in this state, Ikkuru might not show up at the Countdown Party.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>560172</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="125573" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-12-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">花咲町のサンタさん☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Santa Claus From Hanasaki Town Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hanasaki jou no Santa-san Pri!</title>
<summary>Ringo, Leila, and Natsuki have come to the Hanasaki Shopping District, where they are preparing for Christmas. At the Shopping District, there is an old man in a Santa suit handing out fliers for the Christmas sale. His name is Ono Santarou and during the Christmas season, he hands out candy to children, does funny dances, and makes gags.  His performance is enjoyed by the kids and he`s really popular. The girls looked forward to seeing him every year as well. During the performance, there is a boy watching Santarou from the edge of the Shopping District.. This boy is his grandson, Ono Yukio. He is spotted by the girls who call out to him, but he runs away. It seems that for some reason, Yukio thinks poorly of Santarou being Santa Claus...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>560170</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="125574" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-12-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔ペットペットどこいった☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Where`d the Ma-Pet Go Pri!</title>
<summary>One day, Ringo wakes up and notices her Ma-Pet, Sei, is gone. Ringo talks with Leila and Natsuki who say that Dai and Ryoku have been gone since morning too.  The girls walk around the town searching for the Ma-Pets, but are unable to find them. They think back and wonder if they had done something wrong.  Sei was crushed when Ringo rolled over in her sleep, Dai`s crackers were taken away by Leila, and Ryoku was thrown out of the room by Natsuki for being fussy... so many possibilities come to mind. Worried, the girls go to ask Chris. Meanwhile, the Ma-Pets are walking around Hanasaki in their Halloween costume. It seems the Ma-Pets have some reason for doing this...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>560168</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="125575" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-12-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナンとカレーなアイドル☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Naan and Curry Idol Pri!</title>
<summary>After school, Ringo, Leila, and Natsuki are talking with their classmates about Mr. Atsui`s assignment, an essay about their dreams.  The others are excited as they each talk about dreams such as wanting to be a pro soccer player or taking over the world.  However, Okada silently listens to everyone. When Leila asks Okada what his dream is, he says it`s nothing big and laughs it off, but it seems Okada has a dream he wants to come true as well. While walking home that day, Okada spots an old lamp on the ground. Okada stares at the strange lamp and decides to rub it a little. Suddenly, the lamp glows and from inside the lamp, the genie Alijiji comes flying out! Alijiji tells the shocked Okada that he will grant three of his master`s wishes.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>560166</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="126396" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-01-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひめっぷりは∞むげんだい☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Princess Powers are Limitless Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hime Puri wa Mugendai, Pri!</title>
<summary>The Queen of Fairy Land tells the girls she wants to hear their new song. According to the queen, now that the girls` Princess Power has increased, they should be able to find a new song in Fairy Land. The girls bid farewell to the queen and go off searching Fairy Land for the song.  They go all over Fairy Land, but are unable to find it. The girls` vain efforts leave them completely exhausted. This is when Roo passes by carrying a bucket, a shovel, and lots of other things. Apparently Roo is on her way to tend to the flower garden. But with a huge pile of things, Roo is unstable and flying dangerously. Seeing this, the girls want to help Roo. But they also have to search for their song...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>567620</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="126397" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-01-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">カレンに白鳥ジャンプ! ☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Swan Dive Into Karen! Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Karen ni Hakuchou Jump! Pri!</title>
<summary>Ringo has gone skating with her family.  Watching her seven brothers and Sei skate, Ringo also skates around at full speed.  But while looking away, she is about to collide with the wall when a girl gallantly appears and saves her at the last second. Ringo tries to thank the girl, but the girl is the idol of the figure skating world, Karen, who skates away in a hurry.  That afternoon, Ringo and Sei are eating lunch by the by the lake when a swan suddenly appears and steals their lunch. Ringo and Sei chase after the swan. As Ringo and Sei run along the bank of the lake, they spot a depressed looking Karen watching the swans.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>567686</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="126398" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-01-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">赤ずきんちゃんいらっしゃい☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome, Red Riding Hood Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akazukin-chan Irasshai, Pri!</title>
<summary>Chris tells the girls that Little Red Riding Hood is in the human world. They quickly find her, but she becomes hungry and unable to move in no time. That is when Yamamori Azuki, a highschool student, passes by carrying a large paper bag. Azuki`s younger sister, Yamamori Botan, goes to the same kindergarten as Ringo`s brothers. Seeing the famished Little Red Riding Hood, Azuki takes a hamburger out of her bag. Little Red Riding Hood is overjoyed at the deliciousness of her first hamburger. She wants to do something in return for Azuki and is asked to help set up for her little sister`s birthday party. Meanwhile, in Fairy Land, the Big Bad Wolf is searching for Little Red Riding Hood...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>567684</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="126399" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-01-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダイちゃんダイエット☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dai`s on Diet Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai-chan Diet Pri!</title>
<summary>On the way to school with Ringo and Natsuki, Leila seems odd. She totters about while mentioning that her head is heavy and her shoulders are stiff. It`s no wonder she feels this way as riding on her head is a plump Dai. His fatness has everyone surprised.  As they comment on it, Dai pulls out a biscuit and happily devours it. It seems he isn`t aware of it at all. However, Dai has become so fat that he can no longer fit into the dollhouse. Seeing Dai like this, Sei and Ryoku are angered as he is too pitiful for a Ma-Pet. After Leila also persuades him, Dai finally decides to go on a diet . Thus, Leila and Dai`s Super Diet Plan has begun.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>567688</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="126866" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-02-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">リョク, リュウになりタイガー☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ryoku Wants to be a Dragon Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryoku, Ryuu ni Nari Tiger Pri!</title>
<summary>After getting Natsuki hurt when a small dog barks at them, Ryoku questions if he is useless to Natsuki and gets depressed. Moping by himself, Ryoku finds a partitioning screen in Natsuki`s house which has a powerful dragon and a tiger drawn on it. According to Natsuki`s grandfather, the dragon and tiger are said to have been rivals, fighting for the position of the strongest in the world since olden times. Hearing that, Ryoku is determined to become a powerful dragon that can protect Natsuki and begins to train. However, the next day, upon hearing a loud noise from the room with the screen, they take a look and find a huge hole where the tiger was. Natsuki and Ryoku both find this strange.  Truth is, there is a legend that the tiger drawn on the screen sometimes jumps from the screen and prowls around.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>567690</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="127968" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-02-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">チョコっとおとひめおもてなし☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Otohime`s Hospitality Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chokotto Otohime Omotenashi Pri!</title>
<summary>Otohime and Urashima Taro fall into the human world from Fairy Land. Otohime, who loves hospitality, begins serving various extravagant foods in an effort to please people.  The girls try to get Otohime to return to Fairy Land, but neither Otohime nor Urashima Taro will listen. Furthermore, Otohime has become a fan of Wish and says she wants to give him Valentine`s chocolate at his Valentine`s concert. However, Otohime`s handmade chocolate is very strange chocolate that causes the person who eats it grow old.  Not listening to the girls trying to stop her, Otohime goes to the concert hall. The girls also head to the concert hall to try to stop Otohime, but they don`t make it in time and everyone has become elderly.  And on top of that, even Wish eats the chocolate...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>570672</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="128120" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-03-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スペシャルドレスをさがせ! ☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Find the Special Dress! Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Special Dress o Sagase! Pri!</title>
<summary>The girls have come to One-Inch Boy`s village in Fairy Land. However, they and the entire village was swallowed up by a tear and dropped into the human world. It turns out that tears are appearing all over Fairy Land and the lands of various fairy tales have fallen to the human world. As a result, many characters have fallen to the human world and are on the verge of causing a panic in the human world. Meanwhile, having gotten the Golden Needle at One-Inch Boy`s village, the girls have come to the Elves` Shoe Shop to get the Thread of Light. The girls ask for the Thread of Light, but the elves are too busy with work and can`t take care of the worm that creates the thread, Imotan. The girls, who want the Thread of Light no matter what, try to obtain the thread by taking care of Imotan themselves...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>570678</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="128121" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-02-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナンバー1!? 魔女がきた☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Number 1!? The Witch is Here Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Number 1!? Majo ga Kita Pri!</title>
<summary>The Witch finds out that the girls are Lil` Pri and attacks them with magic.  She plans on defeating Lil` Pri and becoming the most beautiful in the land. Under attack, the girls manage to escape to Fairy Land with the Queen`s assistance. However, because the witch has come to the human world, many odd things are happening around Fairy Land. At this rate, Fairy Land will disappear.  The Queen asks the girls to search for the Special Dress. If Lil` Pri, with their increased Princess Power, wear that dress, Fairy Land will be saved. To make the Special Dress, the Golden Needle, the Thread of Light, and the Rainbow Cloth are needed. Hearing this, the girls head straight to One-Inch Boy`s village to find the Golden Needle.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>570676</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="128122" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-02-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さよならWish☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goodbye, Wish Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sayonara Wish Pri!</title>
<summary>Wish suddenly announces that he`s retiring from being an idol. His sudden announcement surprises both his fans and the girls. The girls go to Chris to ask why he`s retiring, but Chris seems odd somehow. They repeatedly try to talk to him, but Chris won`t answer. The girls become anxious, wondering what happened to Chris, when Vivi comes and tells them the secret Chris has been keeping from Lil` Pri. Knowing he accepted his destiny for them, the girls head to the concert hall where Wish`s fans wait, saddened by his retirement. Meanwhile, Vivi runs into the Witch at her mistress`s house. Without knowing the Witch is tricking her, Vivi completely believes her. The Witch successfully deceives Vivi and is finally headed to the human world...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>570674</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="128547" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-03-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">かがやけ! トゥループリンセス☆ぷりっ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shine! True Princesses Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kagayake! True Princess Pri!</title>
<summary>There is no longer anything the girls can do. After agonizing over finding something they can do, they decide to consult with the Queen of Fairy Land.
The girls have obtained all three items to make the Special Dress. However, having revealed Lil` Pri`s identity to their classmates, they can no longer become Lil` Pri. Chaos spreads through the human world as people slowly forget the fairy tales. There is no longer anything the girls can do. After agonizing over finding something they can do, they decide to consult with the Queen of Fairy Land. Thinking that they need to get to the queen as soon as possible, they start to head for Fairy Land when a giant tear opens in the sky and the queen`s castle comes falling through it.  The people watch nervously.  The characters from Fairy Land become greatly panicked as things get even worse for the human world. The girls, figuring they should see the queen, head for the castle in the human world.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>570682</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="128548" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-03-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さよならリルぷりっ☆ぷりっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goodbye Lil`Pri Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sayonara Lil`Pri Pri!</title>
<summary>Ringo and the girls have come to the castle of the emperor with no clothes to find the last tool to make the special dress, the Rainbow Cloth. Saotome and other classmates are also at the castle, doing research on characters of Fairy Land for homework assigned by Mr. Atsui. After meeting everyone, the girls immediately meet the naked emperor and ask for the Rainbow Cloth.  However, he rejects them saying he can`t. The Rainbow Cloth has been used to make a shirt, his favorite shirt which he says he is currently wearing and is showing off. However, Ringo and the girls only see a naked emperor, no matter what. Will the girls be able to obtain the Rainbow cloth?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>570680</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="128745" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-03-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぷりぷりリルぷりっ☆ぷりっ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pri Pri Lil`Pri! Pri!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pri Pri Lil`Pri! Pri!</title>
<summary>Happiness Tones will restore Fairyland, but it will also be the end of this storybook adventure.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>570684</identifier>
<identifier>lilpri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
