<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7429" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-04-28</startdate>
<enddate>2009-04-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Superflat First Love</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">すーぱーふらっと・ファーストラブ</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">SUPERFLAT FIRST LOVE</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5057" type="Same Setting">Superflat Monogram</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="10907" approval="2" total="2">Fastening Days</anime>
<anime id="12309" approval="2" total="2">Fastening Days 2</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="396387">oh Lord! hence this is sooooo short it could be worth to watch this young girl who started to smoke drugs when she was 4 years hold, ahah!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.honeyee.com/feature/2009/superflat/</url>
<creators>
<name id="2151" type="Character Design">Wada Takaaki</name>
<name id="20377" type="Direction">Murakami Takashi</name>
<name id="47876" type="Music">Fantastic Plastic Machine</name>
</creators>
<description>The French fashion company Louis Vuitton and Japanese modern artist Murakami Takashi (村上隆) have produced Superflat First Love, an anime short to mark the revamp of Louis Vuitton`s Multicolor Spring Palette line of leather accessories.
As a sequel to Murakami`s http://anidb.net/a5057 [Superflat Monogram] anime short (2003), the new film also celebrates six years of collaboration between the two pop culture icons. Louis Vuitton officially launched the Multicolor Sprint Palette lineup on April 28. On the same day, Superflat First Love had its world premiere on a Japanese mobile website. The characters in the anime adorn special displays in Louis Vuitton stores during the launch of the product line.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="239">3.37</permanent>
<temporary count="239">5.15</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>48395.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15293</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6607</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.honeyee.com/feature/2009/superflat/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1730" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-08-24">
<name>mobile phone</name>
<description>Character is often or always using a mobile phone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3103" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-11">
<name>first love</name>
<description>Ah… first love. The love that is remembered the most fondly by the participant, as this is commonly what people experience when they first have a first crush, but it is also the love before the Second Love, if that should ever happen, and for a guy, he usually holds her memory very close to him if he is a widower whereas for young girls, the memory of the First Love they ever had is a special memory to them, especially if he later becomes the boyfriend they`ve longed for.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>204995.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4542" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-04-25">
<name>no dialogue</name>
<description>The anime either has no spoken dialogue or no dialogue at all.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4552" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>superflat</name>
<description>Superflat is a postmodern art movement, founded by the artist Takashi Murakami, which is influenced by manga and anime. The term is used to refer to various flattened forms in Japanese graphic art, animation, pop culture and fine arts, as well as the "shallow emptiness of Japanese consumer culture". As self-proclaimed art movement, it was a successful piece of niche marketing, a branded art phenomenon designed for Western audiences.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4610" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-22">
<name>commercial</name>
<description>This title is used to sell and/or promote a real-life product or service. Not to be confused with "product placement" or "subliminal advertising" — this features *direct* promotion for such element.
Depending on the setting, some could even be considered as "animated infomercials".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="50069" type="main character in" update="2012-10-24">
<name>Gaston Luis Vuitton</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>127174.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="50070" type="main character in" update="2012-10-24">
<name>Panda Geant</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>127176.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="50071" type="main character in" update="2012-10-24">
<name>Petite Panda</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>127175.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="548" picture="186185.jpg">Sakamoto Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="118550" update="2015-10-13">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2009-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Special</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
