<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7438" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>4</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-09-06</startdate>
<enddate>2010-12-06</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Tamayura</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">たまゆら</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Tamayura</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">玉响</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8234" type="Sequel">Tamayura: Hitotose</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="2659" approval="54" total="65">Aria the Animation</anime>
<anime id="9722" approval="26" total="31">Non Non Biyori</anime>
<anime id="3195" approval="6" total="12">Kamichu!</anime>
<anime id="424" approval="6" total="8">Yokohama Kaidashi Kikou</anime>
<anime id="9257" approval="6" total="7">Yama no Susume</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="233857">if you want to know what the word fluffy means, watch this anime rightaway! its so cool! ^^</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tamayura.info/</url>
<creators>
<name id="4894" type="Character Design">Iizuka Haruko</name>
<name id="3611" type="Series Composition">Satou Jun`ichi</name>
<name id="3611" type="Direction">Satou Jun`ichi</name>
<name id="21281" type="Music">Nakajima Nobuyuki</name>
<name id="754" type="Animation Work">Hal Film Maker</name>
<name id="3611" type="Original Plan">Satou Jun`ichi</name>
<name id="3562" type="Chief Animation Direction">Onji Masayuki</name>
</creators>
<description>* An original iyashikei ("calming") anime OVA from director http://anidb.net/cr3611 [Satou Jun`ichi].
For her first year of high school, family circumstances force http://anidb.net/ch19342 [Sawatari Fuu] to move to Takehara, a scenic old town near Hiroshima on the Inland Sea and live with her relatives. Her father, who has passed away, grew up in Takehara and always spoke fondly of his childhood while living there. Sawatari learns to love taking photographs with his old film camera, a Rollei 35S while making friends and learning about the town.
Note: All the episodes aired on AT-X prior to the DVD/BD releases of 26.11.2010 for the first volume and 23.12.2010 for the last volume.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1291">6.28</permanent>
<temporary count="1295">7.13</temporary>
<review count="1">9.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>57709.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11375</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9055</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4773</identifier>
<identifier>aaytoc</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tamayura.info/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Tamayura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>たまゆら_(アニメ)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2003</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>337589</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12975</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2669</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2010/tamayura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>tamayura-hitotose</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="569" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-11-18">
<name>clumsy</name>
<description>A clumsy person is one lacking in coordination, and as such prone to often having accidents such as tripping, bumping into objects, or dropping things. In female characters, this is often thought of as endearing.</description>
<picurl>63355.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1651" parentid="2883" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>photography</name>
<description>Photography is the art or process of producing images by the action of radiant energy and especially light on a sensitive surface (such as film or an optical sensor).
Source: Merriam-Webster</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3606" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-11">
<name>family without father</name>
<description>For some reason the protagonists father is no longer among the living. The much too early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family: Possibly the grieve-stricken mother and children barely function as humans. Or adding emphasis to the overall financial predicament of the family, should the father have been the money earner.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3792" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-06">
<name>iyashi-kei</name>
<description>A feel good, "no true conflict within story" type of plot, instead about the daily musings and activities of the characters with an overall tranquil mood. Similar to "Slice of Life", but much more relaxed, peaceful and "zen".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4150" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-01">
<name>everybody is nice</name>
<description>All characters are nice in their own way; nobody has ill intentions to others. Even if a secondary character appears to be bad at the beginning, they will redeem themselves or become tamed/pacified/neutralized swiftly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="19342" type="main character in" update="2015-02-04">
<rating votes="39">6.47</rating>
<name>Sawatari Fuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52046.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19343" type="main character in" update="2013-08-30">
<rating votes="37">7.51</rating>
<name>Hanawa Kaoru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52049.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20089" type="main character in" update="2010-07-27">
<rating votes="33">6.16</rating>
<name>Okazaki Norie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52048.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20090" type="main character in" update="2010-07-27">
<rating votes="39">7.73</rating>
<name>Sakurada Maon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52047.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2228" picture="21776.jpg">Gibu Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20116" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-29">
<rating votes="12">6.02</rating>
<name>Shihomi Riho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52172.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="642" picture="156264.jpg">Hazuki Erino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20757" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-18">
<rating votes="5">3.48</rating>
<name>Yakusa Chimo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70334.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="203" picture="38566.jpg">Matsuki Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20758" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-15">
<rating votes="4">3.72</rating>
<name>Momoneko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53344.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="80" picture="228656.jpg">Fukui Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20759" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-05">
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<name>Shashinkan Owner</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61528.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20760" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-13">
<rating votes="16">6.24</rating>
<name>Hanawa Sayomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53343.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20761" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-18">
<rating votes="5">4.71</rating>
<name>Sawatari Tamae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70359.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="187" picture="17002.jpg">Ogata Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20762" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-18">
<rating votes="4">4.36</rating>
<name>Fuu no Sobo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70341.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2029" picture="236292.jpg">Matsuo Yoshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20763" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-04">
<rating votes="10">5.50</rating>
<name>Sawatari Kou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53345.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10757" picture="81678.jpg">Miyamoto Kanako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73046" type="appears in" update="2015-02-04">
<name>Hoshi Manami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>168351.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="423" picture="37799.jpg">Nakajima Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73047" type="appears in" update="2015-02-04">
<name>Tobita Shimako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>168352.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="120506" update="2016-12-02">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2010-09-06</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大好きがいっぱいの町, なので</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s a Town Full of Things I Love, So Yeah</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daisuki ga Ippai no Machi, na no de</title>
<summary>Fuu and Kao-chan meet two new friends when they stop in to the camera shop to check up on repairs for Fuu`s camera.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>725213</identifier>
<identifier>tamayura-hitotose</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="121254" update="2016-12-02">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2010-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">水色の小さな切符, なので</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Tiny Light Blue Ticket</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mizuiro no Chiisana Kippu, na no de</title>
<summary>Fuu and Kao-chan meet two new friends when they stop in to the camera shop to check up on repairs for Fuu`s camera.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>725213</identifier>
<identifier>tamayura-hitotose</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="121400" update="2010-08-24">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-08-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122006" update="2010-12-09">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-09-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122007" update="2010-12-09">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-09-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="123094" update="2016-12-02">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2010-12-06</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それはあの日のこと, なので</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s About That Day</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sore wa Ano Hi no Koto, na no de</title>
<summary>After finding one of Kou’s childhood drawings, Fuu and her friends think it may be the same as her favorite picture of her father. They set out to discover the location with Sayomi`s help.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>725215</identifier>
<identifier>tamayura-hitotose</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="123095" update="2016-12-02">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2010-11-08</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">みんなで歩けばハッピー, なので</title>
<title xml:lang="en">If We All Walk Together, We`ll Be Happy, So Yeah</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Minna de Arukeba Happy, na no de</title>
<summary>After finding one of Kou’s childhood drawings, Fuu and her friends think it may be the same as her favorite picture of her father. They set out to discover the location with Sayomi`s help.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>725215</identifier>
<identifier>tamayura-hitotose</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="125982" update="2010-12-09">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-12-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
