<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7442" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>6</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-08-09</startdate>
<enddate>2011-03-14</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Queen`s Blade: Utsukushiki Toushi-tachi</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Queen`s Blade OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">クイーンズブレイド 美しき闘士たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Queen`s Blade: Beautiful Warriors</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">女王之刃 美丽的斗士们</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8528" type="Sequel">Queen`s Blade</anime>
<anime id="6653" type="Prequel">Queen`s Blade: Gyokuza o Tsugu Mono</anime>
<anime id="6080" type="Other">Queen`s Blade: Rurou no Senshi</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="521092">Side stories with the secondary characters of QB. Slightly better than the prequels but not by much, still a decent watch if you liked the other QB series.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="126957">Hilarously focused on fan-service, if that even counts when talking about QB world, but some valuable gapfillers all along nonetheless.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://queensblade.tv</url>
<creators>
<name id="3066" type="Character Design">Noguchi Takayuki</name>
<name id="3063" type="Character Design">Rin Sin</name>
<name id="2415" type="Original Work">Hobby Japan</name>
<name id="708" type="Direction">Yoshimoto Kinji</name>
<name id="3066" type="Chief Animation Direction">Noguchi Takayuki</name>
<name id="3063" type="Chief Animation Direction">Rin Sin</name>
<name id="3068" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ishibashi Yukiko</name>
<name id="771" type="Work">Arms</name>
<name id="3326" type="Music">Yokoyama Masaru</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a gamebook by http://anidb.net/cr2415 [Hobby Japan].
Queen`s Blade. An exhibition held once every four years. Various beautiful fighters gathered in order to fulfill their desires. In the end, http://anidb.net/ch5518 [Queen Aldra] lost against wandering warrior http://anidb.net/ch3044 [Leina].
Now, some time after these events...
~ translated and adapted from official site by Cranston
Note: All the episodes were pre-aired on AT-X several days before the DVD/BD releases.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="645">3.68</permanent>
<temporary count="655">6.09</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221968.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11397</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8456</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4769</identifier>
<identifier>zhfobt</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://queensblade.tv</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Queen's_Blade</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>クイーンズブレイド_(アニメ)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1993</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>336856</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13073</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="382" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-11">
<name>warrior</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1609" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-03-01">
<name>elf</name>
<description>The origin of Elves (Norse; álfar(elves), álfr(elf)) can be found in ancient Norse mythology, in which, elves are described as divine, or near-divine, race of humanoids (Vættir), likened to the Æsir. In common description they are described as sage and immortal beings occupying the threshold between humans and the gods. In some cases humans that were beloved by the gods became elves within their lives. Ancient Elves are delineated into a pair of similar but distinct races; Light Elves (Ljósálfar) and Dark Elves (Svartálfar), each originating from separate homes within the nine worlds of Yggdrasil. Within the Poetic Edda the differences are commonly ascribed as:
"There is one place there that is called the Elf Home (Álfheimr which is the elven city). People live there that are named the light elves (Ljósálfar). But the dark elves (Dökkálfar) live below in earth, in caves and the dark forest and they are unlike them in appearance - and more unlike them in reality. The Light Elves are brighter than the sun in appearance, but the Dark Elves are blacker than pitch." (Snorri, Gylfaginning 17, Prose Edda)</description>
<picurl>63489.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2467" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-22">
<name>sword</name>
<description>A sword is a long, edged piece of metal, used as a cutting, thrusting, and clubbing weapon in many civilizations throughout the world. Before firearms became commonplace, and fast enough to render other weapons pointless in the battlefield, they were the main kind of weapon for war and duels alike. A sword fundamentally consists of a blade and a hilt, typically with one or two edges for striking and cutting, and a point for thrusting. That aside, however, they may come in all sorts of designs: the medieval European swords used to be big, heavy weapons that did not actually cut but instead broke the enemy`s bones under their armor; conversely, the Chinese jian sword (called "ken" in Japanese) attempted to exploit the armor`s joints and perforate the enemy`s flesh in those places, but was useless against the armor itself, and did not take the strikes, preferring to redirect them, to this day being considered a highly "circular" weapon and associated to taijiquan; on the other hand, the Japanese katana was a balanced all-purposes weapon that could be used even in an axe-like way, but which a master swordsman could use in many other, more elaborate manners.</description>
<picurl>127113.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2758" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-05">
<name>volleyball</name>
<description>Volleyball is a team sport in which two teams of six players are separated by a net. Each team tries to score points by grounding a ball on the other team`s court under organized rules.
Use the http://anidb.net/t7147 [competitive beach volleyball] tag for competition or professional beach volleyball play. Use the http://anidb.net/t6478 [beach volleyball episode] tag when the beach volleyball game is a one-off event, such as during a beach or pool visit.</description>
<picurl>221599.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2823" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>paper clothes</name>
<description>Worn clothing appears paper-thin and takes little abuse to be shredded or torn from the body. This is common in ecchi anime where the main storyline involves some type of fighting but consists primarily of dialogue and fanservice (Ikkitousen and Platonic Heart). Various girls’ clothing exploding as if made of rice paper is a very enticing prospect.</description>
<picurl>150776.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2824" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>pseudo tentacle rape scene</name>
<description>If this was porn she (or rather the audience) would have even more fun!</description>
<picurl>160554.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2828" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-26">
<name>borderline porn</name>
<description>Breaks the bounds of "excessive fanservice".
While the physical interactions and dialogue between characters may be extremely sexual, the most sexual situations do *not* have sex itself take place.
Specifically descriptive of containing all the plentiful features of (excessive) fanservice in addition to the interactions between characters being quite sexual — at most, sexual in NATURE only. This means physical touching such as groping, molesting, or bondage will focus primarily on the revealed (i.e. nude) upper portion of the body or through/over clothing on the lower half of the body. This is all WITHOUT actual sex acts (penetration, etc.) taking place.</description>
<picurl>214855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4192" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-08-22">
<name>broadcast cropped to 4-3</name>
<description>Although this anime was created in 16:9 (widescreen) aspect ratio, its Japanese TV broadcasts were all cropped to 4:3 (fullscreen). It was only made available in 16:9 upon its DVD/BD release.
Note: This tag does NOT apply to series that had initial broadcasts in 4:3 and 16:9 broadcasts several weeks later, such as Clannad, Asu no Yoichi, K-On!, etc. For those, use "Delayed 16-9 broadcast".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="3044" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-09-27">
<rating votes="122">6.98</rating>
<name>Leina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leina is the protagonist of the Queen`s Blade series. She is the middle sister of the Vance Family, an aristrocratic family of nobles, and is next in line to be the successor. However, she has no intent of becoming countess, and runs away to venture the outside world and become a warrior like her late mother Maria, eventually becoming a contender of the Queen`s Blade tournament. Leina dons silver armor with brown belts across, and is armed with a longsword called "Evindil" and a buckler as weapons.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>18711.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3046" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-16">
<rating votes="115">7.15</rating>
<name>Nanael</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nanael is a guardian angel sent to Earth to supervise and participate in the Queen`s Blade tournament. In her own words, "A messenger from Heaven who came to bring true order to the world." When in actuality, she is an angel dropout in Heaven. After frequent misconduct, the head archangel ordered Nanael to enter Queen`s Blade as a "trial." In addition, she was given a difficult condition: to not spill the "Holy Milk" in the bottle on her hip.</description>
<picture>23476.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4" picture="177060.jpg">Hirano Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3047" type="main character in" update="2013-09-27">
<rating votes="116">6.76</rating>
<name>Tomoe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tomoe is a Warrior Priestess from the island of Hinomoto an alternate rendition of feudal Japan, and is a member of an elite order of warrior priestesses that protect their homeland. Her homeland is currently in a power dispute with schemers from the Imperial Court who plan to overthrow the Mikado, who is only a child. However, most of her fellow priestesses were attacked and killed by the Kouma Ninja in a plot by schemers at the Imperial Court, and Tomoe, armed with the sacred katana Kuchinawa, enters the Queen`s Blade tournament with Shizuka by her side in order to gain the power to rescue the Mikado from their machinations and avenge her sisters. Her official English name is "Musha-Miko Tomoe", and she is named after the historical female samurai Tomoe Gozen.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>23947.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3048" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-09-27">
<rating votes="112">7.67</rating>
<name>Echidna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Echidna is a wild elf from the southern jungles with over 500 years of battle experience. In the past, she led the Assassins of the Fang and was Irma`s former teacher, but is now a mercenary. She is considered a favorite to win the Queen`s Blade tournament, but her current employer is unknown; all that is certain is that she herself has no interest in the throne. She was hired to protect Leina during the tournament, but she abandoned her mission to rescue Irma from her execution. She is an expert with blades, and has a pet snake named Keltan that she wears as a thong, having it help her fight on occasion. In addition, her armor has a snake motif.
Echidna is named after the Greek mythological creature Echidna, whose half-snake appearance is also an homage to her snake-themed armor.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>18713.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1442" picture="18829.jpg">Kaida Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3049" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-09-29">
<rating votes="87">7.31</rating>
<name>Menace</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Menace was a princess from the ancient Egyptian-themed Amara Kingdom. She once lived a life of luxury until she was betrayed by Anarista, her most trusted adviser, and died trapped in her palace as her kingdom fell into ruin. Four thousand years later, the powerful Swamp Witch resurrected her to become part of her army. However, Menace broke free from the witch`s command and sets out on her own to restore the Amara Kingdom. She has a talking scepter named Setora, who does her bidding. As a result from her resurrection by the Witch, she acquired a "cursing power", black flames that she can summon from her fists to weaken her foes, with which she once hit Melona when she took Anarista`s form to tease her.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>18714.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3050" type="main character in" update="2011-05-03">
<rating votes="100">7.03</rating>
<name>Mellona</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Known as the Protean Assassin (千変の刺客), she is a shapeshifting, magic-using girl with a playful, yet sadistic personality who has the ability to take on any physical form, and one of the Swamp Witch`s strongest minions. She can transform into a pink liquid substance to create objects, move from place to place, and imitate people by taking on their shape. One noticeable use of her shape-shifting ability is her hair, which turns into hands that hold up her breasts and cover her nipples. Her primary offense is squirting acid from her breasts. In the first episode of the anime, she is defeated by Leina by jamming her enormous breast plate against Melona`s acid squirting breasts, which caused Melona`s breasts to balloon with acid until they explode.
Created by F.S.</description>
<picture>18715.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5378" type="main character in" update="2009-04-26">
<rating votes="201">8.34</rating>
<name>Airi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A scythe-wielding ghost girl in a maid costume, Airi was given human form by the evil Swamp Witch in her quest for domination. Airi serves every whim of her mistress quite willingly. Used primarily for assassinations, she can literally suck the vitality of her enemies simply by touching them.</description>
<picture>23944.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5379" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-26">
<rating votes="50">6.20</rating>
<name>Nowa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Described as the Guardian of the Forest, the half elf Nowa and her monkey companion protect the creatures who live there.</description>
<picture>23941.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="216" picture="171983.jpg">Takahashi Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5380" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-26">
<rating votes="137">7.67</rating>
<name>Alleyne</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the oldest and most seasoned veteran warriors of a tribe of forest elves, Alleyne is taciturn and blunt in her dealings with others. She`s had a long relationship with Echidna, who she often chastises for her loose ways but is mocked in return for her inexperience with men. The appearance of the half-elf Nowa in the forest elf community marked a turning point for Alleyne, who appointed her "guardian of the forest". The elf village elders did not approve however, and drove her from the village with the excuse that she must join the Queen`s Blade tournament. Distraught, Alleyne secretly set out for the tournament as well, to protect the girl whose sudden appearance had awoken feelings long dormant in the veteran elven warrior.</description>
<picture>23945.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5381" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-25">
<rating votes="77">3.89</rating>
<name>Elina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The daughter of Count Vance, and younger sister of Leina, a prominent Queen`s Blade competitor. She was trained from a young age in all manner of martial arts, from stealth to strict military discipline, and acts as both bodyguard, spy, and assassin for her father. Unlike Leina, Elina`s personality is vicious.</description>
<picture>21945.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="591" picture="226209.jpg">Mizuhashi Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5383" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-13">
<rating votes="61">7.79</rating>
<name>Shizuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A kunoichi from the same land as Tomoe, a money grubbing assassin, she couldn`t care less about the affairs of the battle as long she gets paid. However, she hates working hard in general and instead has a personal group of ninjas to aid her.</description>
<picture>30975.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5516" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-09-27">
<rating votes="93">6.69</rating>
<name>Cattleya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cattleya is a swordswoman who owns a weapon shop in the small town of Vosk. A former adventurer, Cattleya was known as the Giant Slayer for wielding an enormous greatsword with ease. She soon fell in love with another adventurer named Owen, who later became her husband, and together they had a son named Lana. However, their happiness was destroyed when Owen disappeared, and Cattleya enters the Queen`s Blade to find him with Lana by her side. Her combat ability is hampered by Lana constantly clinging about her knees. While many of the female characters have big breasts, Cattleya`s are exceptionally large, measuring 120 cm in circumference.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>23942.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5517" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-09-29">
<rating votes="68">6.12</rating>
<name>Ymir</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ymir is the daughter of the Dwarven King who runs the Iron Mountain weapon factory, which is known for forging top-quality weapons. Ymir entered the Queen`s Blade tournament to prove the superiority of Dwarven weapons. In the anime, she has a strong one-sided rivalrly with Cattleya as a weaponsmith. Despite her childlike appearance, Ymir is actually older than she looks, evidenced by her speech pattern which is reminiscient to that of an old man. She wields a massive battle axe and wears a special guantlet that increases her strength, and spends most of her time hawking cheap weapons at inflated rates to the unsuspecting. Despite her strength, she has an intense fear of snakes, specifically from Echidna`s snake Keltan.
Ymir`s name is taken from Norse mythological being Ymir.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>23943.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="397" picture="43234.jpg">Saitou Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5518" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-09-02">
<rating votes="86">6.81</rating>
<name>Aldra</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>34416.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="307" picture="17142.jpg">Takeuchi Miyuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5519" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-09-27">
<rating votes="33">7.39</rating>
<name>Nyx</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nyx is a young woman who, as a child, was once a peasant girl in the service of Count Vance. She was looked down upon and despised by those of higher station, and was frequently humiliated and abused by the Count`s daughter, Elina. However, her life changed when she stumbled upon Funikura, an evil sentient staff, and was granted immeasurable magical powers. The staff also gives her a split personality: one with the kind and timid side she was born with, and the angry and vengeful side developed through the mistreatment from her career as a servant by Elina (when injected with Funikura`s liquid). However, she is unable to control them effectively, and despite possessing a strong sense of justice, she is just as likely to set an entire village aflame to punish its evil leader. She takes on a gaudy clothing style mannerism so as not to be overlooked by her former tormentors, but the malevolent will of the evil staff she struggles to command continues to oppress her by sexually assaulting her. She entered the Queen`s Blade tournament to prove her worth to those who have looked down on her through her whole life, as well as seek revenge against Elina, her former tormentor.
Nyx is named after the Greek goddess Nyx, who is known as the Goddess of the Night.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>36110.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5520" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-07-24">
<rating votes="52">5.27</rating>
<name>Melpha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Melpha is high-ranking priestess who is widely respected by her followers as a holy woman. Compared to the other competitors, her fighting ability in close quarters is minimal (she is only armed with a spiked flail and a small shield), but through the use of the "Divine Power", she possesses the ability to heal her own wounds and inflict divine punishment on her opponents through the use of provocative "Holy Poses". In the anime, Melpha idolizes Nanael as an Angel of Heaven, which Nanael abuses in order to boss Melpha around as a servant. Much like Cattleya, her breasts are larger than normal.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>205406.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10417" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-16">
<rating votes="9">5.41</rating>
<name>Setra</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31246.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32" picture="16618.jpg">Tachiki Fumihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10419" type="appears in" update="2009-07-16">
<rating votes="17">5.38</rating>
<name>Tenshi-chou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31248.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="442" picture="187043.jpg">Honda Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10420" type="appears in" update="2013-09-29">
<rating votes="37">4.76</rating>
<name>Hachiel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An angel. Best friend of Nanael.</description>
<picture>31253.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3132" picture="223652.jpg">Kikuchi Kokoro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10421" type="appears in" update="2013-09-29">
<rating votes="14">1.56</rating>
<name>Rana</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The son of Owen and Cattelya, he is usually seen near or attached to Cattelya`s leg as she is his only remaining parent and he is far too young and timid to move on his own. During the events of the anime, he would start to gain some courage when bravely fighting against Melona when he went to rescue Cattelya and (unbeknownst to him) his father Owen during the finals of the Queen`s Blade tournament. During the tournament, he makes friends with Airi along with some of the other female competitors. He is training to become weaponsmith as his mother.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>31256.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30615" type="appears in" update="2011-03-31">
<rating votes="2">1.84</rating>
<name>Datenshi Delmore</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68777.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31571" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-09-27">
<rating votes="10">7.21</rating>
<name>Aldra</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aldra is the victor of the past two Queen`s Blade tournaments and reigning Queen of the Continent. As the child of the Pope, the highest religious leader, and the daughter of the Devil King of the Netherworld, she is a cursed half-demon who, along with her sister, was persecuted everywhere they went. One day while searching for some food, Aldra`s sister disappeared. She soon made contact with the fallen angel Delmore, whom she made a contract with and gained demonic powers at the cost of her growth. She then became determined to win the Queen`s Blade and use her power to search for her lost sister. Because of her current position as Queen, she would often have fits of paranoia over the fact that someone might overthrow her, which led her to establishing the Assassins of the Fang. Her official English name is "The Queen Aldra".
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>70556.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="307" picture="17142.jpg">Takeuchi Miyuu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="118128" update="2010-07-19">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2010-08-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">信義! エリナ揺るぎなき絆</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Faith! Erina`s Unshakable Bond</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shingi! Erina Yurubi Naki Kizuna</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118129" update="2010-07-19">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2010-09-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛惜! アレイン千年の別れ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Longing! Alleyne`s Thousand Year Separation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aiseki! Alleyne Sennen no Wakare</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118130" update="2011-01-19">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2010-10-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">憂鬱! アイリの二心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Melancholy! Airi`s Double Cross</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuuutsu! Airi no Nishin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118131" update="2011-01-19">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2010-11-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">再興! メナス愉悦の王宮</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Revival! Menace`s Royal Palace of Pleasure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikou! Menace Yuetsu no Oukyuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118132" update="2011-01-19">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2011-02-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">堕天! 逸楽のナナエル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fallen Angel! The Nanael of Pleasure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daten! Itsuraku no Nanael</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118133" update="2011-01-19">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2011-03-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">奥義! 差添[さしぞ]いの逢魔[おうま]が旅</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mystery! An Escort`s Journey of Disaster</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ougi! Sashizoi no Ouma ga Tabi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121799" update="2011-04-30">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-08-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122058" update="2010-09-23">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-03-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129636" update="2011-04-23">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-04-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Rebellion Ad</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129723" update="2011-04-30">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2010-08-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">ED Full Version</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129724" update="2011-04-30">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-03-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129725" update="2011-04-30">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-02-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129726" update="2011-04-30">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-11-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129727" update="2011-04-30">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-10-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129728" update="2011-04-30">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-09-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
