<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7454" restricted="false">
<type>Other</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1989</startdate>
<enddate>1989</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">All That Gundam</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ALL THAT GUNDAM</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="715" type="Other">Kidou Senshi Gundam</anime>
<anime id="716" type="Other">Kidou Senshi Gundam 0080: Pocket no Naka no Sensou</anime>
<anime id="718" type="Other">Kidou Senshi Z Gundam</anime>
<anime id="719" type="Other">Kidou Senshi Gundam ZZ</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9723" approval="2" total="2">30th Gundam Perfect Mission</anime>
</similaranime>
<creators>
<name id="1946" type="Music">Kawai Kenji</name>
</creators>
<description>An animated short created for Gundam`s 10th anniversary event. One minute in length, it shows some of the popular Gundam models of the first 10 years of the franchise in action. The clip also served as a promotional video for the next Gundam series to be released as it ends with the announcement "http://anidb.net/a716 [War in the Pocket] is coming soon".
Note: It was released on VHS in the same year as "a special present for Gundam freak" together with an original music video, CG art, television commercials and other extras. It was also released as a bonus clip on the War in the Pocket DVD release on 18.12.1999.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="240">3.09</permanent>
<temporary count="241">5.01</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>3141.gif</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17657</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5270</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4542" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-04-25">
<name>no dialogue</name>
<description>The anime either has no spoken dialogue or no dialogue at all.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4664" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-18">
<name>short movie</name>
<description>Typically used when an OVA only has one part and is less than the usual 20 to 25 minutes in length.
So instead of calling it a `short episode`, the `short movie` tag is more appropriate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2536" type="appears in" update="2009-01-18">
<rating votes="10">7.61</rating>
<name>Christina Mackenzie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Al`s former neighbour, who left Libot to attend the Earth Federation`s military academy. Chris returns to the colony just before the first Zeon attack, and quickly becomes a surrogate big sister to her old friend Al. Her current assignment is as a test pilot, fine-tuning the Gundam NT1 and "training" its learning computer - a piece of information she keeps from Al, since the Gundam`s presence at Libot is a top military secret.</description>
<picture>17863.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2537" type="appears in" update="2009-01-18">
<rating votes="6">9.92</rating>
<name>Bernard Wiseman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>This novice pilot is one of thousands of ill-trained students whom Zeon sends to the front lines as its military situation worsens. Shot down on his first mission, Bernie accidentally obtains vital intelligence on the Federation`s new Gundam, and on this pretext he is assigned to the elite Cyclops commando team. His new teammates stick Bernie with the chore of babysitting the curious Al, and this odd pair soon strike up a strong friendship.</description>
<picture>17864.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2545" type="appears in" update="2009-01-18">
<rating votes="6">9.68</rating>
<name>Alfred Izuruha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Al is a fifth-grade student living at Side 6`s Libot space colony. To distract himself from his parents` strained relationship and his own troubles at school, he spends most of his time collecting military paraphernalia with his friends and trading breathless stories of the ferocious battles taking place outside the neutral colonies of Side 6. Al`s fascination with war takes a new turn as the conflict begins to directly affect his home colony.</description>
<picture>17872.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2556" type="appears in" update="2009-01-19">
<name>RX-78NT-1 Gundam NT1 Alex</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The RX-78NT1 is the fourth Gundam unit created by the Federation Forces during the One Year War. Redesigned for use by ace pilot Amuro Ray, whose success in battle was seen as evidence of his Newtype powers, this Gundam was given the designation "NT1." Unlike Zeon`s Newtype weapons, the Gundam NT1 doesn`t have a psycommu interface; instead, its designers concentrated on making it highly responsive and maneuverable. Its special features include magnet-coated joints for increased responsiveness, a new type of panoramic cockpit display, and pop-up gatling guns in its forearms. The Gundam NT1 can also be fitted with optional Chobham armor for extra protection, increasing its overall weight to a massive 95 tons.</description>
<picture>17884.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="3971" type="appears in" update="2012-04-10">
<rating votes="107">7.89</rating>
<name>Amuro Ray</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Amuro is the hero of our story, and the pilot of the mighty mobile suit RX-78 Gundam. As the series begins, he is a civilian living at the Side 7 research colony, the neglected son of a Federation Forces engineer. When Zeon mobile suits attack the colony, Amuro commandeers the prototype Gundam and defeats the invaders. He soon finds himself part of the substitute crew of the Federation warship White Base, and this moody young man begins to develop strong bonds with his newfound "family." Meanwhile, Amuro`s increasing fighting skills suggest that he has potential far beyond that of ordinary mortals...
Source: Official Site</description>
<picture>85679.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="3972" type="appears in" update="2012-04-04">
<rating votes="84">7.42</rating>
<name>Kamille Bidan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>This angry young man is destined to become the star pilot of the AEUG resistance group. A resident of the Green Noa 1 space colony, Kamille is the son of two Federation military engineers, and by entering junior mobile suit competitions he`s proven himself a talented engineer in his own right. He also has something of a complex about his feminine name and, as the story begins, Kamille is a budding juvenile delinquent with a hot temper and a hatred of authority figures. After clashing with the Titans he runs off with the rebel soldiers of the AEUG, and is soon invited to join their ranks as a mobile suit pilot. During his adventures, Kamille begins to outgrow his youthful anger and moodiness, and as his Newtype powers emerge he strives to understand the world around him and the people who fight by his side.</description>
<picture>85170.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6650" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="1">9.23</rating>
<name>RX-178 Gundam Mk-II</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>This prototype mobile suit was developed by the Titans at the Gryps space colony. Based on the legendary RX-78 Gundam, the Mk.II inherits its predecessor`s high performance and remarkable potential, although it suffers from a few lingering design flaws - notably, its obsolete armour materials. On the other hand, the Mk.II also introduces the radical new movable frame design concept, giving it superb manoeuvrability. All three prototype units are captured by the AEUG resistance group during their raid on the Titans` headquarters. The rebels keep one in service, replacing its sinister Titans colours with a more heroic white and blue scheme, and eagerly dissect the other two in order to learn their technological secrets.</description>
<picture>24420.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6678" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<name>MRX-009 Psyco Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>This huge transformable mobile armour, was developed by the Murasame Newtype Lab for use by their artificially-enhanced Cyber-Newtypes. The Murasame Lab`s original goal was simply to equip a Gundam with a psycommu system, the psychic interface developed by Zeon scientists during the One Year War. However, the sheer bulk of this device - and the addition of features like a Minovsky craft flotation system, a protective anti-beam barrier, and complex transformation mechanisms - resulted in the Psyco Gundam becoming a forty-metre monster. As well as its immense firepower, the Psyco Gundam houses a more subtle weapon... a combat system which overrides its pilot`s will and forces her to fight.</description>
<picture>24464.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6679" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="1">4.67</rating>
<name>MRX-009 Psyco Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>This huge transformable mobile armour, was developed by the Murasame Newtype Lab for use by their artificially-enhanced Cyber-Newtypes. The Murasame Lab`s original goal was simply to equip a Gundam with a psycommu system, the psychic interface developed by Zeon scientists during the One Year War. However, the sheer bulk of this device - and the addition of features like a Minovsky craft flotation system, a protective anti-beam barrier, and complex transformation mechanisms - resulted in the Psyco Gundam becoming a forty-metre monster. As well as its immense firepower, the Psyco Gundam houses a more subtle weapon... a combat system which overrides its pilot`s will and forces her to fight.</description>
<picture>24465.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6680" type="appears in" update="2009-05-05">
<name>MRX-010 Psyco Gundam Mk.II</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>This transformable mobile armour, an improved version of the original Psyco Gundam, is theoretically the most powerful mobile weapon in the entire Earth Sphere. However, the Psyco Gundam Mk.II enters battle in an incomplete state, unable to transform into its "mobile fortress" form or deploy its full range of fighting capabilities, and its performance is further hampered by the mental instability of its pilot. In theory, the Psyco Gundam Mk.II can deploy remote-controlled "reflector bits" to redirect its beam fire towards its targets, and the beam swords in its wire-guided detachable forearms make it equally dangerous in close combat.</description>
<picture>24466.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6681" type="appears in" update="2009-05-05">
<name>MRX-010 Psyco Gundam Mk.II</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>This transformable mobile armour, an improved version of the original Psyco Gundam, is theoretically the most powerful mobile weapon in the entire Earth Sphere. However, the Psyco Gundam Mk.II enters battle in an incomplete state, unable to transform into its "mobile fortress" form or deploy its full range of fighting capabilities, and its performance is further hampered by the mental instability of its pilot. In theory, the Psyco Gundam Mk.II can deploy remote-controlled "reflector bits" to redirect its beam fire towards its targets, and the beam swords in its wire-guided detachable forearms make it equally dangerous in close combat.</description>
<picture>24467.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6690" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="1">9.23</rating>
<name>MSZ-006 Zeta Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>This machine is the culmination of the AEUG`s secret "Zeta Project," whose goal was to create a transformable mobile suit capable of operating in every environment from weightless space to Earth`s gravity. By transforming into a streamlined Wave Rider form, the Zeta Gundam can ride the shockwaves of atmospheric re-entry and then cruise through Earth`s atmosphere. As a mobile suit, it combines the movable frame technology of the Gundam Mk.II with the lightweight Gundarium Gamma alloy of the Rick Dias, not to mention an extraordinary level of firepower. In the hands of the young Newtype pilot Kamille Bidan, one of its principal designers, the Zeta Gundam proves to be the most powerful weapon in the rebels` arsenal.</description>
<picture>24478.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6691" type="appears in" update="2015-02-08">
<name>MSZ-006 Zeta Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>This machine is the culmination of the AEUG`s secret "Zeta Project," whose goal was to create a transformable mobile suit capable of operating in every environment from weightless space to Earth`s gravity. By transforming into a streamlined Wave Rider form, the Zeta Gundam can ride the shockwaves of atmospheric re-entry and then cruise through Earth`s atmosphere. As a mobile suit, it combines the movable frame technology of the Gundam Mk.II with the lightweight Gundarium Gamma alloy of the Rick Dias, not to mention an extraordinary level of firepower. In the hands of the young Newtype pilot Kamille Bidan, one of its principal designers, the Zeta Gundam proves to be the most powerful weapon in the rebels` arsenal.</description>
<picture>24479.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="10986" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="9">8.30</rating>
<name>RX-78-2 Gundam</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Gundam is one of three prototype mobile suits secretly developed by the embattled Earth Federation. After suffering tremendous losses to Zeon`s mobile suits earlier in the war, the Federation set out to create its own, using the very latest advanced technology. The Gundam is the most successful of these prototypes, a close-combat mobile suit protected by tough Luna Titanium armour, and armed with both lethal beam sabers and a devastating beam rifle as powerful as a battleship cannon. It`s also equipped with an advanced computer which learns from its pilot, ultimately enabling it to operate the Gundam automatically. In the hands of accidental pilot Amuro Ray, this one prototype mobile suit proves to be the equal of any Zeon weapon.</description>
<picture>32757.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="18916" type="appears in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="5">6.77</rating>
<name>Judau Ashta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is a rather typical of a Gundam protagonist, the beginning of the series shows him growing as a poor junk dealer at the space colony of Shangrila in Side 1. He`s rather loudmouthed and straightfoward but has a good heart and displays Newtype abilities. Unlike most Gundam protagonists, he is optimistic and happy-go-lucky, instead of being anti-social or brooding (Amuro Ray and Kamille Bidan being prime examples). Judau is a young teenage boy enthralled with mobile suits and an avid supporter of the AEUG. He also has a younger sister Leina, whom he might catfight repeatedly with, but still cares very deeply for.</description>
<picture>85259.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="45234" type="appears in" update="2012-05-27">
<name>MSZ-010 ZZ-Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>88502.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="53956" type="appears in" update="2013-03-22">
<rating votes="3">10.00</rating>
<name>RX-93 v Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>134071.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="117197" update="2010-03-28">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
