<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7461" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-06-05</startdate>
<enddate>2010-06-05</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ginmaku Hetalia: Axis Powers - Paint It, White (Shiroku Nure!)</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Военизированная Хеталия: страны Оси. В белом</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Военизирана Хеталия - оцвети в бяло!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Hetalia Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">銀幕ヘタリア Axis Powers Paint it, White(白くぬれ!)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Hetalia: Axis Powers - Paint It, White!</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6234" type="Parent Story">Hetalia: Axis Powers</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://hetalia.com/movie/index.htm</url>
<creators>
<name id="730" type="Animation Work">Studio Deen</name>
<name id="5503" type="Character Design">Kawanami Masaaki</name>
<name id="4220" type="Original Work">Himaruya Hidekazu</name>
<name id="8144" type="Direction">Bob Shirahata</name>
<name id="4221" type="Music">Conisch</name>
</creators>
<description>Earth is under attack by extraterrestrials and a group of eight people meet to decide on a course of action. Although America wishes to fight, England and France are still recovering from an earlier conflict, Japan is indecisive, and Italy decides to wave a white flag.
The meeting ends without consensus, with each faction facing the aliens in their own way. However, all military actions prove useless and the white flag is ignored.
Reluctantly, the eight reconvene and come to the conclusion that the only way to discover the aliens` weakness is to infiltrate their mother-ship.
~ translated and adapted from the official site by Cranston</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="391">4.55</permanent>
<temporary count="392">6.25</temporary>
<review count="1">7.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>68454.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11097</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7337</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4688</identifier>
<identifier>hcgnzu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://hetalia.com/movie/index.htm</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>336805</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12619</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>HetaliaOfficial</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<characters>
<character id="5841" type="main character in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="61">6.40</rating>
<name>Italia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A bright and energetic nation that progressed from being the kin of Roma Antiqua, widely recognised as the strongest nation in the world, to being clumsy and irresponsible. Personified as being carefree, cowardly and lackadaisical (noted by his collection of white flags he uses to surrender), he often depends on Germany to resolve issues. Nods to Italian culture include his artistry and recurrent portrayal of pasta and pizza. He has an older brother, who represents southern Italy and who is commonly known as Italy Romano.</description>
<picture>59514.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5842" type="main character in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="57">7.82</rating>
<name>Doitsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A hard worker and lover of rules. He sticks to them rigidly and trains his troops to do the same. Despite this, he has formed a close relationship with the carefree Northern Italy. He notes at one point that he has a crazy boss.</description>
<picture>59516.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5843" type="main character in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="45">6.93</rating>
<name>Nihon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hard-working, serious, skilled with his hands, and needs time to adjust to other people. He is inexperienced in the outside world, but does his best to learn all he can. Generally quiet, he sometimes seems to have the attitude of an old man.</description>
<picture>59515.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="52" picture="19811.jpg">Takahashi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5844" type="main character in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="33">5.06</rating>
<name>America</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Raised by England and having fought for his independence, America became a country of pioneers. He is an energetic country who loves sticking his nose into other people`s business. He sees everything in a positive light, is quick to take action, and he always has his own idea of doing things. He also has immense physical strength and courage, although he has a crippling fear of ghosts, particularly when they are vague blobs of light in pictures. Strangely, a grey named Tony appears in his house from time to time without him minding it at all. America is frequently seen clutching a hamburger and flashing a thumbs up. America also has a penchant for coming up with elaborate inventions that never go anywhere.</description>
<picture>59509.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5845" type="main character in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="48">7.85</rating>
<name>Igirisu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A nation that was once a pirate and tormented Spain, the United Kingdom is a gentleman who is known for having terrible cooking skills (although America enjoys his food), a foul mouth, and huge eyebrows. He does not get along well with France or Russia, and can sometimes be cynical, particularly towards his somewhat estranged sibling America. Despite being mocked by the other nations for it, England is a strong believer of unicorns, faeries, and magic, going so far as to literally curse his enemies. England cannot hold his liquor well and is a very unhappy sort of drunk. He once formed an alliance with Japan because he felt lonely. He is classified as a tsundere character.</description>
<picture>59510.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="221" picture="17039.jpg">Sugiyama Noriaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5846" type="main character in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="36">6.71</rating>
<name>France</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Once a large nation, but after Napoleon Bonaparte had died, he was no longer good in war and instead attracted tourists to his country with his wine. He has an intense rivalry with England, and loves to argue with him over trivial topics. France is infatuated with most of the nations, often touching them inappropriately. He has been known to streak naked and makes blatant sexual comments at every opportunity. France maintains a bit of facial hair because he feels it makes him look like a big brother. He is constantly pictured with a rose, whether he is carrying it or using it as a censor.</description>
<picture>59511.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="183" picture="16992.jpg">Onosaka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5847" type="main character in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="78">8.26</rating>
<name>Russia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Despite having the cruelty of a child, Russia is the tallest of all the nations. He adores vodka and sunflowers. His primary hate is "General Winter", despite using the cold to his advantage in war. Russia has a kind and gentle face, but has mentally cracked from the strain of his bloody history. The other nations are mortified by him, particularly Lithuania, whom he loves to both physically and emotionally abuse. Occasionally, he stalks others while in a panda costume. Russia promises that eventually "everyone will become one with Russia". He also frequently says "KolKolKolKol" to nations he is threatening. Russia is almost always seen carrying a section of pipe. He is classified as a yandere character.</description>
<picture>59512.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1663" picture="23213.jpg">Takato Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5848" type="main character in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="34">5.27</rating>
<name>Chuugoku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the oldest nations and is regarded as the eldest brother among the East Asian nations. He is extremely superstitious and religious. Slightly disturbed of Russia. He has certain tastes for things and gets irritated if a food has a certain pattern of tastes. He is also a big fan of Hello Kitty and tends to end his sentences with the Japanese suffix -aru.</description>
<picture>59513.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1442" picture="18829.jpg">Kaida Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18035" type="appears in" update="2013-03-25">
<rating votes="24">8.38</rating>
<name>Preussen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59961.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="171" picture="23121.jpg">Kousaka Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="117229" update="2018-10-04">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>85</length>
<airdate>2010-06-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="127686" update="2011-01-26">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
