<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7476" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-04-01</startdate>
<enddate>2010-04-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Chinka</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ちんか</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.dannychoo.com/post/ja/25524/ちんか.html</url>
<description>Since a few years ago, there have been many cases of arson.
In the rural town of Kiyotaki, situated in a beautiful mountain valley, the town folks are talking about the legendary arsonist, Akaneko [赤猫].
The police have completely given up on Akaneko, who has slipped through their fingers every time.
The town`s only hope is its one and only firefighting team - the [URL=http://anidb.net/ch17836]Mizuneko [水猫] Fire Brigade[/URL]. But because of their destructive fire fighting ways, they too are feared by the town folk. Almost every night, Akaneko and the Mizuneko Fire Brigade fight fiercely, taking down many of the town`s buildings in the process. The Mizuneko Fire Brigade have depleted most of the town`s financial resources so the town ends up on the verge of bankruptcy. The town was in a critical state when http://anidb.net/ch16821 [Chinka], a girl with a superhuman ability to smell out fires appears. With her powers, the Mizuneko Fire Brigade close in on the true identity of Akaneko...
Note: Originally released as an animated PV for April`s Fool 2010, the project was announced as a full animated series project shortly after. Nothing came out of it, however.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="47">2.35</permanent>
<temporary count="47">3.97</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>45500.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>29609</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.dannychoo.com/post/ja/25524/ちんか.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1046" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-21">
<name>firefighter</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="16820" type="main character in" update="2013-02-26">
<rating votes="1">2.80</rating>
<name>Kaji Shouka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chief of the "Mizuneko fire brigade". She commands the team with her strong, independent spirit. The town folks fear her and her a firefighting monster. Mist Dragon, the two-wheeled firefighting chopper is her ride. Her father is the town mayor.</description>
<picture>46505.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="162" picture="23208.jpg">Satou Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16821" type="main character in" update="2013-02-26">
<rating votes="1">2.80</rating>
<name>Kasai Chinka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>New member of the team. She`s a bit naïve, clumsy and awkward. She was welcomed to the team by Shouka because of her natural instinct to smell out fires. Not much is known about her past.</description>
<picture>46500.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="162" picture="23208.jpg">Satou Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16822" type="main character in" update="2013-02-26">
<rating votes="1">9.49</rating>
<name>Shinmon Megumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A beautiful, very easy-going, but a bit ditzy girl. She is the descendant of the legendary fire fighter, Shinmon Tatsugouro. She is the best fire fighter out there. She is also the only one who can control Mikoto`s ferocious pump.</description>
<picture>46504.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="162" picture="23208.jpg">Satou Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17836" type="appears in" update="2013-02-27">
<name>Mizuneko Shoubou-dan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Mizuneko Firefighter - Although Mizuneko fire brigade is a private organization, because the town of Kiyotaki does not have a fire department, "Mizuneko fire brigade" are in charge of the day-to-day firefighting. Having said that, it is a very laid back organization that is more like a sorority than anything else.</description>
<picture>45500.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="53259" type="main character in" update="2013-02-26">
<name>Atago Mikoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132837.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="53260" type="appears in" update="2013-02-26">
<name>Hibuse-san</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132838.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="53261" type="appears in" update="2013-02-26">
<rating votes="2">6.01</rating>
<name>Akaneko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An arsonist veiled in mystery. She has a deep-seated grudge against Shouka. She also hates cats.</description>
<picture>132839.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="53262" type="appears in" update="2013-03-02">
<rating votes="7">3.75</rating>
<name>Suenaga Mirai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Suenaga Mirai is the site mascot character for Culture Japan (dannychoo.com) who http://anidb.net/cr17222 [Danny Choo] developed with illustrator Azami Yuuko (アザミユウコ). Mirai started off as a single illustration in the corner of the site back in 2007 and since then has gained much popularity worldwide.
There has been many Mirai collaboration projects with Japanese companies such as Good Smile Company, Cospa, Nitro Plus, Kadokawa, King Records and more.
The kanji of her name is 末永未来 but "Mirai" is written as Hiragana. Her name means "Eternal Future".</description>
<picture>132840.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="126479" update="2012-05-04">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2010-04-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
