<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7477" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-09-23</startdate>
<enddate>2010-12-24</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Togainu no Chi</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Blood of the Reprimanded Hound</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Togainu no Chi: Bloody Curs</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">咎狗の血</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">咎狗之血</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="7902" approval="2" total="9">Deadman Wonderland</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="495673">If you like gay people you can watch it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="443546">nothing really remarkable about this anime. there`s no much shounen ai, as well as there`s no interesting plot. maybe the only thing that is worth watching here is its characters</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="99271">This anime had a lot of potential, I thought, but there`s not enough episodes and the ending doesn`t really feel like an ending. The story is a bit of a mess and I`m not sure if the creators knew what they wanted... Also the only thing that`s gay about this anime is, I guess, that there`s only 1 girl in it. On the plus side the characters look great and there`s a lot of blood.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.togainu.tv/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1303" type="Work">A-1 Pictures</name>
<name id="1465" type="Series Composition">Takahashi Natsuko</name>
<name id="2954" type="Character Design">Konno Naoyuki</name>
<name id="21820" type="Original Work">Nitro+Chiral</name>
<name id="2954" type="Direction">Konno Naoyuki</name>
<name id="4952" type="Music">Iizuka Masaaki</name>
<name id="9097" type="Music">Ishikawa Tomohisa</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the popular boys love visual novel game Togainu no Chi (Blood of the Reprimanded Hound) from Nitro+chiral.
After being devastated in the third World War (known as The Third Division), Japan was divided in two. Several years after the end of the war, a crime organization called Vischio has taken control of the destroyed city of Toshima (formerly Tokyo, Japan`s capital city), where they are holding a battle game known as Igura. The game`s main character, a young man named http://anidb.net/ch18464 [Akira], is falsely accused of a crime. Once arrested, a mysterious woman appears before him, offering him freedom if he agrees to participate in Igura and defeat Igura`s strongest man: the king, or Il-re. The story follows Akira`s life in the harsh, lawless Toshima as he fights both to survive and to unravel the mysteries developing around him.
Note: The first episode was streamed online on NicoNico Douga and U-stream as part of a special preview event on September 23, 2010. The regular television broadcast started on October 8, 2010.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="749">2.31</permanent>
<temporary count="763">5.19</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>47621.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11371</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8449</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4721</identifier>
<identifier>lqolcx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.togainu.tv/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Togainu_no_Chi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>咎狗の血</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2032</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>337592</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12804</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>434</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="920" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-03-22">
<name>perverted</name>
<description>Is a concept describing those types of human behavior that are excessive or deviated from what is considered to be orthodox or normal.</description>
<picurl>245189.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2488" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>multiple personality disorder</name>
<description>Multiple personality disorder is a psychiatric diagnosis that describes a condition in which a single person displays multiple distinct identities or personalities (known as alter egos or alters), each with its own pattern of perceiving and interacting with the environment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2843" parentid="7220" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-08">
<name>sexual abuse -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is to be split into the following new tags under the http://anidb.net/t7220 [sexual abuse] category. Afterwards, delete this tag.

* http://anidb.net/t7222 [groping / molestation]
* http://anidb.net/t1306 [chikan]
* http://anidb.net/t7221 [psychological sexual abuse]
* http://anidb.net/t2715 [rape / attempted rape]
</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2884" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>psychoactive drugs</name>
<description>Psychoactive drugs are chemical substances that affect the function of the central nervous system, altering perception, mood or consciousness.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3573" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-25">
<name>ominous future</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4257" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>survival</name>
<description>The theme/genre of survival typically depicts the act or process of continuing to live, generally in a hostile, possibly post-apocalyptic environment. Survival-centered media tends to be dark, set most commonly in a contemporary context, and generally leads either to small groups of people forming closely knit and functional units or to individuals turning against their fellows in a return to the survival of the fittest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4301" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-22">
<name>play or die</name>
<description>The protagonist(s) are forced into a situation where they have to partake in some form of event, often a game of death, unless they want to bid farewell to their life.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4481" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>protection complex</name>
<description>A character has a protection complex if the character is overly protective of other characters, beyond what would be considered a "normal" or "expected" duty of care.
The magnitude of overprotection can vary. It can be as low as constantly nagging someone to "stay safe". It can be as extreme as the protector making it their mission in life to protect the other character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4606" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>slide show animation</name>
<description>The entire anime or parts of it show sequences of still images. Sometimes used in low budged animations for action scenes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5285" parentid="3411" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>street fighting</name>
<picurl>211275.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5816" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-10-03">
<name>massacre</name>
<description>Mass murder.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5884" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-22">
<name>slow-paced</name>
<description>The story — including its characters and events — develop slowly.
May contain a weak continuity of plot and/or character development. 
Or may be a story telling device to increase the "sense of foreboding" in an anime with thriller or horror setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="18464" type="main character in" update="2010-07-27">
<rating votes="5">4.53</rating>
<name>Akira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52033.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18465" type="main character in" update="2010-07-27">
<rating votes="5">4.32</rating>
<name>Keisuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52034.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18466" type="main character in" update="2010-07-27">
<rating votes="8">6.25</rating>
<name>Shiki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52032.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18467" type="main character in" update="2010-07-27">
<rating votes="4">1.86</rating>
<name>Rin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52031.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18468" type="main character in" update="2010-07-27">
<rating votes="3">2.15</rating>
<name>Motomi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52030.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2062" picture="188714.jpg">Ichijou Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20082" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-27">
<rating votes="3">2.15</rating>
<name>Arbitro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52035.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="389" picture="56097.jpg">Okano Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20083" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-27">
<rating votes="3">1.70</rating>
<name>Kiriwar</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52038.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20084" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-27">
<rating votes="5">5.08</rating>
<name>Gunji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52037.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="181" picture="171560.jpg">Taniyama Kishou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20085" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-27">
<rating votes="3">1.81</rating>
<name>Nano</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52036.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="374" picture="17220.jpg">Yamazaki Takumi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="117304" update="2010-04-01">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122616" update="2014-10-12">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">虚夢/LOST</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Void Dream / Lost</title>
<summary>Akira, the series protagonist, is a participant in a fighting tournament called "Bl@ster," after a successful battle, he retires to his quarters. He`s awakened from sleep when a group of police break into his room and pin the blame for a recent murder on him, a crime which carries a sentence of life imprisonment. With no way to defend himself against the charges, Akira waits in fear for his life. He`s visited in jail by a woman named Emma who offers him the only alternative to a life spent in captivity - join a higher-stakes fighting competition, and defeat the man at the top. Faced with no other option, Akira gathers his things and leaves for the city of Toshima, where the Igura competition is held. He has nothing more than the clothes on his back and the dog tags that peg him as a participant, so when some thugs show up to harass him and take a hit of a drug giving them super powers, he has little recourse. He`s only saved by a man dressed in black, who brutally murders his attackers with his sword. The man threatens Akira as well, only letting him leave with his life when Akira shows too much pride to beg for his life.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="122617" update="2014-10-12">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-10-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">休刑/ease</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Resting Penalty / Ease</title>
<summary>Rin finds Akira after he was dragged off by Takeru. Soon they encounter Tomoyuki, who is someone from Rin`s past. But he just ignores him and tells him to shut up. Akira and Rin have a short conversation as they get back to the hotel and meet up with Motomi. There Keisuke sees Akira and is happy is okay. Rin comes with a bag full of solids and water and asks them if they want to do something fun. They all eat and chat on the roof of a building. At nighttime, Shiki appears and slays a group Line addicts. One person yells that he has appeared and Rin jumps at hearing his name. Akira runs after Rin but instead encounters Shiki in a nearby alley. They have a short fight, which Akira end sup on the ground. Shiki picks him up and pins him against the wall, asking if he really wants to die. He then starts choking him, but Akira fights back by folding up and kicking him away. Shiki is amused by this and tells him he`ll play with him again soon. As he walks off, Akira is oddly energized by this and states "So that`s... Shiki."</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="122618" update="2014-10-12">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-10-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">狂争/igra</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lunatic Dispute / Igra</title>
<summary>Keisuke finally gets his tags, and while exiting the mansion is attacked by Takeru. Akira defends them and Takeru runs off. Akira picks up a cross. Akira is dragged off by Takeru. Takeru is revealed to be an ex-Bl@ster and is playing the Igura because he wants to win and be rich. Takeru takes back his cross which is a memento from his dead sister. Takeru calls Akira Lost because after winning Bl@ster, he always seems to be without emotions.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="122619" update="2014-10-12">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-10-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死街/toshima</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dead Town / Toshima</title>
<summary>Akira wakes up and finds Keisuke entering the room he is staying at. After finding out that Keisuke followed him to Toshima and refuses to leave, he gives Keisuke his knife. The go for a walk where they find Rin fighting a man. They leave, but is soon caught up by Rin who claims that they need to pay for entering his area, however he would let them off this once because they are new. Akira asks where he can get a weapon, and Rin gives him his. Rin brings them to one of the neutral zones where they meet Motomi and got to know the drug, Line - on the way they met the executioner and Kau. Rin then brings them to Arbitro`s Mansion so Keisuke can sign up. The mansion is filled with "pretty boys" statues. Keisuke leaves the mansion without pulling joining the game.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="124741" update="2014-10-12">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">決蔑/crack</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fixed Neglect / Crack</title>
<summary>A mysterious man offers Takeru the drug Line, which he takes. After waking and finding neither Rin nor Akira with him, Keisuke runs off to look for them while Akira is attacked and injured by a rain influenced group, only escaping (with a tag) when the leader of the group goes insane and collapses when he licks Akira`s blood. Shiki meets with Arbitro, and the former gives the latter a black case full what appears to be enhanced Line . After Motomi saves Akira (who was wondering if he did that to the leader of the group) the trouble of an encounter with the Executioners, the two decide to go to the hotel, where they meet up with Rin and Keisuke. Akira, irritated by the way Keisuke always makes light of the situation and puts himself down, yells at Keisuke who, feeling useless, runs away.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="124973" update="2014-10-12">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">怨鎖/desire</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chain of Jealousy / Desire</title>
<summary>A man (in the shadows) murders everyone in a club, meanwhile Takeru drinks Line. Akira goes around the city searching for Keisuke, Rin is back at the hotel, and overhears a conversation between line users. Akira continues to search and discovers the bodies of the men in the club, to which he is sickened. While walking into an alleyway he is attacked and beaten by Takeru; Takeru licks Akira’s blood and begins to choke then slowly retreats. Rin and Motomi have a conversation about drugs/city/life. Takeru thinks about his sister and regrets leaving her, but dreams of winning Igura for his family. He is then discovered by Keisuke, who superpowered on line, crushes Takeru`s skull. Keisuke then goes to meet Akira; whom he knocks out and then carries him off.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="125194" update="2014-10-12">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">因念/sever</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Caused Feeling / Sever</title>
<summary>It is revealed how Keisuke has changed, and why he had taken the drug line. After the flashback, Akira wakes up in the middle of an unknown house with his crazed best friend. After a long talk, Akira is knocked unconscious.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="125303" update="2010-11-18">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-11-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125304" update="2010-11-18">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-11-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125305" update="2010-11-18">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-10-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125306" update="2010-11-18">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-10-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125307" update="2010-11-18">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-10-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125308" update="2010-12-28">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-09-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125309" update="2010-12-28">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-09-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125340" update="2014-10-12">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">酷白/rein</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unjust White / Rein</title>
<summary>Shiki is revealed to be Rin`s half-brother and betrayed Rin by killing all of his friends. After Rin falls of the bridge, he sees a set of tags that is almost a royal flush (only the jack is missing)</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="125374" update="2010-11-20">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-11-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125605" update="2014-10-12">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-12-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">薬束/bond</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chemical Control / Bond</title>
<summary>Keisuke shows Akira all the tags that he gotten, and stating his desire to see more emotions, particularly the “troubled, agonized, dying” face. They begin to fight, throughout the battle Akira tells Keisuke how he really felt all this time which angers Keisuke even more. Akira gets his weapon knocked out of his hands causing him to get cut and bleed. Some blood gets onto Keisuke’s face and mouth which causes him to suffocate. Akira get some black flashes of his past, and snaps back into reality. He finds out that Keisuke is still alive and brings him to a bed, Akira watches over Keisuke until sun rise where Rin finds them and takes off with their tags in order to fight Il re. Arbitro recognize the jack, but still allows Rin to fight.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="125691" update="2010-12-01">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-11-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125705" update="2014-10-12">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-12-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">結脈/il re</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bound Pulse / Il Re</title>
<summary>Rin prepares to fight Il re which turns out to be Shiki but gets defeated quickly, Akira comes to the rescue as the military begins to bomb the place. Shiki saves Arbitro and questions him about Akira. Rin and Akira takes shelter in a abandoned warehouse where they agree to meet Motomi at the church - at first Rin refuse go and questions why Akira would help him after he betrayed him previously. Rin admits that he would have killed Keisuke to get the tags before. Akira points out that Rin refuse to believe in anyone anymore after Shiki betrayed him (at which Rin denied). Akira promise to not betray Rin and asks for his trust. Rin demands that he prove himself, which Akira counters by saying that Rin needs to trust him so he can prove himself. Rin threatens to kill Akira if he is betrayed. - Gunji and Kiriwar shows up. In order to escape, the two of them splits up, Gunji goes after Akira while Kiriwar goes after Rin. Akira gets beaten up badly and before he is killed, N comes to the rescue and carries him off to where Keisuke is. *Flashback* Akira meets Nano as a younger boy, in exchange for a promise to meet again, N gives him a knife *Return to present* Akira wakes up and finds Keisuke unconscious. Emma and Gwen shows up as they are on a mission to bring Premier (Nano) back with them, Emma admits to framing Akira for the murder and got him stuck in Toshima. She shoots Gwen for getting in her way then before she shoots Nano, he uses his arm to pierce through her body. Shiki shows up while Akira gets Keisuke and prepares to escape.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="125721" update="2010-12-04">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-12-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126048" update="2010-12-10">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-12-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126064" update="2014-10-12">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-12-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">増悪/convict</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Augment of Evil / Convict</title>
<summary>Shiki fights Nicole Premier, and ends up drinking Nicole`s blood, from which Line is made, which would normally drive people crazy or kill them. Shiki survives and goes looking for Akira. All the while, Arbitro, Kau, Kiriwar and Gunji watches from the roof of a nearby building. Shiki finds Akira and Keisuke as they are fleeing to safety. When Shiki tries to force Akira to come with him, Keisuke tries to protect Akira, but is killed by Shiki.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="126244" update="2010-12-17">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-12-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126245" update="2014-10-12">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-12-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">同至/beginning</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Equal Climax / Beginning</title>
<summary>After Keisuke`s death, Nicole Premier appear, the fight between Shiki and Nicole Premier continued. When Shiki claims to have surpassed Nicole Premier, he states that Shiki has in fact not won, but lost to himself, lost to his fear. Nicole Premier suffers heavy damages and disappears. Akira moves in to attack Shiki. Rin arrives and tries to help but gets stabbed in the leg. Rin tells Akira to leave, but Akira says he won`t leave Rin behind because that would be betraying Rin`s trust in him. Nicole Premier suddenly reappears, saving Akira and Rin, then helps them escape. Time Skip: Akira now has a "normal" job. Rin is in a hospital healing when Akira visits him and threatens to kill him if he breaks his promise of coming to visit him the next day. Out side of the hospital, Akira meets Motomi who invites him to go and eat with him. He tells Akira that there is a new Line and that their city may soon be overtaken by it. The episode ends with Akira going to fight Shiki (who is on a mountain surrounded by a open box of Line). Akira emphasize with the rest of society`s wish to live. He recognize that value of life only due to Keisuke`s death. Akira say that "this is not another person I am fighting. This is me".</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="126360" update="2010-12-24">
<epno type="3">C13</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-12-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 12</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
