<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7481" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-02-28</startdate>
<enddate>2010-03-07</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Pokemon Ranger: Hikari no Kiseki</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pokemon Ranger: Locus of Light</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pokemon Ranger: Paths of Light</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pokemon Ranger: Trail of Light</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Рейнджер покемонов: Путь света</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ポケモンレンジャー 光の軌跡</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Pokemon Ranger: Guardian Signs</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4728" type="Parent Story">Pocket Monsters: Diamond and Pearl</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.pokemon.co.jp/special/ranger3/</url>
<description>* Two specials based on homonym games.
http://anidb.net/ch24546 [Natsuya] receives a mission from Professor Hastings to protect Pokémon and destroy the Pokémon Nappers, who poach and control wild Pokémon.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="112">3.11</permanent>
<temporary count="115">5.26</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>45727.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15674</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8438</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.pokemon.co.jp/special/ranger3/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2801" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>RPG</name>
<description>Any anime that is based on a role-playing game aka RPG. A role-playing video game is a video game which includes elements of non-electronic role-playing games. The player assumes control of one or several fictional characters (a party) who have joined forces in order to perform quests and overcome a great number of challenges and enemies, usually monsters inspired by fantasy, and, to a lesser extent, science fiction and classic mythology. During the course of the game the characters, or avatars, which are generally defined by quantized characteristics, evolve and improve in that their various attributes increase, as well as by gaining more powerful artefacts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="381" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="16">8.07</rating>
<name>Sihorn</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rhyhorn is a rhinoceros like Pokemon with a rock like hide consisting of plates. Ryhorn stands on all four legs and evolves into Rhydon. Rhyhorn is a portmanteau of rhinoceros (which it resembles) and horn. Its spelling is also influenced by the rock rhyolite. Its Japanese name is a portmanteau of sai (犀), meaning rhinoceros and horn (ホーン). Rhyhorn are easily angered and will not hesitate to charge at what ever or who ever angered it. Rhyhorn are powerful enough to topple buildings with their tackle. Rhyhorn are prime examples of "more brawn than brains", as they often charge head first into things but forget why. In Gold, Silver, and Crystal, Brock uses a Rhyhorn to battle. There is also a Rhyhorn in the Brock Gym Leader set of the trading card game.</description>
<picture>243006.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="442" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="37">6.46</rating>
<name>Kentauros</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tauros is a bull known for its violent urges and rowdy, aggressive disposition in general, as supplied by a tremendous amount of natural stamina. Any given Tauros finds it impossible to keep up its spirits in life without near-constant rampaging. It always tries to find opponent Pokémon to battle outright to serve this purpose, but if it is alone, it will instead concentrate on charging at and knocking down thick trees to calm itself. By locking horns with other Tauros, it fights to assert dominance in a herd. The protector of the herd is usually noted by battle torn horns. As Tauros is based on a bull, it is a male-only Pokémon; its female equivalent is the more cowlike Miltank.
Tauros has a special habit that specifically affects its ability to battle, both in the wild and in trainer-directed Pokémon battles: It whips itself with its three long snapping tails. When it targets an enemy, it heightens its will to battle by whipping its own backside with its tails before charging at full speed.
In the anime, Ash Ketchum captures a herd of thirty Tauros in the Safari Zone (though the episode which features this was banned in America due to its flagrant gun use and politically incorrect humor). They usually remain in Professor Oak`s fields, Ash occasionally picks one up for various tournaments or important battles.</description>
<picture>243020.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="616" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Kirinriki</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Girafarig is a herbivore that resembles a giraffe. It is yellow with dark brown spots for the front half, while the back half is dark brown with yellow spots. The back section is smaller on the females. Most notably, the end of Girafarig`s tail has a simplistic head. The head has a small brain of its own, but can only rely on instinct. If a person gets near the head, it reacts to the person`s scent and bites. The head doesn`t need to sleep, so it watches over its surroundings twenty four hours a day. Girafarig`s name is a palindrome in both English and Japanese, although the Japanese name`s palindromic nature is not evident in romanised form.</description>
<picture>243086.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="843" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="16">8.63</rating>
<name>Raikou</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Raikou is one of the three "Legendary Beasts" that are featured in Pokémon Gold, Silver, and Crystal. According to legend, the Legendary Beasts were reincarnated by Ho-Oh from the spirits of three Pokémon which died in the fire that gave Burnt Tower its name. They are awakened in this tower in their first appearance. Another myth maintains that Raikou descended to earth together with a lightning bolt. Each Beast personifies a force of nature - Raikou, in particular, embodies the speed of lightning.
Like many Electric-type Pokémon, Raikou stores tremendous energy inside its body. This grants it extraordinary vitality, allowing it to run continuously across the land while shooting off electricity from the rain cloud that is on its back. Raikou`s roar is aptly described as "thunderous": it is loud enough to create shock waves and shake the ground as if actual thunder had struck.
Raikou is featured in a special anime episode called Raikou - The Legend of Thunder that forms the first three episodes of Pokémon Chronicles. In the special, two Team Rocket agents named Attila and Hun scheme to capture Raikou with a device that reflects and deflects energy blasts. Three New Bark Town trainers risk their own lives to try and save Raikou. It is thought by the trainers that Raikou attempts to guard other electric Pokémon from danger whenever possible.</description>
<picture>243121.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="877" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Wakasyamo</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Combusken is the evolved form of Torchic. Combusken`s legs are both fast and powerful, and to keep them at peak physical condition, many run through nearby fields and mountains to stay agile and strong. By doing this, Combusken can kick up to 10 times per second, not giving up easily. Like Torchic, Combusken has a place within its body that stores and produces incredibly hot flames, It allows it to spew flames from its beak and to kick continuously until an opponent either faints or gives up.
In the anime, May owned a Combusken that evolved from her Torchic to protect Ash`s Corphish, and it later evolved into a Blaziken.</description>
<picture>243225.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1093" type="appears in" update="2020-01-07">
<name>Latios</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Latios is the male Eon Pokémon. They are a blue and white, dragon-like, legendary Pokémon with small arms and feet, and spiky fighter aircraft-like wings on their back. They appear to have white flesh underneath their blue carapace. They appear extremely similar to Latias, only blue, and more angular. It is said that by folding their arms close to their body, they can fly faster than a jet. Latios are all male.
Latios` intelligence allows them to understand human languages. They have a docile temperament and dislike fighting. A Latios will only open his heart to a trainer with a compassionate spirit. Their signature attack, Luster Purge, may reduce the target`s special defense. Like Latias, Latios can also render themselves invisible.
Latios, along with Latias, have a starring role in the movie Pokémon Heroes as guardians of Altomare, a city modeled after Venice, Italy. At the end of the film, Latios sacrifices himself to protect Altomare from a tremendous tsunami. It is notable that Latios marks the first actual Pokémon death in the anime series so far (the imaginary Entei and Celebi do not count). This may have been the fact that Latios is based on Jesus in characteristics.</description>
<picture>64498.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="1110" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Mukuhawk</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Staraptor is the final evolution of the Starly evolutionary line. It has a savage nature, where it consistently challenges larger Pokémon to battle. Its strong leg and wing muscles allow it to fly easily while gripping small Pokémon.
In the anime, Paul`s brother Reggie owns a Staraptor.</description>
<picture>243342.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1177" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Zugaidos</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cranidos is a Pokémon that first lived in jungles one hundred million years before the settings of the games. It was resurrected from a fossil similar to an iron ball. It uses its iron-like skull to head butt its prey. It evolves into Rampardos at level 30.</description>
<picture>243352.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="24546" type="main character in" update="2011-01-13">
<name>Natsuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Natsuya is an experienced Pokémon Ranger who is sent out on important missions. During a mission to saves Latios, Red Eye managed to stun Natsuya and the Mukuhawk he was riding on and he plummeted into the ocean.
Natsuya was tossed up on shore where he encountered Ukulele Pichu hiding behind a tree. The Pichu watched quietly until Natsuya approached it and tried to capture it.
During a mission to investigate the mysterious eruption in a volcano, Natsuya encounters a wild Heatran. He attempts to capture it but he looses his Capture Styler which James eventually finds. Natsuya managed to use the Ranger Sign for Feraligatr and the Feraligatr takes him to shore where Ash and his friends are camped out.
Natsuya introduces himself and that he is a Pokémon Ranger on a mission. Ash and his friend decide to help him out but as usual Team Rocket interferes. By working together, Natsuya is able to recover his Capture Styler and capture the wild Heatran.</description>
<picture>63190.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27512" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-25">
<name>Ukulele Pichu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Natsuya was tossed up on shore where he encountered Ukulele Pichu hiding behind a tree. The Pichu watched quietly until Natsuya approached it and tried to capture it. Pichu wasn`t too happy with the prospect of being seen and captured by Natsuya and it began charging its electric attack.</description>
<picture>64420.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27513" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-25">
<name>Shinbara Kyouju</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Professor Shinbara was first seen in the anime in the Ranger Union. Professor Shinbara is the creator of the Capture Styler and he gave Pokémon Ranger Natsuya the latest model before he went on a mission to rescue Latios.</description>
<picture>64421.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27514" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-25">
<name>Red Eye</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Red Eye is the leader of the Pokémon Nappers (ポケモンナッパーズ). After Pokémon Ranger Natsuya managed to rescue Latios and allow it to get away, Red Eye appeared and shocked Natsuya and the Mukuhawk he was riding which caused Natsuya to fall into the ocean.</description>
<picture>64422.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27515" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-25">
<name>Pokemon Nappers</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pokémon Nappers are an evil group of poachers that attempt to capture Pokémon for profit. They are lead by Red Eye and mainly operate in the Oblivia region.
While attempting to capture flying Pokémon they use hovering devices which are equipped with handles for balance with a trigger for activating its weapons.</description>
<picture>64423.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27516" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-25">
<name>Booker</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Booker lives at his home on the beach on Cocona Village. He is a carpenter by trade and is quite good at building wooden boats and bridges. Pokémon Ranger Ben encountered him on Dolce Island and Booker offered to lend him his boat so that he could go after the Pokémon Pinchers on Renbow Island.</description>
<picture>64424.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="117460" update="2010-04-05">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2010-02-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117461" update="2010-06-24">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2010-03-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133047" update="2011-09-15">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2010-11-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Pokemon Ranger: Guardian Signs</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
