<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7485" restricted="false">
<type>Music Video</type>
<episodecount>7</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-05-26</startdate>
<enddate>2010-05-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gurren Lagann Parallel Works 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Gurren Lagann Parallel Works 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">그렌라간 Parallel Works 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">ttgl pw 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">グレンラガン パラレルワークス 2</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6082" type="Prequel">Gurren Lagann Parallel Works</anime>
<anime id="4575" type="Other">Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.gurren-lagann.net/gurrepala2/</url>
<description>In the http://anidb.net/a6082 [first project], several staffers of the Gurren Lagann anime created eight spinoff shorts that explored the theme of "multiple universes" with background music from the http://anidb.net/a4575 [television series].
For Parallel Works 2, a different set of animators use all-new background music and character songs.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="682">4.80</permanent>
<temporary count="685">6.25</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>224563.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15324</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8348</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gurren-lagann.net/gurrepala2/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>List_of_Gurren_Lagann_episodes#Gurren_Lagann_Parallel_Works</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>天元突破グレンラガン#グレンラガン_パラレルワークス</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11849</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1393" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-03-08">
<name>drill</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4469" parentid="2644" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-29">
<name>gattai</name>
<description>Gattai is when two fighting spirits collide and unite, when a man`s soul is ablaze!
When you are about to get your asses kicked by the big bad evil, it`s time to show your true fighting spirit and gattai, literally combine with your mecha to become at least ten times as powerful and kick the big bad evil`s ass.</description>
<picurl>66429.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-26">
<name>alternating animation style</name>
<description>The animation style in this show may change between scenes, usually making the anime experimental in a way. This may be a form of artistic visualisation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6399" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-25">
<name>episodic</name>
<description>An episodic anime consists of many successive short arcs that are generally 1-2 episodes in length, with strong plot continuity within each arc but generally little continuity from one arc to the next. For long shows (well upwards of 50 episodes), the episode count constraint is less tight; for example, a show with close to 250 episodes would also be considered episodic if it consisted of a majority of arcs of up to 3 or maybe 4 episodes and possibly also very few slightly longer arcs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="469" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-26">
<rating votes="660">7.68</rating>
<name>Simon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Simon is a fourteen year-old digger from Jeeha village. Although he is initially looked down upon because of it, Simon excels at drilling through the ground, and the drill quickly becomes his trademark symbol. One day, he finds a mysterious drill-shaped item, which is later revealed to be the "Core Drill", for a head-shaped Gunmen he also finds buried in the soil. With the help of the small Gunmen, Kamina, and Yoko, he fights off a much larger Gunmen that falls into the village. In the process of defeating the invader, they reach the surface world. Prior to the time-skip, Simon is mostly depicted as merely following Kamina`s lead and often acting as a counter-balance to Kamina`s impulsiveness. An unfortunate accident forces Simon to mature and take up a leadership role within Team Dai-Gurren.</description>
<picture>14766.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="470" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-16">
<rating votes="1477">8.55</rating>
<name>Youko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl from Jeeha`s neighbouring village of Littner, who had been chasing the Gunmen which entered Jeeha village. She wields an extensive arsenal of firearms and has previous experience fighting Gunmen. She uses her marksmanship from afar to assist Kamina and Simon, while they pilot their respective Gunmen.</description>
<picture>14767.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="471" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-10">
<rating votes="530">6.69</rating>
<name>Nia Teppelin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nia is a mysterious young girl found by Simon sleeping in a capsule in the middle of a dump site. She has had no prior contact with humans except her father. She is very curious, pure and innocent, because of a sheltered childhood in a peaceful environment away from all the battles occurring in the outside world, and because she had only recently gained sentience. During her travels with Team Dai-Gurren, she discovers the harsh realities of the world and has a very close relationship with Simon throughout the story.</description>
<picture>14768.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="472" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-29">
<rating votes="224">1.74</rating>
<name>Rossiu Adai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A boy from another underground village, Adai, in which the people worship the Gunmen as gods. A modest but intelligent person, he`s often seen looking after the young Gimmy and Darry. When the twins are chosen to leave the village, he decides to go with them, thus the trio joins Team Gurren. Before he leaves, the village elder gives him a book that seems to withhold some secrets from humanity`s past, with the task to find someone able to read it, as no one in his village can decipher its content. After Kamina`s death, Rossiu temporarily begins piloting Gurren in his place, though initially has trouble, due to Simon`s breakdown</description>
<picture>14771.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="508" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-26">
<rating votes="184">6.95</rating>
<name>Kittan Bachika</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kittan Bachika is the oldest of the Black Siblings. During his first encounter with Team Gurren, he mistakenly confuses Kamina for a Beastman. This is reconciled, when it is discovered that Kamina is piloting the Gunmen, Gurren. Shortly after, the two teams (the Black Siblings and Team Gurren) come into contact with the sixteen-headed enemy Gunmen, whom the Black Siblings had crossed paths with earlier. After the eventual defeat of the enemy Gunmen, the two teams part ways.</description>
<picture>14807.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="514" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="102">3.22</rating>
<name>Kinon Bachika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kinon is the second oldest of Kittan`s younger sisters. After Team Dai-Gurren`s capture of Dai-Gunzan, she takes up a position within its control tower, monitoring the radar. She seems to be the calmest and smartest member of the Black Siblings.</description>
<picture>14812.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1493" type="appears in" update="2017-10-08">
<rating votes="42">8.50</rating>
<name>Lagann</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Lagann is Simon`s personal Gunmen which he finds in the first episode while digging tunnels in his village. It received its name, Lagann (羅顔), meaning "enveloping face", from Kamina and draws power from the Core Drill, a small golden drill Simon uses similar to an ignition key. Unlike any other Gunmen in the series, the Lagann sports a unique cockpit and stands just short of an average human adult as opposed to the others which are all mostly the sizes of small buildings or larger. This physical handicap, in tandem with the usually average level of fighting spirit supplied to it by Simon, puts the Lagann at a considerable disadvantage in single combat against enemy Gunmen. However, when Simon is driven to give his best during combat the Lagann`s power increases exponentially, giving it the unique ability to generate drills from nearly any part of its frame. Lagann`s other and most notable power is the "Lagann Impact", its trademark ability to combine with other machines by piercing them with its drills. It`s through this ability that the titular Gurren Lagann is created, along with the other more large-scale mechas in the series.</description>
<picture>16032.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1541" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-26">
<rating votes="93">5.91</rating>
<name>Darry Aday</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Darry Aday is a girl from Aday Village, who used to be cared for by Rossiu. She is Gimmy`s twin sister and has a good bond with him. As a young girl, she was shy and quiet and used to cling to a plush doll, which she carried with her at all times. After the timeskip, however, she is much more confident and has left her old personality behind. As a Grapearl pilot, she is careful, calm and perceptive, and puts more thought and planning into her actions than Gimmy.</description>
<picture>16077.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1543" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-26">
<rating votes="79">3.78</rating>
<name>Gimmy Aday</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gimmy Aday is a boy from Aday Village, who used to be cared for by Rossiu. When new children were born into the village, the population exceeded its limit of 50, which mandated that two people be removed and sent to the surface. Since Gimmy and Darry had no parents, the village elder chose them to leave the village, however, Rossiu decided to go with them. The pair of twins have a very good bond with each other, and were often left to their own devices around Dai-Gurren, except when they were with older girls, such as Yoko or Nia. After the timeskip, Gimmy and Darry become important Grapearl pilots, often fighting together. Gimmy tends to be more impulsive and reckless, which sometimes puts the duo in trouble.</description>
<picture>16078.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1544" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-26">
<rating votes="88">6.20</rating>
<name>Kiyal Bachika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The youngest of the Black Siblings.</description>
<picture>16079.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1545" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="74">5.94</rating>
<name>Kiyoh Littner</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The oldest of Kittan`s younger sisters.</description>
<picture>16080.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1561" type="appears in" update="2008-12-26">
<rating votes="83">7.58</rating>
<name>Lordgenome</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A seemingly cruel and ruthless tyrant who employs legions of creatures known as Beastmen to systemically eradicate all human-kind on the planet surface, commanding his armies from a gigantic funnel-shaped castle called Teppelin.</description>
<picture>16099.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1682" type="appears in" update="2008-12-28">
<rating votes="42">8.60</rating>
<name>Gurren Lagann</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Gurren Lagann, the titular mech of the series, is piloted jointly by two pilots for most of the story, with the Lagann portion always operated by the series` main protagonist Simon and the Gurren piloted by Kamina initially and then various other characters after his death. The mech was originally formed as a hotblooded response from Kamina to the Enki`s initial two-headed configuration.</description>
<picture>16226.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1817" type="appears in" update="2009-01-01">
<rating votes="2">4.54</rating>
<name>Kiyalunga</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Kiyalunga, named for and piloted by Kittan`s sister Kiyal, has the ability to transform into a lance and shield for use by the King Kittan, with Kittan referring to the formation as the King Kittan Deluxe. A homage to this Gunman is seen when Kittan piloted the Space King Kittan, where wielded weapons that resembles the Kiyalunga`s lance and shield transformation.</description>
<picture>16408.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="117572" update="2010-06-05">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2010-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">The sense of Wonder</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sense of Wonder</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">The sense of Wonder</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Sense of Wonder</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117573" update="2010-06-05">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2010-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キタンゼロ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kittan Zero</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">키탄 제로</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kittan Zero</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117574" update="2010-06-05">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2010-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガンメンシンフォニア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gunmen Symphony</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">간멘 심포니아</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gunmen Symphonia</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117575" update="2010-06-05">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2010-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キヤルのマジカルタイム, 三分前.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kiyal`s Magical Time, Three Minutes Before</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">키얄의 매지컬 타임~ 3분전</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiyal no Magical Time, Sanpun Zen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117576" update="2010-06-05">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2010-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="5">1.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">BIG BUILDING</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Building</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">BIG BUILDING</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Big Building</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117577" update="2010-06-05">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2010-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さよならダイグレン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dai-Gurren, Good Bye</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">안녕 다이그렌</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sayonara Dai-Gurren</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117578" update="2010-06-05">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2010-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オレノxxxハウチュウヒトツ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My xxx is the Best in the Universe</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">나의 xxx는 우주유일!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore no xxx wa Uchuu Hitotsu</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
