<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7490" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-07-11</startdate>
<enddate>2010-09-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sengoku Basara Ni</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Sengoku Basara Two</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Sengoku Basara 2</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">战国BASARA 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">戦国BASARA弐</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Sengoku Basara: Samurai Kings 2</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">战国BASARA 贰</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8203" type="Sequel">Gekijouban Sengoku Basara: The Last Party</anime>
<anime id="6284" type="Prequel">Sengoku Basara</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="468675">better than 1st season, for sure.
it has a better plot and we get to have some glimpses on some characters` backgrounds.
personally, would have prefered more realistic fights.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.sengokubasara.tv/index2.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="2949" type="Character Design">Ookubo Tooru</name>
<name id="103" type="Series Composition">Mutou Yasuyuki</name>
<name id="1283" type="Original Work">Capcom</name>
<name id="8586" type="Direction">Nomura Kazuya</name>
<name id="6722" type="Music">Sawano Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="721" type="Animation Work">Production I.G</name>
<name id="2949" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ookubo Tooru</name>
</creators>
<description>The deadly confrontation with the Devil King, http://anidb.net/ch5953 [Oda Nobunaga] is over, but the struggle for supremacy continues in Warring Countries-era Japan, as the armies of http://anidb.net/ch5951 [Takeda Shingen] and http://anidb.net/ch5957 [Uesugi Kenshin] repeatedly engage battle at Kawanakajima.
Meanwhile, on the easternmost side of the battlefield, two outstanding characters bound by destiny -one clad in azure and the other in crimson- are about to clash in a long-awaited, decisive duel.
Then a sudden dispatch informs that a huge army has surrounded the forces of Takeda, Uesugi and http://anidb.net/ch5949 [Date] at Kakanakajima. Their leader is http://anidb.net/ch18083 [Toyotomi Hideyoshi], the man who inherited Nobunaga`s dreams and ambitions, and who is now going to bring havoc over Japan once again!
Source: English Production IG Homepage</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="974">6.19</permanent>
<temporary count="983">7.23</temporary>
<review count="1">6.50</review>
</ratings>
<picture>54668.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11431</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9630</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>10483</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>6634</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4737</identifier>
<identifier>wbdtvy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.production-ig.co.jp/works/basara2/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.sengokubasara.tv/index2.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Sengoku_Basara_(anime)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>戦国BASARA</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1969</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>337160</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12743</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1589" parentid="2622" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-08">
<name>samurai</name>
<picurl>244341.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2572" parentid="2282" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-09">
<name>ninja</name>
<description>A ninja was a covert agent or mercenary of feudal Japan specializing in unorthodox arts of war.
The functions of the ninja included espionage, sabotage, infiltration, and assassination, as well as open combat in certain situations.
The ninja, using covert methods of waging war, were contrasted with the samurai, who had strict rules about honor and combat.</description>
<picurl>244347.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2687" parentid="2641" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-02-05">
<name>Sengoku period</name>
<description>The Sengoku period (戦国時代, Sengoku jidai) or Warring States period in Japanese history was a time of social upheaval, political intrigue, and nearly constant military conflict that lasted roughly from the middle of the 15th century to the beginning of the 17th century. The name "Sengoku" was adopted by Japanese historians in reference to the Warring States period in Chinese history (Sengoku jidai (戦国時代) in Japanese) which preceded the unification of China. Likewise, the Sengoku period in Japan would eventually lead to the unification of political power under the Tokugawa shogunate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3327" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-08">
<name>manly</name>
<description>Masculinity is possessing qualities or characteristics considered typical of or appropriate to a man.
Typical characteristics associated with masculinity are: courage, a strong physique, competitive, strong willed, and a sense of honor.
Very important for being considered masculine however is the ability to inspire respect from your fellow brethren and/or being perceived as a virile man by the opposite sex.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6029" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-04-08">
<name>mundane made awesome</name>
<description>Sometimes normal just doesn`t cut it. Eating: you put food in your mouth and chew. Playing sports: you throw a ball around. You need to make it awesome, no matter how mundane it is.
Let`s throw in some gripping orchestral music, lighting changes, different camera angles, something! Don`t write like a man, write like an evil overlord! Exaggerate your expressions and gestures, speak with excessive intonation, and if all else fails, throw in some close-ups, slow motion, and ominous Latin chanting! With practice, even you can turn something like eating chips into an epic battle of light and dark, blinding the viewer with sheer awesomeness.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>149443.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="5949" type="main character in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="127">8.63</rating>
<name>Date Masamune</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Date Masamune (September 5, 1567 - June 27, 1636) was a Japanese samurai of the Azuchi-Momoyama period through early Edo period. Heir to a long line of powerful daimyo in the Tohoku region, he went on to found the modern-day city of Sendai. An outstanding tactician, he was made all the more iconic for his missing eye, for which he was often called dokuganryuu (独眼竜), or the "one-eyed dragon."</description>
<picture>93620.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="259" picture="17082.jpg">Nakai Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5950" type="main character in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="82">7.56</rating>
<name>Sanada Yukimura</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sanada Saemon-no-Suke Yukimura (真田 左衛門佐 幸村 ,Sanada Yukimura?, 1567 - June 3, 1615) was a Japanese samurai, second son of the Sengoku period daimyo Sanada Masayuki (1544-1611). His proper name was Sanada Nobushige (真田信繁), named after Takeda Shingen`s younger brother Takeda Nobushige (武田信繁), who was a brave and respected warrior. Sanada Yukimura was called "A Hero who may appear once in hundred years" and "crimson demon of war", and Shimazu Tadatsune (島津忠恒, arguably the best performer in the invasion of Korea) called him the "number one warrior in Japan." ("日本一の兵", 兵 means soldier originally, but here it is read as "tsuwamono" which means samurai or warrior, so it is not appropriate to translate it as soldier.)</description>
<picture>93619.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="381" picture="186189.jpg">Hoshi Souichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5951" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="29">7.10</rating>
<name>Takeda Shingen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takeda Shingen (武田信玄) (December 1, 1521 - May 13, 1573) of Shinano and Kai Provinces, was a preeminent daimyo or feudal lord with military prestige who sought for the control of Japan in the late stage of Sengoku or "warring states" period.</description>
<picture>93616.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5952" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="31">6.46</rating>
<name>Sarutobi Sasuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sarutobi Sasuke (猿飛佐助) was a famous ninja featured in many Japanese children`s stories from 1911 to 1925. The character was immortalized in contemporary Japanese culture by the 1962 Sampei Shirato comic of the same name. Thereafter the name Sasuke became something of a default ninja moniker.</description>
<picture>93615.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5957" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="14">6.39</rating>
<name>Uesugi Kenshin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Uesugi Kenshin (上杉謙信, February 18, 1530-April 19, 1578) was a daimyo who ruled Echigo province in the Sengoku period of Japan.
He was one of the many powerful lords of the Sengoku period. He is famed for his prowess on the battlefield, the legendary rivalry with Takeda Shingen, his military expertise, strategy and his belief in the god of war — Bishamonten. In fact, many of his followers and others believed him to be the avatar of Bishamonten, and called Kenshin god of war.</description>
<picture>93610.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5958" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-06">
<rating votes="52">7.61</rating>
<name>Kasuga</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93612.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="328" picture="17164.jpg">Kuwatani Natsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5959" type="main character in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="18">5.32</rating>
<name>Maeda Keiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Keiji Maeda, also known as Maeda Toshimasu, is Maeda Toshiie`s and Matsu`s adopted nephew, and occasionally fights with them. He has a mysterious past with Toyotomi Hideyoshi and Takenaka Hanbei. Keiji is what people call a happy-go-lucky man. He enjoys festivals, as well as pulling pranks on Toshiie and others. Despite his demeanor towards his adopted family, he loves them, though sometimes shows resentment towards them due to their objection to his lifestyle. Accompanying him is a small monkey named Yumekichi.</description>
<picture>93590.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="138" picture="23200.jpg">Morita Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5960" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="12">4.56</rating>
<name>Maeda Toshiie</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93588.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1441" picture="18827.jpg">Tsuboi Tomohiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5961" type="appears in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="57">5.11</rating>
<name>Oichi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>O-Ichi (1547 - 1583) lived during the Sengoku Period of Japanese history. She was the sister-in-law of Nouhime (daughter of Saitou Dousan) and the younger sister of Oda Nobunaga. Oichi was renowned for her beauty. She was descended from the Taira clan and Fujiwara clan.</description>
<picture>93614.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18081" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-06">
<rating votes="21">6.12</rating>
<name>Matsu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93587.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="160" picture="30490.jpg">Kaida Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18082" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-06">
<rating votes="3">9.81</rating>
<name>Takenaka Hanbee</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takenaka Hanbee is Hideyoshi Toyotomi`s strategist. He is intelligent and extremely loyal to Hideyoshi. Around his enemies, he is narcissistic, cold and very cruel. Given the chance, he can wipe them all out by swinging his weapon. His favorite methods of assassination are back-stabbing his opponents at his weapon`s reach and snaring his opponents when they are not looking. Despite his physique, he suffers from tuberculosis. He is somewhat similar to Zorro in style and look (the face mask). His weapon is a whipsword.</description>
<picture>93597.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18083" type="main character in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="2">6.57</rating>
<name>Toyotomi Hideyoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93594.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30976" type="appears in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="11">6.29</rating>
<name>Tokugawa Ieyasu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93593.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30977" type="appears in" update="2017-11-16">
<rating votes="7">7.64</rating>
<name>Ishida Mitsunari</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93596.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40265" type="appears in" update="2012-09-06">
<rating votes="5">5.53</rating>
<name>Yumekichi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93589.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="328" picture="17164.jpg">Kuwatani Natsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40268" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-06">
<rating votes="5">1.88</rating>
<name>Magobee</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93622.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="195" picture="17009.jpg">Sakamaki Mitsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40270" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-06">
<rating votes="2">4.88</rating>
<name>Samanosuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93621.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="298" picture="216156.jpg">Tokumoto Yukitoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40271" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-06">
<rating votes="8">2.70</rating>
<name>Bunshichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93624.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4741" picture="45560.jpg">Konno Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40273" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="7">3.77</rating>
<name>Mouri Motonari</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93591.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2218" picture="226178.jpg">Nakahara Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40274" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="37">7.50</rating>
<name>Katakura Kojuurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93586.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40275" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-06">
<rating votes="2">4.88</rating>
<name>Yoshinao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93623.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2474" picture="228619.jpg">Endou Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40276" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="10">7.77</rating>
<name>Chousokabe Motochika</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93595.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2219" picture="23794.jpg">Ishino Ryuuzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48525" type="appears in" update="2012-09-06">
<rating votes="9">2.79</rating>
<name>Honda Tadakatsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93602.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48529" type="appears in" update="2012-09-06">
<name>Shimazu Yoshihiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93606.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="604" picture="154161.jpg">Ogata Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48530" type="appears in" update="2012-09-06">
<rating votes="4">8.31</rating>
<name>Matsunaga Hisahide</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93607.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48531" type="appears in" update="2012-09-06">
<name>Fuma Kotaro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93608.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48532" type="appears in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<name>Miyamoto Musashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93609.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="117657" update="2010-04-12">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode T1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117658" update="2017-12-15">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">乱世再び! 裂界武帝・豊臣秀吉降臨!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Troubled Times Once Again! Advent of the Great Cataclysmic Warlord, Toyotomi Hideyoshi!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ransei Futatabi! Rekkai Butei Toyotomi Hideyoshi Kourin!</title>
<summary>Old rivalries resume at Kawanakajima as Sanada Yukimura battles Date Masamune and Takeda Shingen squares off against Uesugi Kenshin.  Meanwhile, the warlord Toyotomi Hideyoshi seeks ultimate domination in order to unify Japan.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119622" update="2018-07-01">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蒼紅決死戦! 激闘の果てに吹く風の音よ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Azure and Crimson Do-or-Die Battle! To the Sound of the Breeze at the End of the Fierce Struggle!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soukou Kesshisen! Gekitou no Hate ni Fuku Kaze no Oto yo!</title>
<summary>Battles are raging all across Japan! As Date faces off against Toyotomi at Odawara Castle, Sanada fights Mori’s mobile fortress. Meanwhile, Katakura finally gets his showdown with Takenaka.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119623" update="2018-07-01">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">覇走豊臣大本隊! 本気の慶次, 断腸の抜刀!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Toyotomi`s Great Main Army Dashes for Supremacy! Earnest Keiji Draws Sword in Heartbreak!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hasou Toyotomi Daihontai! Honki no Keiji, Danchou no Battou!!</title>
<summary>Sarutobi and Kasugarun run into trouble after making their way into Osaka Castle. Meanwhile, Mori unleashes the true power of his mobile fortress, much to Sanada’s  alarm.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119624" update="2018-07-01">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">復活の若き虎! 改造大要塞・日輪の脅威, 東へ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Young Tiger Restored! The Great Fortress Rebuilt: The Menace of the Sun Heads East!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukkatsu no Wakaki Tora! Kaizou Daiyosai: Nichirin no Kyoui, Higashi e!!</title>
<summary>As Date and Chosokabe adjust their plans to attack Osaka, Mori plots to attack Toyotomi from the west. Meanwhile,  Takeda and Uesugi attempt to outmaneuver Toyotomi in the east.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119625" update="2017-12-15">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">竜と鬼 尾張の激突! 爆走!伊達・長曾我部連合軍!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dragon and Ogre: Clash and Roar in Owari! The Combined Force of Date and Chosokabe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryuu to Oni: Owari no Gekitotsu! Bakusou! Date-Chousokabe Rengougun!!</title>
<summary>Unaware of each other`s identities, Date and Chosokabe clash! Meanwhile, Mori plots to further his own agenda while playing ally to Toyotomi - but Toyotomi and Takenaka have plans of their own.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119626" update="2018-07-01">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">友垣との哀しき再会 猛執刻まれし日の記憶</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Sad Reunion with a Friend: Memory of the Day Etched with Blinding Obsession</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomogaki to no Kanashiki Saikai: Moushuu Kizamareshi Hi no Kioku</title>
<summary>Keiji reflects on the long history he shares with Toyotomi. Meanwhile, Sanada is allowed an opportunity to get to know Miyamoto and Shimazu better, and also gains some surprising insight into Mori.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119627" update="2018-07-01">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最南端・薩摩の地へ! 幸村, 新たなる漢の出逢い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the Southernmost Land of Satsuma! A New Encounter as a Man for Yukimura!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sainantan Satsuma no Chi e! Yukimura, Arata naru Otoko no Deai</title>
<summary>While traveling to Osaka, Date encounters both Kai and Takeda. Meanwhile, Sanada is still shaken by Oyamada`s death, but presses on to Satsuma in order to carry out his mission.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119628" update="2018-07-01">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">脅威の豊臣・毛利同盟! 海原を裂く覇の豪拳!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Menacing Toyotomi-Mori Alliance! The Powerful Fist of Supremacy Cleaves the Sea!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoui no Toyotomi-Mouri Doumei! Unabara o Saku Ha no Gouken!!</title>
<summary>Toyotomi Hideyoshi takes on Chosokabe`s seafaring fortress, the Fugaku. Meanwhile, Sanada is compelled to stray from his mission once again, and Keiji reunites with his aunt and uncle in Kaga.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119629" update="2018-07-01">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">誓願の刻印! 独眼竜対軍神 人取橋の対峙!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Engraved Pledge! The One-Eyed Dragon vs. the War God: Confrontation at Hitotoribashi!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seigan no Kokuin! Dokuganryuu tai Gunshin Hitotoribashi no Taiji!</title>
<summary>When Date’s path is blocked by Uesugi, he has a chance to reflect on the history he shares with Katakura. Meanwhile, Toyotomi prepares to invade Shikoku, and Sanada realizes that time is running out.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119630" update="2017-12-15">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">安土城の亡霊!? 幸村を襲う嘆きと魔の咆哮!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ghost of Azuchi Castle?! The Lamentation and Howl of Evil That Assail Yukimura!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Azuchijou no Bourei!? Yukimura o Osou Nageki to Ma no Houkou!</title>
<summary>Sanada Yukimura encounters someone he thought was long dead. Meanwhile, Keiji’s contemplation of the past leads to a decision, and Mori Motonari and Takenaka Hanbei conclude their negotiations.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119631" update="2017-12-15">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">慶次対利家! 手取川に咽ぶゆずれぬ想い!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Keiji vs. Toshiie! Tedorigawa Choked with Unequivocal Ideals!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Keiji Tai Toshiie! Tetorigawa ni Musebu Yuzurenu Omoi!</title>
<summary>Uesugi Kenshin faces Maeda Toshiie`s invading army! Meanwhile, in the north, Date Masamune prepares to engage Katakura Kojuro, but finds one more obstacle in his way.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="119632" update="2018-07-01">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">失われた右目 斬り裂かれた竜の背中!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Lost Right Eye: The Dragon`s Back Rent Asunder!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ushinawareta Migime Kirisakareta Ryuu no Senaka</title>
<summary>Under attack from all sides, Date Masamune is at a severe disadvantage without his strategist. Meanwhile, Takeda Shingen and Sanada Yukimura are on the move and preparing to outflank Toyotomi.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="120119" update="2010-08-17">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-07-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120120" update="2010-08-17">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-07-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121577" update="2010-08-29">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130149" update="2017-12-15">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2011-04-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">竜虎, 頂の誓い! 熱き未来へ駆ける魂!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dragon and Tiger: Oath of Victory! Souls Racing Towards a Blazing Future!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryuuko, Itadaki no Chikai! Atsuki Mirai e Kakeru Tamashii!!</title>
<summary>The action is over-the-top as Date and Yukimura take on a group of disguised fighters. While Date may realize the the masked men are actually Sasuke, Takeda, and Kojuro, Yukimura appears to have no clue.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="137777" update="2015-12-13">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<rating votes="1">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Tsukiyo no Katakura-kun 1 - Harvest</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137778" update="2012-03-12">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<rating votes="1">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Tsukiyo no Katakura-kun 2 - Delusion</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137779" update="2012-03-12">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<rating votes="1">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Tsukiyo no Katakura-kun 3 - Precision</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137780" update="2012-03-12">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>3</length>
<rating votes="1">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Tsukiyo no Katakura-kun 4 - Outwitted</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137781" update="2012-03-12">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>3</length>
<rating votes="1">3.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Tsukiyo no Katakura-kun 5 - Crash Landing</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137782" update="2012-03-12">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>4</length>
<rating votes="1">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Tsukiyo no Katakura-kun 6 - Showdown</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137783" update="2012-03-12">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>4</length>
<rating votes="1">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Tsukiyo no Katakura-kun 7 - They Return</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
