<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7507" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-05-28</startdate>
<enddate>2014-02-08</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Tezuka Osamu no Buddha</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">手塚治虫のブッダ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Osamu Tezuka`s Buddha</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Bouddha - Le grand départ</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Buda, el Gran Viaje</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="3184" approval="1" total="5">Tezuka Osamu no Kyuuyaku Seisho Monogatari: In the Beginning</anime>
<anime id="1553" approval="1" total="4">Hi no Tori</anime>
<anime id="8937" approval="1" total="2">Asura</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://wwws.warnerbros.co.jp/buddha/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1195" type="Original Work">Tezuka Osamu</name>
<name id="1834" type="Work">Toei Animation</name>
<name id="3626" type="Music">Ooshima Michiru</name>
<name id="7883" type="Character Design">Maniwa Hideaki</name>
<name id="7883" type="Chief Animation Direction">Maniwa Hideaki</name>
<name id="4404" type="Direction">Morishita Kouzou</name>
</creators>
<description>2005 years ago in India, a boy named Siddhartha Gautama of the kingdom Shakya is born. When Siddhartha was born there was a prophecy that the boy would become a king of all the kingdoms. At that time various kingdoms were continuously raging wars with each other. When the boy attained puberty, he associated with people from the lower class like Migaila a girl who was known as a thief. Siddhartha began to have doubts about the strict class system even though he is raised in luxury as a future king.
Later, the powerful kingdom of Kosala attacks the kingdom of Shakya. Both sides fight fiercely. The commander of Kosala`s army is the general`s son Chapra. He is thought of as the most brave soldier in the kingdom of Kosala. Chapra was actually born into slavery but hid his background. By the general`s order he came all the way up into his current position.
Chapra wants to make a successful career for himself and Siddhartha abondons his family`s wealth to find Tao. These two opposite persons meet in the war and changes the fate of their respective kingdoms ...
Source: AsianWiki</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="166">5.74</permanent>
<temporary count="167">6.52</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>60967.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15333</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>11523</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7014</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>20969</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://wwws.warnerbros.co.jp/buddha/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Buddha_(manga)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ブッダ_(漫画)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3298</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>346766</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>337444</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13549</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2868" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-20">
<name>racism</name>
<description>Racism is prejudice, discrimination, or antagonism directed against someone of an ethnically different background based on the pseudo-scientific belief that biological differences between peoples form so-called "races" and that one`s own "race" is superior to another, possibly also holding that members of different "races" should be treated differently. Some definitions include only consciously malignant forms of discrimination, and some views include discriminatory behaviors and beliefs based on cultural, national, ethnic, caste, or religious stereotypes. In works of fiction, this may also include similar actions against other sentient species.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2871" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>anti-war</name>
<description>The anime portrays the insanity of war.</description>
<picurl>70855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3314" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-10">
<name>fate</name>
<description>Fate — The predestined path of all things. The outcome is inevitable and the consequences predetermined. Whether or not the protagonist ultimately decides to follow this path shall weigh heavily on their soul.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3363" parentid="2876" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-04">
<name>Buddhism</name>
<description>Buddhism is a nontheistic religion or dharma, "right way of living", that encompasses a variety of traditions, beliefs and practices largely based on teachings attributed to Siddhartha Gautama, commonly known as the Buddha ("the awakened one").
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>169453.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3432" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>pacifism</name>
<description>The belief and following of principles stating all and any conflict has a peaceful solution without use of violence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3836" parentid="3314" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-28">
<name>the chosen one!</name>
<description>One of the characters in the anime is the "chosen one", the one to bring about change, the only one to "set things right" in a "good" ending, or bring about complete destruction in a "bad" ending.</description>
<picurl>66957.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5091" parentid="2834" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>India</name>
<description>India, officially the Republic of India, is a country in South Asia. It is the seventh-largest country by area, the second-most populous country, and the most populous democracy in the world. It is bounded by the Indian Ocean on the south, the Arabian Sea on the southwest, and the Bay of Bengal on the southeast. It shares land borders with Pakistan to the west; China, Nepal, and Bhutan to the northeast; and Myanmar (Burma) and Bangladesh to the east.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214285.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5459" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>poverty</name>
<description>It refers to the condition of not having the means to afford basic human needs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6248" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>thievery</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="30577" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-02">
<name>Ashita</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145233.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="201" picture="17016.jpg">Nagai Ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30578" type="main character in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="1">1.29</rating>
<name>Siddhartha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145223.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6931" picture="3261.png">Yoshioka Hidetaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30579" type="main character in" update="2013-11-02">
<name>Siddhartha Youshouki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145231.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="588" picture="41015.jpg">Orikasa Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30580" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-30">
<name>Jooteka</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="38709" picture="145220.jpg">Kanze Saburouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30581" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-02">
<name>Suddhodana Ou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145222.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38708" picture="145219.jpg">Kanze Kiyokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30582" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-02">
<name>Tatta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145224.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7" picture="186500.jpg">Ootani Ikue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30583" type="main character in" update="2013-11-02">
<name>Chapra</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145229.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5233" picture="29252.jpg">Sakai Masato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30584" type="main character in" update="2013-11-02">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Chapra no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145230.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25697" picture="71416.jpg">Yoshinaga Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30585" type="main character in" update="2013-11-02">
<name>Chapra Youshouki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145227.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="302" picture="17134.jpg">Takeuchi Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30586" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-02">
<name>Naradatta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145225.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30587" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-30">
<name>Pandaka</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30588" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-02">
<name>Budai Shougun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145232.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30589" type="main character in" update="2013-11-02">
<name>Marikka-hime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145226.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32221" picture="86163.jpg">Kurotani Tomoka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30590" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-02">
<name>Migaila</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145221.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61044" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-02">
<name>Assaji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145212.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61045" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-02">
<name>Deepa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145213.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61046" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-02">
<name>Ruri-ouji no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145214.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="508" picture="140061.jpg">Shimamoto Sumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61047" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-02">
<name>Yatara</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145215.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2053" picture="23204.jpg">Ootomo Ryuuzaburou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61048" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-02">
<name>Yashodara-hi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145216.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="223" picture="228520.jpg">Kakazu Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61049" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-02">
<name>Bubu Daijin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145217.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2361" picture="228618.jpg">Kusumi Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61050" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-03">
<name>Pajapati-hi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145218.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12600" picture="42565.jpg">Toujou Kanako</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="120025" update="2012-02-26">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>110</length>
<airdate>2011-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">赤い砂漠よ! 美しく</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Great Departure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akai Sabaku yo! Utsukushiku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130424" update="2015-01-19">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>85</length>
<airdate>2014-02-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">終わりなき旅</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Endless Journey</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Owarinaki Tabi</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
