<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7518" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>30</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-07-06</startdate>
<enddate>2011-03-08</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Digimon Xros Wars</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">Digimon Cross Wars</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Digimon Fusion Battles</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">digimon6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">digixw</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">デジモンクロスウォーズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Digimon Fusion</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Digimon Fusion</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Digimon Fusion Battles</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Digimon Fusion</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Digimon Fusion</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">数码兽合体战争</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8321" type="Sequel">Digimon Xros Wars: Aku no Death General to Nanatsu no Oukoku</anime>
<anime id="234" type="Other">Digimon Adventure</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="513986">New digimon series? Yup!!! That mean`s you should get ready for a awesome adventure with Taiki, Akari, and Zenjirou to save the digital world from the evil baguramon!!!!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/tv/digimon_xw/</url>
<creators>
<name id="18282" type="Character Design">Asanuma Akihiro</name>
<name id="5737" type="Direction">Endou Tetsuya</name>
<name id="5334" type="Series Composition">Sanjou Riku</name>
<name id="1834" type="Work">Toei Animation</name>
<name id="745" type="Work">TV Asahi</name>
<name id="5659" type="Original Plan">Hongou Akiyoshi</name>
<name id="18282" type="Chief Animation Direction">Asanuma Akihiro</name>
<name id="7392" type="Music">Yamashita Kousuke</name>
</creators>
<description>One day, a Digimon Xros Loader appears before http://anidb.net/ch17981 [Taiki], an exceptionally warmhearted seventh grader, along with http://anidb.net/ch17974 [Shoutmon]`s voice, asking for his help. The D Xros Loader is an essential item that is capable of transferring power to Digimon by means of "DigiXros". He was chosen as a "General" to control it. Taiki and his friends are thrown into a parallel universe, the Digital World. Due to the appearance of rival and enemy Digimon, the Digital World has been driven into a state of "Xros Wars", a large-scale war with battles like those of the Sengoku period. Taiki and Shoutmon form a Digimon Army using the D Xros Loader and battle against formidable opponents with "DigiXros".</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="338">3.91</permanent>
<temporary count="345">6.14</temporary>
<review count="3">3.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>48430.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11450</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8624</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4742</identifier>
<identifier>ioqywt</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/tv/digimon_xw2010/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Digimon_Xros_Wars</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>デジモンクロスウォーズ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1981</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>337153</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12785</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>digimon-xros-wars-the-young-hunters-who-leapt-through-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2839" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>virtual world</name>
<description>A virtual world is a place where the character interacts with a computer (or some other device)-simulated environment, be it real or imagined. The condition for a virtual reality to exist is the existence of an originating "real" (source/anchor) world for the character. In some cases, a virtual reality where characters can get harmed physically is depicted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2863" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>proxy battles</name>
<description>In our terms, a proxy battle is a battle where humans use creatures/robots to do the fighting for them, either by commanding those creatures/robots or by simply evolving them/changing them into battle mode. Often the training aspect is also involved, or in some cases the proxies are nothing more than holographic representatives of some other variation of competition (like for example a card game). While many popular shounen anime fit under this category, it`s not limited to shounen anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4606" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>slide show animation</name>
<description>The entire anime or parts of it show sequences of still images. Sometimes used in low budged animations for action scenes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5505" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-15">
<name>deus ex machina</name>
<description>When the story has been spun so wildly and the plot has been driven so deeply, when all resources are exhausted and the linear truth stands so proudly at the end of the road, ready to bring the never-ending adventure to its epic conclusion...
The writers kick you in the behind and say "Screw that!! Suddenly... UFOs!!! No, wait, Werewolf UFOs!!! Bet you didn`t see that coming!"
It`s the old-Greek form of solving your broken story because it was too much work to do it all over again, or you`ve already shown stuff that compromises what you wanted to do. It`s finding out about a better dragon on a whole different planet because you`ve already been revived 3 times and that`s the cap. It`s breaking a spaceship and "oh wait, there`s an exact copy built in secret by an unknown guy on the other side of the planet, and you can use it free of charge". It`s Doraemon`s pouch, on every single episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5571" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-08-27">
<name>Greek mythology</name>
<description>The anime is derived or draws elements from the Greek mythology, and as such features some mythological characteristics of Ancient Greece. Those may be creatures, such as the Centaur or Hydra, tales, such as that of the Trojan War, or even the Gods themselves, like Zeus or Poseidon. More subtle references also count, such as the careful usage of names of places or people that hold significance in the myths.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6137" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-09">
<name>catchphrase</name>
<description>A catchphrase is a sound, word or phrase commonly used by a person. That may be simply out of habit, or in an attempt to deliver some form of image, like that of cuteness. In fiction, characters often use catchphrases as a way to deliver specific personality traits. Examples include Otohime Mutsumi`s "ara ara" in Love Hina, Yang Wenli`s "yare yare" in Legend of the Galactic Heroes, Misuzu`s "gao" in AIR, Sakura`s "hoe" in Card Captor Sakura, Suiseiseki`s "desu" in Rozen Maiden, and Ayu`s "uguu" in Kanon (as well as several other characters in the same show).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="5136" type="appears in" update="2012-05-11">
<name>Pukamon</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>21531.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20331" picture="73710.jpg">Ai Ichitarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5208" type="appears in" update="2012-05-11">
<rating votes="3">8.52</rating>
<name>Tailmon</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>21651.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="17974" type="main character in" update="2011-03-20">
<name>Shoutmon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68155.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="548" picture="186185.jpg">Sakamoto Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17975" type="appears in" update="2011-03-20">
<name>Sparrowmon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68156.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3132" picture="223652.jpg">Kikuchi Kokoro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17976" type="appears in" update="2011-03-20">
<name>Tactimon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68157.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="199" picture="23218.jpg">Shimada Bin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17977" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-20">
<name>Dorurumon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68153.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17978" type="appears in" update="2012-02-24">
<name>Monitormon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>82126.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16398" picture="171244.jpg">Maruyama Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17979" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-05-08">
<name>Tsurugi Zenjirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>86080.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="63" picture="186695.jpg">Kishio Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17980" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-22">
<rating votes="5">6.43</rating>
<name>Amano Nene</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cute brown hair ponytail girl. Her partner was Solarmon.</description>
<picture>48427.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17981" type="main character in" update="2011-03-20">
<name>Kudou Taiki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68154.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="393" picture="46104.jpg">Takayama Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17982" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-15">
<name>Aonuma Kiriha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68152.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="198" picture="202893.jpg">Kusao Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17983" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-28">
<rating votes="5">6.21</rating>
<name>Hinomoto Akari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48428.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="208" picture="20458.jpg">Shiraishi Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19402" type="appears in" update="2010-07-07">
<name>Nanomon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3132" picture="223652.jpg">Kikuchi Kokoro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19403" type="appears in" update="2012-05-07">
<name>MadLeomon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87419.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34006" type="appears in" update="2011-07-07">
<name>Ballistamon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74904.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="198" picture="202893.jpg">Kusao Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="118747" update="2011-01-11">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Commercial 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="118838" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">タイキ, 異世界へ行く!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Taiki Goes to Another World!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Taiki und die andere Welt!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiki, Isekai e Iku!</title>
<summary>Taiki Kudou is an uncommonly good-hearted seventh grader who "can`t turn his back on" someone in a pinch. One day he follows the voice of a Digimon in need and is granted a Xros Loader, a device that allows him to give Digimon added strength through the command "DigiXros!" Taiki becomes a General and is sent with his two friends to the Digital World, which is currently ravaged by war between the Digimon. Taiki and Shoutmon, the Digimon he saved, use the Xros Loader to build up a new army and join in the battle against the attacking Digimon!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>596731</identifier>
<identifier>digimon-xros-wars-the-young-hunters-who-leapt-through-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="119333" update="2010-06-27">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Commercial 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119596" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">シャウトモン, 吠える!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shoutmon, Roar!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Shoutmon brüllt!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoutmon, Hoeru!</title>
<summary>When Taiki visits Shoutmon`s home, the Village of Smiles, he sees that war has plunged the Digital World into chaos. Shoutmon begs Taiki to stay and fight the enemy with him, but Taiki`s reply creates a rift between the two. Meanwhile, the Imperial Bagra Army launches another attack on Taiki and his friends...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>596733</identifier>
<identifier>digimon-xros-wars-the-young-hunters-who-leapt-through-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="119964" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">強敵キリハ, 現る!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Rival, Kiriha, Appears!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kiriha, der blaue Rivale erscheint!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyouteki Kiriha, Arawaru!</title>
<summary>Taiki has decided to stay with Shoutmon and his other Digimon friends, but when the Bagra Army learns that Taiki can make Digimon DigiXros using the Xros Loader, they initiate attempts to eliminate him. Meanwhile another boy who uses a Xros Loader, Kiriha, shows up and tries to coerce Taiki into working for him...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>596735</identifier>
<identifier>digimon-xros-wars-the-young-hunters-who-leapt-through-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="119965" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アイランドゾーン, 激動!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Island Zone in Chaos!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Insel-Zone im Chaos!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Island Zone, Gekidou!</title>
<summary>After Taiki defeats the Bagra Army`s champion, MadLeomon, by uniting Shoutmon X2 and Dorulumon through a DigiXros, a golden fragment descends from the sky before his eyes. A mysterious girl named Nene Amano appears and tells him it is a fragment of the Code Crown, an object that allows its owner to control the Digital World. Following Nene`s instructions, Taiki places the Code Crown in his Xros Loader and travels to another Zone, unaware that the Bagra Army is taking secret measures to obtain the Code Crown as well...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>596737</identifier>
<identifier>digimon-xros-wars-the-young-hunters-who-leapt-through-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="119966" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">デジメモリ, 輝く!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The DigiMemory Shines!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das DigiMemory Scheint!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">DigiMemory, Kagayaku!</title>
<summary>Taiki and his team arrive in the Island Zone intent on finding more Code Crown fragments. Meanwhile, the Bagra Army learns that the Island Zone`s Code Crown is inside the belly of Whamon, the great Digimon who carries the Island Zone on his back, and tries to feed him explosives to stun him so they can steal it. Taiki and Shoutmon dive into Whamon`s belly themselves to find the Code Crown first, but the Bagra Army`s Flymon squad is close behind...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>596739</identifier>
<identifier>digimon-xros-wars-the-young-hunters-who-leapt-through-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="121126" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">x4(クロスフォー), 危機突破!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">X4, Overcome the Crisis!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">X 4 (Cross Four), Kiki Toppa!</title>
<summary>Taiki and his team have acquired another Code Crown as well as DigiMemories, cards containing the data of legendary Digimon - but now the Bagra Army has them surrounded! Kiriha hears this and offers to save Taiki`s team in exchange for the DigiMemories, but Taiki refuses and summons the DigiMemory of MarineAngemon in order to reach the enemy ship. There he attempts to rescue the chief of the Island Zone, Archelomon, who is held captive by the Bagra Army...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>596741</identifier>
<identifier>digimon-xros-wars-the-young-hunters-who-leapt-through-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="121139" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">火山デジモン, 大爆発!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volcanic Digimon Eruption!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kazan Digimon, Oobakuhatsu!</title>
<summary>After defeating the Bagra Army again, Taiki`s team heads to the Magma Zone. When the team is attacked by more Bagra troops led by DeathMeramon, Dorulumon dashes in to save them. Taiki asks Dorulumon to travel with them, but he refuses and leaves again with Cutemon. Later Taiki learns that the local Digimon are being forced into slavery by the Bagra Army and sets off into a cave to rescue them, but he`s found by the Bagra Army and the giant volcano Digimon, AncientVolcamon!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>596743</identifier>
<identifier>digimon-xros-wars-the-young-hunters-who-leapt-through-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="121302" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">猛将タクティモン, 迫る!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fierce General Tactimon Closes In!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moushou Tactimon, Semaru!</title>
<summary>The Bagra Army has been forcing the Digimon of the Magma Zone to search for the Zone`s Code Crown. Taiki fights to rescue them, but he`s met by a Digimon of overwhelming power, AncientVolcamon! Taiki and his companions let themselves be arrested to find out where the prison is, and team up with the prisoners to attempt an escape. However, when the Bagra Army`s leader Tactimon hears that Taiki and Dorulumon have been captured, he appears to confirm the story personally - and tells Taiki`s team all about Dorulumon`s past...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>596749</identifier>
<identifier>digimon-xros-wars-the-young-hunters-who-leapt-through-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="121407" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドルルモン, 風に駆ける!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dorulumon Runs Like the Wind!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dorulumon, Kaze ni Kakeru!</title>
<summary>Tactimon arrives in the Magma Zone and tells Taiki a shocking story of Dorulumon`s past: he used to be a prodigal warrior in the Bagra Army who conquered many Zones as Tactimon`s right hand man! He calls Dorulumon a traitor, but Taiki still chooses to trust him. They eventually escape from their cage and face AncientVolcamon, who has grown even stronger after absorbing his own allies. Dorulumon and Shoutmon DigiXros to fight him and try to return peace to the Magma Zone for good!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>596751</identifier>
<identifier>digimon-xros-wars-the-young-hunters-who-leapt-through-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="121682" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">タイキ, 騎士(ナイト)になる!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Taiki Becomes a Knight!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiki, Knight ni Naru!</title>
<summary>Xros Heart arrives in the Lake Zone, where Taiki saves Knightmon, a Digimon that had fallen into a frozen lake amidst a Bagra Army attack. A grateful Knightmon takes Taiki to the castle to have him made the captain of its knights, but the princess Bastemon has already chosen someone for that position: Taiki`s rival Kiriha! The two of them must join forces in order to turn back the Bagra Army attacking the castle, but the exhaustion of the battle finally gets to Taiki in the end...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>596753</identifier>
<identifier>digimon-xros-wars-the-young-hunters-who-leapt-through-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="121683" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">クロスハート, 燃える!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Xros Heart Burns Up!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Xros Heart, Moeru!</title>
<summary>With Taiki unconscious from exhaustion, Zenjirou leads the counterattack against the Bagra Army in his place. Meanwhile Bastemon keeps a constant watch over Taiki, leaving Akari feeling a bit like a third wheel. A dejected Akari is then lured by a vision of her mother in a mirror, which turns out to be the magic of Lilithmon telling Akari she`ll help her return to the human world in exchange for the Lake Zone`s Code Crown. As Akari searches for the Code Crown, Lilithmon awakens a secret weapon to launch her ultimate attack on the castle...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>596755</identifier>
<identifier>digimon-xros-wars-the-young-hunters-who-leapt-through-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="122448" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-10-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">サンドゾーン, 遺跡で大冒険!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sand Zone and the Great Adventure in the Ruins!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sand Zone, Iseki de Daibouken!</title>
<summary>Taiki and his team arrive in the Sand Zone, which once thrived as an area rich in precious gems. They decide to take a shot at treasure hunting, but along the way they fall into the Bagra Army`s underground base and find themselves on the run. They are saved by a treasure hunter Digimon, Revolmon, who then insists that they return the favor by helping him hunt for treasure. They set off into the ruins where the treasure is said to be hidden, but are impeded by various traps and pursued yet again by the Bagra Army. At last they reach the final chamber, where the mysterious Digimon Pharaohmon awaits them...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>596757</identifier>
<identifier>digimon-xros-wars-the-young-hunters-who-leapt-through-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="123636" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-10-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦士ベルゼブモン, 舞う!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Warrior Beelzebumon Dances!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senshi Beelzebumon, Mau!</title>
<summary>Baalmon, the survivor of the order of Warriors of the Goddess, falls victim to Lilithmon`s poison. Taiki begins a ritual to revive him using the Xros Loader, which prevents the others from using it to DigiXros in the battle against Lilithmon`s minion. Eventually, Baalmon stops the ritual and sends Taiki to help his companions, saving them but dooming himself to certain death...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>596761</identifier>
<identifier>digimon-xros-wars-the-young-hunters-who-leapt-through-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="123637" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-10-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">タイキ, 女神の戦士!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Taiki, Warrior of the Goddess!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiki, Megami no Senshi!</title>
<summary>As they leave the ruins of the Sand Zone, Taiki`s team finds themselves under fire from the Bagra Army`s assassin, Baalmon. Then a shock wave from the battle between Kiriha, Nene, and Blastmon sends Taiki and Baalmon tumbling into the sacred underground temple of a goddess. When Taiki extends a hand to the goddess statue he finds there, it emits a light that envelops him, which stuns Baalmon. He reveals that the light is called "the light of the Goddess," and those it shines upon have been chosen as "Warriors of the Goddess."
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>596759</identifier>
<identifier>digimon-xros-wars-the-young-hunters-who-leapt-through-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="125151" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヘブンゾーン, 楽園の罠!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heaven Zone, Deception in Paradise</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Heaven Zone, Rakuen no Wana!</title>
<summary>Taiki`s team arrives in the Heaven Zone, a home to many angel type Digimon and a police force so strong that even the Bagra Army can`t lay a hand on them. But the president and chief of police, SlashAngemon, and his subordinates are abusing their authority, punishing the smallest of crimes with severe sentences. Taiki`s companion Dondokomon is almost arrested for making a racket when he`s saved by a local Digimon, Lucemon, but then Taiki and his friends are seized again for a crime they didn`t commit, and SlashAngemon prepares to deal them a harsh sentence...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>596763</identifier>
<identifier>digimon-xros-wars-the-young-hunters-who-leapt-through-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="125276" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒騎士デジモン, 参上!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dark Knight Digimon Arrives!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuro Kishi Digimon, Sanjou!</title>
<summary>Lucemon is elected the new president of Heaven Zone, but the citizens` hopes for peace are quickly betrayed. The moment Lucemon is presented with the armband that symbolizes the presidency, he reveals the evil true nature he had been hiding all along! He uses an incantation to split the Zone and release the airborne shrine in which the Code Crown was sealed. Once he obtains the Code Crown, he returns to his true evil form and reveals that he is a servant of Lilithmon. The stunned Taiki is then faced with the appearance of Nene and a dark knight Digimon...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>596765</identifier>
<identifier>digimon-xros-wars-the-young-hunters-who-leapt-through-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="125277" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">奇跡のデジクロス! シャウトモンX5(クロスファイブ)飛ぶ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Miraculous DigiXros! Shoutmon X5 Soars!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiseki no Digi Cross! Shoutmon Cross Five Tobu!</title>
<summary>The evil Lucemon absorbs all the dark power sealed in the Heaven Zone, even drawing in Nene in the process. Her partner Sparrowmon tries to save her, but his attacks have no effect and he refuses to cooperate with Taiki and Shoutmon. When Lucemon starts to absorb the Heaven Zone itself and all the Digimon in it, Taiki`s team tries to stop him, but can`t reach him since Shoutmon X4 can`t fly. Sparrowmon finally sees that Taiki`s intentions are true and agrees to DigiXros with Shoutmon X4, giving rise to Shoutmon X5!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>596767</identifier>
<identifier>digimon-xros-wars-the-young-hunters-who-leapt-through-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="125435" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スティングモン, デジモン大密林(ジャングル)の勇者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stingmon, Hero of the Digimon Jungle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Stingmon, Digimon Jungle no Yousha</title>
<summary>Taiki`s team reaches the Forest Zone, a home of some very powerful Digimon. Akari and Zenjirou wind up separated from Taiki, so Dorulumon and Revolmon set off into the forest to find them. Then Akari and Zenjirou meet Stingmon, the protector of the forest, and Lilamon, who mistakes them for a dating couple. She takes them to a sacred shrine guarded by a barrier to protect them from the Bagra Army. Meanwhile Taiki`s team encounters Tactimon and fights him with Shoutmon X4B. They prove to be an even match, but then Kiriha and Nene appear and begin to attack Stingmon and Lilamon...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>596769</identifier>
<identifier>digimon-xros-wars-the-young-hunters-who-leapt-through-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="125693" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-12-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">伝説のデッカードラモン, 動く!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Legendary Deckerdramon Takes Action!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Densetsu no Deckerdramon, Ugoko!</title>
<summary>Taiki and his friends are caught up in a massive conflict between the Bagra Army, Team Blue Flare led by Kiriha, and Team Twilight led by Nene in the Forest Zone. Nene and DarkKnightmon head for the shrine in the forest to find the powerful sacred Digimon, Deckerdramon, and add him to their ranks. Taiki follows with Shoutmon X4 to save Nene, and Kiriha joins him, but they struggle against DarkKnightmon`s overwhelming power. Meanwhile, in response to Taiki`s questioning, Nene mentions the name "Yuu"... who could Yuu be?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>596771</identifier>
<identifier>digimon-xros-wars-the-young-hunters-who-leapt-through-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="126071" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-12-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダストゾーン, グランドロコモンの大スクラップ都市!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dust Zone, GrandLocomon`s Giant Scrap City!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dust Zone, GrandLocomon no Dai Scrap Toshi!</title>
<summary>Taiki`s team transports to the Dust Zone, a world full of garbage and scrap, to save Nene. But Taiki`s Xros Loader is soon stolen by a group of ToyAgumon, who receive sustenance from a Bagra Army servant, GrandLocomon, in exchange for "mecha" found among the garbage. They then meet a Digimon called Pinocchimon, who takes them to the ToyAgumon - but when Taiki demands his Xros Loader back, Pinocchimon snatches it and disappears!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>596773</identifier>
<identifier>digimon-xros-wars-the-young-hunters-who-leapt-through-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="126224" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-12-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦! ダークナイトモン VS クロスハート!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Decisive Battle! DarkKnightmon VS Xros Heart!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen! DarkKnightmon VS Cross Heart!</title>
<summary>Taiki`s team has arrived in the Dust Zone to rescue Nene, but they are soon attacked by Kiriha, who is now under DarkKnightmon`s control. Sparrowmon then arrives and tells them Nene has been imprisoned by DarkKnightmon, who is holding her brother hostage to force her into helping him gather dark power to activate the Darkness Loader. What is the Darkness Loader, and how will Taiki retaliate against Kiriha?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>596775</identifier>
<identifier>digimon-xros-wars-the-young-hunters-who-leapt-through-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="126351" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-01-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ワイズモン, デジタルワールドの秘密!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wisemon, The Secret of the Digital World!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wisemon, Digital World no Himitsu!</title>
<summary>While advancing to the next Zone after saving Nene, Xros Heart runs into Arkadimon, a Digimon that catches travelers between Zones and feeds upon their data. Arkadimon turns out to be controlled by Lilithmon in a plot to steal the Xros Loader. While all the others and the Xros Loader are taken away, Taiki is left to drift about the Digital realm alone - until he`s found by Wisemon, a Digimon seeking answers to all the mysteries of the Digital World. Wisemon proceeds to tell Taiki all about the history and structure of the Digital World...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>596777</identifier>
<identifier>digimon-xros-wars-the-young-hunters-who-leapt-through-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="126852" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-02-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">シャウトモン, キングの証!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shoutmon, Proof of a King!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoutmon, King no Okashi!</title>
<summary>After the Disc Zone`s collapse, its residents along with Taiki`s team all take refuge in the Shinobi Zone. But soon shards of Blastmon`s crystals, which had stuck to the Digimon`s bodies after the battle, turn into a doppelganger of Blastmon and begin to attack! Shoutmon manages to defeat Blastmon, but he is clearly not in top form and struggles in the fight. Finally Taiki and the others notice that Shoutmon`s behavior is strange, and begin to suspect that he`s up to something under the cover of night...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>596785</identifier>
<identifier>digimon-xros-wars-the-young-hunters-who-leapt-through-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="126853" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-02-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゾーン崩壊! 火花散るタイキとキリハ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Zone Destruction! Taiki and Kiriha Send Sparks Flying!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zone Houkai! Hibana Chiru Taiki to Kiriha!</title>
<summary>Taiki`s team arrives at the Disc Zone, a land built of many layers of giant light discs. There they find Kiriha, who has obtained the Zone`s Code Crown, in a fierce battle with Blastmon of the Bagra Army. However, the Disc Zone is ancient and its land weak, meaning if their intense battle continues, the whole Zone will collapse. Taiki and Shoutmon X4K try to stop the fighting, but just then, the ground beneath them caves in! Blastmon, Shoutmon, Greymon, and MailBirdramon fall in, leaving their respective teams without their central fighting force as the Bagra Army sends a powerful new enemy, Bulbmon, into the battle!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>596783</identifier>
<identifier>digimon-xros-wars-the-young-hunters-who-leapt-through-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="126854" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-01-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">落ちこぼれモニタモンズ, がんばる!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Drop-Out Monitormonz Do Their Best!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ochikobare Monitormonz, Ganbaru!</title>
<summary>After obtaining the Shinobi Zone`s Code Crown, Taiki and his friends attempt to recover the princess held captive by Mushamon. However, Mushamon`s army breaks their agreement to exchange the princess for the Code Crown, and launches a night attack on the Monitamons` village. While Taiki and the others stay behind to stall them, Zenjirou, Dorulumon, and the less competent Monitamons of the village set off on a rescue mission. But can Zenjirou really stand up to the task of rescuing the princess?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>596781</identifier>
<identifier>digimon-xros-wars-the-young-hunters-who-leapt-through-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="126855" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-01-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">シノビゾーン, お笑い忍者バトル!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shinobi Zone and the Comic Ninja Battle!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinobi Zone, Owarai Ninja Battle!</title>
<summary>Taiki`s team arrives at the Monitamons` homeland, the Shinobi Zone, but it has also been attacked by the Bagra Army, who took their castle and kidnapped their princess. Mushamon of the Bagra Army demands the Zone`s Code Crown in return for the princess, so Taiki and a team of dropout Monitamons set off for the shrine where the Code Crown is kept. However, when they reach the shrine, they learn that the only way to obtain the Code Crown is to make a Digimon called Karatenmon laugh. They show him funny videos, jokes, comedy routines, and even funny DigiXros combinations, but Karatenmon is a tough audience! Can anyone manage to make him laugh and obtain the Code Crown?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>596779</identifier>
<identifier>digimon-xros-wars-the-young-hunters-who-leapt-through-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="128048" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-02-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スイーツゾーン! 甘党デジモンバトル!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sweets Zone! The Sweet-Toothed Digimon Battle!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sweets Zone! Amatou Digimon Battle!</title>
<summary>Taiki`s team visits another Zone that has been overtaken by the Bagra Army, the Sweets Zone. Matadormon, a Digimon with a giant sweet tooth, has taken the Code Crown and locked all the Zone`s patissiers inside the castle, forcing them to make sweets for him. Xros Heart enters the castle to save them by presenting Akari as a patissier and taking on the Bagra Army`s top patissier, WaruMonzaemon, in a sweets-making battle. Akari sets about making a cake, but runs into major difficulties...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>596787</identifier>
<identifier>digimon-xros-wars-the-young-hunters-who-leapt-through-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="128105" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-03-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">新たなる旅立ち!! 東京大決戦!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Embark on a New Adventure!! Decisive Battle in Tokyo!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arata Naru Tabidachi!! Tokyo Dai Kessen!!</title>
<summary>Taiki, Akari, and Zenjirou have been sent back to the human world, but their families don`t believe their stories of the Digital World. A Digital aura appears in the sky over Tokyo, and soon Taiki hears the same mysterious voice he heard on the day he received his Xros Loader. The voice tells him there is no hope left for the Digital World. Taiki decides to return there with Shoutmon and seeks the owner of the voice for help getting back. He then finds the DigiMemory of a knight who protected the Digital World, the owner of the voice - Omegamon. But before Omegamon can send Taiki back, Tactimon begins to rampage in the human world!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>596793</identifier>
<identifier>digimon-xros-wars-the-young-hunters-who-leapt-through-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="128106" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-03-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">タイキ・キリハVSバグラ軍, 全面決戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Taiki &amp; Kiriha VS Bugra Army in an All-Out Showdown!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiki Kiriha VS Bugra-gun, Zenmen Kessen!</title>
<summary>Taiki`s team arrives in the Sword Zone, where swordsman Digimon test their skills in fair fights with one another. But then the Bagra Army`s swordsman unit, led by Grademon, launches an attack. Xros Heart defeats them and gains the Zone`s Code Crown, but then the dying Grademon is reborn as a good Digimon and, ashamed of his transformation, runs away. Soon Kiriha arrives and tells Taiki that he has just obtained the last of the Code Crowns, and that the Digital World has begun to reform. But then, finally, Tactimon appears and an epic battle begins!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>596791</identifier>
<identifier>digimon-xros-wars-the-young-hunters-who-leapt-through-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="128107" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-02-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">最終兵器発動! がんばれキュートモン!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ultimate Weapon Activates! You Can Do It, Cutemon!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saishuu Heiki Hatsudou! Ganbare Cutemon!</title>
<summary>When they`re thrown into the Sweets Zone`s underground, Taiki`s team learns that they`ve entered the factory where the Bagra Army has been forcing local Digimon to build the ultimate weapon. Cutemon believes his parents are among the captives, so everyone sets out find them and free the Zone`s Digimon. However, the Bagra Army`s ultimate weapon, Breakdramon, is near completion. Xros Heart attacks in hope of stopping it, but matters are complicated when Matadormon shows up...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>596789</identifier>
<identifier>digimon-xros-wars-the-young-hunters-who-leapt-through-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
