<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7565" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2012-11-17</startdate>
<enddate>2012-11-17</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Evangelion Shin Gekijouban: Q</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">Evangelion 3.0</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Rebuild of Evangelion: 3.0</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Evangelion: 3.0 You Can (Not) Redo.</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Evangelion: 3.33 You Can (Not) Redo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Evangelion Shin Gekijouban: Quickening</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="short">Євангеліон 3.0</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ヱヴァンゲリヲン新劇場版: Q</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Evangelion: 3.0 You Can (Not) Redo</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Evangelion 3.33: You can (not) redo</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Евангелион 3.33: ты (не) исправишь</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">에반게리온: Q</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8895" type="Sequel">Shin Evangelion Gekijouban:||</anime>
<anime id="6171" type="Prequel">Evangelion Shin Gekijouban: Ha</anime>
<anime id="12423" type="Other">Sakura Nagashi</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="9">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="413367">Amazing artwork and fight scenes</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="64801">I was really disappointed by this movie, and I really love both the tv series, end of eva and the first two rebuild movies.

Eva has never had a linear, easy to follow story, but this time i can`t help, but have the impression that things are simply messy.
What`s more i find really difficult to accept this "rebel" and "super dimensional fortress" like turn of events...

If you are an eva fan you have to watch it, but I place all my hopes in the last movie.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="229165">Hi the movie is for fans from the hell because introduce you in the rebuild universe were some events occur like in the tv series but they did´t mention in the movie so be prepare. they open many questions that i really hope be solved in the final movie, the "Q" is for quite, because the animation is Quite 	
impressive, the history Quite confused. greetings</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="276125">Finally we reach the diverging path of the movies from the show, and the insanity is dialed to 11. Phenomenal art and music as expected, but the story for this movie is much darker and more intense than the previous two, and really ramps things up for the final film. While likely not what most fans were expecting it to be, it still is very much worth watching, and lays all the necessary foundation for things to come.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="317067">I`m honestly not sure what to feel after watching the third Rebuild film. Anger is in there, along with confusion and anticipation, but mostly just sort of resignation.

I enjoyed the movie? In that way where you have to raise the pitch of your voice as you say it. I am fully in favor of changing up the original formula and switching things around - I just wasn`t expecting it to change so drastically with no warning. Not wanting to spoil anything, I spent 99.99% of the film convinced that what I was watching was a coma dream, and when I found out that it wasn`t I didn`t really know how to feel about it. 

I`ll watch the last movie because I`ve come this far and cos, well, it`s Evangelion, but I dunno man.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="371481">A high quality continuation of Rebuild series in terms of its visualization which is simply stunning. The film is also accompanied by well-fitting music highlighting overall despair. On the other hand, its audience is thrown to a world of unknown principles knowing as much as its main protagonist. It might sound interesting, but I see it as its main downfall since it isn`t properly finished. Due to this very fact, it`s necessary to know the (all) previous events otherwise you`ll easily get lost. Well, you`ll get lost even if you know them, to be honest. There is just too great gap between this show and the second film. And it`s full of unanswered questions. Furthermore, the storytelling is greatly hindered by fast pacing. Improper character development focusing only on Shinji neglecting the rest is its inevitable result.

It`s still the high quality angst we all know - Evangelion - but I can`t help to think of it as just too chaotic prelude to the final stage. Challenging, indeed.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="296685">Well, this was indeed the third movie in the series. Being the third movie out of four means that it has no real beginning and end. Big things happen in this movie but none of it has much weight, so the movie just feels like a little bit of filler material.

That said, it is still a good movie, nowhere near as good as the second movie in the series, but still good. The best thing about this movie is just how much the universe has really changed, and boy did it change.

So yeah. Good, but not great.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="395448">Damn awsome movie, awsome fights, awsome story. Must see</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.evangelion.co.jp/news.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="57" type="Original Work">Anno Hideaki</name>
<name id="1389" type="Main Character Design">Sadamoto Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="3578" type="Chief Animation Direction">Honda Takeshi</name>
<name id="23652" type="Chief Direction">Suzuki Kiyotaka</name>
<name id="1955" type="Music">Sagisu Shirou</name>
<name id="58" type="Direction">Tsurumaki Kazuya</name>
<name id="1462" type="Direction">Maeda Mahiro</name>
<name id="3612" type="Direction">Masayuki</name>
<name id="57" type="Chief Direction">Anno Hideaki</name>
</creators>
<description>Fourteen years have passed since Third Impact, yet the Angels continue their attacks against mankind. http://anidb.net/ch309 [Ikari Shinji] is salvaged from http://anidb.net/ch8704 [Evangelion Unit-01] and finds that things have changed, but not for the better: the world has been devastated, his former allies from http://anidb.net/ch5009 [NERV] have become hostile toward him, and http://anidb.net/ch310 [Ayanami Rei], the girl Shinji risked everything for, is nowhere to be found. As he attempts to adjust to this strange new world, Shinji befriends the enigmatic http://anidb.net/ch7960 [Nagisa Kaworu].
Together in their search for Rei, the pair learns the terrible truths behind the Angels, NERV, and the Evangelions. But a faint glimmer of hope remains for the two boys: a single opportunity to undo the mistakes of the past. Now the remnants of mankind are after them, the Angels race to stop them, and their old friends have declared them public enemy number one. With only Kaworu to support him and all the world against him, Shinji must fight for his one chance for redemption. But that may well mean finishing what he started — the end of the world.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2709">6.39</permanent>
<temporary count="2724">7.21</temporary>
<review count="3">5.77</review>
</ratings>
<picture>127046.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8422</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3785</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.evangelion.co.jp/news.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Evangelion:_3.0_You_Can_(Not)_Redo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ヱヴァンゲリヲン新劇場版</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3513</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>343233</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15511</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3227" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-06-24">
<name>introspection</name>
<description>The characters in this anime do not walk through life simply accepting how they are, but quite on the contrary constantly try to understand their own motives, feelings and reactions to the other protagonists. 
This self-searching included the questions: "Who am I?", "What makes me tick?", "What do I want?", "What do others expect of me?", etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3276" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>plot twists</name>
<description>The plot and story of this anime may seem to be going along a quite predictable path, when suddenly there is a jarring unexpected twist in the plot, taking the viewer by surprise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3322" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-04">
<name>remake</name>
<description>This anime is a remake of a previously released story, anime, or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3850" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-11-23">
<name>downer ending</name>
<description>A finale that ends the story in a way that is usually truly miserable and tragic or a similarly low-key or unhappy ending to a normally "happy" series. 
Cruel examples of the ways this ending happens are all the major characters dying or the "bad guy" winning in a way that there`s no sight of happiness in the end.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3929" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-09">
<name>sociocultural evolution</name>
<description>Describes how cultures and societies develop over time, based on both cultural evolution and social evolution.
A post-apocalyptic or a Utopian setting would show very interesting changes in human behaviour, mental state, or simply daily life.</description>
<picurl>191062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3953" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-06">
<name>in medias res</name>
<description>In medias res, also medias in res (Latin for "into the midst of affairs (lit. into mid-affairs)"), refers to a literary and artistic technique where the narrative starts in the middle of the story instead of from its beginning. It is generally a plot-driven concept rather than a character-driven one; though characters are commonly used to provide the backstory. The characters, setting, and conflict are often introduced through a series of flashbacks or through characters relating past events to each other.
Probably originating from an oral tradition, the technique is a convention of epic poetry, one of the earliest and most prominent examples in Western literature being Homer`s Odyssey and Iliad. Virgil`s Aeneid began the tradition in literature of imitating Homer, continued in Torquato Tasso`s Jerusalem Delivered, John Milton`s Paradise Lost and "Inferno" from Dante`s Divine Comedy. George Lucas`s Star Wars saga was told using in medias res.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4537" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-15">
<name>time skip</name>
<description>The plot features at least one skip or jump in time.
Example: A skip from the present into the past, or time skips in increments, e.g. every hour there is a time skip by a day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4560" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-02-23">
<name>psychological manipulation</name>
<description>Psychological manipulation is a type of social influence that aims to change the perception or behaviour of others through underhanded, deceptive, or even abusive tactics. By advancing the interests of the manipulator, often at the other`s expense, such methods could be considered exploitative, abusive, devious, and deceptive. 
Social influence is not necessarily negative. For example, doctors can try to persuade patients to change unhealthy habits. Social influence is generally perceived to be harmless when it respects the right of the influenced to accept or reject it, and is not unduly coercive. Depending on the context and motivations, social influence may constitute underhanded manipulation.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5790" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-30">
<name>family without mother</name>
<description>For some reason, the protagonist`s mother is no longer among the living. The much-too-early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime, and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family. For example: the grief-stricken father and children barely function as humans; the oldest daughter has an extra burden of raising the other children, additional emphasis is given to the only female child in the family, i.e. with bishounen brother and dad in a shoujo setting.
In rare cases the mother may still be alive, just not living with the rest of the family presently, i.e. on some quest or job and gone for a long time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5952" parentid="2874" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-25">
<name>end of the world</name>
<description>The imminent end of the world may range from the total destruction of the planet Earth, to the destruction of Earth`s surface, or to the point where human life on the planet is no longer possible, aka the end of humanity.
In any case it looks grim, and the protagonists battle to preserve what they can.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="309" type="main character in" update="2018-02-15">
<rating votes="1352">4.11</rating>
<name>Ikari Shinji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ikari Shinji is the "Third Children" of the Marduk Report and the pilot of http://anidb.net/ch6997 [EVA-01]. He is the son of http://anidb.net/ch5000 [Ikari Gendou] and the late http://anidb.net/ch9620 [Ikari Yui]. Abandoned by his father when he was a toddler, Shinji has grown up to be reclusive and withdrawn, often choosing to run away from difficult situations. He is reunited with his father when he is summoned to pilot EVA-01, and because of this meets his future caretaker http://anidb.net/ch5007 [Katsuragi Misato] and the mysterious pilot of http://anidb.net/ch6996 [EVA-00], http://anidb.net/ch310 [Ayanami Rei].
Over time and with encouragement from Misato, Rei and his classmates http://anidb.net/ch7981 [Suzuhara Touji] and http://anidb.net/ch8643 [Aida Kensuke], he learns to be more confident and appreciative of others. Shinji is put to task fighting the invading Angels, and later meets a foreign pilot whom he often comes in conflict with, http://anidb.net/ch39 [Souryuu Asuka Langley].</description>
<picture>128273.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="187" picture="17002.jpg">Ogata Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5009" type="appears in" update="2009-06-20">
<rating votes="35">8.13</rating>
<name>Nerv</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>An organisation led by Ikari Gendou and tasked with defending Earth against the Angels through use of the Evangelion units. It was formerly known as Gehirn, a UN Research Agency. It was reorganised into Nerv once Nerv HQ and Tokyo-3 became fully operational. There are several global branches of Nerv besides the main headquarters under Tokyo-3 itself.
The Nerv Logo is half a fig leaf covering its name, with the motto "God`s In His Heaven... All`s Right With The World" forming the quarter circle on the bottom. The motto comes from Robert Browning`s poem "Pippa Passes."
In Genesis 3:7, Adam and Eve cover their "nakedness" with fig leaves. The fig leaf has covered nakedness in art and sculpture for hundreds of years, symbolically representing the guilt of original sin.</description>
<picture>21279.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7701" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-11-18">
<rating votes="89">6.79</rating>
<name>Makinami Mari Illustrious</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128275.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="227" picture="205854.jpg">Sakamoto Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7960" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-11-18">
<rating votes="317">6.59</rating>
<name>Nagisa Kaworu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tabris, the seventeenth and final Angel, holds the form of a human, Kaworu Nagisa. Like the other Angels, he is "born of Adam", although it is implied that he was created by Seele. He contains the soul of Adam, similar to how Rei contains the soul of Lilith. Tabris` AT field is the most powerful ever detected, strong enough to block out "light, magnetism, sub-atomic particles, everything". He may control any Evangelion unit he wishes, even from outside the entry plug, so long as the soul inhabiting the Eva is dormant. Within the entry plug, he can set his synchronization ratio at any level he wishes. The nature or even the very existence of his core is not revealed.
Tabris, as Kaworu, infiltrated Nerv under the pretense of being sent to replace Asuka as Unit 02`s pilot. During his stay in Tokyo-3, he formed an extremely close relationship with Shinji. Kaworu later revealed himself as an Angel, seizing control of Unit 02 and descending with it towards Terminal Dogma. Shinji, in Unit 01, was sent to stop him, but was forced to battle Unit 02 while Tabris proceeded to Terminal Dogma. Tabris` AT field manifested during the battle, effectively cutting both of them off from all contact with anyone outside. After he reached Terminal Dogma, Tabris was surprised to discover that the Angel held there was not Adam, but Lilith. Shinji incapacitated Unit 02 and proceeded to try to stop the Angel. Tabris, gripped in Unit 01`s hand, stated his unwillingness to destroy mankind by causing Third Impact, and asked Shinji to kill him. Shinji, after a long period of hesitation, crushed the Angel in his Eva`s hand.</description>
<picture>128274.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50720" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-15">
<rating votes="47">6.96</rating>
<name>Shikinami Asuka Langley</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shikinami Asuka Langley remains the pilot of http://anidb.net/ch8705 [EVA-02] and is now used by http://anidb.net/ch50735 [Wille] as an expendable tool in their struggle against http://anidb.net/ch8705 [Nerv] and their EVAs. Little is seen of Asuka outside action scenes, and she is now the partner of http://anidb.net/ch7701 [Makinami Mari Illustrious]. Together they fight NERV to prevent them from initiating the Fourth Impact.</description>
<picture>128276.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="164" picture="16962.jpg">Miyamura Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50721" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-14">
<rating votes="25">5.97</rating>
<name>Ayanami Rei (Kashou)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128277.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50722" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-11-18">
<rating votes="5">5.85</rating>
<name>Ikari Gendou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128278.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32" picture="16618.jpg">Tachiki Fumihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50723" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-11-18">
<rating votes="3">7.87</rating>
<name>Fuyutsuki Kouzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128279.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="564" picture="146195.jpg">Kiyokawa Motomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50724" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-20">
<rating votes="15">2.83</rating>
<name>Katsuragi Misato</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128280.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50725" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-11-18">
<rating votes="4">2.16</rating>
<name>Akagi Ritsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128281.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1900" picture="156922.jpg">Yamaguchi Yuriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50726" type="appears in" update="2012-11-18">
<rating votes="2">2.57</rating>
<name>Ibuki Maya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128282.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="290" picture="24139.jpg">Nagasawa Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50727" type="appears in" update="2012-11-18">
<rating votes="2">2.34</rating>
<name>Aoba Shigeru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128283.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50728" type="appears in" update="2012-11-18">
<rating votes="2">4.38</rating>
<name>Hyuuga Makoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128284.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1925" picture="21115.jpg">Yuuki Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50729" type="appears in" update="2012-11-18">
<rating votes="4">6.24</rating>
<name>Suzuhara Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128285.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50730" type="appears in" update="2012-11-18">
<rating votes="3">3.05</rating>
<name>Takao Kouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128286.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50731" type="appears in" update="2012-11-18">
<rating votes="4">4.59</rating>
<name>Nagara Sumire</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128287.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50732" type="appears in" update="2012-11-18">
<rating votes="2">2.34</rating>
<name>Tama Hideki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128288.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2002" picture="21307.jpg">Katsu Anri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50733" type="appears in" update="2012-11-18">
<rating votes="4">2.66</rating>
<name>Kitakami Midori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128289.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="101" picture="16709.jpg">Ise Mariya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50735" type="appears in" update="2016-03-12">
<name>Wille</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Wille is an anti-Nerv organization, dedicated to preventing future Impact events.
Wille was formed following the government disbanding of http://anidb.net/ch5009 [Nerv] after Third Impact and comprised of many former Nerv staff members. It is led by Captain http://anidb.net/ch5007 [Katsuragi Misato]. All staff but Misato and the Eva pilots wear a blue bandanna somewhere on their person, usually tied around the upper left arm.
Its operations have been based in an ocean fleet, led by the massive flagship AAA Wunder. After http://anidb.net/ch8704 [Evangelion Unit-01] is recovered from space and employed as a power source, the fleet becomes airborne.
Source: wiki.evageeks.org</description>
<picture>63627.png</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="128246" update="2011-02-18">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2010-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="140637" update="2013-04-29">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>95</length>
<airdate>2012-11-17</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="140663" update="2012-07-02">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-08-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="140664" update="2012-07-02">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-07-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">EVA-EXTRA08</title>
<title xml:lang="en">EVA-EXTRA 08</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">EVA-EXTRA08</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145480" update="2012-11-17">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2012-11-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview 6:38m</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150116" update="2013-04-27">
<epno type="4">T17</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2013-04-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">EVANGELION:Q 3.33 Blu-ray &amp; DVD Promotional Reel</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150117" update="2013-04-27">
<epno type="4">T16</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-11-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer after launch ver. B</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150118" update="2013-05-20">
<epno type="4">T15</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-11-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer after launch ver. A</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150119" update="2013-05-20">
<epno type="4">T14</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-11-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">『ヱヴァンゲリヲン新劇場版:Q』 TV-SPOT 4</title>
<title xml:lang="en">TVPV 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Evangelion Shin Gekijou Ban: Q" TV-Spot 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150120" update="2013-05-20">
<epno type="4">T13</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-11-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">『ヱヴァンゲリヲン新劇場版:Q』 TV-SPOT 3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">TVPV 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Evangelion Shin Gekijou Ban: Q" TV-Spot 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150121" update="2013-05-20">
<epno type="4">T12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-11-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">『ヱヴァンゲリヲン新劇場版:Q』 TV-SPOT 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">TVPV 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Evangelion Shin Gekijou Ban: Q" TV-Spot 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150122" update="2013-04-27">
<epno type="4">T11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-11-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150123" update="2013-04-27">
<epno type="4">T10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-10-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">サンテFXのCM</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Santen CM</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sante FX no CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150124" update="2013-04-27">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-10-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">予告映像(ニコニコ動画版)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer NicoNico</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yokoku Eizou (Nikoniko Douga Ban)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150125" update="2013-05-20">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-10-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">『ヱヴァンゲリヲン新劇場版:Q』 TV-SPOT 1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">TVPV 1 Piano 15s</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Evangelion Shin Gekijou Ban: Q" TV-Spot 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150126" update="2013-04-27">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-07-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Teaser Piano</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150128" update="2013-05-22">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-07-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">EVA-EXTRA 08 short TV version</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150670" update="2013-05-20">
<epno type="4">T18</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer before launch</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150672" update="2013-05-20">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">AR Script</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150673" update="2013-11-05">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Rebuild Of Evangelion 3.33 (Making Of)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150674" update="2013-05-20">
<epno type="4">T26</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Theme Song Promotion Reel Type B</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150675" update="2013-05-20">
<epno type="4">T25</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Theme Song Promotion Reel Type A</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150676" update="2013-05-20">
<epno type="4">T24</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Theme Song TV Spot 15s</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150677" update="2013-05-21">
<epno type="4">T23</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer NicoNico (long version)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150678" update="2013-05-20">
<epno type="4">T22</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TVPV 30s</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150679" update="2013-05-20">
<epno type="4">T21</epno>
<length>9</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TVPV Type F Collection</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150680" update="2013-05-20">
<epno type="4">T20</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TVPV Type D</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150681" update="2013-05-20">
<epno type="4">T19</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TVPV Type B</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
