<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7568" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-10-07</startdate>
<enddate>2010-12-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kami nomi zo Shiru Sekai</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Одному лишь Богу ведомый мир</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Светът, който само Бог познава</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="synonym">دنیایی که فقط خدا می شناسد</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="synonym">کامی نومی زو شیرو سکای</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="synonym">دنیایی که فقط خدا آن را میشناسد</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">twgok1</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">twgok</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Kaminomi</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">神のみぞ知るセカイ The World God Only Knows</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The World God Only Knows</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Que sa volonté soit faite</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">只有神知道的世界</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8167" type="Sequel">Kami nomi zo Shiru Sekai II</anime>
<anime id="8632" type="Other">Nonstop!! Hunters</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8808" approval="48" total="73">Date a Live</anime>
<anime id="10538" approval="7" total="15">Saenai Heroine no Sodatekata</anime>
<anime id="5975" approval="2" total="15">Toaru Majutsu no Index</anime>
<anime id="12494" approval="2" total="14">Gamers!</anime>
<anime id="9524" approval="2" total="10">Kanojo ga Flag o Oraretara</anime>
<anime id="8869" approval="2" total="10">Oda Nobuna no Yabou</anime>
<anime id="6327" approval="1" total="7">Bakemonogatari</anime>
<anime id="10529" approval="1" total="6">Shinmai Maou no Testament</anime>
<anime id="7506" approval="0" total="6">Amagami SS</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="16">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="376027">The stereotype of modern anime that evolves around stereotype characters with stereotype problems and stereotype solutions. 
Only the main protagonist is so `different` that he makes this series into something special.
He stays very true to himself which i didnt expect what also made me want to watch more.
Great OP also.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="103240">nicely done overall, good comedy. but the last episode was tragically bad :D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="358725">I really like this show ; I don`t watch harem anymore as I`m really tired of these being always the same things full of ecchi, but this one is different, it`s pretty original, and the characters are really likable</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="219300">Mmmm.. This one is just different enough to be good.. More would be nice. might as well check it out in ongoing`s down-time..</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="337356">A nice surprise. Contrary to what you could infer from description, it is actually a quite decent series, with little to no fanservice and a humour that works especially well when it steers from the main topic. The librarian episodes - awesome. Well enjoyed this, except maybe the last ep, which seemed forced.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="452346">Captivating. Definitely one of the best.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="556152">a charming comedy series with a little touch of Romance. definetly one of the better shows i`ve seen. I think it will appeal to everyone, and once you`re done with this you certaintly will want to watch the next season. a must see 
( Also you CAN read the manga but no difference, this anime follows the manga 100% and i agree with that decision since it has a nice flow of story)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="589244">I thought this was one of those stupid moe anime so I put if off for years, but it`s not! Haven`t seen a good anime that can hook me in ages... finally! The main character is cool and funny (because of the gamer stereotype). If you substituted the gaming with something like swordsmanship, he would be like one of those cool characters, except in this anime it turned out to be cool and hilarious (esp. eps 4 &amp; 12). Starts off with a blast, then the middle kind of mediocre, the latter part good, and the final ep as hilarious as ep 4.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="548153">I really enjoyed&amp;love all of the God Only Knows series and can`t wait for more! - I hope there will be more sequels since I can`t get enough of this incredibly polished show! :D
Highly recommended for everyone and a must see for the fans of harem/romance/comedy genre!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="115911">For me TWGOK is by far the best Harem anime I`ve ever seen.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://kaminomi.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3529" type="Character Design">Watanabe Akio</name>
<name id="1557" type="Series Composition">Kurata Hideyuki</name>
<name id="7012" type="Direction">Takayanagi Shigehito</name>
<name id="2529" type="Music">Matsuo Hayato</name>
<name id="986" type="Animation Work">Manglobe</name>
<name id="3693" type="Work">Kawamura Akihiro</name>
<name id="13355" type="Work">Anami Rei</name>
<name id="7178" type="Work">Hatta Shinsaku</name>
<name id="18553" type="Original Work">Wakaki Tamiki</name>
<name id="3529" type="Chief Animation Direction">Watanabe Akio</name>
<name id="14037" type="Work">Oomura Makoto</name>
<name id="13967" type="Chief Animation Direction">Samura Yoshikazu</name>
<name id="3328" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kawamura Toshie</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a manga series written and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr18553 [Wakaki Tamiki], serialised in http://anidb.net/cr23232 [Weekly Shounen Sunday].
http://anidb.net/ch18463 [Katsuragi Keima], a second-year high school student, is an avid dating sim gamer. He is known on the Internet as The Capturing God for his legendary skills to be able to capture any 2D girl in games. However, in his actual school life, Keima is known as otamegane.
Keima receives an e-mail offering him a contract to capture girls. He accepts what is thought to be a challenge, and a demon from Hell nicknamed http://anidb.net/ch18462 [Elsee] appears. She asks for his cooperation to help her in catching the runaway spirits. These spirits hide themselves inside the girls` heart, and Elsee suggests that the only method to force the spirits out is by capturing their hearts — making them fall in love. Appalled by the idea, Keima refuses after clarifying to Elsee that he is only interested in capturing 2D girls and that he detests reality. Nevertheless, with the contract already accepted, Keima will have to help Elsee no matter what; if they fail, both Elsee and Keima will lose their heads.
Note: The first episode was shown during an event at Akihabara UDX theatre on Saturday, September 25, limited to 100 participants chosen through a postcard lottery. The television broadcast started on October 07, 2010. Otamegane is a derogatory portmanteau of the two words otaku and megane (glasses).</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="5019">6.69</permanent>
<temporary count="5045">7.53</temporary>
<review count="5">6.89</review>
</ratings>
<picture>227109.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11571</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9675</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>8525</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4772</identifier>
<identifier>jrqluf</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/kaminomi/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://kaminomi.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Kami_nomi_zo_Shiru_Sekai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>神のみぞ知るセカイ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2040</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>337851</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12994</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1471" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-19">
<name>bad cooking</name>
<description>The character is hopelessly terrible at cooking, and any attempts he or she makes at making even the simplest dishes are spectacular failures.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2391" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>bishoujo</name>
<description>In Japanese, a bishoujo is any pretty female from toddlerhood to late adolescence. In the West, the word specifically refers to attractive girls generally from late childhood or early adolescence, especially those that appeal to males, and particularly to fictional characters designed in a way traditionally associated to shoujo manga. Fictional bishoujo tend to be cute, pastel-coloured teenagers; they lack the sophistication of older women, instead having detailed eye and hair design, fluttery costumes often including ribbons, and all sorts of generally sparkly fluff.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2438" parentid="2794" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-16">
<name>idol</name>
<description>In Japanese culture, idols (アイドル) are media personalities in their teens and early twenties who are considered particularly cute and cuddly and who will, for a period ranging from several months to a few years, regularly appear in the mass media, e.g. as singers for J-pop groups, bit-part actors, TV personalities, models in photo spreads published in magazines, advertisements, etc.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>63097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2795" parentid="1973" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>baking</name>
<description>The art of making bread, cakes, pastries, pies, tarts, quiches, cookies and similar food in the oven.
Mmmm.... smells nice.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3132" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-08-11">
<name>helpful couple</name>
<description>This is a very low key type of romance in which the main two characters spend a great deal of time hanging out together just helping other people solve problems. The couple`s personal interaction tends to be subtle.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3606" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-11">
<name>family without father</name>
<description>For some reason the protagonists father is no longer among the living. The much too early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family: Possibly the grieve-stricken mother and children barely function as humans. Or adding emphasis to the overall financial predicament of the family, should the father have been the money earner.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4301" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-22">
<name>play or die</name>
<description>The protagonist(s) are forced into a situation where they have to partake in some form of event, often a game of death, unless they want to bid farewell to their life.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4388" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-16">
<name>deconstruction</name>
<description>In the context of fiction, a deconstruction is the act of taking storytelling devices and exploring their real-life consequences, commonly in dark and cynical ways. Deconstructions often reveal the dark and terrifying aspects of some of the themes and elements that appear recurrently in fictional works.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5916" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-26">
<name>product placement</name>
<description>Otherwise known as a "plug" or "writing commercials right into a show". The practice of prominently displaying or talking about a recognizable product in a program, in exchange for some consideration from the manufacturer, usually monetary. (Source: TV Tropes)
Particularly notorious example, Pizza Hut for the involvement with Code Geass, Darker than Black and other series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5984" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-09-10">
<name>girly tears</name>
<description>Usually girly tears are the ones not shed by men (duh). 
Like when a (stereotypical) girl watches something and cries her makeup out, a (stereotypical) dude just says, proclaiming his masculinity: "Meh, yet another soap opera bulls..t, I`ll be in my garage fixing my ride while playing heavy metal on a burning guitar ...with my teeth! And where`s my beer, woman?".
So that`s how it goes: girly tears are for girls and sissies! Chuck Norris forbid a guy would weep watching something that has this tag! Now 20 push-ups!
P.S. The opposite of "manly tears". Or is it? Let`s face it - it`s all subjective (and relative, and context-dependent).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6078" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-23">
<name>gotta catch them all</name>
<description>A typical plot or sub-plot for many shows. Either the cast or somebody else, that being often the main antagonist, embarks on a quest to collect things, shiny things. Things that are said to grant simple wishes or even do miracles like bringing people back to life, destroying the whole world, galaxy, universe and in rare cases turning the hero into the greatest Pokemon Master. Those things can be weapons, lost technology, magical artefacts, pieces of a giant magical artefact and in some cases even people or little critters.
The point is, there`s stuff to collect!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="18462" type="main character in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="342">7.50</rating>
<name>Elysia de Lute Ima</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Elucia or Elsie as she is commonly known, is a demon who was assigned to capture evil spirits that have escaped from hell. Her feather cloth (the floating scarf she is always seen with) can change the appearance of an object, create disguises to aid the mission or it can hide people in plain sight. She is left-handed and is rarely seen without her broom, as it was from her original role as a cleaner for hell. To stay close to Keima, she tells Mari, Keima`s mother, that she is an illegitimate child of Keima`s father, and ends up living in the Katsuragi household as well as attending the same class in school. Elsie is often made fun of by the other demons because of the poor grades she had in the demon academy. However, after partnering with Keima, they were able to capture 9 escaped spirits within half a year`s time, which earned her the Section Chief`s Award.
Elsie is also a member of Chihiro`s band in which she plays a left handed bass. She has also developed an interest in fire trucks. She literally idolises Keima, often referring to him as "Kami-sama" or "Kami-nii-sama" in her role as his sister.</description>
<picture>55510.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18463" type="main character in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="620">8.23</rating>
<name>Katsuragi Keima</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Katsuragi Keima is the primary protagonist of the story, a 17-year-old high school student attending Maijima High School Academy. He is known as "The Capturing God (落とし神, Otoshi-gami)" in the gaming world for his legendary skills in "capturing" any girls in dating sims. But ironically, he is called otamegane (a derogatory portmanteau of the two words otaku and megane-"glasses"). At the start of the series, Keima becomes a collaborator for catching runaway spirits when he replies to an e-mail requesting his help to "capture" girls without knowing it was a contract from Hell, to which Elsee appeared and asked for his aid to "capture" girls in real-life. For each individual of the "Capture Targets"—a girl with the runaway spirit in her—Keima utilizes his analytical skills and experiences from dating sims to capture them. Whenever he isn`t capturing runaway spirits, he is almost always seen playing video games on his PFP (a parody of Sony`s PSP). Also, despite the fact he even plays video games in class, he is still at the top of class in every subject. As the story progresses, his perspective of the "real world" girls becomes different.</description>
<picture>55509.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20154" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="176">7.42</rating>
<name>Takahara Ayumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takahara Ayumi is an athletic, cheery girl in Keima`s homeroom at school; Ayumi is a member of the school`s track-and-field team. She is an exceptional runner and was chosen as the representative for the upcoming tournament. As a result however she was pressured by jealous third-year runners, causing her to fake an injury in order to back out of the tournament. Keima, who was able to see through the deception, consoled and encouraged her not to give up which lead to capturing the escaped spirit. Ayumi and Keima are often paired up for cleaning duty together. In an omake from Chapter 14, and much more obviously in the whole of Chapter 30, she has become more eager to be around him. She is also a member of Chihiro`s band. Responsible for the guitar (SG).
Her name comes from Takanohara Station (高の原駅, Takanohara-eki).</description>
<picture>55511.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20155" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="71">5.54</rating>
<name>Aoyama Mio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aoyama Mio is an elitist daughter of Aoyama Central Industry`s president. She is imperious and disdainful, being from a wealthy family; however, not known to the public, she is no longer rich—a secret which Keima discovers after stalking her to a shabby apartment. Despite her financial situation Mio continues to think of herself as a rich woman and is unable to let go of her late father`s memory. In order to get closer to her Keima took on the role of her chauffeur and driving her to school in various rickshaws. He then confronts her at an evening party, convincing her to accept the past and move on. Keima encounter Mio several chapters later, while occupying Yui`s body and learns that instead of him meeting her at the party, she remembers her old chauffeur Morita.
The prototype version of Mio appeared in Tamiki Wakaki`s one-shot Koishite!? Kami-sama!!, with her surname being Tsumagawa.
Her name comes from Aoyamacho Station (青山町駅, Aoyamacho-eki).</description>
<picture>55512.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21505" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="220">7.02</rating>
<name>Nakagawa Kanon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nakagawa Kanon is currently the most popular "traditional idol" for her quaint style, beauty and singing talents. She is also in Keima`s homeroom but had not been attending frequently because of her idol occupation. Kanon hopes that her song would "resound in everyone`s hearts." She is constantly anxious and dependent about the acknowledgment of her existence by others. When she feels ignored the spirit possessing her causes her body to appear transparent to others. Her lack of confidence is so great that when Keima first met her and didn`t recognize her she buzzed him with a pair of stun guns that she carries. On the night of her premiere performance as an idol she was overcome with stage fright, (becoming nearly invisible) until Keima encouraged her to believe in herself, filling the gap in her heart. During the performance afterwards Kanon began to glow so brightly that it was hard to see her. Keima commented on this, saying that she was no longer and `idol` but a `star`. In Kanon`s 4-box comic strips, it shows that there are leftover feelings for Keima; it`s shown that she trips when saying `kiss`, and when she sees something or someone related to Keima`s name (Exa: the wig is called a katsura in japanese).
She debuted as side member of a trio unit "Citron", became center after took off her glasses and started solo after she cut her hair. She does not use the glasses when she performs as an idol, but wears it in school and private. Raises a turtle named Kintarou as a pet.
The cause of Kanon`s crevice in the heart was her doubt of her existance as an idol.
Her name comes from Ise-Nakagawa Station (伊勢中川駅, Ise-Nakagawa-eki).</description>
<picture>73489.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21506" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="181">8.16</rating>
<name>Shiomiya Shiori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shiomiya Shiori is a reticent girl who loves to read books. She is a member of the Library Committee, which acts as the governing body and librarian for the school library. Her official position is a secretary. She has always wanted to talk to others but finds that she cannot articulate as fast as her thought process, as a result by the time she has formulated a response to something, the conversation has already moved on. From the beginning, Keima immediately catches her attention and anger by saying that physical books are no longer necessary in a digital era. As Keima continues to vandalize the books in the library, she becomes more conversational each time. Near the end of her story arc, she learns that three thousand books are to be disposed of to accommodate an audio-visual booth. Protesting, she locks down the building and barricades herself in the library. After Keima literally descends into the library and gives her "courage", she finally overcomes her silence.
She starts to write a story based on her faint memories during Keima`s capture, though the parts including Keima are erased.
The cause of Shiori`s crevice in the heart was her will to speak out her mind, when she had doubts of a good reply.
Her name comes from Shionomiya Station (汐ノ宮駅, Shionomiya-eki).</description>
<picture>73490.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21709" type="appears in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="6">3.41</rating>
<name>Asuka Sora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Asuka Sora is the heroine of Crayon - Sora no Art, Atelier Lilith`s game for PFP that can`t be cleared because of the bugs. Her name is derived from Asuka Station (飛鳥駅, Asuka-eki).</description>
<picture>73491.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="419" picture="17271.jpg">Sakurai Tomo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21742" type="appears in" update="2012-12-30">
<rating votes="18">6.54</rating>
<name>Dokurou Skull</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dokurou Skull is hell`s branch chief of "counter measures". She assigned Elsee to capture spirits in the human world and sent Katsuragi Keima the contract letter. She may be the only person from hell who doesn`t make fun of Elsea.</description>
<picture>58954.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3368" picture="132584.jpg">Kujira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21743" type="appears in" update="2010-09-19">
<rating votes="2">2.52</rating>
<name>Kaketamatai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Kaketamatai (Runaway Spirit Squad) was established ten years ago after the Great Spirit Escape and is tasked with recovering all the Spirits that escaped Old Hell.</description>
</character>
<character id="23171" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-13">
<rating votes="54">8.31</rating>
<name>Nikaidou Yuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nikaidou is Keima`s homeroom and national language teacher. She has been ignoring Keima ever since he told her that there are 5012 games that are more fun than her lessons. She is a sadist.
She is in reality a high ranked devil from hell but is not part of the runaway squad.</description>
<picture>246184.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="222" picture="19786.jpg">Tanaka Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23172" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-13">
<rating votes="21">3.46</rating>
<name>Terada Miyako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Terada Miyako is asecond-year Maijima High School Academy student enrolled in Class 2-B. Miyako is a close friend of Ayumi and Chihiro. She has a long hair and freckles on her cheeks. Track-and-field club member. Her speciality are the 400m.
After the Chihiro Arc, she became a member of Chihiro`s band. Responsible for the keyboard (KORG X50).
Her name is derived from Terada Station (寺田駅, Terada-eki).</description>
<picture>246185.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22168" picture="186262.jpg">Chikamura Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23173" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-02">
<rating votes="6">2.46</rating>
<name>Ishikiri Izumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76333.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2505" picture="141583.jpg">Makiguchi Mayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23174" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-09">
<rating votes="18">5.80</rating>
<name>Hatori Yuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Keima`s 10,000th target captured in galge.</description>
<picture>58950.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23231" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="194">6.74</rating>
<name>Kosaka Chihiro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kosaka Chihiro is a classmate and close friend of Takahara Ayumi. Chihiro is an average girl who has no redeeming features whatsoever: she`s not pretty, her grades are so-so, and she doesn`t have an after-school activity—except for going home. She is described as a "reality girl among reality" by Keima`s visual novel argot, meaning she is void of defining characteristics. Keima therefore refuses at the greatest that he does not want to `capture` her. She has a habit of confessing to handsome, attractive boys without any serious consideration, which yields no success; all because she feels "luminous" as those she is in pursuit of, for that moment. When Keima is tricked into cleaning duty with Chihiro, she demands him to help her latest confession to succeed. Keima reliezes then that a gap does not need to be filled by his love but can be filled by another person` love. He agrees to help Chihiro in her confession. During this period however her feelings begin to shift towards Keima due to their similarities (they both share a sense of disappointment in the real world). After an argument between the two Chihiro ran off and Keima realized that Chihiro did have one defining parameter and vowed to capture the spirit himself, which he does by convincing Chihiro that as long as she truly wants it, nothing can stop her from no longer being generic. Aftrwards, like Ayumi, Chihiro`s attitude towards Keima improves somewhat, becoming one of his `friends`.
Chihiro is the founder of "2B Pencils", an all-female band composed of girls from Class B of Mai-High; its members besides herself are Ayumi Takahara, Elsie, Miyako Terada and Yui Goidou. Responsible for the guitar and vocals (Mustang).
The cause of Chihiro`s crevice in the heart was her disbelief of having a straight-forward path in life that will spark her interests.
Her name is derived from Kawachi-Kosaka Station (河内小阪駅, Kawachi-Kosaka-eki).</description>
<picture>73486.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23425" type="appears in" update="2020-04-13">
<rating votes="56">8.23</rating>
<name>Katsuragi Mari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Keima`s mother resembles a typical shoujo manga-style mother; optimistic, ditsy, and loving. However, when she is angry, Mari removes her glasses and lets her hair down and changes her personality completely. Keima claims that she used to be a part of a biker gang, and has shown violent tendencies that reflect this.</description>
<picture>246186.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23584" type="appears in" update="2010-11-09">
<rating votes="4">2.66</rating>
<name>Morita</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mio`s chauffeur. Modeled from Shin Kishida.</description>
<picture>58951.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2192" picture="196332.jpg">Kashii Shouto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25896" type="appears in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="196">8.57</rating>
<name>Haqua d`rot Herminium</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haqua is a fellow demon and friend of Elsie. She graduated as an outstanding honour student and was promoted to the position of District Chief of District 32 in Nagumo city. However, until meeting Keima, she had never captured an escaped spirit. After hearing of Elsie`s successes in this regard, the gap within Haqua`s heart widened. This allowed a powerful spirit to take control of her. After Elsie calmed Haqua down, they joined forces and defeated the spirit. Even though her human partner is http://anidb.net/ch26096 [Marui Yukie], Keima has occasionally assisted Haqua in her quest to find and capture escaped spirits. She seems to have taken a liking to him.
Haqua`s first name is derived from "Cretaceous (白亜, Hakua)".</description>
<picture>73485.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26036" type="appears in" update="2010-12-26">
<rating votes="2">2.52</rating>
<name>SD</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="22168" picture="186262.jpg">Chikamura Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26037" type="appears in" update="2011-11-02">
<rating votes="5">3.51</rating>
<name>Ryou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76331.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17260" picture="46597.jpg">Teratani Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26038" type="appears in" update="2011-11-02">
<rating votes="5">3.34</rating>
<name>Elf</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76306.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2505" picture="141583.jpg">Makiguchi Mayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26039" type="appears in" update="2011-11-02">
<rating votes="4">3.00</rating>
<name>Seina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76332.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="162" picture="23208.jpg">Satou Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26040" type="appears in" update="2010-12-26">
<rating votes="2">2.52</rating>
<name>Rina</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="6926" picture="31779.jpg">Harui Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26041" type="appears in" update="2011-11-02">
<rating votes="6">4.03</rating>
<name>Hibiki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76311.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17069" picture="80944.jpg">Numakura Manami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26042" type="appears in" update="2013-08-13">
<rating votes="6">3.06</rating>
<name>Fujiidera</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fujiidera is the chairwoman of school library.</description>
<picture>76197.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="347" picture="41555.jpg">Nonaka Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26043" type="appears in" update="2011-11-01">
<rating votes="4">2.87</rating>
<name>Mandragon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75975.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3787" picture="25815.jpg">Miyazaki Hiromu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26044" type="appears in" update="2011-10-18">
<rating votes="38">1.91</rating>
<name>Kodama-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70364.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3149" picture="132209.jpg">Nakao Ryuusei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26045" type="appears in" update="2011-11-01">
<rating votes="5">3.51</rating>
<name>Yuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuri is a member of an idol trio http://anidb.net/ch26049 [Citron].</description>
<picture>75834.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22366" picture="217303.jpg">Uchida Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26046" type="appears in" update="2011-11-01">
<rating votes="5">3.85</rating>
<name>Lime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lime is a member of an idol trio http://anidb.net/ch26049 [Citron].</description>
<picture>75831.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="430" picture="246278.jpg">Hidaka Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26047" type="appears in" update="2018-11-25">
<rating votes="10">4.45</rating>
<name>Okada</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch21505 [Kanon]`s manager.</description>
<picture>227115.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="229" picture="152363.jpg">Itou Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26048" type="appears in" update="2011-11-01">
<rating votes="6">2.70</rating>
<name>Make-up</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A guy who took care of Kanon`s appearance before concert at Narusawa Seaside Hall and who found that she is missing.</description>
<picture>75858.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="378" picture="46436.jpg">Oota Tetsuharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26049" type="appears in" update="2011-11-01">
<rating votes="4">3.37</rating>
<name>Citron</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Citron was an idol trio that http://anidb.net/ch21505 [Kanon] was a member of. Originally meant to promote its leader http://anidb.net/ch26046 [Lime], Kanon eventually became more popular and the center of the group after taking off her glasses.</description>
<picture>75835.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="26050" type="appears in" update="2011-11-01">
<rating votes="4">3.51</rating>
<name>Roushinshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of Kanon fans.</description>
<picture>75836.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6082" picture="222919.jpg">Hirano Toshitaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26051" type="appears in" update="2011-11-01">
<rating votes="4">3.00</rating>
<name>Shikai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Producer/director of Kanon`s video.</description>
<picture>75925.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23246" picture="61476.jpg">Tajiri Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26052" type="appears in" update="2011-11-01">
<rating votes="5">3.34</rating>
<name>Joshi Announcer</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Announcer of the NNS award for best new artist.</description>
<picture>75819.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2228" picture="21776.jpg">Gibu Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26053" type="appears in" update="2011-10-31">
<rating votes="4">3.00</rating>
<name>Mio no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mio`s dead father.</description>
<picture>75740.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="601" picture="165793.jpg">Nakamura Hidetoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26061" type="appears in" update="2011-11-01">
<rating votes="4">3.37</rating>
<name>Kitarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kanon`s pet turtle. He likes to eat parsley.</description>
<picture>75855.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="26062" type="appears in" update="2010-12-27">
<rating votes="4">3.91</rating>
<name>2 nen B-gumi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The class Keima is in.</description>
</character>
<character id="26096" type="appears in" update="2011-11-02">
<rating votes="5">3.52</rating>
<name>Marui Yukie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yukie is a 54 year old saleswoman and is still currently single. However, she is also Haqua`s human partner in capturing escaped spirits. Yukie loves to practice Tai Chi Chuan in her spare time and she always likes to offer stuff to others. She spends her day walking to nearby towns, delivering and selling the drink Gokult to other people. Yukie is seen as useless by her partner Haqua because even though they managed to discover 15 escaped spirits, Yukie could not get a single one of them to come out in the past couple months, even when she`s visiting them daily. However that was proved to be wrong later on as Yukie was able to capture 4 spirits in one week.</description>
<picture>76330.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="121997" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-10-21</airdate>
<rating votes="18">6.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドライヴ・マイ・カー / パーティーはそのままに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Drive My Car / I Don`t Want to Spoil the Party</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Drive My Car / La soirée continue</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Drive My Car / Party wa Sono Mama ni</title>
<summary>The next loose soul was hiding in Maijima Academy`s resident rich girl and daughter of the owner of a big company, Mio Aoyama.  Keima and Elsie followed Mio home and discovered that she was actually living in a run-down apartment.  Now that Keima knows Mio`s secret, he offers to become her new driver!  He continues to take care of Mio while enduring the abusive title of "commoner."  And then one day, Mio receives an invitation to a high society party...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>560136</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="121998" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="20">6.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あくまでも妹です / ベイビー・ユー・アー・ア・リッチ・ガール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Demon of a Sister / Baby, You`re a Rich Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ma petite soeur / Baby, You Are a Rich Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akuma Demo Imouto Desu / Baby, You Are a Rich Girl</title>
<summary>Keima and Elsie have successfully conquered Ayumi and captured the loose soul.  ──But they haven`t completed their contract yet...!!
Elsie transfers into Keima`s class, declares that she`s his little sister, and announces that she`s going to live in his house as well!
All for the sake of rounding up the loose souls in this city...  Who holds the next loose spirit?  And will Elsie be able to become Keima`s little sister??
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>560134</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="121999" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="25">7.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">世界はアイで動いている</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love Makes the World Go Round</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`amour fait tourner le monde</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sekai wa Ai de Ugoite Iru</title>
<summary>Katsuragi Keima, a high school sophomore in class 2-B of Majima Academy, is a dating sim master and known as the "God of Conquest." Elsie, a demon descended from Hell, comes to speak to Keima for entering into a deal with the devil. In order to protect his life, he must capture the "Loose Souls" which exist in people`s hearts. To do this, he must make real-life girls fall in love with him! A loose soul escapes into his classmate, track-and-field athlete Takahara Ayumi`s heart. Will he really get her to fall in love with him?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>560038</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="122542" update="2011-05-18">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">FLAG.0</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Flag 0</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Flag 0</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122748" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-10-28</airdate>
<rating votes="20">5.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">今そこにある聖戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">On a Crusade</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La guerre sainte</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ima Soko ni Aru Seisen</title>
<summary>A short break from hunting down loose souls!  Keima is finally free to toil away at his dating sims, but now there`s a game that the "God of Conquest" cannot conquer...!?  Keima begs (intimidates) Elsie into helping him conquer the buggy mess that everybody`s talking about, "Crayon," the game with an ending nobody`s ever seen.  Elsie watches as Keima desperately tries to "save" the heroine Sora Asuka...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>560138</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="124217" update="2011-09-07">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124224" update="2013-04-17">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124686" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-04</airdate>
<rating votes="17">6.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">IDOL BOMB!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Idol Bomb!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">IDOL BOMB!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Idol Bomb!!</title>
<summary>Maijima Academy is in an uproar because the current most popular orthodox idol, Kanon Nakagawa (who`s actually a student there!), is coming for the first time in two months!!  Keima is playing his games on the roof of the south building when he happens to run into Kanon.  Kanon panics when she discovers that Keima doesn`t recognize her, a national idol!  Why is she so obsessed with drawing attention to herself?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>560142</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="124862" update="2011-09-07">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-10-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124863" update="2013-04-17">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-10-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124945" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-11</airdate>
<rating votes="17">5.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ワタシ平凡?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m Ordinary?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Suis-je banale ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi Heibon?</title>
<summary>...I`m going to turn you into a fan!  And so, Kanon sings on the roof for Keima.  Keima treats her coldly in an attempt to learn what is troubling her, but Kanon is so hurt that she goes into a state of shock and her body becomes transparent!  It appears to be related to the loose soul inside her...but as Elsie looks for information about Kanon, she learns about something that happened in Kanon`s past.  In the meantime, Kanon`s dream concert at Narusawa Seaside Hall is drawing near.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>560146</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="125138" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-18</airdate>
<rating votes="16">5.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Shining Star</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shining Star</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Shining Star</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shining Star</title>
<summary>Kanon appeared to have cheered up, thanks to Keima`s support, but then she disappeared right before the concert!  The staff members are all flustered as Keima and Elsie desperately search for Kanon, but the pumped up audience doesn`t realize that Kanon is missing.  Meanwhile, a transparent Kanon is sitting by herself in a corner of the hall, unable to bear the pressure.  What will happen to the concert...?  Will Keima make it in time?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>560148</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="125294" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-25</airdate>
<rating votes="19">4.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Coupling with with with with</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Coupling With With With With</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Coupling With, With, With, With...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Coupling With With With With</title>
<summary>Elsie tries to cook for her divine brother, but Keima is never pleased.  This time, she tries to make a "self-propelled" lunch, but she gets yelled at again...  Elsie is feeling down, but after some advice from Chihiro, she decides to try again!  As she prepares to make a strawberry shortcake, she prepares sugar from hell and eggs of all kinds of colors.  One of the eggs is...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>560154</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="125456" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="14">4.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神以上, 人間未満</title>
<title xml:lang="en">More Than a God, Less Than a Human</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Plus qu`un dieu, moins qu`un homme</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kami Ijou, Ningen Miman</title>
<summary>Due to spending all of his time chasing after loose souls, Keima`s room is filled with dating sims that haven`t been completed...  "Conquest mode" is activated to clear off the backlog of games!  Keima is truly a god as he conquers game after game!!  ...After a few  hours, Keima is still gaming away after ignoring warnings from a concerned Elsie when his body finally gives out and he falls unconscious...as the end draws near, he is greeted by an unexpected sight...!?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>560164</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="125457" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-12-16</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おしまいの日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Last Day</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le jour final</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oshimai no Hi</title>
<summary>The library has decided to dispose of a number of books to prepare for the new media room.  Shiori can`t bear the thought of her precious books being thrown away, so she sets up a barricade and holes herself up in the library.  The members of the library committee pay no heed to Shiori`s silent protests and prepare to storm the library and dispose of the books as planned.  Shiori begins to falter in the face of adversity, when Keima suddenly appears before her.  Has he come to save her, or perhaps...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>560162</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="125458" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-12-09</airdate>
<rating votes="14">6.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あたしの中の......</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inside of Me......</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">À l`intérieur de moi...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atashi no Naka no...</title>
<summary>Keima proclaims that books are no longer necessary in this day and age and the soft-spoken Shiori finally loses her cool!?  As a result, Keima is able to hear how Shiori truly feels, but now there`s an uproar in the library...?  The "fortress of paper" that`s protected Shiori from the real world is about to change...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>560160</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="125459" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-12-02</airdate>
<rating votes="15">5.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大きな壁の中と外</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inside and Outside the Big Wall</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le mur : Dedans et en dehors</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ookina Kabe no Naka to Soto</title>
<summary>Elsie`s cake ended up blowing up!  Keima yells at Elsie for lacking common sense, so Elsie goes to the library to study up on common sense in the human world.  Maijima Academy`s library houses an expansive collection of books.  Elsie gets excited after finding a flashy picture book, but then she detects a loose soul in the librarian, Shiori Shiomiya!  Shiori is a quiet and soft-spoken girl.  It will be difficult to get her to speak, much less open up...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>560156</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="125461" update="2012-02-20">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-11-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126234" update="2012-02-20">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-12-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126235" update="2012-02-20">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-12-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126349" update="2012-02-20">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-12-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131925" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-07-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">PV</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>560302</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="131926" update="2011-09-07">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-08-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">PV「Kiss,Kiss,Kiss...」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV2 Kiss, Kiss, Kiss...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">PV Kiss,Kiss,Kiss...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132839" update="2011-09-07">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2011-06-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Liner Notes 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132840" update="2011-09-07">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2011-05-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Liner Notes 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132841" update="2011-09-07">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2011-05-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Liner Notes 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132842" update="2011-09-07">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2011-03-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Liner Notes 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132843" update="2011-09-07">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2011-02-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Liner Notes 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132844" update="2011-09-07">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2011-01-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Liner Notes 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132845" update="2011-09-07">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2011-05-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Nakagawa Kanon Concert</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132846" update="2011-09-07">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-03-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Idol Song Scene 05 - Happy Crescent</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132847" update="2011-09-07">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-03-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Idol Song Scene 04 - Happy Crescent</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132848" update="2011-09-07">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-03-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Idol Song Scene 03 - All 4 You</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132849" update="2011-09-07">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-03-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Idol Song Scene 02 - Love Kanon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132850" update="2011-09-07">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-03-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Idol Song Scene 01 - All 4 You</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132851" update="2011-09-07">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132852" update="2011-09-07">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132853" update="2011-09-07">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132854" update="2011-09-07">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
