<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7595" restricted="true">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-08-27</startdate>
<enddate>2010-11-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Otome Juurin Yuugi: Maiden Infringement Play</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">처녀 유린 유희</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">乙女蹂躙遊戯~Maiden Infringement Play~</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.guilty-soft.com/jyurinanime/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="13144" type="Character Design">Lee Si-Min</name>
<name id="957" type="Original Work">Guilty</name>
<name id="11516" type="Direction">Yokoyama Hiromi</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch28136 [Ibuki] and http://anidb.net/ch28137 [Akira] are being held in a villa located deep in the mountains. After awaking in a dungeon cell, they find out that http://anidb.net/ch64073 [Shuuji] and three others intend to train them as sex-slaves.
~ translated and adapted from official site by Cranston</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="231">4.41</permanent>
<temporary count="236">5.76</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>49423.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11610</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9009</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5160</identifier>
<identifier>iwzxcy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.suzukimirano.com/product/jurin01.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.guilty-soft.com/jyurinanime/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14573</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4352</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2072" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>maid</name>
<description>A maid is a female employed in domestic service. They usually wear uniforms. Since their nature is to be obedient and serve their goshujin-sama (master), they are one of the most desired types of women in Japan, a dream of every Japanese man, particularly http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku]. Often seen in so-called Maid Cafes in Akihabara, where male customers can for a little time enjoy the feeling of being served by a woman. The male gender opposite is the butler.</description>
<picurl>4954.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2615" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-25">
<name>18 restricted</name>
<description>This isn`t really an "audience".
While some anime might feature sexual content they still might not be considered pornography. This category is meant only for when the content is clearly *not* intended for minors. The distinction is made by whether the content is sold only to adults.</description>
<picurl>67867.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2695" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>yuri</name>
<description>Yuri refers to anime that portray lesbian (female/female) sex. Do not confuse this with the http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai] category under Romance, which only portrays girl/girl relationships, but generally not anything pornographic. This is real female/female porn.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>150944.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2696" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-13">
<name>threesome</name>
<description>Tag for any scene where sexual acts take place with three people of any gender. Should not be used if more than three.</description>
<picurl>150774.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2697" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-05">
<name>voyeurism</name>
<description>Voyeurism is the sexual interest in or practice of spying on people engaged in intimate behaviors, such as undressing, sexual activity, or other actions usually considered to be of a private nature. The principal characteristic of voyeurism is that the voyeur does not normally interact directly with the subject of his/her interest, who is often unaware of being observed. The essence of voyeurism is the observing but may also involve the making of a secret photograph or video of the subject during an intimate activity. When the interest in a particular subject is obsessive, the behavior may be described as stalking.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162189.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2704" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-15">
<name>cum play</name>
<description>Fetish of sorts where the focus is of the semen that is ejaculated. This can include snowballing, drinking copious amounts of semen, eating it off food, using it to brush one`s teeth, acting as a urinal for semen, gargling it, rinsing one`s mouth with it, or any other act where semen is involved that does not have to do with fertilization of an egg.
This should not be used if one cannot visibly see semen in scenes or if the scene is extremely short.</description>
<picurl>236279.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2705" parentid="2848" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-20">
<name>creampie</name>
<description>The act of a man ejaculating inside a girl`s vagina, leaving the semen oozing out of her.</description>
<picurl>160720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2706" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>masturbation</name>
<description>Manual erotic stimulation of the genitals or other erogenous regions, often to orgasm, either by oneself or a partner.</description>
<picurl>210612.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2710" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-18">
<name>squirting</name>
<description>Squirt, a small, quick stream, a jet when girl gets orgasm.</description>
<picurl>227795.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2712" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>sex toys</name>
<description>A sex toy is an object or device that is primarily used to facilitate human sexual pleasure, such as a dildo or vibrator.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2713" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>oral</name>
<description>Oral sex is sexual activity involving the stimulation of the genitalia of a sex partner by the use of the mouth, tongue, teeth or throat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2715" parentid="7220" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-11">
<name>rape</name>
<description>Rape means to force someone to engage in sexual interaction without their consent. If the rape is not successfully executed (both fellatio and penetration did not occur), tag with http://anidb.net/t7238 [attempted rape] instead.</description>
<picurl>212186.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2717" parentid="2848" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>anal</name>
<description>Sodomy, buggery, buttsex, cornholing, or the poop-chute polka. Call it whatever you like, but somebody is getting something stuck where the sun does not shine.</description>
<picurl>173755.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2719" parentid="2848" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-19">
<name>gang bang</name>
<description>A situation in which one person has sexual intercourse and performs other sex acts with a number of people, either in turn or at the same time.</description>
<picurl>181529.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2721" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-13">
<name>public sex</name>
<description>Public sex refers to sexual acts that take place in public or semi-public places.</description>
<picurl>175406.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2722" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-21">
<name>doggy style</name>
<description>Bang her from behind and use her boobies as a steering wheel!</description>
<picurl>161394.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2724" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-15">
<name>double penetration</name>
<description>Double penetration is a situation during which someone is simultaneously penetrated by two penises or strap-ons.</description>
<picurl>172771.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2733" parentid="2715" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-20">
<name>enjoyable rape</name>
<description>This anime features a rape scene during which the raped character also reaches orgasm or somehow else derives sexual pleasure from the act.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2866" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>slavery</name>
<description>Someone is owned by somebody else. In anime this usually affects body (slaves in a fantasy setting) or mind (the evil villain brainwashes a sidekick, creates an obedient minion or places a spell on some poor bloke). Slavery is also a common element of hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2877" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>revenge</name>
<description>A primary factor that drives the plot forward, is the almost obsessive desire of one of the characters to get back at someone else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2894" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>female student</name>
<description>Pretty much exclusive to hentai shows only unless an ecchi show has implied sex and/or a strong indicator of nudity. A character is considered a student if she goes to school, doesn`t matter if it`s high school, college or homeschooling, but she should be of appropriate age for a student; a housewife going to college should not get this category.</description>
<picurl>210611.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2896" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-23">
<name>deflowering</name>
<description>Deflowering is the act of breaking the hymen of a female who hadn`t yet had vaginal intercourse. This tag can be applied only to pornographic anime in which a female is seen being deflowered; most often, one knows she had been a virgin because blood is seen coming out of her vagina during sex or after it, but her word on the matter is also considered valid.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2899" parentid="2712" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-04-21">
<name>strapon</name>
<description>Employs the use of an artificial phallus so that the female can engage in the penetrating role during intercourse. Not to be confused with a http://anidb.net/t6455 [double-sided dildo].</description>
<picurl>185955.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2900" parentid="2712" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-20">
<name>dildos - vibrators</name>
<description>These are toys that are used for sexual pleasure.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2901" parentid="2729" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-09">
<name>bondage</name>
<description>Bondage is the use of restraints for the sexual pleasure of the parties involved. It may be used in its own right, as in the case of rope bondage and breast bondage, or as part of sexual activity or BDSM activity. When a person is sexually aroused by bondage, it may be considered a paraphilia, known as vincilagnia (from Latin vincio, to bind or fetter with chains, and lagneia, lust).
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42021.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2914" parentid="2704" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-25">
<name>bukkake</name>
<description>Bukkake is a group sex practice wherein a group of men ejaculate onto a woman.</description>
<picurl>208870.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2918" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>cunnilingus</name>
<description>Cunnilingus is an oral sex act performed on a female. It involves the use by a sex partner of the mouth, lips and tongue to stimulate the female`s clitoris and vulva. A female may receive cunnilingus as part of foreplay before sexual intercourse, or the sex partner may proceed until the female reaches orgasm.
The term is derived from the Latin words for the vulva (cunnus) and tongue (lingua).</description>
<picurl>161636.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2920" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>rimming</name>
<description>Rimming is the act of using one`s tongue on the anus or perineum of another person in order to gain and/or give sexual pleasure.</description>
<picurl>165410.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2921" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-12">
<name>throat fucking</name>
<description>The act of actively thrusting one`s penis into a persons mouth and throat.</description>
<picurl>236088.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3244" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-04-08">
<name>sexually dominant</name>
<description>Sexually dominant is a designation applied to those able to assertively assume and maintain control over the actions of their partner(s) during sexual activity, actively steering it towards their own intents and preferences and possibly to the detriment of those of their partner(s).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3299" parentid="6268" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-11">
<name>double fellatio</name>
<description>Double fellatio is when oral sex is performed on the penis simultaneously by two individuals.</description>
<picurl>168623.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3993" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-28">
<name>kidnapping</name>
<description>In criminal law, kidnapping is the taking away or transportation of a person against that person`s will, usually to hold the person in false imprisonment, a confinement without legal authority. This may be done for ransom or in furtherance of another crime, or in connection with a child custody dispute.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10583.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4049" parentid="2721" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-13">
<name>outdoor sex</name>
<description>Popular place for sex in visual novels and manga.</description>
<picurl>175405.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4492" parentid="2715" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>gang rape</name>
<description>Gang rape occurs when a group of people (at least 2) participate in the rape of a single victim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4560" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-02-23">
<name>psychological manipulation</name>
<description>Psychological manipulation is a type of social influence that aims to change the perception or behaviour of others through underhanded, deceptive, or even abusive tactics. By advancing the interests of the manipulator, often at the other`s expense, such methods could be considered exploitative, abusive, devious, and deceptive. 
Social influence is not necessarily negative. For example, doctors can try to persuade patients to change unhealthy habits. Social influence is generally perceived to be harmless when it respects the right of the influenced to accept or reject it, and is not unduly coercive. Depending on the context and motivations, social influence may constitute underhanded manipulation.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5406" parentid="2729" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-02">
<name>submission</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5936" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>uniform fetish</name>
<description>Focuses on many different kinds of, often sexy, uniforms.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5984" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-09-10">
<name>girly tears</name>
<description>Usually girly tears are the ones not shed by men (duh). 
Like when a (stereotypical) girl watches something and cries her makeup out, a (stereotypical) dude just says, proclaiming his masculinity: "Meh, yet another soap opera bulls..t, I`ll be in my garage fixing my ride while playing heavy metal on a burning guitar ...with my teeth! And where`s my beer, woman?".
So that`s how it goes: girly tears are for girls and sissies! Chuck Norris forbid a guy would weep watching something that has this tag! Now 20 push-ups!
P.S. The opposite of "manly tears". Or is it? Let`s face it - it`s all subjective (and relative, and context-dependent).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6083" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>master-servant relationship</name>
<description>To some genres, this would suggest a genuine pairing where one person exists to serve another person, such as in some action/dramas where the pair becomes united by destiny as partners — fighting or battles between different pairs/partners will usually be a dominant part of the story.
In other genres, this suggests a relationship where one person may be occupied as or even forcefully treated as a servant or slave to the other who designates themself the master — these services usually apply anywhere from tsundere/romantic-comedies to ecchi or to the more extreme in hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6268" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>fellatio</name>
<description>Fellatio is oral sex performed upon the penis. It may be performed to induce male orgasm and ejaculation of semen, or it may be used as foreplay prior to sexual intercourse.</description>
<picurl>165408.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7221" parentid="7220" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>psychological sexual abuse</name>
<description>Psychological sexual abuse is the exercise of sexual coercion through non-physical means, such as verbal sexual behaviour, stalking, and emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="28136" type="main character in" update="2011-02-02">
<rating votes="9">5.34</rating>
<name>Kurata Ibuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64922.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="28137" type="main character in" update="2011-02-02">
<rating votes="8">8.94</rating>
<name>Miyauchi Akira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64923.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="28138" type="main character in" update="2011-02-02">
<rating votes="11">6.35</rating>
<name>Yakushima Karen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64924.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="64072" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-21">
<name>Oomori Takeshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154669.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="64073" type="main character in" update="2014-04-09">
<name>Yakushima Shuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153384.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="64074" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-21">
<name>Akagi Kouhei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154668.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="64075" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-21">
<name>Kurosaki Kazuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154670.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="118781" update="2010-06-10">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2010-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121903" update="2010-09-06">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2010-11-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
