<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7655" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-10-16</startdate>
<enddate>2010-10-16</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Omae Umasou Da na</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">You are Umasou</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">おまえうまそうだな</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Heart and Yummie</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">To je Bašta!</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7942" type="Other">Miyanishi Tatsuya Gekijou: Omae Umasou Da na</anime>
<anime id="11054" type="Other">Anata o Zutto Aishiteru</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="3436" approval="7" total="8">Arashi no Yoru ni</anime>
<anime id="8211" approval="4" total="10">Usagi Drop</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="655269">when I started watching this movie, I thought it was going to be a run-of-the-mill kids movie with anthropomorphic dinosaurs.
But thank God I was wrong, what I found is one of the greatest emotional roller coaster experiences in anime with amazing animation, great characters and superb voice acting.
Don`t miss it :)</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.umasoudana.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="4787" type="Direction">Fujimori Masaya</name>
<name id="4233" type="Character Design">Yanagida Yoshiaki</name>
<name id="19592" type="Original Work">Miyanishi Tatsuya</name>
<name id="4233" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yanagida Yoshiaki</name>
<name id="5754" type="Music">Terashima Tamiya</name>
<name id="960" type="Animation Work">Ajia-dou</name>
<name id="917" type="Work">TMS Entertainment</name>
</creators>
<description>A female Maiasaura finds a lost egg and decides to take care of it along with her own baby. Much to everyone`s surprise, the child born from the stray egg is a Tyrannosaurus. Although the baby is a carnivore and his adoptive mother a herbivore, she is determined not to leave the newborn behind, so she abandons the pack and raises the two kids by herself.
Named Heart by his mother, the Tyrannosaurus grows up together with his Maiasaura brother, Light. Soon enough, Heart realizes the difference between carnivores and herbivores; as a result, he makes the tough decision of leaving the family and discovering where he belongs.
One day, Heart stumbles upon a baby Ankylosaurus. The baby mistakes him for his father, and accepts the word "umasou", which means "you seem delicious", as his actual name. Originally intending to eat him, Heart comes to be genuinely concerned for Umasou`s well-being as a familial bond develops between them.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="215">8.32</permanent>
<temporary count="215">7.51</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>67958.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11715</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9204</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.umasoudana.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>You_Are_Umasou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>おまえうまそうだな</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>336875</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13030</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="566" parentid="2611" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-10">
<name>dinosaur</name>
<description>Dinosaurs are vertebrate animals that dominated terrestrial ecosystems for over 160 million years, first appearing approximately 230 million years ago. At the end of the Cretaceous Period, 66 million years ago, non-avian dinosaurs suffered a catastrophic extinction, which ended their dominance on land. Taxonomists consider modern birds to be the direct descendants of theropod dinosaurs.
Since the first dinosaur was recognized in the 19th century, mounted, fossilized dinosaur skeletons have become major attractions at museums around the world. Dinosaurs have become a part of world culture and remain consistently popular, especially among children. They have been featured in best-selling books and films such as Jurassic Park, and new discoveries are regularly covered by the media.
Source: Dinopedia</description>
<picurl>191115.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1846" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>kodomo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word kodomo refers to a children`s audience roughly for the ages 12 and younger. In Japanese, the word means simply "child", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4669" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-27">
<name>parenting</name>
<description>This anime is about parenting and its many challenges.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5865" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>manly tears</name>
<description>Somewhere down the line, it became the "norm" that boys don`t cry. The scenario does not matter; shedding tears is the ultimate no-no in terms of what you can and cannot do as a man (at least in the West, anyway). But there comes a time when a man`s emotions do get the better of him, and they pour forth - as prerequisite an impassioned speech may or may not be present - by cascading down his cheeks. These are what we like to call "manly tears". Extremely powerful. Not limited but often used in hot-blooded / super robot shows. Examples include Yuusha Ou GaoGaiGar, Getter Robo and Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann.
The opposite of manly tears are "girly tears".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="82209" type="main character in" update="2016-05-26">
<rating votes="2">9.24</rating>
<name>Heart</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187058.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82210" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-05-26">
<rating votes="1">6.51</rating>
<name>Katame no Baku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63830.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="33747" picture="92670.jpg">Bessho Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82211" type="main character in" update="2016-05-26">
<rating votes="2">7.40</rating>
<name>Umasou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63831.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="32548" picture="87344.jpg">Katou Seishirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82254" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-05-29">
<name>Okaasan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187161.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6408" picture="164120.jpg">Harada Tomoyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82255" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-05-29">
<name>Light</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187162.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2248" picture="170362.jpg">Kawashima Tokuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="119731" update="2011-03-17">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>90</length>
<airdate>2010-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124209" update="2010-10-17">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2010-10-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode T2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124210" update="2010-10-17">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2010-10-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode T2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124211" update="2010-10-17">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2010-10-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode T1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
