<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7656" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-10-04</startdate>
<enddate>2010-12-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Yosuga no Sora: In Solitude, Where We Are Least Alone.</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">In Solitude, Where We are Least Alone</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Связанные Небом</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">요스가노소라</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">yns</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">yosuga no sora</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">yosuga</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">yosusora</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ヨスガノソラ In solitude, where we are least alone.</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">In Solitude Where We Are Least Alone</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">緣之空</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">缘之空</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="6782" approval="82" total="109">Aki Sora</anime>
<anime id="7506" approval="33" total="51">Amagami SS</anime>
<anime id="1675" approval="31" total="53">Koi Kaze</anime>
<anime id="9520" approval="10" total="15">Photokano</anime>
<anime id="5435" approval="3" total="11">Myself; Yourself</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="15">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="214257">for those who saying that this anime is bad seriously I dont know what you are smoking because its f-king amazing. story line is way better than any other anime that belongs to this harem type.  and incest is not bad thing at all its way more interesting then all those boring usual school love stories.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="319146">Watch the first 4 episodes and stop, after that its meh on the plot resets</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="96822">Nice touch, good story and drama. give a try if you like Visual novels.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="436483">A very good slow paced ecchi... It`s a good watch if you love ecchi and the story is quite good too, just a little hard to follow each arc.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="345202">I liked this, don`t know why though since most people would see this one as poorly made or sloppy...

But I liked this one because these are the kinds anime I grew up with since I felt some kind of nostalgia watching this and sometimes grade isn`t everything, you just have to watch it yourself and judge it afterwards!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="333272">At least this is a series where it doesn`t stop when you want it to continue for a bit longer. It even reaches the H scenes, but ofcourse that`s not the main point of the story(well, a bit).
The drama and music of this anime is great. The arcs follow the same system as a VN, so choices differ between the routes. Great adaptation.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="475258">Hey I dont get whats the fuss is all about.. I loved it!
Sora so cute! &amp;lt;3
watch it and see for yourself
NOTE: not for purehearts ;P</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="398971">The comments about this series being close to hentai are definitely exaggerated. Sure it does have those scenes which aren`t exactled aimed for kids but other than that it`s an ordinary romance anime, and an underrated one at that.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="78003">Interesting plot with couple returns. Last episodes contains some Incest, but depite that it`s great drama type anime. Opening and two endings definitely deserve some award!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="422319">I couldn`t stand to watch more than 8 eps. It`s just bad story, bad story, bad story, sex, rewind and play again...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="8102">Rather than a traditional harem anime where the women trip over each other getting at the main character, this one is set up in separate story arcs telling the `what if he chose this girl?` and how the others would deal with the situation. In this way, over the course of the four arcs, we learn a great deal about each woman`s background and shared history. We also see how they each react to our protagonist hooking up with the other girl(s). I thought this was perfectly done, though I would have preferred the other girls getting happy endings in addition to the main girl of the arc. I`m polyamorous though, and prefer when everyone can get happy (or at least generally positive) endings. The incest elements aren`t for everyone, but nothing ever is.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="249582">The very first title of TV-sized(meaned - Non-hentai) anime i would recommend watching. It`s exactly what you expecting (and usually never get) from dating VN port.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="558180">I must say this is best anime I saw so far!!!
Strong and intensive story full of romance, twists with nudity and ecchi.
Sora Arc (last one) made me almost cry and I consider her arcs as one of best romance I saw so far. (And I saw already other masterpiece like Clannad, Amagami SS, Kanon, Air etc.) 
I think this is a masterpiece between masterpieces and it should get 2nd season, but I think it will never happend though. :(</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.starchild.co.jp/special/yosuganosora/</url>
<creators>
<name id="9387" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kamimoto Kanetoshi</name>
<name id="1006" type="Animation Work">Feel</name>
<name id="9387" type="Character Design">Kamimoto Kanetoshi</name>
<name id="3760" type="Series Composition">Arakawa Naruhisa</name>
<name id="3211" type="Direction">Takahashi Takeo</name>
<name id="22916" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ishii Takehiro</name>
<name id="987" type="Work">Gansis</name>
<name id="8546" type="Chief Animation Direction">Masuda Kuniaki</name>
<name id="12228" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sugiyama Ryouzou</name>
<name id="21729" type="Music">Miwa Manabu</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch19422 [Kasugano Haruka] and his twin sister http://anidb.net/ch19427 [Sora] have lost both their parents in an accident, and with them all their support. They decide to move out of the city to the rural town of Okukozome, where they once spent summers with their late grandfather. At first everything seems familiar and peaceful, but then things start to change as Haruka starts to remember his youth.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="3267">4.20</permanent>
<temporary count="3307">6.47</temporary>
<review count="3">4.50</review>
</ratings>
<picture>55953.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11603</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8861</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4794</identifier>
<identifier>psvmlg</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.starchild.co.jp/special/yosuganosora/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Yosuga_no_Sora</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ヨスガノソラ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2028</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>337845</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12979</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1194</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>yosuga-no-sora-in-solitude-where-we-are-least-alone</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1241" parentid="2881" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-18">
<name>swimming</name>
<description>Swimming is an individual or team sport that involves using arms and legs to move the body through water. Typically, the sport takes place in pools or in open water. Competitive swimming is one of the most popular Olympic sports, with events in butterfly, backstroke, breaststroke, freestyle, and individual medley. In addition to these individual events, swimmers take part in relays.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>208479.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2072" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>maid</name>
<description>A maid is a female employed in domestic service. They usually wear uniforms. Since their nature is to be obedient and serve their goshujin-sama (master), they are one of the most desired types of women in Japan, a dream of every Japanese man, particularly http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku]. Often seen in so-called Maid Cafes in Akihabara, where male customers can for a little time enjoy the feeling of being served by a woman. The male gender opposite is the butler.</description>
<picurl>4954.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2216" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-13">
<name>stuffed toy</name>
<description>A stuffed toy is a toy sewn from cloth, plush, or other textiles, and stuffed with straw, beans, plastic pellets, cotton, synthetic fibres, or other similar materials. Stuffed toys are also known as plush toys (U.S. English) from plush, the outer material used, and soft toys or cuddly toys (British English).
Stuffed toys are made in many different forms, often resembling animals, legendary creatures, cartoon characters or inanimate objects. They are often used as comfort objects, for display or collecting and given as gifts, such as for graduation, Valentine`s Day or birthdays.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2302" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-19">
<name>helpful</name>
<description>This character is serviceable for an end or purpose.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2396" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-08">
<name>swimsuit</name>
<description>A swimsuit is one of several kinds of garments designed to be worn by people engaging in water-based activities or sports or during certain activities under sunlight. Most kinds of swimsuit reveal a large portion of the body surface area, but exceptions exist. The more revealing kinds may also be worn as undergarment in sports that require wetsuits, or when there is a need to display the body, as in the case of beauty pageants or bodybuilding contests.
There is a very wide range of styles of modern swimsuits, which vary in relation to body coverage and materials. The choice of style of swimsuit is dependent on current fashions, community standards of modesty, and plain personal preference. Swimsuits for men usually expose the chest, while those for women do not usually do so; however, many women prefer to engage in water or sun activities with their torso uncovered, in a practice commonly described as toplessness or topfreedom. Since the early twentieth century a naturist movement has developed in western countries that seeks a return to non-sexual nakedness when swimming and during other appropriate activities; in some places around the world, nude beaches have been set aside for people who choose to engage in normal beach activities in the nude, and such beaches may or may not enforce nudity onto their goers.
In anime, it is common for at least one episode to feature the characters in swimsuits, usually as an excuse for gratuitous fanservice; when that happens, the episode is usually labeled a pool or beach episode, after the place the characters went to. Swimsuits, and in particular one-piece swimsuits, are a very common fetish in Japan; while the reason for that is uncertain, a common folk explanation is the fact that boys throughout their entire adolescence are commonly exposed to their female classmates wearing them, in what might be called an experiment in sexual discovery waiting to happen.</description>
<picurl>149786.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2455" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>tsundere</name>
<description>Tsundere (ツンデレ) (pronounced /(t)sʌnˈdɪə(r)/ in English or /t͡sun.de.ɽe/ in Japanese) is a Japanese concept of a character archetype which describes a person with a conceited, irritable, and/or violent personality that suddenly becomes modest and loving when triggered by some sort of cause (such as being alone with someone). The inverse scenario, where a modest and loving person becomes conceited/irritable/violent, is also a tsundere.
The default state does not matter. The character can default to "tsuntsun" or "deredere"; the key concept is the fact that there`s a (generally very quick) flip from one mode to the other.
It can also describe a contradictory personality which is good-willed on the inside, but with a harsh attitude on the outside. Originally found in Japanese bishoujo games, the word is now part of the otaku moe phenomenon, reaching into other media such as anime, manga, novels, and even mass media.
Tsundere is a portmanteau of the two words tsuntsun (ツンツン), and deredere (デレデレ). Tsuntsun is defined as "aloof, morose, pointed", and deredere is defined as "exhausted, lovestruck". Tsunderekko (ツンデレっ娘) is a related noun, referring to a girl with a tsundere personality. Like nekomimi, tsundere is considered a moe-inspiring character trait. The concept has received increasing attention in Japan, with a tsundere cafe opened in Akihabara and tsundere-themed products released (like Tomy Co.`s portable television set), and the concept increasingly reflected in recent anime, from an extended discussion of the meaning of the concept and its origin on the internet in http://anidb.net/a4777 [Lucky Star]`s Lucky Channel segment to merchandise for http://anidb.net/a3651 [The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya] classifying the characters according to tsundere-ness. Another accepted definition of tsundere is a girl who has a combative attitude toward others but is also kind on the inside. She usually plays out as having an attitude toward the main character, usually a male, and often criticizing him in one way or another, but as the series progresses she eventually warms up to him and sometimes even falls in love with him.</description>
<picurl>30388.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2520" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>school swimsuit</name>
<description>A school swimsuit (also known as sukumizu, shorthand for school mizugi) is a standardised navy blue one-piece swimsuit worn by schoolgirls. Typically they also have a name tag on the front. Sukumizu can also be black or white.
Normally worn at schools though sometimes also worn at beaches when the character feels this to be easier, forgot to buy a normal swimsuit of their own or wants to give some fan service to those that like school swimsuits better than regular swimsuits.
In http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] anime, a swimsuit of this type sometimes serves censoring purposes when characters take a bath. If there is a group of female characters donning swimsuits, you can expect the youngest or youngest-looking girl to wear one of these.</description>
<picurl>52174.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2566" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-31">
<name>loli</name>
<description>Lolita (often also just abbreviated to loli) refers originally to a novel by Vladimir Nabokov. The book is internationally famous for its controversial subject: the narrator and protagonist, middle aged Humbert Humbert, becomes obsessed and sexually involved with a 12-year-old girl named Dolores Haze.
Nowadays the name "Lolita" describes a sexually precocious young girl.
Related to this is http://anidb.net/t2415 [lolicon], the Japanese abbreviation of the English phrase "Lolita Complex". Sometimes written as "roricon" or "rorikon" due to the inexact mapping between Japanese and English phonemes. This is the term used to describe the fetish/fascination some mature people have for underage girls. There is an entire industry in Japan devoted to providing legal but schoolgirl-themed pornography, taking advantage of the cute childlike appearance some Japanese women maintain well into their twenties.
Because the characters in anime are often young by convention, many fans think that a character can only be Lolicon if she is twelve or younger. Exceptions are granted if the other character in the relationship is a lot older.
One particular device used to skirt the boundaries of taste and legality is the exotic being (alien, creature of magic, robot or the like) which takes the form of an underage human girl, but is in fact for all other practical purposes an adult.
Another reason why lolicon is fetishized by people may be because some of them just view it as a substitute for their fetish for flat-chested, but otherwise well-developed, women.
Source: Wikipedia / TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2634" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>countryside</name>
<description>The anime takes place far from the any densely populated areas like cities, i.e. out in the suburbs, in the countryside with many fields and forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2706" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>masturbation</name>
<description>Manual erotic stimulation of the genitals or other erogenous regions, often to orgasm, either by oneself or a partner.</description>
<picurl>210612.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2738" parentid="2842" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>twincest</name>
<description>Or “incest between twins”. Often describes a sexual relationship between twins.
The twins might be or not be actually related (in the latter case they may have previously been thought to be related, but are later discovered not to be).
This is not exclusive to gender or sexual preference, and can be a heterosexual or homosexual relationship.</description>
<picurl>210886.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2739" parentid="2842" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>brother-sister incest</name>
<description>Immoral or illegal sexual relations between two siblings of opposite sex.</description>
<picurl>210881.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2828" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-26">
<name>borderline porn</name>
<description>Breaks the bounds of "excessive fanservice".
While the physical interactions and dialogue between characters may be extremely sexual, the most sexual situations do *not* have sex itself take place.
Specifically descriptive of containing all the plentiful features of (excessive) fanservice in addition to the interactions between characters being quite sexual — at most, sexual in NATURE only. This means physical touching such as groping, molesting, or bondage will focus primarily on the revealed (i.e. nude) upper portion of the body or through/over clothing on the lower half of the body. This is all WITHOUT actual sex acts (penetration, etc.) taking place.</description>
<picurl>214855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2842" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-19">
<name>incest</name>
<description>Incest is human sexual activity between family members or close relatives by consanguinity (blood relations) and sometimes by affinity (marriage or stepfamily), adoption, clan, or lineage. The incest taboo is among the most widespread cultural taboos in present and past societies. Most modern societies have laws regarding incest or social restrictions on closely consanguineous marriages, with first cousins being the closest kin that is often (but not always) considered legally acceptable.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210769.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2865" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>summer festival</name>
<description>The summer festival is used to show off the female protagonists in traditional Japanese clothing — the yukata — a casual form of kimono.
The festivities include food stalls (cotton candy, candy apples, choco bananas, taiyaki), various games (scoop goldfishes), and a fireworks display.</description>
<picurl>161023.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2894" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>female student</name>
<description>Pretty much exclusive to hentai shows only unless an ecchi show has implied sex and/or a strong indicator of nudity. A character is considered a student if she goes to school, doesn`t matter if it`s high school, college or homeschooling, but she should be of appropriate age for a student; a housewife going to college should not get this category.</description>
<picurl>210611.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3020" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-01">
<name>chibi ED</name>
<description>Some or all of the endings feature chibi versions of the characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4090" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-08">
<name>cardiopulmonary resuscitation</name>
<description>Cardiopulmonary resuscitation, commonly known as CPR, is an emergency procedure that combines chest compression often with artificial ventilation in an effort to manually preserve intact brain function until further measures are taken to restore spontaneous blood circulation and breathing in a person who is in cardiac arrest. It is indicated in those who are unresponsive with no breathing or abnormal breathing. CPR involves chest compressions at a rate of at least 100 to 120 per minute. The rescuer may also provide artificial ventilation by either exhaling air into the subject`s mouth or nose (mouth-to-mouth resuscitation) or using a device that pushes air into the subject`s lungs (mechanical ventilation).
CPR alone is unlikely to restart the heart; its main purpose is to restore partial flow of oxygenated blood to the brain and heart. The objective is to delay tissue death and to extend the brief window of opportunity for a successful resuscitation without permanent brain damage. Administration of an electric shock to the subject`s heart, termed defibrillation, is usually needed in order to restore a viable heart rhythm. In general, CPR is continued until the person has a return of spontaneous circulation or is declared dead.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>68242.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4116" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-13">
<name>eternal blush</name>
<description>It is no ordinary blush it is a blush that does not disappear.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4386" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-19">
<name>eating Pocky</name>
<description>Pocky (ポッキー) is a Japanese snack food produced by the Ezaki Glico Company of Japan. Pocky was first sold in 1966, and consists of a biscuit stick coated with chocolate. It was named after the Japanese onomatopoetic word for the sound Pocky makes when bitten, pokkin (ポッキン). The original was followed by "Almond Pocky" in 1971, with an almond coating, and "Strawberry Pocky" in 1977. Today, the product line includes such variations as milk, mousse, green tea, honey, banana and coconut flavored coatings, and themed products such as "Decorer Pocky," with colourful decorative stripes in the coating, and "Men`s Pocky," a dark (bittersweet) chocolate and "mature" version.
Source: Wikipedia
It`s marketed in Germany under the name Mikado (Note: NOT the game, the snack).</description>
<picurl>73630.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5593" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-13">
<name>branching story</name>
<description>The whole series consists of alternative stories, starting at the same point, branching off to different endings. It is like a normal dating sim, where you have different choices to meet different girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5794" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-01">
<name>forbidden love</name>
<description>This anime contains characters pursuing a romantic interest that their parents, grandparents, the police, the fire department, the neighbourhood watch association and local politicians do not approve of.
Potential relationships defined as such may be ones that are incestuous, violations of caste systems, or socially unsanctioned.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5840" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>birthday</name>
<description>All about the birthday celebration of at least one of the protagonists in this anime.
This includes a birthday party with a birthday cake and other food and presents — lots of them.</description>
<picurl>161031.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="19422" type="main character in" update="2010-09-29">
<rating votes="40">4.20</rating>
<name>Kasugano Haruka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55663.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="435" picture="188447.jpg">Matsumoto Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19423" type="main character in" update="2010-09-29">
<rating votes="25">7.22</rating>
<name>Amatsume Akira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55660.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3182" picture="55949.jpg">Sakata Kayo</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="435" picture="188447.jpg">Matsumoto Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19424" type="main character in" update="2010-09-29">
<rating votes="33">5.30</rating>
<name>Yorihime Nao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55661.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19679" picture="207991.jpg">Inokuchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19425" type="main character in" update="2010-09-29">
<rating votes="28">6.74</rating>
<name>Migiwa Kazuha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55659.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="594" picture="156858.jpg">Ono Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19426" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-29">
<rating votes="20">7.44</rating>
<name>Nogisaka Motoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55658.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="618" picture="223541.jpg">Okajima Tae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19427" type="main character in" update="2010-09-29">
<rating votes="131">8.23</rating>
<name>Kasugano Sora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55662.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="638" picture="151683.jpg">Taguchi Hiroko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19428" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-29">
<rating votes="23">5.46</rating>
<name>Kuranaga Kozue</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55657.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20300" picture="53064.jpg">Minegishi Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19429" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-29">
<rating votes="20">7.69</rating>
<name>Ifukube Yahiro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55656.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1617" picture="19642.jpg">Tanaka Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19430" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-29">
<rating votes="12">4.66</rating>
<name>Nakazato Ryouhei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55655.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2135" picture="66343.jpg">Nakakuni Takurou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23403" type="appears in" update="2010-10-19">
<rating votes="5">3.27</rating>
<name>Migiwa no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>57256.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="282" picture="223615.jpg">Houki Katsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24676" type="appears in" update="2010-11-02">
<rating votes="8">4.90</rating>
<name>Migiwa no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>58378.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1983" picture="151694.jpg">Murai Kazusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25310" type="appears in" update="2010-11-24">
<rating votes="4">3.82</rating>
<name>Nao no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59785.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1917" picture="151688.jpg">Natsuki Rio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25637" type="appears in" update="2010-12-10">
<rating votes="2">4.06</rating>
<name>Haruka no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60560.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19" picture="50583.jpg">Imaruoka Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25638" type="appears in" update="2010-12-10">
<rating votes="4">5.57</rating>
<name>Haruka no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60561.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="206" picture="228617.jpg">Hikami Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="121635" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="20">4.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハルカナキオク</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Distant Memories</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haruka na Kioku</title>
<summary>After the sudden death of their parents, Haruka and his twin sister Sora move to their grandparents` house, hoping to create a new life with old, and new, friends.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685595</identifier>
<identifier>yosuga-no-sora-in-solitude-where-we-are-least-alone</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="122253" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-10-25</airdate>
<rating votes="13">4.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハルカズハート</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Haruka`s Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haruka`s Heart</title>
<summary>Kazuha and Akira have a deep connection, one that only they acknowledge.  Haruka is instrumental in providing some clarity to Kazuha`s misconceptions.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685601</identifier>
<identifier>yosuga-no-sora-in-solitude-where-we-are-least-alone</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="122254" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="14">4.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ツカズハナレズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Careful Distance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsukazu Hanarezu</title>
<summary>Even as Kazuha is guilt-ridden and upset over Akira`s standing, Haruka determines that a date with Kazuha might make the whole situation better.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685599</identifier>
<identifier>yosuga-no-sora-in-solitude-where-we-are-least-alone</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="122255" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-10-11</airdate>
<rating votes="18">2.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アキラハズカシ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Akira Embarrassed</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akira Hazukashi</title>
<summary>Sora finally starts attending school with Haruka, though she is disappointed to find that she and Haruka are in different classes. Does Haruka misinterpret a conversation he was not meant to hear?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685597</identifier>
<identifier>yosuga-no-sora-in-solitude-where-we-are-least-alone</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="122889" update="2010-10-04">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="123958" update="2010-10-09">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124183" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-08</airdate>
<rating votes="12">3.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アキラメナイヨ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Give Up</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akiramenai yo</title>
<summary>Akira and Kazuha finally get some answers, as a DNA test prompts Kazuha`s mother to divulge her secret.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685605</identifier>
<identifier>yosuga-no-sora-in-solitude-where-we-are-least-alone</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="124184" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-01</airdate>
<rating votes="12">4.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヤミアキラカニ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Darkness Brightens</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yami Akiraka ni</title>
<summary>Has Haruka misunderstood the message he heard on the cellphone?  Has he jumped to the wrong conclusion?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685603</identifier>
<identifier>yosuga-no-sora-in-solitude-where-we-are-least-alone</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="125130" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-22</airdate>
<rating votes="10">3.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナオクラキソラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Still Dark Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nao Kuraki Sora</title>
<summary>Sora is consumed with hatred, even as Haruka seems to be oblivious to the depth of her feelings---and his own.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685609</identifier>
<identifier>yosuga-no-sora-in-solitude-where-we-are-least-alone</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="125131" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-15</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ツミナオトメラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sinful Maidens</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsumi na Otomera</title>
<summary>Nao is driven to explain her past actions.  Do they impact her current relationship?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685607</identifier>
<identifier>yosuga-no-sora-in-solitude-where-we-are-least-alone</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="125132" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-29</airdate>
<rating votes="10">3.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハルカナオモイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Distant Feelings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haruka na Omoi</title>
<summary>Sora becomes even more insecure when she learns the details of a drowning accident that almost took the life of her brother.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685611</identifier>
<identifier>yosuga-no-sora-in-solitude-where-we-are-least-alone</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="125193" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-12-06</airdate>
<rating votes="9">3.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トリノソラネハ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Imitating the Bird`s Cry</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tori no Sorane wa</title>
<summary>Nao is beginning to see her relationship with different eyes, giving her a clearer picture of the two siblings.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685613</identifier>
<identifier>yosuga-no-sora-in-solitude-where-we-are-least-alone</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="125972" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-12-13</airdate>
<rating votes="10">9.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ソラメクフタリ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Uncertain Pair</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soraneku Futari</title>
<summary>Sora is finally able to explain her actions and feelings to her brother, even as Nao is left to wonder where her relationship is heading.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685615</identifier>
<identifier>yosuga-no-sora-in-solitude-where-we-are-least-alone</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="126017" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-12-20</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハルカナソラヘ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the Distant Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haruka na Sora e</title>
<summary>The twins finally make peace with their relationship, as friends and lovers begin to understand the siblings.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>685617</identifier>
<identifier>yosuga-no-sora-in-solitude-where-we-are-least-alone</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="126587" update="2011-01-03">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-10-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Insert</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129083" update="2011-03-31">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending Full Version</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147758" update="2013-02-28">
<epno type="6">O7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview - Migiwa Kazuha Arc</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147759" update="2013-02-28">
<epno type="6">O6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview - Kasugano Sora Arc</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147760" update="2013-02-28">
<epno type="6">O5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview - Amatsume Akira Arc</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147761" update="2013-02-28">
<epno type="6">O4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview - Yorihime Nao Arc</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147762" update="2013-02-28">
<epno type="6">O3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview - Kasugano Sora Arc (Short)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147763" update="2013-02-28">
<epno type="6">O2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview - Amatsume Akira Arc (Short)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147764" update="2013-02-28">
<epno type="6">O1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview - Yorihime Nao Arc (Short)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
