<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7660" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1979-03-17</startdate>
<enddate>1979-03-17</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Alps no Shoujo Heidi (1979)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">アルプスの少女ハイジ 劇場版</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Alps no Shoujo Heidi Gekijouban</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">アルプスの少女ハイジ (1979)</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Heidi - O Filme</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7658" type="Alternative Setting">Alps no Shoujo Heidi: Alm no Yama Hen</anime>
<anime id="7659" type="Alternative Setting">Alps no Shoujo Heidi: Heidi to Clara Hen</anime>
<anime id="426" type="Full Story">Alps no Shoujo Heidi</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="4098" type="Character Design">Kotabe Youichi</name>
<name id="10118" type="Original Work">Johanna Spyri</name>
<name id="3637" type="Music">Watanabe Takeo</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the Heidi novels by http://anidb.net/cr10118 [Johanna Spyri].
Five years after the TV series, a theatrical version was screened in film theatres, which included a different voice cast for some characters.
Later, two OVAs, http://anidb.net/a7658 [Alps no Shoujo Heidi: Alm no Yama Hen] and http://anidb.net/a7659 [Alps no Shoujo Heidi: Heidi to Clara Hen] were released, which offered a differently cut longer summary of the http://anidb.net/a426 [TV series] and replaced the changed voice actors with the ones from the series.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="75">5.81</permanent>
<temporary count="75">6.27</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>54902.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15539</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9547</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2980</identifier>
<identifier>jtsukw</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Heidi,_Girl_of_the_Alps</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>アルプスの少女ハイジ_(アニメ)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>146639</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3081</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2811" parentid="2831" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Germany</name>
<description>Germany, officially the Federal Republic of Germany, is a federal parliamentary republic in central-western Europe. It includes 16 constituent states, and has a largely temperate seasonal climate. Germany is the most populous member state of the European Union. Germany`s capital and largest metropolis is Berlin, while its largest conurbation is the Ruhr, with its main centres of Dortmund and Essen.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214345.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4691" parentid="2831" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-08">
<name>Switzerland</name>
<description>Switzerland, officially the Swiss Confederation is a federal republic in Europe. While still named the "Swiss Confederation" for historical reasons, modern Switzerland is a federal directorial republic consisting of 26 cantons, with Bern as the seat of the federal authorities, called "federal city". The country is situated in Western-Central Europe, and is bordered by Italy to the south, France to the west, Germany to the north, and Austria and Liechtenstein to the east. Switzerland is a landlocked country geographically divided between the Alps, the Swiss Plateau and the Jura, spanning an area of 41,285 km². While the Alps occupy the greater part of the territory, the Swiss population of approximately eight million people is concentrated mostly on the plateau, where the largest cities are to be found: among them are the two global and economic centres Zürich and Geneva.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192470.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="14341" type="main character in" update="2015-01-01">
<rating votes="25">8.72</rating>
<name>Heidi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Heidi is an orphan child, happy and carefree, loving and interested in everything that happens around her. Whether its the ringing of church bells, the sounds of the trees, her grandfather`s homemade cheese or fresh cheese cake - Heidi appreciates the little things of everyday life. Because she is always helpful and caring, Heidi soon wins the hearts of all. And of course she would never exchange the beloved animals and mountains against the confines of city life.</description>
<picture>41901.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2890" picture="23182.jpg">Sugiyama Kazuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14342" type="main character in" update="2010-01-25">
<rating votes="7">10.00</rating>
<name>Ojiisan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The grumpy old grandfather of Heidi lives like a hermit in a small hut on his alm. He has little contact with the inhabitants of the village below and they in return think he is strange and avoid him. When Heidi`s aunt drops her off at his place he is far from happy about it. He soon learns to appreciate Heidi`s joyful, honest way which also makes him more helpful and friendly towards other people.</description>
<picture>41902.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3059" picture="203228.jpg">Miyauchi Kouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14343" type="main character in" update="2014-12-26">
<name>Peter</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Peter is Heidi`s best friend. He is a friendly character, energetic and always hungry but always reliable when he is needed.
He lives with his mother and grandmother, providing for their lives as a goatherder.
Peter does not like to go to school because he has difficulties at learning to read.</description>
<picture>41903.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7641" picture="32436.jpg">Maruyama Hiroko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14344" type="main character in" update="2015-01-01">
<rating votes="4">7.23</rating>
<name>Clara Sesemann</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Clara Sesemann, daughter of a wealthy merchant is bound to a wheelchair and lives (motherless) with her governess Miss Rottenmeier and a butler in a mansion in Frankfurt. Her father is constantly on the road and has little time for his daughter. So Clara is lonely and unhappy - until Heidi appears in her life. The two immediately become friends.</description>
<picture>166924.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="364" picture="202614.jpg">Han Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14345" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-01-01">
<name>Rottenmeier</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The strict governess is responsible for Mr. Sesemann`s household and for Clara`s wellbeing and education. When Heidi comes to Frankfurt, Miss Rottenmeier has tremendous difficulties in coping with the open and cheerful nature of the little girl. She believes Heidi is too wild and must be tamed.</description>
<picture>166931.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34" picture="240893.jpg">Kyouda Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14346" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-01-02">
<rating votes="5">9.68</rating>
<name>Sesemann</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mr. Sesemann is a wealthy merchant, widow and Clara`s father. He loves his daughter dearly but has very little time for her since his work requires him to travel extensively.</description>
<picture>166974.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2489" picture="22426.jpg">Suzuki Taimei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14348" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-12-26">
<name>Obaasan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Peter`s grandmother who has gone blind and spends a lot of time sitting at her spinning wheel, enjoys it when Heidi reads to her. She treats Heidi quite naturally as a family member. Heidi in return treats her as if she were her grandmother.</description>
<picture>166511.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24890">Nunami Terue</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="30017" picture="79273.jpg">Shima Miyako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72270" type="appears in" update="2014-12-26">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Dete</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Heidi`s aunt. She took care of Heidi after her parents died, but after being offered a good job in Frankfurt, she won`t have the time anymore. Thus she sends Heidi off to the Alps, to be with her grandfather.</description>
<picture>166493.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2247" picture="72125.jpg">Nakanishi Taeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72469" type="appears in" update="2015-01-01">
<name>Sebastian</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sebastian is part of the house staff in the Frankfurt Sesemann residence.</description>
<picture>166926.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3285" picture="193568.jpg">Kimotsuki Kaneta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72471" type="appears in" update="2015-01-01">
<name>Johann</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Johann is part of the Frankfurt Sesemann residence household.</description>
<picture>166925.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30838">Nemoto Yoshiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72483" type="appears in" update="2015-01-02">
<name>Clara no Obaa-sama</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Clara`s grandmother. A very kind and joyful woman that is also delighted by Heidi`s presence. She`s very down to earth and treats people with respect.</description>
<picture>166975.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1801" picture="146194.jpg">Asou Miyoko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="122146" update="2010-09-12">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>110</length>
<airdate>1979-03-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
