<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7664" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-07-16</startdate>
<enddate>2010-07-16</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Zettai Karen Children OVA: Aitazousei! Ubawareta Mirai?</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">絶対可憐チルドレン OVA 愛多憎生! 奪われた未来?</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Zettai Karen Children OVA: Changing Love! Take Back a Stolen Future?</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5674" type="Prequel">Zettai Karen Children</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.z-child.com/haishin/ova.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="1163" type="Animation Work">SynergySP</name>
<name id="2211" type="Character Design">Kagami Takahiro</name>
<name id="2841" type="Work">Shogakukan-Shueisha Productions</name>
<name id="1573" type="Music">Nakagawa Koutarou</name>
<name id="7262" type="Original Work">Shiina Takashi</name>
<name id="6090" type="Direction">Kawaguchi Keiichirou</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a shounen manga by http://anidb.net/cr7262 [Shiina Takashi], serialised in http://anidb.net/cr23232 [Shounen Sunday].
The children enter a junior high school. One day, they receive an emergency contact that B.A.B.E.L. (Base of Backing ESP Laboratory) is attacked.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="380">5.71</permanent>
<temporary count="381">6.86</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>51104.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11244</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7745</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4778</identifier>
<identifier>dpmtpm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.z-child.com/haishin/ova.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Zettai_Karen_Children</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>絶対可憐チルドレン</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>337539</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12878</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2649</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1864" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-14">
<name>extrasensory perception</name>
<description>Extrasensory perception (ESP), involves reception of information not gained through the recognized physical senses but sensed with the mind. The term was coined by Sir Richard Burton, and adopted by Duke University psychologist J. B. Rhine to denote psychic abilities such as telepathy and clairvoyance, and their trans-temporal operation as precognition or retrocognition. ESP is also sometimes casually referred to as a sixth sense, gut instinct or hunch, which are historical English idioms. The term implies acquisition of information by means external to the basic limiting assumptions of science, such as that organisms can only receive information from the past to the present.
In Japanese usage the term is often misappropriated to refer to any supernatural, non-magical, super power. Users of such powers are called `esper` in Japanese. The term `esper` is not normally in use outside of Japan but is slowly being introduced due to its usage in anime and manga.
In anime/manga the following powers, among others, are described as ESP:
- telepathy
- precognition
- clairvoyance
- retrocognition
- remote viewing
- aura reading
- out-of-body experiences (OBE)
- psychokinesis</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2481" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-08">
<name>teleportation</name>
<description>Teleportation is the transfer of matter from one point to another, possibly a distant one, without application of force, and generally instantly. This contradicts scientific law as we know it, and is therefore nowadays impossible. Sometimes it appears as a paranormal or supernatural ability, and sometimes it is shown in science fiction through technological devices backed up by scientific laws yet to be discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="4730" type="main character in" update="2013-03-25">
<rating votes="45">7.05</rating>
<name>Akashi Kaoru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A ten-year-old Level 7 psychokinetic (the maximum esper potency designation), Kaoru is the reckless and zealous member of "The Children" Special Esper Team alongside Shiho and Aoi that often goes overkill with her psychic powers.</description>
<picture>20851.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4" picture="177060.jpg">Hirano Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4731" type="main character in" update="2013-03-25">
<rating votes="26">6.46</rating>
<name>Nogami Aoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A ten-year-old esper with Level 7 teleportation capability, Aoi is the rational member of "The Children" Special Esper Team alongside Kaoru and Shiho that likes playing video games in her spare time. Like her teammates, Aoi is introduced at series inception as behaving in a somewhat cavalier manner that annoys her adult superiors.</description>
<picture>20852.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="208" picture="20458.jpg">Shiraishi Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4732" type="main character in" update="2013-03-25">
<rating votes="31">6.55</rating>
<name>Sannomiya Shiho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A ten-year-old esper with Level 7 psychometry, Shiho is the sarcastic, sharp-tongued and often childishly sadistic member of "The Children" Special Esper Team alongside Kaoru and Aoi. While initially not able to do much during missions aside from gathering information that is not immediately obvious from the environment, Shiho still supports her teammates by doing whatever she can.</description>
<picture>20853.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4733" type="main character in" update="2012-08-11">
<rating votes="37">4.45</rating>
<name>Minamoto Kouichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The first lieutenant workaholic field leader of "The Children" Special Esper Team, he is tasked with overseeing their day-to-day care and making sure they do not get too carried away when they are doing their jobs. Even as they mistreat him and generally give him super fits, the girls highly esteem Minamoto enough to ask the B.A.B.E.L. chief to be allowed to reside with him after he leads them in their introductory mission and protects Kaoru from her own out-of-control telekinesis. While he is quite courageous and sincere in his belief that Kaoru/Shiho/Aoi are little girls to be protected and cherished before they are Level 7 espers (which Shiho says are treated the same as mass-destruction weapons) and has grown to be very fond of them enough to spend time with them on diurnal outings, Minamoto has a hard time applying those life-equality ideals to Momotarou (who wrecks his apartment when Kaoru decides to nurse him back to health) and refraining from behaving toward his esper charges as if they are a bunch of brats (an accurate but counterproductive assessment). Minamoto generates quite a convoy of female admirers during the course of the Zettai Karen Children series as he works to pre-empt the precognition of a mortal showdown with Kaoru in a war-torn city during Kyousuke`s esper-led war against humans a decade in the future.</description>
<picture>20854.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4734" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-10">
<rating votes="27">6.37</rating>
<name>Kashiwagi Oboro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Even if her job title is simply being Taizou`s secretary or personal assistant, Kashiwagi is no exception to the sidekick/alter ego dynamic and is generally very handy to have around. Kashiwagi performs many roles as she accompanies Taizou which include assisting with visual aids during mission briefings and preventing Taizou from giving an order or making a decision whose aftermath would most likely be rather messy.</description>
<picture>20855.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4735" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-03-10">
<rating votes="11">3.50</rating>
<name>Kiritsubo Taizou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The leader of B.A.B.E.L. He dotes on "The Children" all the time and spoils them rotten not realising that this overindulgence is probably the reason for the bad behaviour of "The Children". Taizou can and does point to Minamoto as the scapegoat for The Children`s fallibilities and poor attitudes. Whether Taizou overindulges "The Children" because he really loves them or because he is frightened for his job/personal safety remains to be seen; still, Taizou is extremely attached to Kaoru, Shiho, and Aoi (who are starting to realize that Taizou`s intense affection for them is not entirely altruistic) and goes into a frenzy comparable to a Level 6 esper whenever he feels that "The Children" are in distress.</description>
<picture>20856.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4737" type="appears in" update="2009-03-10">
<rating votes="14">6.50</rating>
<name>Tokiwa Natsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Natsuko wields her Level 5 clairvoyance as one member of the Doubleface esper receptionist team alongside her partner Hotaru and is charged with identifying and intercepting possible incoming threats. Not only can she detect dangerous items such as packaged explosives or concealed personal weaponry, but Natsuko also can even tell if a visitor is in good hygienic repair. It would not be out of the question for Natsuko to use her clairvoyance to spy on a visitor during his time on the B.A.B.E.L. premises to ensure good behaviour.</description>
<picture>20858.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="218" picture="17036.jpg">Nakao Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4738" type="appears in" update="2009-03-10">
<rating votes="14">6.58</rating>
<name>Nowaki Hotaru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hotaru avails her Level 5 telepathy as the other member of The Doubleface esper receptionist team alongside her partner Natsuko. Hotaru is charged with reading the visitor`s thoughts to determine whether or not they pose a threat to either the espers or B.A.B.E.L`s other personnel. The infatuation that she and Natsuko share for Minamoto has ignited a low-level rivalry between the two even as they are often kept in the loop with all the drama involving Minamoto and his esper charges.</description>
<picture>20859.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4740" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-11">
<rating votes="32">3.57</rating>
<name>Sakaki Shuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dr. Sakaki Shuuji is the old-enough-to-know-better playboy psychometric physician of B.A.B.E.L. whose job it is to inspect espers at the conclusion of every mission as well as to take care of general medical needs. Before meeting Minamoto (who is originally a medical researcher before enrolling in an overseas supervisor course), Sakaki did not have anybody to understand him as a person and advocate for him. To compensate for this, he behaved like the typical sports jock - popular in school but dangerous if obstructed. Given how he had beaten up several people and how injured they were, it is not that unreasonable to speculate that Sakaki is very well-practised in the martial arts and that it was probably in that forum that he discovered his psychometry and taught himself how to use it to his advantage. Fortunately, Sakaki saw fit to clean up his act after his Level 6 psychometry imports an admonishment to grow up from Minamoto even as he behaves as quite a lady`s man.</description>
<picture>20861.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="181" picture="171560.jpg">Taniyama Kishou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4741" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-11">
<rating votes="72">7.75</rating>
<name>Hyoubu Kyousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A misanthropic former major-rank military esper with eight decades of life under his belt, Kyousuke is one tough adversary with an abundant anthology of different esper capabilities. As is the case with Kaoru`s berserk runaway telekinesis, Kyousuke has the capability to defy fully powered-up ESP Counter Measure generators but does so as "the rule". Kyousuke has a lengthy history of teleporting out of his subterranean holding cell, walking around for a breath of fresh air, and teleporting back in without anybody detecting and challenging him. Given that there are few efficacious avenues for damaging him (never mind the subjugation and confinement), Kyousuke believes that he do whatever he wishes and it would not be that outrageous to suspect that Kyousuke is either one of the alpha adversaries or the alpha adversary. He delights in giving B.A.B.E.L. fits as he foils their attempts to apprehend him and using his hypnosis to especially manipulate Minamoto for his own amusement (such as creating the illusion that Kaoru, Shiho, and Aoi are physically older than in reality). Kyousuke`s misanthropy also extends to other espers if they defy him (although he will offer them a chance to serve him first). He views Kaoru as his queen and soul mate due to her ability to defy the fully powered-up ESP Counter Measure generator and wishes for her to grow up quickly not caring anything that Kaoru is much more like a child than she initially appears as Minamoto is forced to endure on a daily basis. He and Momotarou have a social dynamic where they always see the worst of normal people and behave as if the word of an esper always takes precedence over the word of a normal person—with which they both have had several dysphoric experiences.</description>
<picture>20862.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15856" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-26">
<rating votes="13">6.85</rating>
<name>Tsukushi Mio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>In addition to the normal position displacement (disappearing in one position followed by reappearing in another) much like Aoi, the young teleporter Mio can also generate distance-displacement portals that can even ignore physical obstacles as Dr. Sakaki has been forced to endure while in the middle of a fight with her bodyguard Yamada. Mio is unwilling to accept Kaoru as any kind of ruler that could replace her crush Kyousuke and demonstrates this by kidnapping Minamoto to her very run-down hideout. Minamoto guiding her through proper nutrition/hygiene and even giving her a new outfit inspires Mio but does not stop her vendetta against Kaoru. Mio`s downfall is brought about when Minamoto reasons that Mio probably has the same weakness as Akira`s metempsychosis. Sure enough, Minamoto transporting Mio`s genuine lower half out of range causes Mio to recall her clones, one of which has gone maverick. Kaoru`s intercession along with Minamoto`s compassion for her inspires Mio to reflect on her conduct even if her jealousy is not yet resolved.</description>
<picture>44727.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16073" type="appears in" update="2010-03-25">
<rating votes="2">3.04</rating>
<name>Bullet Silver</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An esper who specializes in controlling bullets using telekinesis. He can penetrate most espers` defenses in this way. He is a member of the esper criminal organization Black Phantom, perhaps against his will.</description>
<picture>45176.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="616" picture="18138.jpg">Kondou Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16194" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-29">
<rating votes="13">2.79</rating>
<name>Patty Crew</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An unwilling member of Black Phantom. She can transform her entire body into black smoke and recreate herself at any location the black smoke occupies. Physical attacks have no effect on her.</description>
<picture>45347.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19947" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-23">
<rating votes="4">2.20</rating>
<name>Hino Kagari</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A boy who is part of P.A.N.D.R.A. Kagari is a multipower esper, having abilities such as precog, psychokinesis, and pyrokinesis. He seems to be paired up on missions with Kazura often, considering her reactions towards her. In recent chapters, Kagari transferred into The Children`s class with other P.A.N.D.R.A. members as new students.</description>
<picture>45349.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="470" picture="17419.jpg">Irino Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19948" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-23">
<rating votes="4">4.43</rating>
<name>Tamaki Kazura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl under P.A.N.D.R.A. who has a synthesized power, using tentacles and psychometry. She seems to be paired up on missions with Kagari often, considering her reactions towards him. In recent chapters, Kazura transferred into The Children`s class with other P.A.N.D.R.A. members as new students.</description>
<picture>45348.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19949" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-23">
<rating votes="11">4.50</rating>
<name>Kumoi Yuuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Phantom Daughter, aka Kumoi Yuuri, is the daughter of the head of BLACK PHANTOM. She dresses in a gothic lolita fashion has long hair, and is of the same age as "The Children". She is an esper, her power being to put people in a different mindset, for example, Minamoto becoming a child in mind only, while Hyoubu from P.A.N.D.R.A. placed an illusion on him, making him seem like a child in every other way. She seems extremely loyal to her father, although when she meets Kaoru and reads her mind, she finds out that she is the Queen of Catastrophe, and seems extremely glad to have met her. She might think of her as a savior of some sort. At the end of the anime, Yuuri seems to have been liberated from BLACK PHANTOM, and is in fact joining the same middle school as Kaoru, Aoi and Shiho. Although it is known that she is the daughter of Black Phantom, not much is known about her, although later, Yuuri is revealed to have multiple personalities.</description>
<picture>45175.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="120192" update="2010-07-23">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120251" update="2010-07-23">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-07-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
