<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7666" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-12-04</startdate>
<enddate>2010-12-04</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gekijouban Bleach: Jigoku-hen</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Bleach: Hell Chapter</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Bleach: Cehennem Bölümü</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Белина: Адът</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Bleach Movie 4</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">劇場版 BLEACH 地獄篇</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Bleach the Movie 4: Hell Verse</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2369" type="Parent Story">Bleach</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/bleach/</url>
<creators>
<name id="979" type="Original Work">Kubo Taito</name>
<name id="5806" type="Character Design">Kudou Masashi</name>
<name id="4566" type="Direction">Abe Noriyuki</name>
<name id="5806" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kudou Masashi</name>
<name id="1955" type="Music">Sagisu Shirou</name>
<name id="724" type="Animation Work">Studio Pierrot</name>
</creators>
<description>"Hell" is the place where a person is sent to who committed violent crimes when they were alive. Shinigami are forbidden to go there. One day prisoners revolt and make their escape to Karakura - the real world - where http://anidb.net/ch2069 [Ichigo] and his friends live in. Ichigo and his friends are defeated one after the other by prisoners with overwhelming power. A mysterious man appears who comes to their rescue. With http://anidb.net/ch36163 [Kokutou] leading the way Ichigo, http://anidb.net/ch3720 [Rukia], http://anidb.net/ch3723 [Uryuu], and http://anidb.net/ch8722 [Renji] marches into Hell to save the world.
Note: Episode 299 of http://anidb.net/a2369 [Bleach] serves as a prologue to this movie.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1668">5.29</permanent>
<temporary count="1689">6.93</temporary>
<review count="1">4.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>226374.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11723</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8247</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/bleach/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Bleach:_Hell_Chapter</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>劇場版BLEACH_地獄篇</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>337057</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13050</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B00AHSM8YG</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2632" parentid="6563" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>hell</name>
<description>"Abandon hope all ye who enter here"
You been a sinner? Welcome to Hell, where you will suffer for all eternity for your sins. The devils with pitchforks will take good care of you there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3575" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-13">
<name>damsel in distress</name>
<description>The damsel in distress is usually a young, nubile woman placed in a dire predicament by a villain or a monster and requires a hero to dash to her rescue. Often used to unite the cast of a show for this one goal, to make them put differences aside and become a band of nakama. 
Examples: Sakoshita Yanagi from Rekka no Honoo, Yuuki Miaka from Fushigi Yuugi or Higurashi Kagome from Inuyasha.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3993" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-28">
<name>kidnapping</name>
<description>In criminal law, kidnapping is the taking away or transportation of a person against that person`s will, usually to hold the person in false imprisonment, a confinement without legal authority. This may be done for ransom or in furtherance of another crime, or in connection with a child custody dispute.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10583.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4566" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-08">
<name>transforming weapons</name>
<description>This anime features transforming weapons, this can either be cars or household appliances that transform into weapons, such as transformers or weapons that themselves transform into bigger badder shapes to deal more and more damage.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6563" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-23">
<name>spirit realm</name>
<description>A spirit realm is a place where inhabited by the spirits of the dead, deities, demons, and other such entities. Examples would be Heaven and Hell in Christianity, the Elysium in Greek mythology, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2069" type="main character in" update="2013-05-11">
<rating votes="1320">6.46</rating>
<name>Kurosaki Ichigo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kurosaki Ichigo was raised by his father together with his two sisters after the traumatic experience of losing his mother. One day, minding his own business, he meets Rukia, the Shinigami, who needs his help. While protecting his family they find out about his supernatural abilities and thus a still-living - substitute - Shinigami is born....</description>
<picture>136529.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="138" picture="23200.jpg">Morita Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3720" type="main character in" update="2009-02-23">
<rating votes="577">6.24</rating>
<name>Kuchiki Rukia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A sarcastic Soul Reaper who is assigned hollow extermination duties in Ichigo`s hometown. Though her physical appearance is that of a teenage girl, in reality she is around 150 years old. At the opening of the story, Rukia is forced to transfer her powers to Ichigo and assume a temporary lifestyle as a regular human. She registers at the local high school and takes up residence in Ichigo`s closet, while teaching him how to be a substitute Soul Reaper in her place.</description>
<picture>19580.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3721" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-15">
<rating votes="312">5.10</rating>
<name>Inoue Orihime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A long-time classmate of Ichigo, linked to him by mutual friend Tatsuki Arisawa. She is effectively an orphan, as when she was 3, her older brother Sora left their abusive parents` home with Orihime and raised her on his own, later on, when Orihime was in middle school he died in a car accident. Though initially devoid of spiritual powers, she develops spiritual awareness early in the plot and later obtains one of the strongest powers in the Bleach universe.
Which is practically a power of the gods: being able to literally reject happened things and making them undone.</description>
<picture>19581.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="392" picture="17237.jpg">Matsuoka Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3722" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-23">
<rating votes="121">4.66</rating>
<name>Sado Yasutora</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Better known as Chad, is one of Ichigo`s friends at school. He is a biracial Japanese/Mexican student who towers over his classmates. Despite his imposing appearance he is quite meek, and refuses to fight unless it is for the sake of another. Chad does not have awareness of ghosts at first, but this changes when he witnesses a group of children being attacked by a hollow. He discovers a unique ability that strengthens and armours his right arm, enabling him to fight hollows.</description>
<picture>19582.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3723" type="main character in" update="2009-02-23">
<rating votes="135">5.02</rating>
<name>Ishida Uryuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Quincy, descendant of a line of priest-like hollow-hunting archers who were historical enemies of the Soul Reapers. He bears a deep grudge against all Soul Reapers, including Ichigo, and is an early antagonist in the series.</description>
<picture>19583.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="221" picture="17039.jpg">Sugiyama Noriaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3724" type="appears in" update="2010-04-07">
<rating votes="56">6.17</rating>
<name>Arisawa Tatsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A classmate of Ichigo Kurosaki and the best friend of Orihime Inoue. She has known both since she was young, sparring with Ichigo in their karate classes and defending Orihime whenever people picked on or bothered her. Tatsuki is very tomboyish, displaying few feminine traits and even ranking as the second strongest student in her age group in all of Japan.</description>
<picture>19584.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="140" picture="170306.jpg">Noda Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3725" type="appears in" update="2009-02-23">
<rating votes="86">6.75</rating>
<name>Kurosaki Isshin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The father of the Kurosaki family. He is initially portrayed as a silly, fight-loving father who takes a keen interest in what his children are doing. He shows them affection either offensively or with an all-too-happy tone, which elicits comical reactions from his kids, usually in the form of a kick.</description>
<picture>19585.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3749" type="appears in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="125">7.87</rating>
<name>Ulquiorra Schiffer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Cuarta Espada, signified by the "4" tattooed to his chest. His name stems from that of a furniture designer named Patricia Urquiola. He has a largely stoic appearance, rarely even changing his facial expression, and does not allow the actions of others to impede the tasks set to him by http://anidb.net/ch3746 [Aizen Sousuke]. He will attack his comrades to get them to pay attention to him, and deems anyone he does not find of particular interest to be "trash" and therefore expendable.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>55022.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7629" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="461">7.66</rating>
<name>Kuchiki Byakuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kuchiki Byakuya is the 28th head of the noble Kuchiki clan, one of the four great noble families in Soul Society. As such, Byakuya acts in an aristocratic manner — he seems always serene and apathetic towards other people, even when he is actually deeply conflicted. He is also extremely calm, even in battle, and is very seldom surprised by even the most drastic of actions. Ironically, when he was younger, he was quick to anger and very hotheaded, as noted by his grandfather, http://anidb.net/ch9327 [Kuchiki Ginrei]; similar to the the way http://anidb.net/ch2069 [Ichigo] and http://anidb.net/ch8722 [Renji] are now.
Byakuya strongly believes in law and order. As the head of one of the great noble families and as a captain in the http://anidb.net/ch9291 [Gotei 13], he always works hard for a peaceful society. He thinks that if someone in his position doesn`t follow the rules as a good example, then no one will follow them. He believes that to maintain the order, all law-breakers must be punished, even if that goes against his own wishes. Despite his icy and regal manner, Byakuya cares for and protects those important to him, even referring to http://anidb.net/ch3720 [Rukia] as his "pride".
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picture>54978.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8354" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="413">7.52</rating>
<name>Hitsugaya Toushirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hitsugaya Toushirou is the captain of the 10th division. He is also the youngest captain. His zanpakutou is called Hyourinmaru, an ice dragon. His bankai is called Daiguren Hyourinmaru.</description>
<picture>54897.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8722" type="main character in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="251">5.05</rating>
<name>Abarai Renji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Abarai Renji is the rough and ready vice captain of the sixth squad. He is already strong, but aims to improve even further in order to surpass his captain, http://anidb.net/ch7629 [Kuchiki Byakuya]. He is particularly weak at using kidou in battle, but he makes up for it in pure determination. He is a bit dense at times but he has a good heart and wants to protect his friends, especially http://anidb.net/ch3720 [Rukia], who is his childhood friend. His zanpakutou is http://anidb.net/ch10815 [Zabimaru], a wild animal-type katana.
Source: Anime-Planet</description>
<picture>54893.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="493" picture="65381.jpg">Itou Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9307" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="147">7.57</rating>
<name>Yamamoto-Genryuusai Shigekuni</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yamamoto-Genryuusai Shigekuni is the captain commander of the thirteen protection squadrons and leader of the first company. Though he may appear to be little more than a frail elderly man, Yamamoto is the most powerful shinigami in Soul Society. He commands the utmost respect from his subordinates and manages to remain calm throughout any emergencies, taking control of each situation with ease. His zanpakutou is the fiery Ryuujin Jakka.
Source: Anime-Planet</description>
<picture>54994.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="385" picture="215702.jpg">Tsukada Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9342" type="appears in" update="2015-05-27">
<rating votes="280">6.73</rating>
<name>Matsumoto Rangiku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Matsumoto Rangiku is the busty vice-captain of Soul Society`s tenth protection squad. She is quite energetic and likes to have fun, especially if it involves a bottle of sake. Despite having a completely contrasting personality to her captain, http://anidb.net/ch8354 [Hitsugaya], Matsumoto bounces off well against her superior. When in battle, she fights with her zanpakutou, http://anidb.net/ch10805 [Haineko], which has the ability to turn into ash, surrounding the enemy to attack them.
Source: Anime-Planet</description>
<picture>79577.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4956" picture="28490.jpg">Matsutani Kaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9351" type="appears in" update="2009-06-18">
<rating votes="125">6.81</rating>
<name>Ukitake Juushirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28876.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="258" picture="17080.jpg">Ishikawa Hideo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9394" type="appears in" update="2011-07-13">
<rating votes="73">4.95</rating>
<name>Kurosaki Yuzu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ichigo`s little sister.
She`s kind hearted and likes to cook. After the mother`s death, she probably sees herself as some kind of replacement - at least in the kitchen.</description>
<picture>28923.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5080" picture="2292.gif">Sena Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9395" type="appears in" update="2009-06-18">
<rating votes="77">6.27</rating>
<name>Kurosaki Karin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28924.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9400" type="appears in" update="2009-06-18">
<rating votes="8">3.98</rating>
<name>Kojima Mizuiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28931.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9401" type="appears in" update="2009-06-18">
<rating votes="10">6.56</rating>
<name>Asano Keigo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28933.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25469" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-12-02">
<rating votes="5">2.18</rating>
<name>Shuren</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shuren is a resident of Hell. He leads a group of three other Togabito. He is the antagonist of the fourth Bleach movie.</description>
<picture>60180.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="454" picture="17354.jpg">Furuya Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36117" type="appears in" update="2011-08-30">
<rating votes="5">4.88</rating>
<name>Kurosaki Ichigo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50579.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="138" picture="23200.jpg">Morita Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36163" type="main character in" update="2013-05-11">
<rating votes="2">2.68</rating>
<name>Kokutou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52496.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="259" picture="17082.jpg">Nakai Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="119896" update="2010-12-06">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>95</length>
<airdate>2010-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122869" update="2010-10-03">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
