<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7680" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-10-06</startdate>
<enddate>2010-12-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Motto To Love-Ru: Trouble</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">mtlr</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">もっとTo LOVEる -とらぶる-</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Motto To Loveru</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">좀 더 To LOVE루 -트러블-</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">更多 出包王女</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9133" type="Sequel">To Love-Ru: Trouble - Darkness</anime>
<anime id="6463" type="Prequel">To Love-Ru: Trouble (2009)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="96608">Good show. Maybe even best in genre. Chars are nice, plot dont disturb your brain with suddenly epic problems. And it make me remember old-school harems.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="421413">Cute and lovely with full load of high-lvl ecchi .D Even comedy was still quite good. There is no more to it and no more is needed for this series. I have to admit that in the end I liked it even more than the first season. Every episode is split into 3 mini-episodes, so there is no major storyline, but those short stories are of high quality. 

BTW there is no meaning in watching censored version. You will have white screen almost all the way .D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="92243">awesome ecchi show.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.j-toloveru.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="719" type="Animation Work">Xebec</name>
<name id="123" type="Series Composition">Yamada Yasunori</name>
<name id="2985" type="Original Work">Yabuki Kentarou</name>
<name id="9782" type="Direction">Ootsuki Atsushi</name>
<name id="2971" type="Music">Watanabe Takeshi</name>
<name id="9087" type="Character Design">Oka Yuuichi</name>
<name id="9086" type="Original Work">Hasemi Saki</name>
<name id="9087" type="Chief Animation Direction">Oka Yuuichi</name>
<name id="3544" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takami Akio</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a shounen manga written by http://anidb.net/cr9086 [Hasemi Saki] and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr2985 [Yabuki Kentarou], serialised in http://anidb.net/ch5372 [Weekly Shounen Jump].
A year after http://anidb.net/ch2355 [Lala] came to Earth, she is all the more determined to make http://anidb.net/ch2354 [Rito] fall for her, putting all her effort into it, even though she knows that Rito actually loves http://anidb.net/ch2358 [Haruna]. Poor Rito will have to face tough times since Lala`s younger twin sisters, http://anidb.net/ch13068 [Nana] and http://anidb.net/ch13069 [Momo], now live in the same house, along with Rito`s reliable sister, http://anidb.net/ch2371 [Mikan], and http://anidb.net/ch16805 [Celine].
Fun and trouble await with their friends from school, with Lala`s usually catastrophic inventions, and http://anidb.net/ch2357 [Yami]`s contract to kill Rito...</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2471">5.85</permanent>
<temporary count="2495">7.16</temporary>
<review count="1">5.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>51629.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11725</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9181</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4798</identifier>
<identifier>ktvmsi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.j-toloveru.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>To_Love-Ru</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>To_LOVEる_-とらぶる-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2033</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>337849</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12957</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>motto-to-love-ru</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1179" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-21">
<name>indecisive</name>
<description>This character has trouble taking their own decisions, and may rely on others to do that instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1773" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-12">
<name>tentacle</name>
<description>A tentacle or bothrium (plural: bothria) is one of usually two or more elongated flexible organs present in animals, especially invertebrates. Usually, Tentacles are used for feeding, feeling and grasping.</description>
<picurl>236087.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2259" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-30">
<name>naked apron</name>
<description>A character wearing nothing but an apron appears in the show.</description>
<picurl>162045.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2396" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-08">
<name>swimsuit</name>
<description>A swimsuit is one of several kinds of garments designed to be worn by people engaging in water-based activities or sports or during certain activities under sunlight. Most kinds of swimsuit reveal a large portion of the body surface area, but exceptions exist. The more revealing kinds may also be worn as undergarment in sports that require wetsuits, or when there is a need to display the body, as in the case of beauty pageants or bodybuilding contests.
There is a very wide range of styles of modern swimsuits, which vary in relation to body coverage and materials. The choice of style of swimsuit is dependent on current fashions, community standards of modesty, and plain personal preference. Swimsuits for men usually expose the chest, while those for women do not usually do so; however, many women prefer to engage in water or sun activities with their torso uncovered, in a practice commonly described as toplessness or topfreedom. Since the early twentieth century a naturist movement has developed in western countries that seeks a return to non-sexual nakedness when swimming and during other appropriate activities; in some places around the world, nude beaches have been set aside for people who choose to engage in normal beach activities in the nude, and such beaches may or may not enforce nudity onto their goers.
In anime, it is common for at least one episode to feature the characters in swimsuits, usually as an excuse for gratuitous fanservice; when that happens, the episode is usually labeled a pool or beach episode, after the place the characters went to. Swimsuits, and in particular one-piece swimsuits, are a very common fetish in Japan; while the reason for that is uncertain, a common folk explanation is the fact that boys throughout their entire adolescence are commonly exposed to their female classmates wearing them, in what might be called an experiment in sexual discovery waiting to happen.</description>
<picurl>149786.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2438" parentid="2794" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-16">
<name>idol</name>
<description>In Japanese culture, idols (アイドル) are media personalities in their teens and early twenties who are considered particularly cute and cuddly and who will, for a period ranging from several months to a few years, regularly appear in the mass media, e.g. as singers for J-pop groups, bit-part actors, TV personalities, models in photo spreads published in magazines, advertisements, etc.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>63097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2788" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-21">
<name>confession</name>
<description>Someone confesses his/her love to someone else.</description>
<picurl>160903.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2819" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-31">
<name>pussy in your face</name>
<description>Either by accident or intentionally, a character`s face ends up in the sweet spot between a girl`s legs.</description>
<picurl>160842.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2822" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>skirt flipping</name>
<description>Naughty characters — usually boys — flip the skirts of female protagonists to ascertain what panties they are wearing (also see Pantsu category).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2824" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>pseudo tentacle rape scene</name>
<description>If this was porn she (or rather the audience) would have even more fun!</description>
<picurl>160554.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2830" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>furo scene</name>
<description>Furo (polite: Ofuro) is Japanese for bath, specifically a type of bath which originated as a short, steep-sided wooden bathtub. Baths of this type are found all over Japan in houses, apartments and traditional Japanese inns (Ryokans).
Furo are part of the Japanese ritual of bathing, not used for washing but for relaxing and warming oneself. Washing is carried out separately outside the furo, and only when completely clean does the bather enter the water. Generally Japanese bathrooms are small, so the bathroom is set up much like a walk-in shower area but containing the ofuro.
The cheapest and shortest way to show naked skin on TV, at least as much as allowed. It usually only takes up few minutes at most and as such it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales while still maintaining a "non-filler" episode.
Compare to the big brothers http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode] and http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160785.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2873" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>Valentine`s Day</name>
<description>Valentine`s Day is a festive day celebrated every February 14.
In Japan, South Korea, Taiwan, and China, Valentine`s Day is one month before http://anidb.net/t3147 [White Day], a celebration unique to those countries.
In the rest of the world:
On Valentine`s Day, both males and females will express their feelings of affection towards their loved ones, by exchanging gifts (such as cards, candies, and chocolates), going on dates, and other signs and actions of affection. Some people also take the opportunity to confess and propose for marriage. In Western countries, it is generally expected of the male to offer gifts to the significant other.
In many countries, friends and co-workers also exchange small gifts to show their friendship towards each other.
In Japan, South Korea, Taiwan, and China:
On Valentine`s Day, many women feel obliged to give chocolates to all male co-workers, except when the day falls on a Sunday, a holiday. This is known as giri choco (義理チョコ, "obligation chocolate"), with unpopular co-workers receiving only chougiri choco (超義理チョコ, "ultra-obligatory chocolate") cheap chocolate.
This contrasts with honmei choco (本命チョコ, "love chocolate"), chocolate given to a loved one.
Friends, especially girls, may exchange chocolate referred to as tomo choco (友チョコ, "friend chocolate").
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>160891.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2880" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-01">
<name>Christmas</name>
<description>Christmas, also referred to as Christmas Day, is an annual holiday celebrated on December 25 that commemorates the birth of Jesus of Nazareth. The day marks the beginning of the larger season of Christmastide, which lasts twelve days. The nativity of Jesus, which is the basis for the Anno Domini system of dating, is thought to have occurred between 7 and 2 BC. December 25 is not known to be Jesus` actual date of birth, and the date may have been chosen to correspond with either a Roman festival or the winter solstice.
On the Julian calendar, followed by most Orthodox churches, Christmas Day also falls on O.S. December 25th; this corresponds to N.S. January 7th on the Gregorian calendar, followed by Western churches.
Modern customs of the holiday include gift-giving, Church celebrations, and the display of various decorations—including the Christmas tree, lights, mistletoe, nativity scenes, and holly. Santa Claus (also referred to as Father Christmas, although the two figures have different origins) is a popular mythological figure often associated with bringing gifts at Christmas for children. Santa is generally believed to be the result of a syncretization between Saint Nicholas and elements from pagan Nordic and Christian mythology, and his modern appearance is believed to have originated in 19th century media.
Christmas is celebrated throughout the Christian population, but is also celebrated by many non-Christians as a secular, cultural festival. Because gift-giving and several other aspects of the holiday involve heightened economic activity among both Christians and non-Christians, Christmas has become a major event for many retailers.</description>
<picurl>160837.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3108" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-20">
<name>catastrophic gadgets</name>
<description>Comedy element: One of the characters in the anime tends to "invent", "create", or "call into existence" all sorts of wacky gadgets. The intent is to help the other protagonists in some way. Only that this fails every single time, ending in a catastrophe.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3679" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-26">
<name>engaged to an alien</name>
<description>The human protagonist in this show is engaged to an alien for some strange reason. Comedy element used to create many strange situations and misunderstandings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3738" parentid="2202" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-05">
<name>aliens living on earth</name>
<description>There`s an alien or a hive of aliens blending into society near you!</description>
<picurl>70750.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3908" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-02">
<name>lap pillow</name>
<description>As a sign of closeness the usually male character is encouraged to rest his weary head on the female’s lap.</description>
<picurl>167007.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4113" parentid="6347" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-20">
<name>body exchange</name>
<description>Two or more characters swap bodies (or, equally, swap minds).
When this plot is done, usually the voices also switch as narrative cheat to help viewers keep track of who`s who. More subtly, it`s just the eyes. More serious/action-oriented shows might not do this. The Flip often involves characters of different ages, genders, races, or social classes. Another variation is a protagonist and antagonist switching, which usually involves each trying to undermine the other`s organization while simultaneously trying to switch back. If one or both of the characters have superpowers or other special abilities, they`ll have a lot of trouble figuring their new powers out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4290" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>bath house visit</name>
<description>A sentou is a type of Japanese communal bath house where customers pay for entrance. Some Japanese find social importance in going to public baths, out of the theory that physical intimacy brings emotional intimacy, which is termed skinship in Japanese. Traditionally it is gender-segregated — men usually bathe only with men, and women with women. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales.
See also http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode], http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160783.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5863" parentid="2798" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-06">
<name>Weekly Shounen Jump</name>
<description>The Weekly Shounen Jump is a Japanese manga magazine released on a weekly basis. Its main target audience consists of young males and it features several manga titles. The magazine was created by http://anidb.net/cr780 [Shueisha] in July, 1968, and was originally only called Shounen Jump, because it was not published every week at the time. A number of very famous shounen manga were or are published in it, such as http://anidb.net/a386 [Hokuto no Ken], http://anidb.net/a231 [Dragon Ball], http://anidb.net/a942 [City Hunter], http://anidb.net/a826 [Saint Seiya], http://anidb.net/a590 [Slam Dunk], http://anidb.net/a312 [Yuu Yuu Hakushou], http://anidb.net/a69 [One Piece], http://anidb.net/a239 [Naruto], http://anidb.net/a2369 [Bleach], http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], http://anidb.net/a3468 [Gintama], to name a few of the most well-known.</description>
<picurl>66685.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5943" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-14">
<name>misunderstanding</name>
<description>Suggests that a large portion of storyline revolves around a rather large misunderstanding between two or more characters, usually forming long lasting situations of separation or hostility between all those involved.
A large portion of the story may be dedicated to gradually working all parties into a mutual understanding to true intentions or changes of heart.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6021" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>gender bender</name>
<description>Term used to refer to a person who takes on the role of their opposite gender. This often only reaches to the extent of cross-dressing (involving physical appearance and clothing only), but in rarer cases, involves a total gender swap (which seems to be more common in anime) - where the willing or unwilling victim receives a body opposite of their original gender (either permanently or temporarily), with all natural parts per their new body fully (or just all-out amply) included.
Example of cross-dressing gender bender: "Maria+Holic"
Examples of body-swap gender bender: "Kashimashi: Girl meets Girl", "Birdy the Mighty Decode"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6046" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>pool episode</name>
<description>An episode playing at the pool, mostly in school, sometimes outside of it when the cast does not have a chance for a beach episode.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version of the http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode].
Other variants are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160904.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6137" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-09">
<name>catchphrase</name>
<description>A catchphrase is a sound, word or phrase commonly used by a person. That may be simply out of habit, or in an attempt to deliver some form of image, like that of cuteness. In fiction, characters often use catchphrases as a way to deliver specific personality traits. Examples include Otohime Mutsumi`s "ara ara" in Love Hina, Yang Wenli`s "yare yare" in Legend of the Galactic Heroes, Misuzu`s "gao" in AIR, Sakura`s "hoe" in Card Captor Sakura, Suiseiseki`s "desu" in Rozen Maiden, and Ayu`s "uguu" in Kanon (as well as several other characters in the same show).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6347" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>body and host</name>
<description>When a foreign entity like that of a symbiote, body snatcher, puppeteer parasite, or even a hacker (when regarding machines like robots and computers) enters/outright hijacks a body, the possessed subject becomes what is usually called: the host.
The basic purpose of the host varies on what the point was for it to have been hijacked in the first place. Sometimes it`s used as a disguise, other times it`s used as a decoy and destraction, even simply being used as a weapon and piece of armor that the possessor uses to cause sheer chaos and destruction, but sometimes... a host can be used for fetish fuel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6349" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>multi-segment episodes</name>
<description>Multi-segment episodes are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes], which are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length (up to and including 10 minutes).
Also not to be confused with an OVA or music video with multiple (otherwise unrelated) full-length http://anidb.net/t7241 [bundled episodes] consolidated into a single episode video track.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2354" type="main character in" update="2013-12-24">
<rating votes="351">2.61</rating>
<name>Yuuki Rito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The male protagonist of To Love-Ru, Rito is a 16 year-old high-school student. Rito used to be on the soccer team in junior high and was quite good, but quit because he was constantly helping his father with his mangaka duties, thus did not want to leave his sister Mikan alone in the house. Mikan comments he is very good at the most "useless little things", like crane and festival games. Along with the numerous useless little things Rito is good at, he is also an accomplished florist/gardener/horticulturalist.</description>
<picture>61497.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2355" type="main character in" update="2013-12-24">
<rating votes="542">8.21</rating>
<name>Lala Satalin Deviluke</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The female protagonist of To Love-Ru, Lala is the princess of Deviluke. A rather childish girl, she is somewhat naïve of the culture and familiarities on Earth. Lala initially runs away from home, citing she does not wish to get married to any of her arranged suitors. She enjoys making all manners of inventions (usually designed as pranks) and uses them frequently, often prompting some disastrous effect or another. Upon arriving on Earth, Lala pretends to love Rito to keep herself from getting married, but does exactly what she did not intend, after she misinterprets what Rito shouts in self-defence. Throughout the series, she always tries to get Rito to love her more, and barely shows any form of negativity towards him; she even states it is impossible for her to hate him.</description>
<picture>61495.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2356" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-02-08">
<rating votes="85">5.82</rating>
<name>Peke</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lala`s all costume robot, who acts as a module to form her clothing. Peke is exceptionally devoted to Lala and has the ability to shapeshift into any kind of clothing for her to wear, but this also drains her power supply. As her batteries run out, the clothing Lala wears will slowly dissolve, until it completely disappears. To recharge, Peke simply needs to sleep.</description>
<picture>17592.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2357" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-16">
<rating votes="526">8.45</rating>
<name>Konjiki no Yami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A dispassionate, withdrawn assassin, Golden Darkness is hired by one of Lala`s arranged suitors, Lacospo to kill Rito, until she breaks the contract, noting the true nature behind her target. Golden Darkness is currently staying on Earth, roaming around the city streets and Sainan High, with a motivation to continue her duty to assassinate Rito, although she has yet to accomplish this (hinting she only said this as an excuse to stay on Earth). Commonly referred as "Yami-chan", she spends her time reading books and magazines, while eating taiyaki (it is the only thing she eats on Earth since it is the first food offered by Rito, prior to spending a night at the Yuuki residence for a sukiyaki dinner). By her planet`s calculations, she is 24 years-old, despite having an appearance of an 11 year-old and has a weakness towards anything slimy.
http://anidb.net/ch2387 [Eve] from http://anidb.net/a3321 [Black Cat], another of http://anidb.net/cr2985 [Yabuki Kentaro]`s works, and her are alternative reality versions of each other.</description>
<picture>61500.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="304" picture="17139.jpg">Fukuen Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2358" type="main character in" update="2013-12-24">
<rating votes="267">6.06</rating>
<name>Sairenji Haruna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of Rito`s classmates and the girl of his affections, Haruna has similar feelings for him, having been attracted to his kind, gentle nature since junior high. Despite her growing love for Rito, which she believes to be unrequited, she usually suppresses her feelings and cannot confess to him because of her friendship with Lala, who also loves Rito. However, with some encouragement, she tells Lala of her ordeal, to which Lala accepts, claiming Haruna as her rival for Rito`s heart, while remaining friends. She lives with her older sister in an apartment and has a severe fear of ghosts and the supernatural, the exception being Shizu Murasame, to an extent. When frightened, she has a habit of grabbing the nearest thing around her -- typically Rito -- and swinging wildly, in an attempt to get rid of whatever frightens her. Some people know about her love for Rito like Oshizu, Ryouko, Nana, and Lala.</description>
<picture>61496.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="89" picture="148709.jpg">Yahagi Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2359" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-24">
<rating votes="54">2.93</rating>
<name>Saruyama Ken`ichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The perverted best friend of Rito, Kenichi has known him since junior high and is more open and obvious of his obsession with girls and is one of the few male characters Rito can talk to about his situations involving Haruna or Lala.</description>
<picture>17595.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2360" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-24">
<rating votes="210">5.57</rating>
<name>Momioka Risa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Momioka Risa is one of the mischievous, cheerful best friends of Haruna, Risa and Mio spend as much time as they can with her and Lala. Whenever Lala inquires about Earth culture and habits, the two divulge as much information as they can for her (although it is often misleading and perverted). Risa and Mio are known for their playful habit of groping other girls.</description>
<picture>126812.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2361" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-04-01">
<rating votes="116">5.36</rating>
<name>Sawada Mio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the mischievous, cheerful best friends of Haruna, Risa and Mio spend as much time as they can with her and Lala. Whenever Lala inquires about Earth culture and habits, the two divulge as much information as they can for her (although it is often misleading and perverted). Risa and Mio are known for their playful habit of groping other girls.</description>
<picture>184983.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="540" picture="41046.jpg">Chiba Chiemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2362" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-04-01">
<rating votes="149">6.87</rating>
<name>Run Elsie Jewelria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>As Run is from planet Memorze, she can change gender in mind and body upon triggering a specific stimulus; in her case, a sneeze. As a girl, Run is in love with Rito, due to the kiss, and blames Lala for her misfortunes. However, her boy form, Ren, is still in competition, albeit one-sided, with Rito for Lala`s hand in marriage. Currently, Run is a famous idol, having released several albums.</description>
<picture>184984.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="142" picture="68482.jpg">Ooura Fuyuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2363" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-24">
<rating votes="62">5.03</rating>
<name>Ren Elsie Jewelria</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A childhood friend of Lala, Ren is infamously known for wearing girls clothing during his play dates with Lala when he was a child. He arrives on Earth to win Lala by proving he is "man enough" for her, but becomes jealous of her relationship with Rito. Due to his pursuit of her, he accidentally gives Rito his first kiss. While Ren is furious, it has an unexpected consequence towards his "alter ego". As Ren is from planet Memorze, he can change gender in mind and body upon triggering a specific stimulus; in his case, a sneeze. As a girl, Run is in love with Rito, due to the kiss, and blames Lala for her misfortunes, while Ren is still in competition, albeit one-sided, with Rito for Lala`s hand in marriage.</description>
<picture>17600.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="142" picture="68482.jpg">Ooura Fuyuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2364" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-24">
<rating votes="434">8.51</rating>
<name>Kotegawa Yui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An uptight, high-strung girl placed in Rito`s class during the second year, Yui has little to no tolerance for anything she does not consider to be "acceptable behavior". Her haughty opinions, quick temper, and habit of speaking her mind often results in her vocally reprimanding classmates. Yui quickly grows annoyed and disgusted by the eccentricities and bizarre actions, particularly with regards to Rito and Lala. Unfortunately, almost every encounter with Rito usually ends up with her embarrassed, and though her complicated nature prevents her from easing her behaviour, she does slowly warm up to his usual antics and develops feelings for Rito.</description>
<picture>61498.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2365" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-24">
<rating votes="173">6.53</rating>
<name>Murasame Shizu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The ghost of a girl who died in the old abandoned school building 400 years ago, Oshizu is sincere, kind, and very curious about the modern world, but has a severe fear of dogs, likened to Haruna`s level of fear to the supernatural. When frightened, she can emit blasts of mental stress, blowing apart various objects and surroundings, but is also capable of manipulating others through sheer willpower. Since her meeting with Rito and the others, she begins exploring the world outside the old school building. Oshizu is aware of Haruna`s crush on Rito by her ability to sense feelings while possessing another person and becomes very supportive towards cheering Haruna into confessing her feelings to him.</description>
<picture>61499.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2366" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-04-01">
<rating votes="157">6.01</rating>
<name>Tenjouin Saki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The arrogant queen bee of the school, third-year student Saki consistently tries to one-up Lala, stating there can only be "queen" in Sainan High. She once tries to seduce Rito to make Lala jealous, but when that does not work, Saki takes up any excuse to physically assault Rito. She gains a crush on Zastin, only to be horrified when she discovers he is Lala`s servant. However, this makes her very determined to win his heart, at any cost.</description>
<picture>184979.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2367" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-04-01">
<rating votes="137">6.63</rating>
<name>Kujou Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saki`s loyal and assisting friends, Rin is skilled in the kendo arts and has been a loyal bodyguard of Saki for years, as her family has always served the Tenjouin in this position.</description>
<picture>184981.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="602" picture="79633.jpg">Hashimoto Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2368" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-04-01">
<rating votes="85">3.62</rating>
<name>Fujisaki Aya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saki`s loyal and assisting friends, The bespectacled Aya is weak-willed and became associated with Saki after she and Rin protected her from bullies when they were children.</description>
<picture>184982.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="591" picture="226209.jpg">Mizuhashi Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2369" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-04-01">
<rating votes="142">7.26</rating>
<name>Mikado Ryouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The provocative school doctor at Sainan High, Ryouko helps out other extraterrestrials on Earth in various manners, usually those dealing with medical care, though she does offer students a variety of her own concoctions. Formerly an operative for a shadowy, black market extraterrestrial organization, she fled from her superiors to Earth in hopes of hiding her identity. Proof of her non-human origins are the elf-like ears hidden by her short hair, though it has yet been specified what her species is.</description>
<picture>184980.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="603" picture="223012.jpg">Jou Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2370" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-14">
<rating votes="80">3.56</rating>
<name>Kouchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The unnamed principal of Sainan High is well-known throughout campus as a pervert. He will impulsively enrol girls into the school body, so as to ogle and grope them without hesitation, though this is not restricted in Sainan High, but in public, as well.</description>
<picture>17607.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="604" picture="154161.jpg">Ogata Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2371" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-24">
<rating votes="428">8.43</rating>
<name>Yuuki Mikan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuuki Mikan is Rito`s independent and reliable 11 year-old sister, Mikan takes care of the housework while their parents are away on business. In contrast to her brother, she is very mature and does not hesitate to tease him, going as far as stating they aren`t blood related, just for a laugh. Mikan also seems to have a certain lack of respect for Rito because of this (she hardly ever addresses him by his honorific as an older brother), but does answer him "Onii-chan" as thanks for trying so hard to take care of her when she develops a fever and when he got her a Christmas present. Mikan may not show it, but she cares very deeply for Rito and misses his company, and states how they used to play together before Lala entered their lives.</description>
<picture>126813.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2372" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-24">
<rating votes="45">6.84</rating>
<name>Zastin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lala`s personal bodyguard and the best swordsman on Deviluke. Initially, Zastin disapproves of Rito, deeming him weak and subsequently soughts to test his strength. However, once Rito exclaims his opinion of marriage in self-defense, Zastin is swayed by his words (though not in the way Rito intends) and summarily approves of him, believing he truly understands Lala`s feelings.</description>
<picture>17609.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2373" type="appears in" update="2017-09-12">
<rating votes="18">3.75</rating>
<name>Gido Lucion Deviluke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The King of Deviluke and Emperor of the known universe, Gido is the father of Lala, Nana, and Momo. Despite his near omnipotent power, he has the physical appearance of a child, looking slightly devilish, with shark-like teeth, spiky black hair, and the characteristic Devilukean tail; while his daughters` tails end in spades, his appears as a wicked looking trident. Gido`s personality borders juvenile delinquency and perversion, thus Lala claims the only reason he wants her to get married is so he can step down as king and be free to pursue his perverted hobbies. Lala states his current appearance is due to him using too much power during the "Galaxy Unification Wars", which desized his body, following his conquest.</description>
<picture>17610.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="601" picture="165793.jpg">Nakamura Hidetoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6926" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-24">
<rating votes="38">5.75</rating>
<name>Yuusaki Riko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rito`s female alter-ego, she is a beautiful girl (with a physical appearance resembling a tomboy) who gets much attention from men, such as Motemitsu, the perverted principal and even Saruyama, Rito`s best friend. Later, Saruyama falls in love with "Riko-chan" and asks Lala to invite her for a date, which out of pity she will forcefully change Rito so he can go on a date with him.</description>
<picture>25096.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11892" type="appears in" update="2013-12-24">
<rating votes="57">7.61</rating>
<name>Magical Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A magical girl persona of http://anidb.net/ch11893 [Kirisaki Kyouko] which she portrays in her own show that http://anidb.net/ch2355 [Lala] and http://anidb.net/ch2354 [Rito] love watching.</description>
<picture>35991.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="540" picture="41046.jpg">Chiba Chiemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11893" type="appears in" update="2013-12-24">
<rating votes="72">8.16</rating>
<name>Kirisaki Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A half-Earthling half-alien girl, Kyouko is a famous idol which has the ability to create and throw fire at will and becomes a friend with http://anidb.net/ch2362 [Run] when Run portrays an antagonist on her show. She is best known for her role as http://anidb.net/ch11892 [Magical Kyouko], a fictional magical girl character who stars in her own television series that http://anidb.net/ch2355 [Lala] loves watching, often forcing http://anidb.net/ch2354 [Rito] to watch it with her.
Kyouko is based on http://anidb.net/ch2440 [Kirisaki Kyouko] from http://anidb.net/a3321 [Black Cat].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>146729.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="540" picture="41046.jpg">Chiba Chiemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13068" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-24">
<rating votes="230">6.71</rating>
<name>Nana Astar Deviluke</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of Lala`s twin younger sisters, she is introduced when most of the characters are in a virtual game world created by Lala that she and Momo subsequently modify. Nana has long hair, a single visible sharp tooth and unlike her sisters, a flat chest. She understands and can talk to animals. Like her big sister, she too has cell phone capable of transporting objects, however instead of gadgets Nana summons animals.</description>
<picture>61501.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13069" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-24">
<rating votes="542">8.98</rating>
<name>Momo Belia Deviluke</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of Lala`s twin younger sisters, she is introduced when most of the characters are in a virtual game world created by Lala that she and Nana subsequently modify. Momo has short hair and is generally sweeter than her twin Nana, but develops a bad attitude whenever Nana takes credit for what she does; she shares a connection to plant life. Like her big sister, she too has cell phone capable of transporting objects, however instead of gadgets Momo summons plants.</description>
<picture>39003.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16805" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-24">
<rating votes="56">6.00</rating>
<name>Celine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Celine is Lala`s gift for Rito`s 17th birthday, she is a multi-story, carnivorous, sentient sunflower kept in the Yuuki`s residence backyard. Although seemingly monstrous, Rito cares for Celine deeply, referring to her as his family. The plant behaves akin to a human: perspiring when the climate is humid, wearing an oversized scarf during a chilly day and eating a bowl of ramen when hungry (though Celine still needs the basic nutrients of water and sunlight). When Celine contracts a deadly disease, Rito is fully dedicated to saving her from Kare Kare and finding the luckyberry. With his friends they journey to an S-level-danger class planet of Misletoe to retrieve an antidote, only to return and find the plant all dried up. In reality, it was germinating and from its single seed burst out Celine, taking the appearance of an infant girl, with a flower on her head. This event even shocks Momo, who is very knowledgeable with the galaxy`s flora, stating Celine`s biological makeup is still a complete mystery to her.
Referring to Rito as her "mama", the infant Celine develops a low tolerance for cola and can spray a pollen from the flower on her head that temporarily causes anyone who inhales it to fall in love with Rito - a side-effect that originates from Celine`s own affection for him from taking care of her everyday. A running gag as a child is Celine will playfully tackle any girl and attempt to breast feed on them. Comically mistaken for being Rito`s daughter, Celine as a plant and infant does make an appearance in the animated adaptation.</description>
<picture>126814.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24934" type="appears in" update="2010-11-08">
<rating votes="13">5.47</rating>
<name>Nitta Haruko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mikan`s homeroom teacher in her elementary school. She is shown to be a otaku and big fan of Saibai`s work.</description>
<picture>58791.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3202" picture="24193.jpg">Nakamura Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24935" type="appears in" update="2010-11-08">
<rating votes="12">4.46</rating>
<name>Kotegawa Yuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yui`s 19 year-old brother, Yuu is a ladies` man, something Yui dislikes. After finding Rito and Yui being chased by hoodlums, he defends the two from the ruffians, while commenting that he hopes Yui will grow to be more mature. At the moment, he is dating Akiho, Haruna`s older sister but unknown to him she isn`t taking the relationship as seriously as he does. He also is one of the few people to know that Rito is Riko.</description>
<picture>58792.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="545" picture="188506.jpg">Abe Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25010" type="appears in" update="2010-11-11">
<rating votes="6">2.90</rating>
<name>Smutts</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Zastin`s assistant.</description>
<picture>59110.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3797" picture="65487.jpg">Matsuo Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25011" type="appears in" update="2010-11-11">
<rating votes="6">2.90</rating>
<name>Maul</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Zastin`s assistant.</description>
<picture>59111.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4741" picture="45560.jpg">Konno Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25153" type="appears in" update="2010-11-17">
<rating votes="6">2.55</rating>
<name>Honegawa-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59421.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3064" picture="24692.jpg">Asou Tomohisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25844" type="appears in" update="2010-12-20">
<rating votes="13">5.55</rating>
<name>Marron</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61098.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="310" picture="17147.jpg">Kazama Yuuto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25845" type="appears in" update="2010-12-20">
<rating votes="12">1.45</rating>
<name>Yuuki Saibai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rito`s father is a mangaka and is very different compared to Rito in terms of both looks and personality. Saibai draws at amazing speeds and can be utterly serious before deadlines are met, but seems to have a bit of a goofy side, such as making a joke about Rito and Lala "sleeping" together every night and punching Rito when he got drunk and mistook his son for a burglar. With the help of Lala he returns for the Christmas party, stating how much Zastin and his workers have grown since starting out. In the anime, he writes a (not-so-encouraging) letter to him at the end of the first season.</description>
<picture>61100.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25846" type="appears in" update="2010-12-20">
<rating votes="9">5.33</rating>
<name>Yuuki Ringo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rito`s mother is a fashion designer and a scout for fashion models. Normally working overseas, she returns home to check up on the family. Despite initially appearing to be refined and chic, Ringo`s personality is equally as odd as Saibai`s, where she has a tendency to start sizing women up with her hands, whenever she spots pretty girls. Ringo seems to take her work very seriously, having immediately entered "work-mode", when she meets Lala and Haruna for the first time. Like her daughter, Ringo is also highly perceptive, able to read Haruna`s feelings towards Rito. With the help of Lala, she returns for the Christmas party and mistakes Celine as her son`s child.</description>
<picture>61101.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26360" type="appears in" update="2011-01-02">
<rating votes="36">6.06</rating>
<name>Sairenji Akiho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haruna`s older sister, she shares her apartment with Haruna. Extremely popular with the guys (having received confessions from two men at the same time), Akiho continuously turns them down, as her sister states she is not looking for love at the moment. However, she has been dating Yuu Kotegawa.</description>
<picture>61857.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="216" picture="171983.jpg">Takahashi Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77304" type="appears in" update="2015-09-09">
<rating votes="13">3.78</rating>
<name>Kogure Sachie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>177232.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="304" picture="17139.jpg">Fukuen Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77305" type="appears in" update="2015-09-09">
<rating votes="14">5.26</rating>
<name>Nogiwa Mami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>177233.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="89" picture="148709.jpg">Yahagi Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="120937" update="2010-08-07">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2010-08-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122277" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヤミヤミファッション / ワンダフルラブ♥ / ツインズ☆エスケイプ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yami Yami Fashion / Wonderful Love / Twins Escape</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yami Yami Fashion / Wonderful Love / Twins Escape</title>
<summary>Since Yami always wears the same clothing, Risa and Mio take her shopping. However, her new and improved wardrobe prevents her from using her weapons properly. Haruna thinks she may have a stalker. Nana and Momo go to extremes to avoid studying the Royal Lineage of Deviluke.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>683445</identifier>
<identifier>motto-to-love-ru</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="122278" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">特恋薬(とっこーやく)♡ / レンズ越しに見る君は... / 愛しの君はシンデレラ♡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special Love Potion / Looking at You Through the Lens... / The Lovely You Is Cinderella</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokkou Yaku / Lens Goshi ni Miru Kimi wa... / Itoshi no Kimi wa Cinderella</title>
<summary>Rito delivers assignments to a sick Yuki who panics with a boy in her room. Frazzled and fumbling, Rito accidentally touches her breasts. Rito wears Lala’s glasses, which enable the wearer to see through people’s clothing. Saruyama falls in love with Rito, and Lala sets up a date for them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>683443</identifier>
<identifier>motto-to-love-ru</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="122279" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暗闇の中でうつるもの / ようこそ! 結城家へ / お泊り会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Thing That Surfaces in the Darkness / Welcome to the Yuuki Household! / Slumber Party</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kurayami no Naka de Utsuru Mono / Youkoso! Yuuki Ie e / Otomari Kai</title>
<summary>As Rito attempts to keep Haruna away from Lala’s gadgets, they accidentally activate one and are warped to another location—naked, of course! Haruko wants to meet Saibai, as she is a fan of his manga. However, deadlines prevent Saibai’s visit, forcing Rito to impersonate him. Unaware that Rito is in the bathroom, Lala and the girls decide to bathe. An unfortunate event finds Rito in front of a group of naked and surprised girls.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>683441</identifier>
<identifier>motto-to-love-ru</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="122280" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">もう一度ここから / お風呂場戦争 / チクタクチクタク恋の音♡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Once Again from Here / Bathroom War / Tick-Tock, Tick-Tock, the Sound of Love</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une fois de plus en partant d`ici / Guerre dans les bains publics / Tic tac tic tac le son de l`amour</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mou Ichido Koko kara / Ofuroba Sensou / Tick Tack Tick Tack Koi no Oto</title>
<summary>Lala and Rito are late for school, and Lala takes the opportunity to confess her feelings for him. They use a teleportation device to get to school faster, but they arrive sans clothing!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>683439</identifier>
<identifier>motto-to-love-ru</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="123683" update="2020-01-03">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-10-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="123684" update="2010-10-07">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-10-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124878" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋愛クィーン!? / お遊戯しましょ♪ / 甘い気持ちはチョコの味</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Queen of Romance!? / Lets`s Play a Game / That Sweet Feeling Tastes Like Chocolate</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ren`ai Queen!? / Oyuugi Shimasho / Amai Kimochi wa Choco no Aji</title>
<summary>Rito avoids Lala while Saki daydreams of Zastin. Ren and Lala have a gas—literally! An alien skunk gas turns them both into children. Everyone prepares for Valentine’s Day, and Rito is the object of desire for many. Yui tries to find the confidence to give her chocolate to Rito.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>683447</identifier>
<identifier>motto-to-love-ru</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="125128" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-10</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ビーチ・ガールズ♡ / 深夜の家庭教師 / 恋愛マスター♡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beach Girls / Late Night Private Tutor / Master of Romance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Beach Girls / Shin`ya no Kateikyoushi / Ren`ai Master</title>
<summary>Things go awry when the group visits Saki’s private beach. Lala helps Rito study for an upcoming math test, but when the day comes, he cannot remember how to solve the problems. Lala tries to win Rito’s attention, but she is not having much luck.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>683449</identifier>
<identifier>motto-to-love-ru</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="125176" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-17</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">闇の診療所 / 敵対心 / おかしな春菜ちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yami`s Clinic / Hostility / A Weird Haruna</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yami no Shinryousho / Tekitaishin / Okashina Haruna-chan</title>
<summary>Yami falls ill with fever, and Rito rushes her to the hospital. When she recovers, Yami questions why Rito would help her since he is her target. Kyouko and Ren eat lunch together where they end up bonding and proving useful to each other. When Lala and Rito meet with Haruna, they notice something is wrong. Haruna is not acting like herself—and, as it turns out, she’s not!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>683451</identifier>
<identifier>motto-to-love-ru</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="125298" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">「妹」戦線異常アリ / 偽りの恋? / 恋愛予報</title>
<title xml:lang="en">All Quiet on the "Sister" Front / The False Love? / Predicting Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Imouto" Sensen Ijou Ari / Itsuwari no Koi! / Renai Yohou</title>
<summary>Momo sneaks into Rito’s bed. Mikan, who wants to catch Momo, sneaks in as well but does not find anything. She does, however, end up staying the night. Rito and Lala pursue a drunk Celine, who spreads her pollen to Yami, which causes her to fall for Rito. Haruna cannot fight her feelings any longer, so she tells Lala that she also likes Rito.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>683459</identifier>
<identifier>motto-to-love-ru</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="125299" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-12-08</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">花粉伝心 / オンナノコノキモチ / ドキドキ☆メール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pollen Telepathy / A Girl`s Feelings / Heart-Throbbing Email</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kafun Denshin / Onnanoko no Kimochi / Dokidoki Mail</title>
<summary>Celine is drunk and spreads her pollen, making Saki and the others fall for Rito. Rito sets out to buy groceries and runs into Misa. After she takes him around town, he ends up not accomplishing any tasks. Momo mistakes an innocent message for something sexual and after a series of misunderstandings, Yui ends up with a nude photo of Lala.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>683457</identifier>
<identifier>motto-to-love-ru</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="125300" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-12-01</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">誰がためにベルは鳴る / 迷惑暴走? / 恋心アイドル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">For Whom the Bell Tolls / The Troubling Rampage / Loving Idol</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ta ga Tame ni Beru wa Naru / Meiwaku Bousou? / Loving Idol</title>
<summary>Mikan’s and Rito’s parents are never home, so the approaching Christmas holiday does not excite them. Lala helps fulfill a wish of Mikan’s. Rito is accidentally transported into Peke’s body, and chaos ensues during gym class. Rito pretends to be Ren’s boyfriend as a favor, but they aren’t fooling anyone.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>683455</identifier>
<identifier>motto-to-love-ru</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="125301" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-24</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大きくなぁ~れ♪ / ワンダフルライフ / 気分はトランス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Become Bigger / Wonderful Life / The Trance of Feelings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ookiku Naare / Wonderful Life / Kibun wa Toransu</title>
<summary>Haruna feels self-conscious about the size of her bust but ultimately decides that the quality of her character is more important than her exterior. Haruna finds a stray dog who turns out to be Rito. Mikan and Yami switch bodies to experience each other’s abilities.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>683453</identifier>
<identifier>motto-to-love-ru</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="126225" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大スキ♡1 / 大スキ♡2 / 大スキ♡3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Love You 1 / I Love You 2 / I Love You 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daisuki 1 / Daisuki 2 / Daisuki 3</title>
<summary>Lala vows to help Haruna find love. Saruyama points out that Rito has changed since became close with Lala. An outing goes horribly wrong, and Rito chooses to give his own life for Lala and Haruna. During this time, he realizes that he loves Lala. Rito loves Lala. The problem is, he loves Haruna, too. Lala suggests that he marry them both.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>683481</identifier>
<identifier>motto-to-love-ru</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="133103" update="2020-01-03">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-12-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136474" update="2012-01-18">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
