<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7698" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>4</episodecount>
<startdate>1989-10-27</startdate>
<enddate>1991-03-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Bucchigiri</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ぶっちぎり</title>
</titles>
<creators>
<name id="728" type="Animation Work">Nippon Animation</name>
<name id="9754" type="Character Design">Endou Eiichi</name>
<name id="3639" type="Direction">Kusuba Kouzou</name>
<name id="1743" type="Direction">Yatabe Katsuyoshi</name>
<name id="20188" type="Original Work">Nakahara Yuu</name>
</creators>
<description>To all his schoolmates, Jin comes across as a hot-headed class clown who typically barges in late, sleeps the whole way through classes and always responds to any situation with reckless stupidity. The fact that he used to be the charismatic leader of a legendary biker gang has turned into an urban legend; however, after starting a rivalry with the captain of the school baseball team he and two former gang members become their star players. But it`s not long before his past catches up to him...
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2">6.01</permanent>
<temporary count="2">5.50</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>238890.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7141</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9665</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2739</identifier>
<identifier>citfzu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ぶっちぎり</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88676</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2370</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>2618</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>2619</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>2779</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="28" parentid="2881" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-16">
<name>baseball</name>
<description>Baseball is like a complicated version of Rounders. It involves hitting a ball with a stick, then running around several bases placed in the form of a diamond on a field. Big in the US, and also in Japan.</description>
<picurl>29801.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2069" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-15">
<name>delinquent</name>
<description>Delinquents - Every school has them, but not all anime with school setting make delinquents a central topic. There are several versions of these delinquents, though some are grounded on a misunderstanding:
* The student with a really bad image and attitude, based on his real criminal actions outside of the school and is even feared by teachers.
* The primitive "class bully" that pushes around ("clobbers") his classmates for no apparent reason, possibly extorting lunch money.
* The student with an sinister complexion or "evil eye", but is actually a "good" student (unfoundedly feared character).
* The rebellious student, who does not care for studying, but is otherwise docile. Called a "delinquent" as a joke.</description>
<picurl>243713.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="120070" update="2010-07-22">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>1991-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120071" update="2014-05-18">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>1990-07-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120072" update="2014-05-18">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>1990-02-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120073" update="2010-07-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>1989-10-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
