<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="771" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2002-11-20</startdate>
<enddate>2002-11-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Blue Gender: The Warrior</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Blue Gender The Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Blue Gender Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ブルージェンダー ザ・ウォリアー</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Blue Gender: The Warrior</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Blue Gender - The Warrior</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Blue Gender - Zrozen k boji</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Blue Gender - Harcra született</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="official">Blue Gender: Războinicul</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="416" type="Full Story">Blue Gender</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="149149">Great anime</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.anime-int.com/works/bluegender/movie/</url>
<creators>
<name id="732" type="Animation Production">AIC</name>
<name id="1077" type="Financial Production">Toshiba EMI</name>
<name id="102" type="Character Design">Kizaki Fuminori</name>
<name id="1391" type="Direction">Oohata Kouichi</name>
</creators>
<description>It is a time of chaos. Earth is no longer what it used to be. It has been infested with a bug-like species called the Blue. http://anidb.net/ch16747 [Kaidou Yuuji], who has a mysterious disease, is put into suspended animation until a cure can be found. When he wakes up, Yuuji learns that more than 30 years have passed since he was put into suspended animation, and the world is now controlled by these creatures. He then decides to join a group of soldiers fighting against the Blue in hope of a better future.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="614">3.50</permanent>
<temporary count="620">6.14</temporary>
<review count="1">7.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>150332.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2404</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1380</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.anime-int.com/works/bluegender/movie/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>337080</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3267" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>everybody dies</name>
<description>Not necessarily everyone, but a good portion of the characters kick the bucket.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3516" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-28">
<name>insects of doom</name>
<description>Concerns insects, be them biological, magical or robotic in nature, that are either the bane, or a major stepping stone in the way of the main character(s) of the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3648" parentid="2637" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-25">
<name>person from the past</name>
<description>Possibly via stasis or cryogenic chamber, a person from the past will reawaken into a future present.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3798" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>giant insects</name>
<picurl>222266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="16747" type="main character in" update="2011-11-26">
<rating votes="17">7.27</rating>
<name>Kaidou Yuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaidou Yuuji worked at a gas station, in what used to be the near future (2009), until a life-threatening disease (later discovered to be B-cells) required him to be put into cryogenic stasis so that his state would not get worse. He awakens in the future to find that the Blue have destroyed everything he knew. He then begins his journey to Second Earth, learning to defend himself and others on the way. His mental state changes greatly during the series, as he sees more of the ruined earth and meets all the people left behind.</description>
<picture>77675.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16748" type="main character in" update="2014-06-06">
<rating votes="31">9.01</rating>
<name>Marlene Angel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Marlene Angel was orphaned at the age of ten because her parents were killed by the Blue, Marlene was one of the few lucky ones to make it to Second Earth. Since then, Marlene has dedicated and trained herself to defeat the Blue. Though seeming very cold in the earlier episodes, as time progresses, Yuji opens up Marlene`s emotions. Towards the end of the series, she conceives Yuji`s child.</description>
<picture>77676.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16754" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-26">
<rating votes="8">5.17</rating>
<name>Joey Heald</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77677.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2226" picture="23215.jpg">Suganuma Hisayoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16756" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-14">
<rating votes="8">2.31</rating>
<name>Rick Kilmer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46361.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2224" picture="21768.jpg">Itou Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16757" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-14">
<rating votes="7">4.55</rating>
<name>Seamus Han</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46362.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5243" picture="29266.jpg">Isobe Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16758" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-17">
<rating votes="10">7.86</rating>
<name>Seno Miyagi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Seno Miyagi is a high-ranking member of the science division on Second Earth. He suggests that Marlene and Yuuji are kept together in order to get the best results from Yuuji in the sleeper program. Not agreeing with the High Council`s leadership of Second Earth or its reckless use of the sleepers, he eventually forms a group called The Ark, which would later overthrow the High Council`s "government" on Second Earth. Seno would subsequently become the leader of Second Earth, but only for a brief time. His order to abandon Earth eventually results in a revolt and his execution by citizens whom wanted to return to Earth.</description>
<picture>46363.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="710" picture="228657.jpg">Hori Katsunosuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16763" type="appears in" update="2010-04-14">
<rating votes="10">4.83</rating>
<name>Yung</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46368.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="553" picture="170553.jpg">Kaneda Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16764" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-14">
<rating votes="12">4.94</rating>
<name>Amick Hendar</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46373.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17081" picture="46372.jpg">Yonemoto Chizu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39067" type="appears in" update="2012-02-12">
<rating votes="7">4.57</rating>
<name>Robert Bradley</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81450.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4686" picture="171399.jpg">Hori Yukitoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39068" type="appears in" update="2012-02-12">
<rating votes="3">3.60</rating>
<name>Keith Bean</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81449.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="211" picture="17028.jpg">Kanna Nobutoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="8019" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>100</length>
<airdate>2002-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22938" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>55</length>
<airdate>2002-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22939" update="2005-09-05">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>2002-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
