<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7718" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-10-02</startdate>
<enddate>2011-04-02</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Super Robot Taisen OG: The Inspector</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Super Robot Wars OG: The Inspector</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">超级机器人大战OG2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">スーパーロボット大戦OG -ジ・インスペクター-</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">超级机器人大战OG -The inspector-</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="3394" type="Sequel">Super Robot Taisen: Original Generation - The Animation</anime>
<anime id="4761" type="Prequel">Super Robot Taisen: Original Generation - Divine Wars</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.suparobo.jp/srw_lineup/srw_ogin/</url>
<creators>
<name id="153" type="Direction">Oobari Masami</name>
<name id="23461" type="Music">Terada Shiho</name>
<name id="3826" type="Character Design">Hamazaki Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="9863" type="Character Design">Yamane Masahiro</name>
<name id="13437" type="Character Design">Oogomori Yukihito</name>
<name id="21597" type="Series Composition">Yatsufusa Tatsunosuke</name>
<name id="1016" type="Animation Work">Asahi Production</name>
<name id="3539" type="Character Design">Ebata Risa</name>
<name id="4891" type="Series Composition">Takeda Yuuichirou</name>
<name id="13937" type="Music">Kuriyama Yoshichika</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the Super Robot Taisen series of tactical role-playing video games.
The story takes place half a year after the end of Divine Wars which had Earth`s government facing off against the rebel Divine Crusaders and alien Aerogators.
As the struggle continues against Divine Crusader remnants, a new alien menace draws near.
~ translated and adapted from official site by Cranston</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="263">5.37</permanent>
<temporary count="266">6.91</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>55497.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11760</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9241</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4810</identifier>
<identifier>xmcxgb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.suparobo.jp/srw_lineup/srw_ogin/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Super_Robot_Wars_Original_Generation:_The_Inspector</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>スーパーロボット大戦OG_-ジ・インスペクター-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2035</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>337799</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13000</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="920" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-03-22">
<name>perverted</name>
<description>Is a concept describing those types of human behavior that are excessive or deviated from what is considered to be orthodox or normal.</description>
<picurl>245189.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1589" parentid="2622" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-08">
<name>samurai</name>
<picurl>244341.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2801" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>RPG</name>
<description>Any anime that is based on a role-playing game aka RPG. A role-playing video game is a video game which includes elements of non-electronic role-playing games. The player assumes control of one or several fictional characters (a party) who have joined forces in order to perform quests and overcome a great number of challenges and enemies, usually monsters inspired by fantasy, and, to a lesser extent, science fiction and classic mythology. During the course of the game the characters, or avatars, which are generally defined by quantized characteristics, evolve and improve in that their various attributes increase, as well as by gaining more powerful artefacts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2867" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>politics</name>
<description>From commies to fat capitalist pigs, all the stuff done by the "guys with the power", mainly evil tactics for gaining more power over the masses.
Watching this title may remind you why CNN is boring.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3087" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>super robot</name>
<description>These robots tend to have almost semi-magical attacks, which seem impossible or non-realistic, and/or perform non-realistic transformation sequences where they seem to gain/lose mass and utterly change their form, even if it means making their super-hard armour bend like plastic sheets.</description>
<picurl>222137.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3327" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-08">
<name>manly</name>
<description>Masculinity is possessing qualities or characteristics considered typical of or appropriate to a man.
Typical characteristics associated with masculinity are: courage, a strong physique, competitive, strong willed, and a sense of honor.
Very important for being considered masculine however is the ability to inspire respect from your fellow brethren and/or being perceived as a virile man by the opposite sex.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4004" parentid="2638" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>organic mecha</name>
<description>An organic mecha is a mecha that has organic tissue in its composition. The most prominent historical example is http://anidb.net/a22 [Neon Genesis Evangelion].</description>
<picurl>224892.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4081" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space battles</name>
<description>There are space battles in this anime. Usually between Earth forces and some alien invader, but ship to ship skirmishes in deep space are just as common.</description>
<picurl>242377.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4182" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-01-22">
<name>hidden power</name>
<description>For some reason or another a character has powers (or potential) he or she can`t access and may not even know about. 
In some anime these hidden powers are used quite frequently to overcome an enemy or threat (e.g. Naruto, Bleach).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4308" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-03-26">
<name>delayed death</name>
<description>The Final Battle has begun. The two opponents square off, and one of them hits the other with a series of mighty blows that would fell a mountain. But what`s this? Nothing seems to be happening! That`s when your opponent tells you that You Are Already Dead, right before your head explodes, your body separates in two, or you disintegrate into a fine mist. If you`re unlucky, only one of those happens. Sometimes, you may also discover that you were Made of Explodium.
A common trope in martial arts series, this involves some form of Finishing Move that does not take effect immediately. When used with martial arts, it may involve Pressure Point attacks or some form of Ki Attacks. Assassins may use Universal Poison to achieve a similar effect. In video games, Damage Over Time abilities often have this effect.
When used with swords there are a number of common variations, often shown with a Diagonal Cut. In sword duels, the two sides charge each other and attack. There will be a pause as the two pose, then one (or both) will fall down. Another one is for a Master Swordsman to perform a series of lightning-fast slashes, and then slowly and dramatically sheath their sword (with an audible *click*) before their attacks take effect.
This trope is not necessarily limited to martial arts, either. In more modern settings, gunshot wounds can often have this effect, since getting shot typically feels like getting punched hard and it is not uncommon for victims to take some time to realize it. This can be exploited for dramatic effect in war movies, where fatally wounded soldiers wander the battlefield before succumbing.
Source: TVTropes</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4404" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-28">
<name>real robot</name>
<description>A smaller form of mecha with no special abilities. They are mostly used by deploying them in battle just like modern tanks. They can be mass produced and their pilots (usually military officers or soldiers) are (mostly) interchangeable. Tanks are often a threat to them and they are more easily destroyed than their bigger counterparts.</description>
<picurl>42787.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4469" parentid="2644" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-29">
<name>gattai</name>
<description>Gattai is when two fighting spirits collide and unite, when a man`s soul is ablaze!
When you are about to get your asses kicked by the big bad evil, it`s time to show your true fighting spirit and gattai, literally combine with your mecha to become at least ten times as powerful and kick the big bad evil`s ass.</description>
<picurl>66429.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4612" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep?</name>
<description>The title of Philip K. Dick`s SF novel (movie: Blade Runner). 
The phrase implies a set of existential questions: Do artificial beings (e.g. Replicants, Bioroids, or other AI constructs) dream, feel, or have a soul? If memories can be implanted, what makes real memories real? By contrast — what makes humans human? What is reality? 
These are central themes e.g. in all of the Ghost in the Shell and Appleseed series / movies.</description>
<picurl>210067.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5162" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-14">
<name>inter-dimensional travel</name>
<description>Inter-dimensional travel is the ability to move between dimensions. It is often also explained as moving between dimensional planes. Holders of this ability are generally called sliders.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6050" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-11">
<name>human - non-human relationship</name>
<description>The relationship between a human and a non-human — be it alien, or artificial — is explored in this anime.
This usually means between a male human and a female (humanoid) alien or AI (avatar).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="20076" type="main character in" update="2010-11-20">
<rating votes="1">7.01</rating>
<name>Axel Almar</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He has good control over machines, and excels in taijutsu. He`s commander of the Shadow Mirror`s special forces, and is Lemon`s lover.
He`s a former member of the EFA, and worked in the same squad as Beowulf. He left Beowulf`s team due to a difference in ideals, which were caused by the sudden change in Beowulf`s personality. He joined the Shadow Mirror in order to gain power, and to try and save the world from Beowulf`s influence.
He encountered Raul and Fiona`s group transporting the Excellence units while he was testing the Soulgain. He tried to capture the two Excellences, but failed. He badly damaged Fiona`s machine, and requested that Raul surrender his unit. Dunamis appeared suddenly, and caused a dimension jump, forcing Axel to retreat before his demands were met.
When the Shadow Mirror were ready to use System XN to go to the new world, Axel decided that he would stay behind and fight against Beowulf forces one last time, while preventing the enemies from jumping with them.
He followed them soon after, but happened to arrive before any of his comrades did. He arrived during the end of the L5 Campaign, and participated in Operation SRW. It took him nearly six months to rejoin his comrades, and it`s unknown as to what he was doing during that time.
He doesn`t view Kyosuke as the Beowulf, and is able to see the differences between them. He comes to the conclusion that there is only one way to keep Kyosuke from becoming an abnormal existence like Beowulf, and that is to challenge and defeat him in a fight before he undergoes the same changes as Beowulf.
He later encountered Raul`s group when they jumped to the other side, and did battle with them. He tried asking them to join him, but he was unsuccessful, since they hated him for what he did to Fiona.
He had a dislike for Lemon`s W Number series, and always talked down to them, but that began to change as he started to see them grow. He was impressed by Lamia`s actions when she decided to disobey her orders and betray the Shadow Mirror since that meant that she had a mind of her own. He offered her a chance to return, but she refused.
Echidna died protecting him while they were fighting the EFA outside of the White Star. He was disappointed in the fact that they lost yet another valuable soldier. He retreated to the inside of the White Star, where he was eventually defeated. He told Lamia that her and the other W Numbers were more than just lifeless dolls, since they`ve decided to things on their own. He thought about Lemon during his final moments.</description>
<picture>59558.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="211" picture="17028.jpg">Kanna Nobutoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20077" type="main character in" update="2017-08-03">
<rating votes="14">7.67</rating>
<name>Excellen Browning</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A purely fun loving entertainer it`s Excellen`s habit to tease younger and thus less experienced crew-members, especially Bullet, on private matters like relationships, always speaking in an unserious cutey-girly manner. She`s always first to add weird nicknames on others and intentionally mistakes idioms for some daily slapstick. Though showing this light hearted attitude most of the time, she still knows to act serious on occasions, as indeed she is very skilled in range fight and dodging attacks. Despite his cold treatment of her on the outside, she deeply loves her Kyousuke, always supporting him either on battlefield or financially after another lost bet. She`s also a hard-drinking woman, accompanying her superiors at times, as she just loves to entertain.</description>
<picture>205738.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1870" picture="186893.jpg">Mizutani Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20078" type="main character in" update="2017-08-03">
<rating votes="4">9.57</rating>
<name>Kyosuke Nanbu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kyosuke is of hotblooded nature, a fierce close combatant, but stays quiet most of the time outside the battlefield, also making him an excellent tactician, whos foresight of enemy behavior never seems to fail. Famous for his unbelievable good luck to survive terrible accidents and dangerous combats likely unharmed, he also loves to gamble, always betting on the worst odds` side. He and Excellen form up a great combination in their PTs, also being a couple in private. Though Kyosuke constantly seems to ignore his girlfriend and her lovey-dovey sweet talk in public, he holds her dear more than anything else, so whoever might dare to harm her will be doomed to have summoned her darling`s true rage. He still holds his former commander Zanger in high regards, despite his betrayel, as he respects his reasoning and both share a similar personality, mostly stoic but "do-or-die"-mentality in battle. With Zanger gone, Kyosuke becomes also a mentor to Bullet, whos impetuous behaving has to be tamed at times.</description>
<picture>205737.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20079" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-08-03">
<rating votes="8">5.79</rating>
<name>Kusuha Mizuha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kusuha Mizuha is a fictional character in the Super Robot Wars series. Kusuha`s background story was changed in the Original Generation universe. Here, she becomes SRX Team member Ryusei Date`s high school classmate and childhood friend, developing a crush on him. However, Ryusei never shows his interest in women and their relationship is far from that of a real couple. While accompanying Ryusei to the Burning PT Tournament, Kusuha was injured when the stadium was attacked by Aerogaters. Kusuha eventually drafts into the Earth Federation Army, as the medical crew of the Hagane, in order to help Ryusei, after he was recuited into the SRX Team. Through Ingram Prisken, Kusuha becomes the pilot of the Grungust Type-2, due to her newly discovered Psychodriver background. She doesn`t meet Bullet until the end of the Divine Crusaders War, when she and the SRX Team particpated in live-fire exercise against the ATX Team. When Ingram betrays the team, he would manipulate Kusuha into siding with the Aerogaters, but be rescued by Bullet. With Operation SRW over, Kusuha transfers to the ATX Team.</description>
<picture>205740.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="216" picture="171983.jpg">Takahashi Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20080" type="main character in" update="2011-05-13">
<rating votes="2">4.81</rating>
<name>Brooklyn Luckfield</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Brooklyn "Bullet" Luckfield is a fictional character in the Super Robot Wars series. In the Original Generation universe, Bullet is already an Earth Federation Army pilot and student of the Jigen-Ryu tradition of swordsmanship, under the tutelage of Master Rishu Togo, alongside his senior, Sänger Zonvolt, to whom he shows great respect for (in the Alpha universe, Bullet does not actually meet Sanger until Alpha 3, and it is directly from Sanger that he trains to refine his skills). Bullet does not meet Kusuha until after the Divine Crusaders War, when he and the rest of the ATX Team are ordered to attack Kusuha and members of the SRX Team in a live-fire exercise. Bullet, upon discovering that a girl (Kusuha) is the pilot of the opposing Grungust Type-2, refuses to lay a hand on her. Although he is slightly reprimanded for his conduct, he is smitten with Kusuha the moment he sees her in person, but is too shy to display any romantic feelings for her.</description>
<picture>71478.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20081" type="main character in" update="2017-08-03">
<rating votes="7">7.61</rating>
<name>Lamia Loveless</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205739.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56" picture="16651.jpg">Shimizu Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21632" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-08-03">
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<name>Raidiese F. Branstein</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Younger son of Maier von Branstein and so brother to Elzam Rai didn`t follow a military career in the ranks of the Colony Corps as he broke away from his noble family early and left their home of colony Elpis. He adopted the name of Fujiwara from his late sister-in-law Kathreia, who he held in high regards, as he blamed her husband for her death during the terrorist encounter known as " the Elpis-incident". Still being a highly skilled pilot he shifted to Earth Alliance as test pilot for the RTX-007 Hückebein. A catastrophic malfunction of its black hole-engine left him heavily wounded, the reason he is hiding his crippled left hand under a glove. A calm and collected person with great pride from the start, this past forged him a slightly sinister character with lacking humor, resulting in the early quarrels between him and Ryu after being assigned to SRX-team thanks to Irm`s recommendation. Though just being a year older Rai always criticized and lectured him in an arrogant manner as he saw his team mate just as an inexperienced robot maniac-child without any sense of tactics and only limited pilot skills, but later acknowledges him due to his improvements as a comrade and also kind of rival. He feels a bit uncomfortable about the admiration 7 years younger princess Shine holds for him, as he became her "prince on his white horse", but indeed cares for her. Still he has to solve his issues with his brother as well as his cousin Leona as she tried to mediate between both. Being the only SRX-pilot without any T-LINK abilities Rai is in charge of the Tronium-engine of the machine.</description>
<picture>205742.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21633" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-08-03">
<rating votes="2">9.42</rating>
<name>Ryuusei Date</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>At 18-years old, Ryuusei Date is an extremely hot-blooded young individual. A mecha otaku, Ryuusei is heavily into mobile machines, specifically those of the super robot type. When he receives his R-1, he was disappointed at the fact that it was a real robot, but was surprised at the specifications of the SRX, where it is classified as a super. Ryusei has an odd habit of naming certain attacks, and often shouts them aloud when performing them, á la classic super robot pilots. He abbreviates some of the SRX`s and Banpreios` attacks with the words "Tenjou Tenga", literally meaning "Heaven and Earth".
Before joining the SRX Team, Ryuusei was a childhood friend with Kusuha Mizuha. Though she initially developed a crush on him, Ryuusei didn`t return the same feelings, either due to his obsession with mecha, or because he simply didn`t share them. He does show some support for the relationship she develops with Brooklyn Luckfield, however. His relationship with the rest of the female cast of Original Generation is still in question, but it seems he is exceptionally close with Latune Subbota and Aya`s sister, Mai. While he doesn`t show much interest in women, he usually says that mechs with feminine shapes and appearances, like Lune Zoldark`s Valsione, Lamia Loveless` Angelg or Virtual-ON`s Fei-Yen the Knight, are cute or sexy.
Ryuusei proves influential to the women he is close with. Both Latune and Mai have begun imitating his otaku nature in attempt to garner his attention, though this has yet to produce any significant results.</description>
<picture>205741.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21634" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-08-03">
<rating votes="10">7.16</rating>
<name>Aya Kobayashi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>21-year old Aya Kobayashi is the oldest daughter of Dr. Kenzo Kobayashi, the creator of the T-Link System. As captain of the SRX Team, she often looks out for the well-being of her teammates, both on and off the battlefield. Aya is also an adept Psychodriver, in fact, a very powerful one, for she is the key in forming the mighty SRX machine. A nice, charming woman, who enjoys walking around art museums, she looked up to ex-SRX Team Commander Ingram Prisken a lot before he betrayed the team and allied with the Aerogaters.</description>
<picture>205743.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1446" picture="19314.jpg">Touma Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21638" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-08-03">
<rating votes="2">9.42</rating>
<name>Masaki Andoh</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A rash, young pilot of the mysterious Cybuster, he pursues his nemesis, Shu Shirakawa, with the help of his familiar cats, Kuro and Shiro, in order to settle old scores.</description>
<picture>205747.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21640" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-13">
<rating votes="3">7.97</rating>
<name>Ibis Douglas</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ibis Douglas is a character in the Super Robot Taisen series of video games. Ibis also had a brief appearance in the Super Robot Wars Original Generation: Divine Wars anime series, where she is seen as a test pilot for the Divine Crusaders` new Armored Module, the Lion.</description>
<picture>71484.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21641" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-04">
<rating votes="5">4.13</rating>
<name>Lefina Enfield</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The 19 year old captain of the Hiryuu Kai.</description>
<picture>71479.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2068" picture="28743.jpg">Iwao Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21642" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-16">
<rating votes="5">7.26</rating>
<name>Leona Garstein</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55094.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1666" picture="54036.jpg">Sakakibara Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21644" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-16">
<name>Irmgard Kazahara</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He has a cool, calm, and joking personality and loves to flirt with women, which often gets him into trouble. Whenever he sees a girl, he tries to get her number into his little black book.</description>
<picture>55096.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21645" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-16">
<name>Daitetsu Minase</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55097.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2271" picture="23219.jpg">Shibata Hidekatsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21647" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-04">
<name>Tetsuya Onodera</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>58509.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7432" picture="69009.jpg">Horikawa Jin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21648" type="appears in" update="2010-09-16">
<name>Robert Hajime Oomiya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55100.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="294" picture="53586.jpg">Kirimoto Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21649" type="appears in" update="2010-09-16">
<name>Laker Randolph</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55101.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="564" picture="146195.jpg">Kiyokawa Motomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21650" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-16">
<name>Shuu Shirakawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A brilliant scientist, who is familiar with Masaki Andoh, he helps Bian Zoldark establish the Divine Crusaders and revolt against the Earth government.</description>
<picture>55102.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21651" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-08-03">
<rating votes="8">6.80</rating>
<name>Latuni Subbota</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A quiet young girl who was the part of an experimental project to create Personal Trooper pilots. She begins to open up more after befriending Ryuusei and develops a crush on him.</description>
<picture>205745.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22337" picture="58551.jpg">Hirai Riko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21654" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-08-03">
<rating votes="6">6.75</rating>
<name>Viletta Vadim</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The new SRX Team Commander replacing Ingram and is a Captain rank. She has very good PT piloting skills, and is always able to judge cooly on the battlefield. Actually, she`s the the fourth clone in the mass-produced Balshem series, based off of Ingram, the Originator. Her codename is "Bet Balshem." She`s a spy for the Aerogaters sent by Ingram, to go to the Earth Federation in order to gather data. During the final battle with Septuagint, Gilliam asks her who she really is. She tells him her real name is "Viletta Plisken", and she was created from Ingram to act on his behalf once he becomes unable to act of his own free will. Ingram created her before he`s fully taken over by the Judecca, then sends her away to complete his will. She goes on to explain to him about the Balmar Empire.</description>
<picture>205744.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="222" picture="19786.jpg">Tanaka Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21660" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="4">9.83</rating>
<name>Zengar Zombolt</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Zengar Zombolt began as a member of the Aggressors unit, an elite group of pilots formed by the Earth Federation Army, with other notable members as Elzam von Branstein, Guiliam Jeager and Kai Kitamura. When the unit was disbanded, Sanger was relocated to the North American Langley Base, and started to form the ATX Team. When the Divine Crusaders declared war on the Earth Federation, Sanger chose to leave the ATX Team and join forces with the Divine Crusaders, fighting once more alongside his old friend, Elzam V. Branstein.</description>
<picture>58492.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="338" picture="17174.jpg">Ono Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21664" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-20">
<name>Kai Kitamura</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59597.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="235" picture="17053.jpg">Saizen Tadahisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21889" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-13">
<rating votes="2">4.50</rating>
<name>Arado Balanga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>58511.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18086" picture="48107.jpg">Kaichi Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21890" type="appears in" update="2014-02-01">
<name>Wendoro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60867.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1442" picture="18829.jpg">Kaida Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21891" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-13">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Ouka Nagisa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71487.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="158" picture="38198.jpg">Neya Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21892" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-05">
<name>Gilliam Yager</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>58504.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1733" picture="25839.jpg">Tanaka Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21894" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-08-03">
<rating votes="5">5.54</rating>
<name>Seolla Schweitzer</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205749.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="223" picture="228520.jpg">Kakazu Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21896" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="7">6.62</rating>
<name>Mai Kobayashi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A very shy and silent girl, with particularly powerful Psychodriver abilities. Mai is loyal to those that have helped her, including her sister Aya, her father Kenzo, her crush Ryusei Date and the rest of the SRX Team. She also seems to be particularly close to Latune Subbota, Shine Hausen, Arado Balanga and Seolla Schweitzer, probably due to their similar ages.
Mai has a crush on fellow SRX Team member Ryusei Date. This gives her a sort of rivalry with Latune Subbota for his affection, however, they remain close friends. She`s adapted some of his mannerisms, including shouting during attacks. This crush is taken to its logical conclusion in Super Robot Wars Original Generations, in which Mai (piloting the ART-1) and Ryusei (piloting the R-1) get a combination attack, the T-Link Double Knuckle.
As Levi, Mai has a completely different personality. Believing herself to be the leader of the Balmarians, due to mind-washing, Levi is ruthless, sees humans as nothing more than weaponry for the Balmarians, and seems to have little concern for anything other than her. She`s also particularly egocentric, thinking that nothing can defeat her and her Judecca.</description>
<picture>55503.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="588" picture="41015.jpg">Orikasa Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21897" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-13">
<name>Mekiboss</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71509.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21899" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-13">
<rating votes="4">8.71</rating>
<name>Ryune Zoldark</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>16 years old. She`s the daughter of Bian Zoldark, leader of the DC. She has superhuman reflexes, eyesight, and coordination. She`s beautiful, but is still a tomboy. She is weak to compliments and flattery. Her three sizes are 87, 59, and 88.
She encountered the Hiryuu Kai and Hagane after her father was killed in combat. She ends up joining them since she`s not happy with what the DC has become, since she knows it wasn`t what her father wanted. She falls in love with Masaki, though he doesn`t feel the same way. She`s always trying to get him to compliment her.
After the war with the Aerogators, Ryuune recieved a request from Guilliam to accompany him into the Aerogators space fortress, Neviim, which was currently being held under the federations jurisdiction.
Her father created the Valsione for her after she stated that she disliked the Valsion`s design.</description>
<picture>71482.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4436" picture="244738.jpg">Hidaka Narumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21901" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-08-03">
<rating votes="1">7.37</rating>
<name>Ratsel Feinschmecker</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205748.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1616" picture="23191.jpg">Inada Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21902" type="appears in" update="2014-02-01">
<name>Vigaji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60868.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="198" picture="202893.jpg">Kusao Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23562" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-08-03">
<rating votes="3">3.40</rating>
<name>Rio Meilong</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205746.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1917" picture="151688.jpg">Natsuki Rio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24689" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-04">
<name>Hikawa Ryouto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>58508.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="320" picture="66660.jpg">Kobayashi Yumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24745" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-04">
<name>Eita Nadaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>58489.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4003" picture="77566.jpg">Tanaka Hirofumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24747" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<name>PTX-003C Alteisen</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>58517.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="24748" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="2">9.52</rating>
<name>PTX-007-03C Weissritter</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>58518.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="24751" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<name>R-1</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>58521.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="24754" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<name>PTX-007-03 Gespenst MK-II</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>58524.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="24755" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<name>Space Noah Class Number Ship 02 Hagane</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>58525.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="24758" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<name>RPT-007 Gespenst MK II M</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>58528.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="24760" type="appears in" update="2011-05-13">
<name>AGX-05 Cybuster</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>It`s one of Langran`s four Masoukishin, and is also one of the seventeen Masouki that were designed to fight against the revival of Volkruss and its minions.
It`s been blessed with protection from the Wind class` Saint Grade spirit, Cyfith. This Masoukishin is one of the fastest units ever created, and the only one to gain the ability to transform. In Cybird form, it allows the Cybuster to have even more speed and agility, which also allows it to travel at high-speeds in any atmospheric areas.
The Cybuster is basically equipped with same system equipment as other Masouki, but what makes it different is the Laplace Demon Computer; a computer system which is sought out by many, as it has the power to foretell the future.
During one of its early appearances on Earth, the Earth Federation designated this mech as AGX-05, which was later declared a misnomer, seeing as the Cybuster was also fighting against the Aerogators.</description>
<picture>58531.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="24761" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<name>DCAM-00 Granzon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>58532.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="24762" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<name>DCAM-004 Lion</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>58533.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="24763" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<name>DCAM-05 Barrelion</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>58534.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="24765" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<name>DCAM-006 Guarlion</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>58536.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="24769" type="appears in" update="2010-11-05">
<name>Kenzou Kobayashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>58540.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39" picture="16629.jpg">Mugihito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24771" type="appears in" update="2010-11-05">
<rating votes="4">5.54</rating>
<name>Tsugumi Takakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>58543.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30061" picture="156859.jpg">Hasegawa Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24772" type="appears in" update="2011-05-13">
<rating votes="4">5.54</rating>
<name>Sleigh Presty</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71485.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="290" picture="24139.jpg">Nagasawa Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24773" type="appears in" update="2010-11-05">
<name>TYPE-82 Government</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>58545.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="24774" type="appears in" update="2010-11-05">
<name>Sakae Takanaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>58546.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1406" picture="18432.jpg">Suzuki Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24775" type="appears in" update="2010-11-05">
<name>Space Noah Class Ship Number 01 Shirugane</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>58547.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="24777" type="appears in" update="2011-05-13">
<name>PTX-006 (L) Wildrauptier</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>58549.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="25012" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-13">
<rating votes="6">5.63</rating>
<name>Shine Hausen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is a young princess that has precognitive powers. Adler had targeted her because he wanted to use her powers in order to gather data for his new School project, and the Game System. During the attack on the capital, Adler had used her to control the Valsion Kai`s game system, however she was saved by the Hagane and Hiryuu.</description>
<picture>71483.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12647" picture="42727.jpg">Kaihara Reina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25013" type="appears in" update="2010-11-11">
<name>Joyce Ledhal</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59139.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6082" picture="222919.jpg">Hirano Toshitaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25039" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-11-13">
<name>AGX-04 Fuleh</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The Aerogators` combat mother ship. It`s a very large ship, with it`s total length being equal to the Hagane`s. It stores many Megillot all along its sides. It`s hard to find since it is equipped with a special space navigation device that hides its position. The serial number given to it from the Earth Forces is AGX-04, and its recognition code is "Flower."</description>
<picture>59222.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="25044" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-04-07">
<name>AGX-06 Neviim</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>At the close of the Divine Wars, the EFF would not have much time to rest. An abnormal gravity distortion at the fifth Lagrange point would signal the appearance of the Neviim Battlestation, the central piece for a Ze-Balmary invasion force. Giving it the codename AGX-06 White Star, the EFF forces would scramble to form an attack plan against this strange new threat. At the same time, Neviim would launch countless attack forces made up not only of the Megillot, but also of more powerful humanoid machines only previously seen by mankind in the form of data contained within Meteor Three.
The actual size of the White Star is 40 kilometers in diameter and it effectively appears as Earth`s artificial second moon. Even after the Aerogator conflict, the White Star would remain, and prove a critical role in future wars.</description>
<picture>59220.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="25181" type="appears in" update="2010-11-20">
<name>EG-X Soulgain</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>It was developed by Tesla Leicht Institute in another world. It`s nicknamed "Mustache Man" because of the face armor that resembles a mustache.
The Soulgain is a powerful Super Robot that uses the life energy of its pilot as a source of power to unleash vicious attacks. It`s equipped with the Direct Feedback System, which allows the pilot to control it using his own movements. It has excellent combat abilities, and is oftenly capable of destroying its enemies within one blow.
It was first seen fighting the Aerogators during Operation SRW, by Guilliam Yeager, but it disappeared soon after. It was badly damaged, and couldn`t be repaired until the rest of the Shadow Mirror forces arrived.
The Soulgain is possibly a customized Earthgain.</description>
<picture>59554.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="25182" type="appears in" update="2010-11-20">
<name>RTX-010-1~3 Huckebein MK-II</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>It`s a PT that was co-developed by Mao Industries, and uses the same nuclear fusion reactor that is found in the 009. There were three units created, and they are equipped with the G Impact Cannon, and the Gravicon (Gravity Controller) system which uses EOT. It`s capable of spreading a gravitational field in front of it due to the Gravicon system, which allows the gravity wall to block the enemy`s attack. It`s the first unit to be equipped with the T-Link System.
In addition, the Huckebein MK-II`s are brother units to the R series since knowledge used to make the R machines were used on them.
The first unit was used by Brooklyn Luckfield. The second was damaged during a battle with the UCC, but is later repaired into the Huckebein Trombe. The third went missing during the war.</description>
<picture>59555.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="25183" type="appears in" update="2010-11-20">
<name>Stork</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>59556.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="25184" type="appears in" update="2010-11-20">
<name>SMSC AngelG</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>It`s a mysterious Super Robot that is in the shape of an armored female with wings. It`s capable of shooting spear and arrow shaped projectiles, and its sword resembles that of a slender sword used by western knights. Its power source and armor materials remain a mystery, as well as many other things regarding the Angelg`s technical information.
Lamia Loveless is the only one that is able to pilot it due to the controls being set only for her. Isurugi Heavy Industries claim this unit to be a next generation machine for the Earth Federation Army, but that`s not the truth. It actually came from the Shadow Mirror`s world, along with its pilot, Lamia, who is W17 of the W-Series androids.
Due to its similarities in looks and model number, the Angelg is possibly a customized Simurgh S.</description>
<picture>59557.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="25187" type="appears in" update="2010-11-20">
<name>TG-1 Koouki</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>It was discovered at an ancient Chinese ruins site during the 19th century. This unit represents one of the four super mechanical gods known as the fierce tiger. It has the form of the white tiger, Byakko.
For the sake of convenience, it was given the model designation TG-1.</description>
<picture>59561.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="25189" type="appears in" update="2010-11-20">
<name>DR-1 Ryuouki</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>It was discovered at an ancient Chinese ruins site during the 19th century. This unit represents one of the four super mechanical gods known as the invincible dragon. It has the ability to fold its wings so that it can fight in under water combat.
For the sake of convenience, it was given the model designation DR-1.</description>
<picture>59563.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="25194" type="appears in" update="2010-11-20">
<name>PTX-014-1~3 R-Blade</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>It`s the first machine in the mass produced series of the R-1, the Arblade, that Mao Industries developed. Its performance is high, though the transformation mechanism, the T-Link system, and all other special features that the R-1 has have been omitted. It`s not counted as one of the R series, and the plans to mass produce this unit are already in planning thanks to this prototypes data.</description>
<picture>59567.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="25195" type="appears in" update="2010-11-20">
<name>PTX-016-R Wildfalken R</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>This experimental machine, which was created by Mao Industries, is the sucessor of the Weissritter. It`s equipped with a Tesla Drive and features top class mobility for a PT.
Its main weapons are the Ochstan Rifles, which use the ball cartridge and energy beam properly. It works well with the Wildwuerger for high speed combo attacks.
It was siezed from the EF by Seolla Schweitzer, who belonged to the DC remnants.</description>
<picture>59568.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="25197" type="appears in" update="2010-11-20">
<name>Killer Whale</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>It`s a nuclear powered submarine that is used by the DC.</description>
<picture>59569.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="25201" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-20">
<name>Lee Linjun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>29 years old. He`s a former Captain in the EFA. He graduated with top scores in his class, and has treated Tetsuya with disrespect since their school days. He has only his job on his mind, and will do anything to succeed his mission, even if it makes him look heartless.
His family died during the L5 Campaign due to Ingram`s betrayl. This caused him to grow bitter, making him eventually join the Shadow Mirror forces due to a similar belief in ideals, in addition to him wanting revenge against the Hagane`s forces. During Operation Plantagenet he dealt a devasting blow to the Hagane, killing Daitetsu in the process.
During the battle near the White Star, he was defeated by Tetsuya. Although his ship was badly damaged, he did not die. His current whereabouts are unknown.</description>
<picture>59570.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="389" picture="56097.jpg">Okano Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25203" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-13">
<name>Kenneth Garret</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71481.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6942" picture="41078.jpg">Takaoka Binbin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25204" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-13">
<name>Archibald Grims</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>34 years old. He serves as a Neue DC soldier, and his ranking is Lieutenant Colonel. He comes from an old aristocratic background, and appears to have a nice look to him, though he`s really rather cruel. He was the main cause of the Elpis Event. He has a strong hatred for the Choukijin, since they were the cause of his clans fall. He betrays his superior officer, Van, and kills him. He joins forces with the Shadow Mirror forces afterwards. His final battle took place inside of the Earth Cradle, and he piloted an Ashsaber. Rai and Elzam cooperate with eachother, and attack him at the same time, causing him to be driven into a corner. He had no chance of escaping, and was then killed by a bomb.</description>
<picture>59573.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="374" picture="17220.jpg">Yamazaki Takumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25205" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-13">
<name>Yuuki Jegunan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>18 years old. He worked as part of the DC remnants, and his ranking is Second Lieutenant. He`s calm, and is always thinking clearly. He also acts like a gentleman. His sense of justice is strong, and he dislikes seeing the weak getting bullied, which gets him into several disagreements with his superior, Archibald Grims. He considers Bullet his rival, though he comes to understand him during their many battles with eachother, and he later joins him.
He enjoys astronomy and tea. Though he`s usually quiet, he gets quite talkative once someone brings up those subjects. He has a very specific way he likes his tea, and always drinks it during the same time every day.
He fought against an Aerogators unit that attacked San Diego during the L5 Campaign.</description>
<picture>59574.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="231" picture="23486.jpg">Madono Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25208" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-13">
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<name>Rilcarla Borgnine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>18 years old. She worked as part of the DC remnants, and her ranking is Second Lieutenant. She`s a very passionate girl, and is slightly masculine. Since she`s very nice to her companions, she usually ends up helping them with their problems.
She`s a optimistic, though she is troubled by things from her past. She was born in San Diego, and dreamed of entering the entertainment business with her singing and dancing skills. She lost her family during the L5 Campaign, when the Aerogators attacked her hometown.
After those events, she joined Yuuki Jegunan, and fought as part of the DC remnants in order to get revenge on those that killed her family.
Her hobbies include writing song lyrics, and watching romantic movies.</description>
<picture>59575.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1682" picture="41033.jpg">Matsumoto Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25209" type="appears in" update="2011-05-13">
<name>Graien Grusman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71518.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1683" picture="223030.jpg">Kanemitsu Nobuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25210" type="appears in" update="2011-05-13">
<name>Bryan Midokrid</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71519.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27" picture="26123.jpg">Hayami Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25211" type="appears in" update="2010-11-20">
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<name>Eri Anzai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59580.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="627" picture="170955.jpg">Saitou Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25212" type="appears in" update="2011-05-13">
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<name>Mitsuko Isurugi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She`s the new president of Isurugi Heavy Industries, and is Renji Isurugi`s daughter. Contrary to her gentle appearance, she does many things to promote war, so that her company will profit from it.
She took over Project TD, and protected it because she felt that they were needed as weapons. She secretly worked with the Shadow Mirror and Neue DC forces under the codename "Rose."</description>
<picture>71520.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6305" picture="223494.jpg">Takaguchi Yukiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25213" type="appears in" update="2011-05-13">
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<name>Echidna Iisakki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She`s part of the W series created by Lemon, and her designation is W16. She dies while protecting Axel and his Soulgain during the Shadow Mirror`s attempt at defending Neviim. Her orders from Lemon were carried out to the very end, though it appears as if that is what she wanted to do on her own.</description>
<picture>71508.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3128" picture="24744.jpg">Suzuki Mariko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25214" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-20">
<rating votes="3">4.43</rating>
<name>Azuki Sawa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59584.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="539" picture="228668.jpg">Aizawa Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25215" type="appears in" update="2010-11-20">
<name>Cuervo Sero</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aguila`s subordinate. He used to know Radha Bairaban from Mao Industries. He disliked Aguila`s way of handling the School children, so he tried being nice to them, and gave them names. He was well liked by them.
He died during the attempted self-restoration of the Earth Cradle. He asked for Radha to forgive him for betraying her, and for what he did to Ouka and the others.</description>
<picture>59585.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25216" type="appears in" update="2010-11-20">
<name>Eagreat Fehu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He`s a DC scientist. He`s the creator of School, and one of the chosen few selected for the Earth Cradle. He created the Machinery Children in an attempt at creating a more advanced human, and had them act as guardians for the Earth Cradle.
During the decisive battle at the Earth Cradle, he piloted a Bergelmir, though Wodan and his Thrudgelmir defeated him by self destructing.</description>
<picture>59586.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25217" type="appears in" update="2010-11-20">
<name>Ban Ba Chun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59587.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="282" picture="223615.jpg">Houki Katsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25218" type="appears in" update="2011-05-13">
<name>Wodan Ymir</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He`s a masked man of mystery, and has the voice and personality of Zengar Zonbolt. He calls himself "The Sword of Magus." It`s revealed that he`s part of the W Number series, and his codename is W15. He differs from the others in the series because of the fact that they copied Zengar`s personality completely, and made him devoted to nothing but protecting the Earth Cradle and Magus.
He and Zengar have their final showdown inside of the Earth Cradle, which results in his loss. In the end, he died in a suicide attack while protecting Sophia from Dr. Egret.</description>
<picture>71507.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="338" picture="17174.jpg">Ono Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25219" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-13">
<name>Vindel Mauser</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He`s the leader of the special group known as the Shadow Mirror, and his ranking is a Colonel.</description>
<picture>71505.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="469" picture="17418.jpg">Umezu Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25220" type="appears in" update="2013-07-13">
<name>Philio Presty</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60869.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="31" picture="65365.jpg">Ueda Youji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25221" type="appears in" update="2010-11-20">
<name>Rishu Tougou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>66 years old. He`s an advisor for the Tesla Leich laboratory. He`s a master of Jigen-Ryuu, and teaches both Zengar and Bullet. He also assisted in the development of the Grungust series` swords, and in producing the motion data for them. Though he`s very strict concerning matters of the sword, he`s usually a good-natured man. He assists Zengar and Elzam in the stealing of the Daizengar and Aussenseiter. His skills with a sword are so great, that he`s able to cut bullets into two.</description>
<picture>59592.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2279" picture="23207.jpg">Satou Masaharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25222" type="appears in" update="2010-11-20">
<name>Thrudgelmir</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>It`s the result of the Grungust Type-3 being transformed by Machine Cells. It`s capable of healing minor damage instantly because of it.
It`s equipped with the Drill Boost Knuckle and the Zankantou.</description>
<picture>59594.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="32241" type="appears in" update="2011-05-13">
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<name>Ring Mao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71486.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="187" picture="17002.jpg">Ogata Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32250" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-13">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Lemon Browning</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71506.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1870" picture="186893.jpg">Mizutani Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32251" type="appears in" update="2011-05-13">
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<name>Agiha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71510.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="82" picture="216596.jpg">Asakawa Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32258" type="appears in" update="2011-05-13">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Ainst Arufimi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71517.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1870" picture="186893.jpg">Mizutani Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32261" type="appears in" update="2011-05-13">
<name>RPT-005 Wildschwein</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>71521.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="32262" type="appears in" update="2011-05-13">
<name>PTX-EXAMB Huckebein Boxer</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>71523.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="32263" type="appears in" update="2011-05-13">
<name>PTX-EXAMG Huckebein Gunner</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>71524.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="32264" type="appears in" update="2011-05-13">
<name>PTX-EX Exbein</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>71525.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="32265" type="appears in" update="2011-05-13">
<name>PTX-001 Gespenst R</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>71526.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="32266" type="appears in" update="2011-05-13">
<name>RPT-007 Gespenst MK-II</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>71527.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="32267" type="appears in" update="2011-05-13">
<name>XAM-007S Fairlion</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>71528.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="32268" type="appears in" update="2011-05-13">
<name>XRAM-006VC Sieguarlion</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>This is a remodeled version of Leona`s Guarlion Custom that was designed by Tasuku Shinguji. The lastest Personal Trooper data was used in its development, and it features the latest technology, such as a Tesla Drive to help increase its performance. It also has the T-LINK System installed.</description>
<picture>71529.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="32269" type="appears in" update="2011-05-13">
<name>DCSMH-02R Valsione R</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>It`s the original Valsione after being repaired in La Gias, and being upgraded with the help of their alchemy. It had some minor changes in weapons, and an overall boost in perfomance due to the new upgrades.</description>
<picture>71530.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="32270" type="appears in" update="2011-05-13">
<name>XAM-007G Fairlion</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>71531.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="32271" type="appears in" update="2011-05-13">
<name>ASK-G03C Rapiecage</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>It`s a custom variation of the Ashsaber, and was developed within the Earth Cradle. It was created using data gathered from the ATX Plan units, such as Alt Eisen, Weissritter, Wild Wuerger, and Wild Falken, in addition to using parts borrowed from the Randgrith. It`s also equipped with the GEIM System.</description>
<picture>71532.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="32272" type="appears in" update="2011-05-13">
<name>YSAM-009-01 Gravilion</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>71533.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="121566" update="2010-08-29">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">赤い衝撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Red Impact</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akai Shougeki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121944" update="2010-09-07">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122848" update="2010-10-03">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">未知なる声</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unknown Voice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Michinaru Koe</title>
</episode>
<episode id="123685" update="2011-06-06">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-10-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">DCの名の下に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In The Name Of DC</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">DC no Na no Moto ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="123686" update="2010-10-07">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絆と約束</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bonds And Promises</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kizuna to Yakusoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="123687" update="2010-10-07">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">背負った十字</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Cross Borne</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seotta Juuji</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124181" update="2011-03-23">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124182" update="2010-10-16">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124731" update="2011-06-06">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">桜花幻影</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cherry Blossom Phantom</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ouka Gen`ei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125048" update="2010-11-07">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒い潜入者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Black Infiltrator</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuroi Sennyuusha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125213" update="2010-11-14">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">凶鳥の眷属</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Servants of the Dark Bird</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyouchou no Kenzoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125391" update="2010-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">インスペクター</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inspector</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inspector</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125694" update="2010-12-02">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">月下に妖精は舞う</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Fairy Dances in the Moonlight</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekka ni Yousei wa Mau</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125699" update="2010-12-03">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-12-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハルパーの鎌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Harpe Sickle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Harpe no Kama</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126034" update="2010-12-10">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-12-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シャドウミラー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shadow Mirror</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shadow Mirror</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126258" update="2010-12-18">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">楽園からの追放者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Exiles From Paradise</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rakuen kara no Tsuihousha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126428" update="2010-12-26">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">汚れのないその瞳(め)で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">With Those Pure Eyes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kegare no nai Sono Me de</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126841" update="2011-01-11">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-02-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">誘う鬼火</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Inviting Fires of Demons</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sasou Onibi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126842" update="2011-01-11">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-01-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鋼の咆哮</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Steel Cry</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hagane no Houkou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126843" update="2011-01-11">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オンリー・ワン・クラッシュ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Only One Crash</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Only One Crash</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126844" update="2011-01-11">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-01-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">武神装攻(ぶしんそうこう)ダイゼンガー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">War God`s Armament "DyGenGuar"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bushin Soukou DyGenGuar</title>
</episode>
<episode id="127981" update="2011-02-06">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-02-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">龍虎王顕現</title>
<title xml:lang="en">RyuKohOh Appears</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryuuko Ou Kengen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128089" update="2011-02-10">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">眠れ, 地の底で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rest in the Cradle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nemure, Chi no Soko de</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128090" update="2011-02-10">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-02-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">若き猛禽</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Young Raptor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakaki Moukin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128525" update="2011-03-23">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-01-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128536" update="2011-03-05">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-03-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">散りぬべき時知りてこそ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Is by Knowing the Time to Fall</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chirinubeki Toki Shirite koso</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128537" update="2011-03-05">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-03-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">堕天使の心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Heart of a Fallen Angel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Datenshi no Kokoro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128661" update="2011-03-10">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">貫け, 奴よりも速く</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pierce Faster than He</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuranuke, Yatsu yori mo Hayaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128662" update="2011-03-10">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-03-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かつて在りしもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What Once Was</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Katsute Arishi Mono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128663" update="2011-03-10">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-03-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">白き魔星(ませい)へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the White Hellstar</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiroki Masei e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128961" update="2011-03-23">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-01-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128962" update="2011-03-23">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-03-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156013" update="2013-11-16">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">ep. 26 Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
