<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7723" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-07-23</startdate>
<enddate>2010-12-17</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Iron Man</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">Ironman</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Железный Человек</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Geležinis Žmogus</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Железия Човек</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Залізна людина</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">アイアンマン</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Homem de Ferro</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Vasember</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="official">Demir Adam</title>
<title xml:lang="vi" type="official">Người Sắt</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">钢铁侠</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7384" type="Same Setting">Wolverine</anime>
<anime id="8162" type="Same Setting">Blade</anime>
<anime id="8058" type="Same Setting">X-Men</anime>
<anime id="9468" type="Other">Iron Man: Rise of Technovore</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="89734">I dont understand the low ratings for this anime. I enjoyed watching it, still i`d say its only for fans. But if you are just into some action and some cool music this anime will be a good time killer for you!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="356469">Doesn`t have a good storyline but packed a good action. Just watch and you will see what i mean.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.animax.co.jp/special/marvelanime/ironman/</url>
<creators>
<name id="23423" type="Story Composition">Warren Ellis</name>
<name id="8071" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kikuchi Ai</name>
<name id="22557" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kim Dong-Sik</name>
<name id="6655" type="Chief Animation Direction">Umehara Takahiro</name>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="8583" type="Original Work">Marvel Comics</name>
<name id="4790" type="Direction">Satou Yuuzou</name>
<name id="6655" type="Character Design">Umehara Takahiro</name>
<name id="8259" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takada Haruhito</name>
<name id="3719" type="Series Composition">Inoue Toshiki</name>
<name id="4642" type="Music">Takahashi Tetsuya</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch21266 [Tony Stark], CEO of a large weapons manufacturer, physicist, engineer, and brilliant inventor, is wounded by shrapnel from one of his own weapons. While held captive by terrorists, he develops the http://anidb.net/ch21282 [Iron Man Suit] and escapes. From that day on, he vows not to waste his second chance at life and to change the world for the better. For that purpose, he comes to Japan.
In Lab 23 in Japan, great strides have been taken to develop, and build, a unique power station which does not run on fossil fuels, the Arc Station. Stark intends to join this project, and, for that, he is ready to announce his retirement as Iron Man. At the same time, he will also announce the Mass-produced Iron Men, to which he will pass on his duties. However, during the ceremonies, Stark is suddenly attacked by combat mecha belonging to an organization known as Zodiac.
~ translated and adapted from official site by Cranston 
Note: The first episode was aired at Comic-con 2010 in San Diego on July 23, 2010.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="715">2.69</permanent>
<temporary count="723">5.44</temporary>
<review count="1">2.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>53873.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11786</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6875</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4690</identifier>
<identifier>culfqu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.animax.co.jp/special/marvelanime/ironman/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Marvel_Anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>アイアンマン_(2010年のアニメ)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2047</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>337770</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12529</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="29" parentid="6234" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-18">
<name>Western zodiac</name>
<picurl>161118.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2643" parentid="2638" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>power suit</name>
<description>Power Suits are similar to Piloted Robots which are controlled from inside the robot except that Power Suits tend to be more directly tied to how the character moves and they are usually not as big as Piloted Robots can be. They are still mechanical and shouldn`t be confused with plug suits.</description>
<picurl>222235.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3315" parentid="2623" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-28">
<name>superhero</name>
<description>In modern popular fiction, a superhero is a type of costumed heroic character who possesses supernatural or superhuman powers and who is dedicated to fighting crime, protecting the public, and usually battling supervillains. A female superhero is sometimes called a superheroine. Fiction centered on such characters, especially in American comic books since the 1930s, is known as superhero fiction.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3430" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-01-04">
<name>Western comics</name>
<description>This anime is based on a western comic book.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4424" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>American derived</name>
<description>A work which was created as a continuation/remake of an American based franchise or cartoon series. These works are completely Japan original, but which lack roots within Japanese media.
See also: http://anidb.net/t3714 [cartoon remake]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5773" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-14">
<name>secret organisation</name>
<description>A secret organisation or secret society is an organisation whose activities and inner functioning are concealed from non-members. The society may or may not attempt to conceal its existence itself. Examples of historical and existing secret societies include Freemasonry, the Knights Templar, the Rosicrucians, Skull and Bones, the Thule Society, and the Illuminati.</description>
<picurl>192876.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6234" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>motifs</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="21266" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="10">6.38</rating>
<name>Tony Stark</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Born Anthony Edward Stark, and usually called Tony, he is an industrialist playboy and ingenious engineer who suffers a severe heart injury during a kidnapping in which his captors attempt to force him to build a weapon of mass destruction. He instead creates a powered suit of armour to save his life and escape captivity. He later uses the suit to protect the world as Iron Man. Through his multinational corporation, Stark Industries, Tony created military weapons and his own metal suit is laden with technological devices that enable him to fight crime. Initially, Iron Man was a vehicle for Stan Lee to explore Cold War themes, particularly the role of American technology and business in the fight against communism. Subsequent re-imaginings of Iron Man have gradually removed the Cold War themes, replacing them with more contemporary concerns such as corporate crime and terrorism.</description>
<picture>54329.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21267" type="main character in" update="2010-09-03">
<rating votes="8">9.11</rating>
<name>Pepper Potts</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pepper, originally in the secretarial pool, gets her job by fixing an accounting mistake made by Stark himself.</description>
<picture>54331.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="317" picture="17155.jpg">Oka Hiroe</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21268" type="main character in" update="2010-09-03">
<rating votes="2">8.59</rating>
<name>Oota Nanami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54337.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21269" type="main character in" update="2010-09-03">
<rating votes="2">7.46</rating>
<name>Tanaka Chika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54333.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="442" picture="187043.jpg">Honda Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21270" type="main character in" update="2010-09-03">
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<name>Kuroda Boueidaijin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54334.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21282" type="main character in" update="2010-10-02">
<rating votes="11">5.50</rating>
<name>Iron Man</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Iron Man is a fictional superhero who appears in comic books published by Marvel Comics. The character debuted in Tales of Suspense #39 (March 1963), and was created by writer-editor Stan Lee, scripter Larry Lieber, and artists Don Heck and Jack Kirby.</description>
<picture>54325.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="21290" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-01">
<name>Nomura Desk</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54339.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4742" picture="54426.jpg">Fukumatsu Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21291" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-01">
<name>Masuda Ichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54340.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="78" picture="16686.jpg">Shimura Tomoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21292" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-02">
<rating votes="1">5.71</rating>
<name>Iron Man Dio</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54341.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="24888" type="appears in" update="2011-03-01">
<rating votes="27">4.10</rating>
<name>Logan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60101.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67196" type="appears in" update="2014-05-05">
<name>Zodiac</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="67294" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-08">
<rating votes="1">1.86</rating>
<name>Doctor Ho Yinsen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155315.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="323" picture="211661.jpg">Hirata Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67295" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-08">
<name>Sakurai Nagato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155316.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3161" picture="69050.jpg">Yamanoi Jin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67391" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-11">
<rating votes="1">8.23</rating>
<name>Ramon Zero</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155473.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="121979" update="2018-08-12">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="10">2.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アイアンマン, 来日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Iron Man Comes to Japan</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Geležinis Žmogus atvyksta į Japonija</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iron Man, Rainichi</title>
<summary>Tony Stark travels to Japan to supervise the construction of a new arc power station and unveil the new mass-production version of the Iron Man suit - Iron Man Dio.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="122827" update="2018-08-12">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-10-08</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">消えた核を追え</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chase the Missing Nuke!</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Surasti dingusi branduolinį kurą</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kieta Kaku o Oe</title>
<summary>A shipment of plutonium is stolen, leading Tony to be accused of smuggling nuclear materials into Japan and having to give a statement before the Diet of Japan. In order to get away from the press, Tony hitches a ride with a reporter he had previously met, Nanami Ōta. Whilst investigating the ship where the plutonium was being transported, Iron Man encounters another Zodiac warrior, Cancer. Tony locates the culprits and drives them towards a security checkpoint, but he is blocked off by a self-proclaimed good samaritan named Nagato Sakurai. Nanami mixes her camera with the plutonium the culprits were carrying and is chased by an armored tank equipped with stealth camouflage. After Sakurai helps Iron Man deal with the tank, Iron Man faces off against Cancer again and defeats him. Tony`s name is cleared and Nanami was able to write a good article.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="122830" update="2018-08-12">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-10-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アークステーション, 感染</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Arc Station Infection</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Arktinės jėgainės užkratas</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arc Station, Kansen</title>
<summary>An epidemic in which people`s bodily fluids are turning blue spreads across Tokyo, and the JSDF suspects that the Arc Station is causing it and puts Tony under watch. He is approached by Sakurai who informs him that a satellite has been taken over by a Zodiac warrior, which is causing the radiation. Meanwhile, Nanami also gets sick from the radiation. Using an experimental coating to protect him from the radiation, Iron Man launches into space with the help of Sakurai to face the Zodiac. However, he is at a disadvantage in zero gravity and is taken inside where he is exposed to high radiation. However, Iron Man manages to send the radiation data back to Earth so they can cure the victims, and break free from the Zodiac and destroy it.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="122831" update="2018-08-12">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-10-22</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">再会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reunion</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Susitikimas</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikai</title>
<summary>Tony recalls five years ago when he was attacked and captured by terrorists, receiving life threatening injuries. Agreeing to make weapons for the terrorist, he was saved by fellow prisoner Ho Yinsen who installed his magnetic chest plate to keep him alive and helped him realize the deaths his weapons manufacturing has caused. This led to the creation of the mini arc-reactor and, subsequently, Iron Man, but Yinsen sacrificed himself to give Tony a chance to escape. Meanwhile in the present, a race driver named Kawashima, who had broken his legs and desires to drive again, is given cybernetic enhancements on the condition that he kill Tony. When Tony is targeted, he is saved by the sudden appearance of James "Logan" Howlett, who is in Japan investigating A.I.M. Iron Man later fights against Kawashima, who controls the Zodiac warrior Taurus but is soon taken over by it. With the help of Logan, Iron Man defeats Taurus and rescues Kawashima, but soon comes face to face with Dio and is shocked to find what appears to be Yinsen inside.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="122832" update="2018-08-12">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-10-15</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蘇るプロジェクト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Project, Revived!</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Projektas atnaujintas!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yomigaeru Project</title>
<summary>Strange tornadoes are appearing in Tokyo, targeting and killing two professors. When another tornado attacks a military base, Iron Man enters it and finds the cause, another Zodiac warrior who easily defeats him. Meanwhile, Nanami attends a meeting with Chika Tanaka, Tony`s co-worker, and another Professor, Sakamoto, who talk about the Tesla Project, an anti-natural disaster machine worked on by them and the other professors, before they themselves are attacked by the tornado. Tony tries to help some survivors, but is met with harsh criticism from the rescue team. As Chika and Nanami research the Tesla Project, they soon learn that Sakamoto is the man responsible for selling the Tesla research to the Zodiac, though thanks to Nanami they manage to escape. With the armor repaired, Iron Man reenters the tornado and defeats the Zodiac with an EMP cannon.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="122833" update="2010-10-17">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2010-07-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122834" update="2010-10-02">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-07-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122861" update="2010-10-03">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124748" update="2018-08-12">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-05</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">電脳戦線</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Electronic Warfare</title>
<title xml:lang="lt">Elektroninis karas</title>
<summary>As Tony tries to learn more about the whereabouts of Yinsen, Laboratory #23 is attacked by a virus which causes the robotic cleaners to go berserk and greatly reduces the temperature in the complex. Tony and Chika try to shut out the virus with a firewall, but this allows the virus to infect computers around the city and even takes over some fighter jets. In order to lure the culprit out and protect the Arc Station, Tony takes the virus into the Iron Man armor in order to fight it. Hearing Tony`s promise to protect people, the culprit, a boy named Sho who was approached by Zodiac, is reminded of his promise to his late mother to protect others and destroys the virus. As Iron Man returns, he is attacked by more Zodiac mechs but is saved by someone piloting a new armor.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="125058" update="2018-08-12">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">脱出</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Escape</title>
<summary>Whilst wondering about the mysterious new armor, Tony and Chika are kidnapped. Nanami spots Tony`s car and attempts to follow it, but they are stopped by a Zodiac. Tony and Chika awake to find themselves on a remote island, and Tony`s arc reactor is missing. They are then approached by Yinsen, who reveals himself to be a member of Zodiac and tells Tony he has 24 hours of pacemaker power to decide whether to join Zodiac or not. Tony and Chika attempt to use the various scrap on the island to find a method of escape, but are thwarted at every opportunity. They eventually manage to evade him by using a hologram, and manage to build a flare to alert Sakurai, who had received some information from Nanami. Impressed by him not using weapons, Yinsen returns the arc reactor before escaping. As they wait for rescue, Tony and Chika kiss each other.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="125208" update="2018-08-12">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-19</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">少女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoujo</title>
<summary>While being curious about why Chika is turning down his date requests, Tony encounters a telekinetic girl named Aki who claims to have escaped from Zodiac and is asking for protection. While Tony has trouble with Aki wrecking his lab, and his relationships, he asks Nanami to research her which leads her to an orphanage. They learn that her parents died two years ago and she was adopted by a strange group six months ago. Tony later learns from Aki that her parents died when Aki`s powers went out of control and caused their plane to crash. Later, Sakurai takes them both into custody, explaining Zodiac were planning to use her powers for a weapon. Just then, they are attacked by the Zodiac warrior Virgo. After admitting Aki into Lab #23, Iron Man goes to battle Virgo, but soon learns it is synchronized with Aki`s brainwaves, meaning destroying it would kill Aki. As Iron Man tries to prevent Sakurai from destroying Virgo, it incorporates Aki and produces a destructive field. Iron Man breaks through the shield to rescue Aki and shut down Virgo. As a result, Aki loses both her powers and her memories but is much happier.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="125376" update="2018-08-12">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-12-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鋼鉄の意志</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Iron Will</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koutetsu no Ishi</title>
<summary>Yinsen forces Chika to work on the arc reactor, before making his demands for the dissolution of the Armed Forces and National Diet. Nanami attempts to escape the hostage situation but is caught and thrown into a storage room. Tony is rescued by Sakurai and tries to contact Chika, but she is caught by Yinsen and throw into storage with Nanami. Meanwhile, the Defense Secretary Kuroda offers to be held captive in place of the hostages. As Chika and Nanami go through an air duct and retrieve Tony`s armor, Tony and Sakurai are attacked by the Zodiac Saggitarius. Nanami gets the armor to Tony so he can defeat Sagittarius, before facing off against Yinsen. Just as Iron Man starts to get the upper hand when Yinsen hesitates attacking in front of Chika, someone overrides the Sigmas and attacks them both, with Yinsen getting critically wounded. Yinsen warns Tony that Zodiac`s plan has just started.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="125377" update="2018-08-12">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-11-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">VSアイアンマン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">VS Iron Man</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">VS Iron Man</title>
<summary>Yinsen recalls when he was saved from being shot by terrorists by a woman named Sandra. Meanwhile, Tony is nearly finished with his arc reactor, but Yinsen apprehends the shipment of plutonium needed to complete it using the Dio armor. Iron Man and the two battle before Yinsen escapes with the plutonium, leaving Iron Man to fight the Zodiac warrior Sagittarius, but he soon loses him. Yinsen then contacts Stark, telling him that the people who rescued him were killed by Stark Industries weaponry. The two once again fight for the plutonium, with Yinsen insisting that Tony has not changed. He reveals several models of Iron Man Sigma, which he created by reverse engineering Dio, which he uses to attack the arc station. Yinsen defeats Tony, takes him out of his armor and chucks him into a river.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="126035" update="2018-08-12">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-12-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒幕</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mastermind</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuromaku</title>
<summary>Although the hostage situation was brought to a close, Tony is suspected of having links to Zodiac and is arrested by the JSDF. Sakurai briefly takes him to his home, where he teaches him how to control his ego. Meanwhile, Chika is somehow controlled into overloading the Arc Station, which causes power outages in various facilities which are then taken over by Zodiac who then attack the National Diet. They then send a message saying they have taken control of the government and claim Tony is their ally. Kuroda orders Sakurai to kill Tony, but Tony escapes and learns about the power regulation from Chika, who tells him that power is being directed to Tokyo Bay before she is taken hostage. As Iron Man heads towards the location, he is attacked by Sakurai in Ramon Zero, but Tony manages to snap him out of it before they are attacked by another Zodiac warrior. Whilst Iron Man fights the Zodiac, Sakurai heads to the location and discovers Zodiac`s weapons factory, also learning their leader is Kuroda, who plans to rebuild Japan as a military nation. Sakurai destroys the factory but is killed by Kuroda using his Retetsu armor, managing to warn Tony before he dies.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="126061" update="2018-08-12">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">永遠の光</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Light in the Distance</title>
<summary>Kuroda enacts a coup d`etat and declares martial law over Japan. Meanwhile, Chika admits to Tony that she`s been having blackouts and has been controlled into altering the arc reactor, wanting to commit suicide for causing Tony`s suffering. Just then, Kuroda approaches them in his Retetsu armor and takes control of Chika, who had really been a Zodiac warrior, and has her attack Tony. As Tony tries to get Chika to believe in herself, she stabs herself to break free from Kuroda`s control. Tony leaves Chika in Nanami`s care whilst he goes to fight Kuroda, who was resentful due to his grandparents being killed in the Nagasaki bombing. Meanwhile, Chika decides to transfer her consciousness into the arc reactor program in order to take control of it and transfer its energy over to Iron Man. Iron Man manages to defeat Kuroda with the power provided, but Chika dies as a result of the transfer. A month later, the Arc Station is finally activated, providing clean energy for Japan.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
