<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7765" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2000-03-11</startdate>
<enddate>2000-03-11</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">The Doraemons: Dokidoki Kikansha Daibakusou!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Doki Doki Wildcat Engine</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ザ☆ドラえもんズ ドキドキ機関車大爆走!</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">The Doraemons: Aventuras en un tren</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Doraemon - Aventuras no Comboio</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1078" type="Parent Story">Doraemon (1979)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="4732" type="Original Work">Fujiko F. Fujio</name>
<name id="1603" type="Direction">Nishikiori Hiroshi</name>
<name id="5660" type="Music">Miyazaki Shinji</name>
<name id="1284" type="Work">Shin-Ei Animation</name>
<name id="745" type="Work">TV Asahi</name>
<name id="1082" type="Work">Shogakukan</name>
</creators>
<description>The evil professor Achimov steals an energy capsule from the power centre of the 22nd century. As a result, the whole city suffers a power outage. In order to save the city, the Doraemons take on the mission to deliver the only remaining energy capsule to the power centre and go there with the help of a girl named Robin who drives a steam locomotive.
Source: Japanese Wikipedia</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="18">4.27</permanent>
<temporary count="18">4.44</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>52315.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3931</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2633</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4250</identifier>
<identifier>rdprvy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Doki_Doki_Wildcat_Engine</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ザ☆ドラえもんズ_ドキドキ機関車大爆走!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>239059</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3866</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1846" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>kodomo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word kodomo refers to a children`s audience roughly for the ages 12 and younger. In Japanese, the word means simply "child", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="8456" type="main character in" update="2015-08-14">
<rating votes="868">7.63</rating>
<name>Doraemon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Doraemon is the titular robotic cat sent back in time by Sewashi to aid Nobita. He possesses a fourth-dimensional pocket from which he can acquire various kinds of futuristic tools, gadgets, and playthings from a future department store. Doraemon originally had ears but they were bitten off by a robotic mouse in the 22nd century. As a result, he developed a morbid fear of mice despite being a robotic cat. He also has the tendency to panic during emergencies, characterized by him frantically trying to pull out a very much-needed tool from his pocket, only to produce a huge assortment of unrelated household items.
Doraemon`s physical appearance changed as the manga progressed. At first, he was predominantly blue, with a blue tail, a white stomach, and flesh-coloured hands and feet. He also stooped, and had a body much larger than his head. In later issues, he sported a smaller body, white hands and feet, and a red tail--the appearance most identify him with today.
In "The Doraemons" story arc, it is revealed that Doraemon`s original paint color was yellow. After getting his ears gnawed off by a robot mouse, he slipped into depression on top of a tower, where he drank a potion labeled "sadness". As he wept, the yellow color washed off and his voice changed due to the potion.
Doraemon weighs 129.3 kg (285 lbs) and measures at 129.3 cm (4`3") tall. He is able to run at 129.3 km/h (80.3 mph) when scared and jump 129.3 m (424.2 ft) when threatened. His maximum power is 129.3 bhp. His wrist, head, and chest circumference are all 129.3 cm. His feet is 129.3 mm in diameter. He is manufactured on September 3, 2112 (12/9/3), at the Matsushiba Robot Factory. Doraemon is considered a substandard product because many of his robotic features (ie. radar whiskers and cat-calling bell) malfunctioned after production. One can turn off Doraemon by pulling his balloon tail.
Doraemon`s favourite food is dorayaki, a Japanese treat filled with red bean paste. Speculations led to dorayaki being the origin of his name. However, it was revealed in one of the manga chapters that his name originates from the Japanese word nora neko for "stray cat", and the -emon ending which is part of traditional Japanese names, as seen also in, for example, Ishikawa Goemon.
In the 2007 birthday episode, `MS-903` is used to call Doraemon by the factory owner where Doraemon is produced.
Doraemon usually uses the phrase "nanoda".</description>
<picture>2237.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="4729" picture="37796.jpg">Ooyama Nobuyo</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="120557" update="2010-08-01">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2000-03-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
