<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="777" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1989-07-15</startdate>
<enddate>1989-07-15</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kidou Keisatsu Patlabor</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">機動警察パトレイバー 劇場版</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Mobile Police Patlabor: The Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Patlabor Movie 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Kidou Keisatsu Patlabor Gekijouban</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">機動警察パトレイバー PATLABOR THE MOBILE POLICE</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Patlabor the Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Patlabor - The Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Patlabor 1</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Полиция будущего</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Patlabor - Mobile Police</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="official">פאטלייבור: הסרט ה-1</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="official">Patlaborai</title>
<title xml:lang="et" type="official">Patlabor</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Patlabor: La Película</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="395" type="Sequel">Kidou Keisatsu Patlabor 2 the Movie</anime>
<anime id="537" type="Alternative Setting">WXIII: Patlabor the Movie 3</anime>
<anime id="1518" type="Parent Story">Patlabor: Mobile Police</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="83" approval="3" total="8">Jin-Rou</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="533655">Another great movie directed by Mamoru Oshii. The animation style, character design and atmosphere is quite similar to Ghost in the Shell movie and Jin-Roh. If you liked any of those or Oshii in general then this is a must watch. Same goes for Patlabor fans.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.b-ch.com/cgi-bin/contents/ttl/det.cgi?ttl_c=175</url>
<creators>
<name id="730" type="Work">Studio Deen</name>
<name id="3008" type="Character Design">Takada Akemi</name>
<name id="131" type="Direction">Oshii Mamoru</name>
<name id="1946" type="Music">Kawai Kenji</name>
<name id="5264" type="Original Plan">Yuuki Masami</name>
<name id="5428" type="Original Work">Headgear</name>
</creators>
<description>At the top of a large structure in Tokyo Bay, a scientist walks to the edge and, despite the cries of onlookers, throws himself into the sea to his death. Weeks later, the Special Vehicle Division (SVD) has had little respite due to a recent rash of Labor malfunctions resulting in massive citywide destruction.
No one seems to know the cause of the malfunctions; the only hint points to a cover-up involving a military-class Labor going on a rampage — without a pilot. It is soon evident that a disaster of epic proportions is taking shape, and only http://anidb.net/ch9016 [Gotou], http://anidb.net/ch11745 [Shinobu], and the SVD can counter it. If they succeed, they will be heroes... but if they fail, they will be the most hated villains in history.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1401">7.27</permanent>
<temporary count="1405">7.53</temporary>
<review count="1">8.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>83834.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>191</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1095</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>676</identifier>
<identifier>mqbfyt</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.b-ch.com/cgi-bin/contents/ttl/det.cgi?ttl_c=175</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.productionig.com/contents/works_sp/26_/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Patlabor:_The_Movie</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>機動警察パトレイバー_the_Movie</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>574</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>107</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>90351</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2861" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>cyberpunk</name>
<description>Cyberpunk focuses on computers or information technology, usually coupled with some degree of breakdown in social order. The plot often centres on a conflict among hackers, artificial intelligences, and mega corporations, tending to be set within a near-future dystopian Earth.</description>
<picurl>211264.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4404" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-28">
<name>real robot</name>
<description>A smaller form of mecha with no special abilities. They are mostly used by deploying them in battle just like modern tanks. They can be mass produced and their pilots (usually military officers or soldiers) are (mostly) interchangeable. Tanks are often a threat to them and they are more easily destroyed than their bigger counterparts.</description>
<picurl>42787.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4667" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-20">
<name>hard science fiction</name>
<description>Hard science fiction is a category of http://anidb.net/t2846 [science fiction] characterised by an emphasis on scientific accuracy, technical detail, or both. The term is not defined precisely, and is often seen as an approximate way of describing works. Stories revolving around scientific and technical consistency were written as early as 1860s and 1870s; http://anidb.net/cr5973 [Jules Verne] is generally considered the creator of the genre. Although not always accurate in his scientific depictions, and though Verne himself denied writing as a scientist or seriously predicting machines and technology of the future, the attention to detail in his work became an inspiration for many future scientists and explorers.
Nowadays, the term http://anidb.net/t7086 [soft science fiction] is also often used to refer to science fiction stories which lack scientific focus or rigorous adherence to known science; the categorization "hard science fiction" thus represents a position on a broad continuum ranging from "softer" to "harder". There is a degree of flexibility in how far from "real science" a story can stray before it leaves the realm of hard science fiction; some authors scrupulously avoid such technology as faster-than-light travel, while others accept such notions but focus on realistically depicting the worlds that such a technology might make possible. In this view, a story`s scientific "hardness" is less a matter of the absolute accuracy of the science content than of the rigour and consistency with which the various ideas and possibilities are worked out. Furthermore, later discoveries do not necessarily invalidate the label of hard science fiction; the designation remains valid even when a crucial plot element is later discovered to be incorrect.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="9011" type="main character in" update="2013-08-10">
<rating votes="98">7.89</rating>
<name>Izumi Noa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Born in Tomakomai, Hokkaido in 1978, she is the pilot of the first Ingram in Unit 2 (first forward of Division 2). She loves Labors to the point of obsession, and nicknames her Ingram "Alphonse" after her deceased pet dog and cat. A dedicated police officer, very easy going and cheerful, she never loses her cool. That is unless somebody damages her beloved Alphonse. Character designer Akemi Takada says she named Noa after a sales woman from a securities company who visited her.</description>
<picture>141281.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3940" picture="54324.jpg">Tominaga Miina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9016" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-13">
<rating votes="185">9.09</rating>
<name>Gotou Kiichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gotou is the Captain of Unit 2 and was born in the Taito Ward in Tokyo. Although he may seem very laidback and even apathetic, he`s quite a strategist, and knows how to get the best out of his team even if it means tricking them. He has gained the reputation of being very sharp and rumour has it he was purposely sent out to the SV2 so he wouldn`t cause any trouble, which he still manages to do so anyway. Gotou is a heavy smoker, has athlete`s foot and can often be seen wearing traditional Japanese wooden sandals around the office. Character designer Takada Akemi based Gotou`s appearance on Japanese actor Nakagai Tatsuya`s physical appearance in the Kurosawa Akira film "High and Low".</description>
<picture>141450.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3383" picture="24325.jpg">Oobayashi Ryuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11745" type="main character in" update="2013-08-10">
<rating votes="50">7.31</rating>
<name>Nagumo Shinobu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shinobu is the Captain of Division 1 and was born in in Setagaya Ward in Tokyo. She is a professional, competent police officer. Basically the exact opposite of Captain Goto. She always keeps her mind on the job and never loses her cool. Often she talks back to her superiors when she disagrees with an order, and this is probably why she remains at the SV2 rather being promoted to another job more worthy of her skills. She is often slightly jealous of Division 2`s successes and the equipment they get, but she never really lets on.</description>
<picture>141267.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="571" picture="172734.jpg">Sakakibara Yoshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11746" type="main character in" update="2013-08-10">
<rating votes="49">7.51</rating>
<name>Shinohara Asuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Asuma was born in Maebashi in Gunma Prefecture and is the son of the owner of Shinohara Heavy Industries, the makers of the Ingram. So why is he a public servant? Apparently his father forced him into being one. As a member of Unit 2, he provides backup for Noa`s Ingram and is her partner. He can be quite short tempered and sometimes gives the impression he would rather be somewhere else. Still he`s a competent police officer.</description>
<picture>141268.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2583" picture="23188.jpg">Furukawa Toshio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11747" type="main character in" update="2013-08-10">
<rating votes="28">7.70</rating>
<name>Yamazaki Hiromi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Born on Ishigaki Island, Okinawa Prefecture, Hiromi is the quiet giant amongst the members of the SV2. Even though he looks rather intimidating, he`s quite gentle and hardly ever speaks. He tends the tomatoes in the greenhouse and looks after the henhouse at the SV2 in his spare time. His main duty in Division 2 is driving the first Labor carrier.</description>
<picture>141272.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2946" picture="23373.jpg">Gouri Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11748" type="main character in" update="2013-08-13">
<rating votes="29">7.03</rating>
<name>Oota Isao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Born in Kamaishi, Iwate Prefecture, Ota is the 2nd forward of Division 2. He`s a complete gun maniac and will almost always try to use force over all other options when solving a dispute. Though he`s reckless and violent, he`s an integral part of the team, and actually manages to end situations quicker than Noa.</description>
<picture>141440.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3312" picture="24691.jpg">Ikemizu Michihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11749" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-25">
<rating votes="89">8.89</rating>
<name>Kanuka Clancy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kanuka Clancy is a police officer on loan from the New York Police Department. She`s a Japanese-American born in Oahu, Hawaii. A competent officer who is skilled at jobs as varied as bomb disposal and anti-terrorism, she does everything by the book and is often disgusted by the tactics used by the SV2, where she acts as http://anidb.net/ch11748 [Oota]`s backup. Among the SV2, there is a rumour that the NYPD sent her to them because she was a problem officer.</description>
<picture>141269.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5008" picture="28621.jpg">Inoue You</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11751" type="main character in" update="2013-08-13">
<rating votes="15">7.71</rating>
<name>Shinshi Mikiyasu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shinshi is the driver for the second carrier. He was born Fujieda, Shizuoka Prefecture. He is a quite introverted man, but can become surprisingly violent if provoked enough. Shinshi is the only married member of the team.</description>
<picture>141444.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="281" picture="151723.jpg">Futamata Issei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11752" type="main character in" update="2013-08-13">
<rating votes="38">7.95</rating>
<name>Sakaki Seitarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakaki is the head mechanic of the SV2. His training was was in mechanics, and he doesn`t really understand the electronics and computers in the Labors. Even though he`s only the head mechanic he only seems to order a lot of the other staff around, including members of Division 2, and not do any of the `grunt` work. A very respected member of the SV2 (though some would say feared rather than respected).</description>
<picture>141441.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="416" picture="23206.jpg">Saka Osamu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11753" type="main character in" update="2013-08-13">
<rating votes="31">7.52</rating>
<name>Shiba Shigeo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shigeo or just plain Shige, is second in command of the mechanics at the SV2. He`s a man that is truly dedicated to his work, though sometimes he can go overboard. He`s a proud member of the SV2, and makes sure the Labors work perfectly. He will most likely take over from Sakaki when he retires.</description>
<picture>141442.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="541" picture="26117.jpg">Chiba Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11755" type="appears in" update="2009-09-15">
<rating votes="23">8.70</rating>
<name>AV-98 Ingram</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>A labor designed specifically for law enforcement by Shinohara Heavy Industries. The Ingram`s advanced design allows for more human-like movements. As a law enforcement labor, the Ingram is equipped with an anti-labor stun stick and a 37mm revolver cannon, but it can also carry a shotgun-like 90mm riot cannon. To facilitate transport to the field, each Ingram features its own transport trailer.</description>
<picture>35547.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="11765" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-10">
<rating votes="6">3.91</rating>
<name>Jitsuyama Tsuyoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jitsuyama is head of the Shinohara Labor factory. His career in mechanics began when he started a business up with Asuma`s father. To Asuma he is kind of like a substitute father and he often comes to him when he needs advice concerning Labors.</description>
<picture>141265.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3321" picture="228645.jpg">Tsujimura Mahito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11768" type="appears in" update="2009-09-15">
<rating votes="3">5.71</rating>
<name>ARL-99 Helldiver</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Devised as a Labor version of a paratrooper, this Labor is a much more slimmed down and manoeuvrable Labor than the AL-97 Atlas.</description>
<picture>35570.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="11828" type="appears in" update="2009-09-19">
<rating votes="5">5.61</rating>
<name>HL-98 Hercules 21</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Construction Labor who`s biggest claim to fame in Patlabor is being destroyed by Noa`s Ingram in three quick cuts during the opening animation of the Original OVA Series. It can also be used for underwater operations with the addition of optional air tanks.</description>
<picture>35854.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="9764" update="2005-04-30">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>1989-07-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9765" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>1989-07-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13357" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>100</length>
<airdate>1989-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
