<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="78" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2001-05-26</startdate>
<enddate>2001-05-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Metropolis</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="synonym">Ozamu Tesukas Metropolis</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Славімо Зіґґурат!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="synonym">大都會</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">大都会</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">メトロポリス</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Metropolis</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Robotic Angel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Metropolis</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Metropolis</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Метрополис</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Metropolis</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="official">Metropolis</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Metropolis</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Metrópolis</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Metropolis</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Metropolis</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="official">מטרופוליס</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Metropolisz</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="official">Metropolis</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="official">Metropolis</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="official">Metropolis</title>
<title xml:lang="et" type="official">Metropol</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="official">Метрополіс</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Metrópolis</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="904" approval="4" total="9">The Big O</anime>
<anime id="570" approval="3" total="11">Sennen Joyuu</anime>
<anime id="23" approval="2" total="12">Cowboy Bebop</anime>
<anime id="421" approval="2" total="9">Lupin Sansei</anime>
<anime id="219" approval="2" total="8">Cowboy Bebop: Tengoku no Tobira</anime>
<anime id="388" approval="1" total="3">Kaze o Mita Shounen</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="6">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="368986">Without doubt , i put this anime along with ghost in the shell "innocence" for the love and beauty they put in every cell ,some scenes along with the music ... are just biuutifull</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="30109">Quite good, story is wierd but the art is before it`s time (in 2002)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="406294">This is definately recommended! A great piece of work. I remember how amazed I was when I watched it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="552277">Great story and an amazing setting. It`s a classic and was one of the movies I loved to watch growing up.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.bandaivisual.co.jp/metropolis/</url>
<creators>
<name id="148" type="Direction">Rintarou</name>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="3306" type="Character Design">Nakura Yasuhiro</name>
<name id="3306" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nakura Yasuhiro</name>
<name id="1195" type="Original Work">Tezuka Osamu</name>
<name id="6461" type="Music">Honda Toshiyuki</name>
</creators>
<description>Metropolis is a grand city-state populated by humans and robots, the cohabitants of a strictly segmented society. Amidst the chaos created by anti-robot factions, detective http://anidb.net/ch35816 [Ban Hunsaku] and his sidekick http://anidb.net/ch84408 [Ken`ichi] are searching for rebel scientist http://anidb.net/ch84410 [Dr. Laughton]. But when they locate him, his secret laboratory is destroyed by fire under sinister circumstances, and instead Ken`ichi finds http://anidb.net/ch84409 [Tima], a beautiful young girl bereft of memory and speech, seemingly helpless at the site. Little does he know that Tima is a new top-of-the-line android created to take over Metropolis, and that behind her creation lie the ambitions of a powerful man and his fierce desire to reclaim a tragic figure from his past.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2787">5.61</permanent>
<temporary count="2805">7.04</temporary>
<review count="9">5.59</review>
</ratings>
<picture>222117.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>176</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>522</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>798</identifier>
<identifier>pttfht</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.bandaivisual.co.jp/metropolis/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Metropolis_(2001_film)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>メトロポリス_(2001年の映画)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>344</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>163030</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4650</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7548</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2861" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>cyberpunk</name>
<description>Cyberpunk focuses on computers or information technology, usually coupled with some degree of breakdown in social order. The plot often centres on a conflict among hackers, artificial intelligences, and mega corporations, tending to be set within a near-future dystopian Earth.</description>
<picurl>211264.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2870" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-17">
<name>steampunk</name>
<description>Steampunk is a sub-genre of science fiction that typically features steam-powered machinery, especially in a setting inspired by industrialized Western civilization during the 19th century. Steampunk works are often set in an alternative history of the 19th century`s British Victorian era or American "Wild West", in a post-apocalyptic future during which steam power has regained mainstream use, or in a fantasy world that similarly employs steam power.
Noteworthy attributes of the theme include large amounts smoke pollution from wood or coal burning, the affinity to metal constructs like cogs and metal tubing, and the mechanization of everyday objects.
Steampunk perhaps most recognisably features anachronistic technologies or retro-futuristic inventions as people in the 19th century might have envisioned them, and is likewise rooted in the era`s perspective on fashion, culture, architectural style, and art.
Such technology may include fictional machines like those found in the works of H. G. Wells and Jules Verne, or the modern authors Philip Pullman, Scott Westerfeld, Stephen Hunt and China Miéville. Other examples of steampunk contain alternative history-style presentations of such technology as lighter-than-air airships, analog computers, or such digital mechanical computers as Charles Babbage`s Analytical Engine.
Steampunk can also exemplify everything that is bad about unrestrained technological progress (dead matter), when compared to life and nature. The anime usually makes a point to propound the latter.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162830.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2882" parentid="2952" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-17">
<name>dystopia</name>
<description>A dystopia (from Ancient Greek: δυσ-, "bad, ill", and Ancient Greek: τόπος, "place, landscape"; alternatively cacotopia, or anti-utopia) is, in literature, an often futuristic society that has degraded into a repressive and controlled state, often under the guise of being utopian. Dystopian literature has underlying cautionary tones, warning society that if we continue to live how we do, this will be the consequence. A dystopia, thus, is regarded as a sort of negative utopia and is often characterized by an authoritarian or totalitarian form of government. Dystopias usually feature different kinds of repressive social control systems, a lack or total absence of individual freedoms and expressions and constant states of warfare or violence. Dystopias often explore the concept of humans abusing technology and how humans individually and collectively cope with technology that has evolved too quickly such as the car, the flamethrower or the microwave. A dystopian society is also often characterized by widespread poverty and brutal political controls such as a large military-like police.</description>
<picurl>69879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4203" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>rebellion</name>
<description>Rebellion, uprising, or insurrection is a refusal of obedience or order. It may, therefore, be seen as encompassing a range of behaviors aimed at destroying or taking over the position of an established authority such as a government, governor, president, political leader, financial institution, or person in charge. On the one hand the forms of behaviour can include non-violent methods such as the (overlapping but not quite identical) phenomena of civil disobedience, civil resistance and nonviolent resistance. On the other hand it may encompass violent campaigns. Those who participate in rebellions, especially if they are armed rebellions, are known as "rebels".&#13;
&#13;
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>163803.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4343" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2009-09-21">
<name>main character dies</name>
<description>At least one of the main characters in the anime dies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="35816" type="main character in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="5">1.63</rating>
<name>Hige Oyaji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1264.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3301" picture="24327.jpg">Tomita Kousei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79431" type="main character in" update="2016-09-10">
<name>Rock Holmes</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>In the world of show business, it is common knowledge that actors who start out playing the role of children rarely make it to the top of their profession. This is because child stars, who are loved in the role of cute children, even if they grow, are burdened with the fate of having to continue showing the same image to audiences. In the same way, in the Manga of Tezuka Osamu, loveable, law-abiding characters like Kenichi and Atom were restricted to continuously playing the same role. But Rock is different. He was not simply a virtuous character. From the time he started performing in child roles, he never believed in the image that "a bright future will be born if only justice triumphs". "The world is full of inconsistencies. The world will not weep even if the fight for justice is lost and evil triumphs. Come spring the flowers will still bloom, the sunshine will still pour down in the summer." Rock was a boy who stared these realities in the face. As might be expected from a character that got his name from Sherlock Holmes, Rock is a highly intelligent young boy. That`s why he never had to trade on his charms even as he grew up. He concealed the malicious face of the devil under his handsome visage. He built up his character as the portrait of a villain. Part of the appeal of Tezuka Osamu`s Manga lies in the fact that such warped boy stars are incorporated into the stories, and in the inclusion of elements of profundity and philosophy.</description>
<picture>191106.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40872" picture="161348.jpg">Okada Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84408" type="main character in" update="2016-09-01">
<name>Ken`ichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190730.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36351" picture="134042.jpg">Kobayashi Kei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84409" type="main character in" update="2016-09-01">
<name>Tima</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190732.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40871" picture="161347.jpg">Imoto Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84410" type="appears in" update="2016-09-01">
<name>Laughton-hakase</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190734.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3790" picture="50436.jpg">Takiguchi Junpei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84411" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-01">
<name>Duke Red</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190735.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3280" picture="24278.jpg">Ishida Tarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84412" type="appears in" update="2016-09-01">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Emmy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190747.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="407" picture="17254.jpg">Koyama Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84413" type="appears in" update="2016-09-04">
<name>Marukabi Boon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190874.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="261" picture="151648.jpg">Ikeda Masaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84414" type="appears in" update="2016-09-01">
<name>Hamegg</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190739.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="467" picture="38026.jpg">Ebara Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84415" type="appears in" update="2016-09-01">
<name>Atlas</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190740.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="633" picture="33549.jpg">Inoue Norihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84416" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-01">
<name>Pero</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190741.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2" picture="16471.jpg">Wakamoto Norio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84417" type="appears in" update="2016-09-01">
<name>Fifi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190742.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1937" picture="92109.jpg">Aikawa Rikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84418" type="appears in" update="2016-09-01">
<name>Acetylene Lamp</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190743.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="541" picture="26117.jpg">Chiba Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84419" type="appears in" update="2016-09-01">
<name>Notarlin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190744.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30715" picture="94899.jpg">Yashiro Shun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84420" type="appears in" update="2016-09-01">
<name>Lyon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190745.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="614" picture="18136.jpg">Hashi Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84421" type="appears in" update="2016-09-01">
<name>Ponkotsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190746.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28" picture="23184.jpg">Aono Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84422" type="appears in" update="2016-09-01">
<name>Skunk Kusai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190748.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2583" picture="23188.jpg">Furukawa Toshio</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="472" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>110</length>
<airdate>2001-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11475" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>2001-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11476" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2001-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11485" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>35</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Making Of</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11486" update="2003-10-01">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>8</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Interview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13438" update="2010-04-16">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>2001-05-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 3 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17631" update="2010-04-16">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>2001-05-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17632" update="2010-04-16">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>2001-05-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="78552" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">I Can`t Stop Loving You</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121056" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
