<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7940" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-04-08</startdate>
<enddate>2011-06-24</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Dororon Enma-kun: Meeramera</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">meeramera</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">Dororonえん魔くん メ~ラめら</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Ghastly Prince Enma Burning Up</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">咚隆隆 炎魔君熊熊燃烧</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1685" type="Alternative Setting">Dororon Enma-kun</anime>
<anime id="4411" type="Alternative Setting">Kikoushi Enma</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="407996">Just fun from a to z. A little (wish it could bt longer) gem.  And ecchi, not to much and too little. A perfect balance. For everyone, who is seekimg a good comedy and is not afraid of  a woman (not) naked body. I couldn`t said better. Way to go!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="496851">wackiness for 12 straight episodes. mega parody and lots of risque behavior, but never full on nakedness. well, there is lots of ass! both from humans of this world and other beings. better than average character designs and animation, topped off with good voice work is the soulperglue that holds this hilarious show together. one of my favorites of 2011 and highly recommended.   mera mera mera mera mearaaa!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="484892">This anime was awesome.  It was a seinen and ecchi remake of a shounen anime from 1973 that still used character designs reminiscent of 70`s anime.  This anime is entirely slap-stick and has some very risque scenes as well as some borderline hentai, but if you don`t mind extreme ecchi wackiness with a hint of lolicon, give this anime a watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="52443">Take an (un)healthy combination of Nagai Go madness and sexual innuendo, and accompany it with high production values! What can possibly go wrong?</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.starchild.co.jp/special/dororon-enmakun/</url>
<creators>
<name id="982" type="Animation Work">Brain`s Base</name>
<name id="665" type="Character Design">Kimura Takahiro</name>
<name id="1531" type="Series Composition">Yonetani Yoshitomo</name>
<name id="1531" type="Direction">Yonetani Yoshitomo</name>
<name id="868" type="Original Work">Nagai Gou</name>
<name id="665" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kimura Takahiro</name>
<name id="7267" type="Music">Suzuki Kei`ichi</name>
<name id="24612" type="Music">Moonriders</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the Dororon Enma-kun manga by http://anidb.net/cr868 [Nagai Gou], serialised in Weekly Shounen Sunday.
Tokyo in the 1970s. Evil spirits are threatening the human world and the only ones who can stop them are a group known as the Spirit Patrol. Sent from the underworld the team consists of the hot-headed http://anidb.net/ch29099 [Enma], the stuck-up http://anidb.net/ch29110 [Yukiko], the half-water sprite http://anidb.net/ch29101 [Kapael] and http://anidb.net/ch29103 [Chapeau-jii] — the old man spirit in the form of a hat, who guides the group. This may not bode well... though.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="663">4.56</permanent>
<temporary count="673">6.29</temporary>
<review count="1">7.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>68926.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12267</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9493</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.starchild.co.jp/special/dororon-enmakun/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://starchild.fm/special/en/enma/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Dororon_Enma-kun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Dororonえん魔くん_メ〜ラめら</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2119</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>339087</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13448</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ghastly-prince-enma-burning-up</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="520" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-14">
<name>nopan</name>
<description>The character foregoes underwear.</description>
<picurl>162753.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1774" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-05">
<name>gigantic breasts</name>
<description>Gigantic breasts are unnaturally large breasts, even by anime standards; they are true gargantuan monstrosities, either because of sheer size or through the combination of size and exceedingly unnatural shape. Essentially, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are gigantic; smaller breasts are the more common http://anidb.net/t2741 [large breasts], even if they`re as big as the character`s head.</description>
<picurl>160446.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2346" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-14">
<name>angel</name>
<description>An angel is a supernatural being, said to be the messenger of God. They are often depicted as human beings with a pair of white feathered wings and sometimes with a halo.
In contrast, a fallen angel who has turned evil will be depicted with black wings.</description>
<picurl>35521.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2566" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-31">
<name>loli</name>
<description>Lolita (often also just abbreviated to loli) refers originally to a novel by Vladimir Nabokov. The book is internationally famous for its controversial subject: the narrator and protagonist, middle aged Humbert Humbert, becomes obsessed and sexually involved with a 12-year-old girl named Dolores Haze.
Nowadays the name "Lolita" describes a sexually precocious young girl.
Related to this is http://anidb.net/t2415 [lolicon], the Japanese abbreviation of the English phrase "Lolita Complex". Sometimes written as "roricon" or "rorikon" due to the inexact mapping between Japanese and English phonemes. This is the term used to describe the fetish/fascination some mature people have for underage girls. There is an entire industry in Japan devoted to providing legal but schoolgirl-themed pornography, taking advantage of the cute childlike appearance some Japanese women maintain well into their twenties.
Because the characters in anime are often young by convention, many fans think that a character can only be Lolicon if she is twelve or younger. Exceptions are granted if the other character in the relationship is a lot older.
One particular device used to skirt the boundaries of taste and legality is the exotic being (alien, creature of magic, robot or the like) which takes the form of an underage human girl, but is in fact for all other practical purposes an adult.
Another reason why lolicon is fetishized by people may be because some of them just view it as a substitute for their fetish for flat-chested, but otherwise well-developed, women.
Source: Wikipedia / TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2568" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-06">
<name>deity</name>
<description>Some religions say that there is a supernatural being called God. Other religions say there is more than one god. A supernatural being is also sometimes called a deity. Many religions believe that a deity created everything that exists. In most religions, a god is believed to be immortal (cannot die), and to have powers to control nature far beyond the powers of humans.</description>
<picurl>32415.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2578" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-12">
<name>vulgar</name>
<description>Talking (and acting) in a way that is considered uncultivated, bawdy, common, coarse or unrefined, or "taboo" according to existing cultural standards. Includes boorish manners and obtrusive display of carnal "assets".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2658" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>toilet humour</name>
<description>Everything leads back to poo.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2659" parentid="2660" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Moon</name>
<description>The Moon is an astronomical body that orbits planet Earth, being Earth`s only permanent natural satellite. It is the fifth-largest natural satellite in the Solar System, and the largest among planetary satellites relative to the size of the planet that it orbits.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214385.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2697" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-05">
<name>voyeurism</name>
<description>Voyeurism is the sexual interest in or practice of spying on people engaged in intimate behaviors, such as undressing, sexual activity, or other actions usually considered to be of a private nature. The principal characteristic of voyeurism is that the voyeur does not normally interact directly with the subject of his/her interest, who is often unaware of being observed. The essence of voyeurism is the observing but may also involve the making of a secret photograph or video of the subject during an intimate activity. When the interest in a particular subject is obsessive, the behavior may be described as stalking.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162189.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2730" parentid="2848" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>exhibitionism</name>
<description>Exhibitionism is the act of exposing in a public or semi-public context the parts of one`s body that are not normally exposed. That may be done to prompt sexual arousal, but many forms of exhibitionism actually mean to create humour or disparagement through shock value or mockery. The idea of exhibitionism is closely tied to the notions of decency and modesty in dressing, and as such is highly dependent on one`s own cultural background. Certain forms of exhibitionism may be considered indecent exposure, and thus in many jurisdictions they may lead to civil or criminal charges. While both deal with the lack of clothing and may in certain cases overlap, exhibitionism is very different from and not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t2304 [nudism].</description>
<picurl>162657.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2746" parentid="2901" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-26">
<name>shibari</name>
<description>Not to be confused with Hojoujutsu (捕縄術) or Nawajutsu (縄術), which is the traditional Japanese martial art of restraining a person using cord or rope.
More commonly known as Kinbaku (緊縛) in Japan, Shibari is the word for "erotic bondage" or Kinbaku-bi which means "beautiful bondage". Kinbaku (also Sokubaku) is a Japanese style of sexual bondage or BDSM which involves tying up the bottom using simple yet visually intricate patterns, usually with several pieces of thin rope usually hemp or jute (generally 6 mm or 8 mm in diameter). The person`s body can also be hanging from the rope while tied to it.
The word Shibari came into common use in the West at some point in the 1990s to describe the bondage art Kinbaku. Shibari (縛り) is a Japanese word that literally means "to tie" or "to bind". It is used in Japan to describe the artful use of twine to tie objects or packages.
In anime/manga, Shibari or Kinbaku is often seen as a tool of rape or torture, rather than intended for a concept of bondage aesthetics.</description>
<picurl>161702.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2823" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>paper clothes</name>
<description>Worn clothing appears paper-thin and takes little abuse to be shredded or torn from the body. This is common in ecchi anime where the main storyline involves some type of fighting but consists primarily of dialogue and fanservice (Ikkitousen and Platonic Heart). Various girls’ clothing exploding as if made of rice paper is a very enticing prospect.</description>
<picurl>150776.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2824" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>pseudo tentacle rape scene</name>
<description>If this was porn she (or rather the audience) would have even more fun!</description>
<picurl>160554.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2828" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-26">
<name>borderline porn</name>
<description>Breaks the bounds of "excessive fanservice".
While the physical interactions and dialogue between characters may be extremely sexual, the most sexual situations do *not* have sex itself take place.
Specifically descriptive of containing all the plentiful features of (excessive) fanservice in addition to the interactions between characters being quite sexual — at most, sexual in NATURE only. This means physical touching such as groping, molesting, or bondage will focus primarily on the revealed (i.e. nude) upper portion of the body or through/over clothing on the lower half of the body. This is all WITHOUT actual sex acts (penetration, etc.) taking place.</description>
<picurl>214855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2893" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>female teacher</name>
<description>Any kind of female teacher will do, even if she only does home visits. Female teachers imply mature women (even if they sometimes look like schoolgirls) dressed in what women would typically wear when doing official business (like a blouse, pinstripe dress with side front slit), but of course, not limited to that. Furthermore, school nurses also count as female teachers unless they`re actually wearing a nurse outfit, which they almost never are.
Almost completely exclusive to hentai animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2901" parentid="2729" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-09">
<name>bondage</name>
<description>Bondage is the use of restraints for the sexual pleasure of the parties involved. It may be used in its own right, as in the case of rope bondage and breast bondage, or as part of sexual activity or BDSM activity. When a person is sexually aroused by bondage, it may be considered a paraphilia, known as vincilagnia (from Latin vincio, to bind or fetter with chains, and lagneia, lust).
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42021.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3087" parentid="2274" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>super robot</name>
<description>These robots tend to have almost semi-magical attacks, which seem impossible or non-realistic, and/or perform non-realistic transformation sequences where they seem to gain/lose mass and utterly change their form, even if it means making their super-hard armour bend like plastic sheets.</description>
<picurl>222137.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3167" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-16">
<name>Tokyo destroyed</name>
<description>Tokyo is depicted as being or having been destroyed, either partially or completely, by some sort of disaster, such as a nuclear blast, a very large-scale fire, or rising sea levels. Should the situation be dire enough, Tokyo may be destroyed again after a recovery, or a new Tokyo may be built and subsequently destroyed, by a new disaster.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3322" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-04">
<name>remake</name>
<description>This anime is a remake of a previously released story, anime, or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3339" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2013-02-11">
<name>demon hunt</name>
<description>Demons are tracked down and probably killed in this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3356" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-12-20">
<name>banana peel</name>
<description>Used as slapstick comedy element in this anime: At least one of the characters in this anime will slip on a banana peel, leading to humorous or even ecchi situations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3363" parentid="2876" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-04">
<name>Buddhism</name>
<description>Buddhism is a nontheistic religion or dharma, "right way of living", that encompasses a variety of traditions, beliefs and practices largely based on teachings attributed to Siddhartha Gautama, commonly known as the Buddha ("the awakened one").
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>169453.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3443" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-05">
<name>orgy</name>
<description>A wild gathering marked by promiscuous sexual activity.</description>
<picurl>190911.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3667" parentid="2676" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo Tower</name>
<description>Tokyo Tower is a communications and observation tower in the Shiba-koen district of Minato, Tokyo, Japan. At 332.9 metres, it is the second-tallest structure in Japan. The structure is an Eiffel Tower-inspired lattice tower that is painted white and international orange to comply with air safety regulations.
Source: Wikipedia
Note: Not to be confused with the very much younger http://anidb.net/t3037 [Tokyo Skytree].</description>
<picurl>161123.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3854" parentid="2891" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-03-13">
<name>breast expansion</name>
<description>When the breasts grow in size, right before the viewers eyes!
The breasts will slowly grow larger, either stretching clothing to its limit or bursting free completely!</description>
<picurl>184159.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4048" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>Japanese mythology</name>
<description>Japanese mythology is a system of beliefs that embraces Shinto and Buddhist traditions as well as agriculture-based folk religion. The Shinto pantheon alone consists of an uncountable number of kami (Japanese for "gods" or "spirits").
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4112" parentid="3842" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-14">
<name>excessive censoring</name>
<description>There are basically two cases to which this term can be applied to:
1) creative censorship
The TV station airing the anime does its best to remove most ecchi parts from the show, using various and original methods. Usually, an uncensored BD/DVD is released later. Apart from the publisher`s greed - sometimes the censorship is used intentionally to make a scene look more obscene than it actually is.
2) convenient censorship
Another case of it - more often known under the term of "convenient censoring/ship" - is a blatant substitute for mosaic/steam/etc. over nether regions. This applies both to normal shows with occasional nudity as a normal part of human life (or just occasional flash of fanservice), as well as to heavy ecchi / borderline hentai shows where /literally/ everything is a fair (and far more "obscene" no matter how to look at it) game, except that misinterpreted taboo nonsense coming from §175 of JPC.</description>
<picurl>169459.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5485" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-28">
<name>penis jokes</name>
<description>A penis or other phallic object is used as a device to elicit laughter from the viewer. This also includes indirect references to such objects provided the intent is clearly the same.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5838" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-26">
<name>fire</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5859" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-30">
<name>monster of the week</name>
<description>On a pretty much regular basis — weekly or episodic — the protagonists engage in some kind of conflict. This can be an actual showdown between mecha, or the all-out fight against an enemy, or a (car) race that needs to be won.
This can make the anime quite repetitive.</description>
<picurl>60013.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5871" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-19">
<name>breathing in space</name>
<description>Find yourself in space without an oxygen tank? Not a problem! Breathing in the vacuum of space is just as easy as breathing on Earth, especially if you are a superhero or somehow able to leave the atmosphere under your own power.</description>
<picurl>166122.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6006" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>Tokyo is the centre of the universe</name>
<description>Whether it`s the big bad evil aiming for world domination, demons bringing the hell over to this site or aliens attacking the Earth, their centre of attention is always Tokyo, as if the rest of the world did not even exist!
But worry not if you happen to live there, because your neighbour could just be the leader of a senshi team or the pilot of a giant mecha and they are surely going to save the day again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="29099" type="main character in" update="2012-03-24">
<rating votes="9">6.20</rating>
<name>Enma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Enma-kun is the leader of the Spirit Patrol group - a group dedicated to defeating evil spirits.
His http://anidb.net/ch29109 [uncle] is the judge of the afterlife down in the underworld, and he has told Enma-kun to capture as many evil spirits as possible and bring them back down to the underworld... but Enma sees the work as nothing but a chore. He`s fairly confident that any spirits that appear will be quick work when he uses his magic to burn them into ashes, and in all honestly he would rather be trying to find a way to sneak a peek at http://anidb.net/ch29110 [Yuki]-chan`s naked body instead of searching for evil spirits.
Source: Official Site</description>
<picture>84528.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29100" type="appears in" update="2012-03-24">
<rating votes="4">8.06</rating>
<name>Chiiko-sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chiiko is the teacher responsible for http://anidb.net/ch29107 [Harumi]`s classes health lessons. She is well known around the school as a kind and popular teacher. However, underneath her kind mask and nice body she is hiding her true identity...
Source: Official Site</description>
<picture>84533.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29101" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-24">
<rating votes="7">3.14</rating>
<name>Kapael</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kapael is half-kappa and half-water sprite. He fulfills the role of intelligence officer in the Spirit Patrol, specializing in finding information about things in the human world, which makes him an invaluable ally to the others. He isn`t exactly the luckiest of creatures however, and often finds himself in the wrong place at the wrong time.
Source: Official Site</description>
<picture>69450.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29102" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="4">3.01</rating>
<name>Gariben</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69452.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2191" picture="21747.jpg">Itou Maiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29103" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-24">
<rating votes="7">3.64</rating>
<name>Chapeau-jii</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chapeau-jii is a spirit sent by the Judge of the Afterlife to watch over http://anidb.net/ch29099 [Enma]-kun and his Spirit Patrol.
He is an old spirit in the form of a hat that possesses great knowledge in all matters that relate to the underworld and spirits, so much so that he is known as the "Underworld`s Living Encyclopaedia". However he isn`t having the easiest time watching over Enma-kun... it seems that Enma-kun is a lot more interested in http://anidb.net/ch29110 [Yukiko-hime] than searching for spirits... and getting him to listen to some words of wisdom certainly isn`t a simple task for Chapeau-jii.
Source: Official Site</description>
<picture>69943.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2220" picture="188715.jpg">Inaba Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29104" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-14">
<rating votes="3">2.30</rating>
<name>Supokon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69784.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="478" picture="17453.jpg">Nakamura Daiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29105" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-24">
<rating votes="4">3.01</rating>
<name>Tsutomu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsutomu is one of http://anidb.net/ch29107 [Harumi]`s classmates. He tends to get involved with spirits almost every day, even if he doesn`t mean to.
Source: Official Site</description>
<picture>84531.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2038" picture="49098.jpg">Shishido Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29106" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-24">
<rating votes="4">3.01</rating>
<name>Tobacchiri-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tobacchiri is the teacher in charge of http://anidb.net/ch29107 [Harumi] and http://anidb.net/ch29105 [Tsutomu]`s class. He might be part of the reason the two of them always seem to end up with spirits.
Source: Official Site</description>
<picture>84532.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="478" picture="17453.jpg">Nakamura Daiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29107" type="main character in" update="2012-03-24">
<rating votes="7">8.42</rating>
<name>Fudou Harumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Harumi is a student at Hiromi Primary School in lower Tokyo, who happens to chance upon http://anidb.net/ch29099 [Enma]-kun and his spirit patrol. After that she soon ends up helping them out with their spirit hunting work... even if it simply means becoming the bait.
Source: Official Site</description>
<picture>84530.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29108" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-14">
<rating votes="4">3.81</rating>
<name>Renkonman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69781.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="469" picture="17418.jpg">Umezu Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29109" type="appears in" update="2012-03-24">
<rating votes="3">4.31</rating>
<name>Enma Daiou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>King Enma is the big boss of the underworld, and he is also the one responsible for sending his nephew http://anidb.net/ch29099 [Enma] down to the human world as the leader of the Spirit Patrol. The reason he chose to send Enma was obviously because he was sure Enma could capture all the evil spirits living in the human world... right...?
Source: Official Site</description>
<picture>84534.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2" picture="16471.jpg">Wakamoto Norio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29110" type="main character in" update="2012-03-24">
<rating votes="17">8.70</rating>
<name>Yukiko-hime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yukiko is the daughter of the Yukionna noble family and http://anidb.net/ch29099 [Enma]-kun`s childhood friend. She also uses magic to defeat evil spirits alongside Enma-kun, and is constantly annoyed by his perverted antics.
Source: Official Site</description>
<picture>84529.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31170" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-14">
<rating votes="9">8.59</rating>
<name>Enpi-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69780.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2038" picture="49098.jpg">Shishido Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49130" type="appears in" update="2012-09-21">
<rating votes="1">9.56</rating>
<name>Mark Angel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94593.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49131" type="appears in" update="2012-09-21">
<name>Kan Tengu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94594.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2782" picture="23189.jpg">Ginga Banjou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49132" type="appears in" update="2012-09-21">
<name>En Tengu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94595.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="456" picture="17358.jpg">Ootsuka Chikao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49133" type="appears in" update="2012-09-21">
<name>Sutten Douji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94599.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49134" type="appears in" update="2012-09-21">
<name>Benten-sama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94600.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49135" type="appears in" update="2012-09-21">
<name>Haguromo Hime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94601.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="128740" update="2012-03-24">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-08</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">昭和だ! えん魔だ! 妖怪集合!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s the Shouwa Era! Here Comes Enma! Demons Come Forth!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shouwa Da! Enma Da! Youkai Shuugou!</title>
<summary>This story begins in Tokyo during the Showa period...
One night, a young girl named Harumi and her classmates from Hiromi primary school are attacked by spirits at their school. Harumi manages to escape and is saved by a strange frog-like creature, who takes her down into the basement of the school, where she finds a group that call themselves the `Spirit Patrol`. Harumi asks the group for help saving her friends that were attacked by the spirit, and Chapeau-jii explains that this particular spirit is known as a `face eater`.
Apparently the Spirit Patrol was sent by the leader of the underworld to stop evil spirits having their way in the human world... but they don`t exactly seem very skilled when it comes to stopping them... will Harumi be alright by putting her trust in them?
Source: Official Site</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>619071</identifier>
<identifier>ghastly-prince-enma-burning-up</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129194" update="2011-04-07">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129223" update="2012-01-20">
<epno type="3">C13</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-04-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129224" update="2012-02-05">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-04-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129240" update="2012-03-24">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あんたあの子の夢なのさ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You`re Her Dream</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anta Ano Ko no Yume na no sa</title>
<summary>Tsukiko-hime and Harumi are put to sleep by a spirit and imprisoned in the world of dreams. Enma-kun and the others try everything they can think of to try and wake them up, but all to no avail... and eventually get sent into the world of dreams themselves. But the world of dreams isn`t as bad as Enma-kun originally thought - he can do whatever he wants and everything he wants is there!
But back in the real world, another spirit is coming for their sleeping bodies!
Source: Official Site</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>619077</identifier>
<identifier>ghastly-prince-enma-burning-up</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129241" update="2012-03-24">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大きいことはイイコトか?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bigger is Better?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ookii Koto wa Ii Koto ka?</title>
<summary>Chiiko is normally one of the kindest, most respected teachers at Harumi`s school, but all of a sudden she starts acting violently. The reason can only be that she inhaled some of the toxic gas from a certain evil spirit, and the biggest problem is that anyone who inhales the gas will also be consumed by that spirit in just three days time!
The only way the group can save Chiiko is by putting Yukiko-hime in her place... but in order to do that they first need to somehow get Chiiko`s bikini off her so that Yukiko-hime can wear it in her place. Harumi and Yukiko-hime sneak into Chiiko`s bedroom while she is asleep to try and get the bikini, but it might not go quite as planned...
Source: Official Site</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>619075</identifier>
<identifier>ghastly-prince-enma-burning-up</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129242" update="2012-03-24">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">右も左も妖怪だらけじゃ~ござんせんか</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Demons, Everywhere You Turn</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Migi mo Hidari mo Youkai Darake Ja: Gozansenka</title>
<summary>A squid spirit attacks Harumi and her friends while they are out for a trip at an amusement park. The Spirit Patrol quickly arrives at the scene, but Yukiko-hime gets captured by the squid spirit - can Enma-kun find a way to rescue Yukiko-hime from the spirit`s tentacles... and for that sake does he want to?
In the first place, why is the Spirit Patrol even in the human world? The secret behind it`s formation lies within this episode!
Source: Official Site</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>619073</identifier>
<identifier>ghastly-prince-enma-burning-up</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129415" update="2012-03-24">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">女だらけの大ハチの巣大会! シャッポじいもおるかも?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An All-girls Competition in the Beehive! With Chapeau-jii?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onna Darake no Dai Hachi no Sutaikai!</title>
<summary>The spirit known as the `Beehive Priest` has sucked out Enma-kun`s brain and left him acting like nothing more than a little baby. In order to get his brain back, Yukiko-hime and the others are forced into entering a tournament with the Beehive Priest - but the tournament seems to be about harassing Yukiko-hime and Harumi more than anything else... but just when things are looking down, a mysterious near-naked new-comer arrives!
How will the tournament turn out? Who will be the victor? Who is this mysterious beauty? Will Enma-kun ever return to his normal self again?
Source: Official Site</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>619079</identifier>
<identifier>ghastly-prince-enma-burning-up</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129709" update="2012-03-24">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">止めてくれるな, 天狗さん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stop Them, Tengu-san!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomete Kurena, Tengu-san</title>
<summary>Enpi-chan has broken a seal which has almost let demonic beasts from the realm of darkness escape - and there is only one way that they can be stopped now... and that is to use... `that`.
But the only way they can use `that` is by finding the key which Harumi has dropped somewhere - and if they don`t hurry and find it, the beasts are going to escape! Enma and the others all split up in search of the key, and even the Flame and Ice Tengu start working with them in order to prevent a disaster from happening.
Will they be able to find the key before it`s too late? Will they be able to activate `that` in time!?
Source: Official Site</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>619089</identifier>
<identifier>ghastly-prince-enma-burning-up</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129710" update="2012-03-24">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ホッカホカだよ天狗さん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Nice and Warm, Tengu-san!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hokkahoka Da yo Tengu-san</title>
<summary>A powerful spirit known as the `Flame Tengu` has suddenly attacked the Spirit Patrol`s hell hideout - and not even Enma-kun can stand against his flames - he is turning the hideout into a scorching hot oven!
Yukiko-hime just can`t take the heat and calls on the protector of her family, the `Ice Tengu` for help. When he arrives the Flame Tengu and the Ice Tengu start battling it out, but that`s not good for the temperature at all! It keeps getting hot, then cold, then hot again - the Spirit Patrol keep having to switch their clothes to keep with the temperature! The fight between the two Tengu is even having an effect on the human world - Harumi comes by to ask for some help and runs into a bit of trouble herself!
What could possibly have caused the Flame Tengu to attack in the first place!?
Source: Official Site</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>619087</identifier>
<identifier>ghastly-prince-enma-burning-up</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129711" update="2012-03-24">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">およ妖! じっと我慢のコであった</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mysterious! The Demon Who Waited Patiently</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oyoyou! Jitto Gaman no Ko de Atta</title>
<summary>The Four Kings of the Abashiri Underworld have challenged the Spirit Patrol to a duel! Yukiko-hime and the others are off being kicked by `Kettobashi`, or about to be split in half by `Manuke-oni`... but Enma is just relaxing nice and comfortably - with no will to fight at all!
It turns out Enma-kun doesn`t do well in the cold - and `Nadare-kozou`, another one of the Four Kings, found out about this and decided the challenge would take place in the cold and snowy mountains! Plus Enma is also somewhat down after hearing the secret of his crown from Enpi-chan.
Will the Spirit Patrol be able to get out of this one? And just who is the fourth of the Four Kings that just never seems to show himself?
Source: Official Site</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>619085</identifier>
<identifier>ghastly-prince-enma-burning-up</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129712" update="2012-03-24">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">のんびり這おうよ, おいらたち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Crawl Our Way There</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nonbiri Haou yo, Oira-tachi</title>
<summary>Everything in the world seems to be falling over! People, animals, vehicles - nothing seems to get away from it. Harumi and the others are visiting the Ueno Zoo when suddenly everything starts falling over - themselves included.
It turns out it is all the cunning ploy of a spirit of course - but not just any spirit this time - it`s a spirit that Enma-kun knew when he was little, and the reason he is doing all this is to try and get hold of the flame crown that Enma is always wearing!
It also seems like the spirit has some interesting secrets about Enpi-chan as well...
Source: Official Site</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>619083</identifier>
<identifier>ghastly-prince-enma-burning-up</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129713" update="2012-03-24">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あっと驚くゴロゴロ~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Roly-poly Surprises</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atto Odoroku Gorogoro</title>
<summary>A transfer student has joined Harumi`s class at school - his name is Gorou Goro. He is also not quite what he seems, as beneath his cover as a transfer student, he is in fact a spirit that will turn anyone who touches him into a ball!
Of course, Harumi and the others end up touching him and rolling all over - but the biggest problem is that the ball changing is contagious, and if something isn`t done soon all of Japan, even the whole world might end up as balls! Even Enma-kun and Yukiko-hime end up as balls while trying to stop the spirit...
Eventually Yukiko-hime rolls off toward a hotter area than she can take... so hot that it could even be life threatening for the ice princess - will Enma-kun be able to save her before it`s too late?
Source: Official Site</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>619081</identifier>
<identifier>ghastly-prince-enma-burning-up</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129926" update="2012-03-24">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">股合う日まで</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Until we Meet Again</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mata Au Hi made</title>
<summary>The conference that took part between heaven and the underworld has resulted in the approval of the removal of the entire human race.
Harumi steps up to find a way to prevent this from happening, but it turns out that the only way is for Enma-kun`s underworld team to defeat Heaven`s team in a final battle. Who will be the final victor? Is the human race doomed to become extinct?
Source: Official Site</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>619093</identifier>
<identifier>ghastly-prince-enma-burning-up</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129927" update="2012-03-24">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あたしにはかかわりのないことでござんす</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Not My Problem</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atashi ni wa Kakawari no Nai Koto de Gozansu</title>
<summary>Enpi-chan was pulling the strings behind the spirits, but it turns out that the angel, Markangel was pulling the strings behind Enpi-chan - and the ones who ordered him to do so were the gods of the heavens themselves!
It is time for a conference between the heavens and the underworld to begin, and so the angel know as Benten has come down from the heavens, while King Enma is taking the stage for the underworld - what will the outcome of the fated meeting be?
Source: Official Site</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>619091</identifier>
<identifier>ghastly-prince-enma-burning-up</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="131702" update="2011-07-08">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Long Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131768" update="2012-02-05">
<epno type="3">C15</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-04-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131769" update="2012-01-20">
<epno type="3">C14</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-04-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131770" update="2011-07-09">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-05-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131771" update="2011-07-09">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-04-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131772" update="2011-07-09">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-04-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131773" update="2011-07-09">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-04-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134807" update="2012-01-20">
<epno type="3">C22</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-06-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134808" update="2012-01-20">
<epno type="3">C21</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-06-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134809" update="2012-01-20">
<epno type="3">C20</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-06-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134810" update="2012-01-20">
<epno type="3">C19</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-05-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134811" update="2012-01-20">
<epno type="3">C18</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-05-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134812" update="2012-01-20">
<epno type="3">C17</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-05-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134813" update="2012-01-20">
<epno type="3">C16</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-05-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134824" update="2012-01-20">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-06-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134825" update="2012-01-20">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-06-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134826" update="2012-01-20">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-06-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134827" update="2012-01-20">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-06-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134828" update="2012-01-20">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-05-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134829" update="2012-01-20">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-05-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134830" update="2012-01-20">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-05-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136511" update="2012-01-20">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136512" update="2012-01-20">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136513" update="2012-01-20">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136514" update="2012-01-20">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
