<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="795" restricted="true">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1995-07-14</startdate>
<enddate>1995-07-14</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Keiraku no Houteishiki Level-C</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pleasure Education Level-C</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Level C</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">快楽の方程式 LEVEL-C</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Level-C</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Level-C</title>
</titles>
<creators>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="4133" type="Character Design">Nakayama Yumi</name>
<name id="6032" type="Direction">Yamaguchi Yorifusa</name>
<name id="18645" type="Music">Shiraishi Kimihiko</name>
<name id="33962" type="Original Work">Aoi Futaba</name>
<name id="33963" type="Original Work">Kurenai Mitsuba</name>
</creators>
<description>Mizuki is a popular male fashion model with a promising future. When the mysterious Haruno sees him, she wants to make him the centerpiece for her company`s latest promotion. To lure Mizuki in, she calls on the talents of her twin brother, Kazo. He is quick to seduce the young supermodel, but things soon escalate beyond business as usual. As Kazo`s feelings run away with him, it looks like true love for him and Mizuki.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="332">2.78</permanent>
<temporary count="336">5.48</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>33704.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1356</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>736</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3904</identifier>
<identifier>trnxir</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.jcstaff.co.jp/sakuhin/nenpyo/1994/03_LEVEL-C/LEVEL-C.htm</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Level_C</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>LEVEL-C</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>235916</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2134</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2615" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-25">
<name>18 restricted</name>
<description>This isn`t really an "audience".
While some anime might feature sexual content they still might not be considered pornography. This category is meant only for when the content is clearly *not* intended for minors. The distinction is made by whether the content is sold only to adults.</description>
<picurl>67867.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2723" parentid="2848" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>yaoi</name>
<description>Yaoi refers to anime that portray gay (male/male) sex. Do not confuse this with the http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai] category under Romance, which only portrays male/male relationships, but generally not anything pornographic. This is real male/male porn.
Yaoi works are generally targeted at a female audience. Females that enjoy Yaoi are oftern referred to as http://anidb.net/t2268 [Fujoshi].
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri].</description>
<picurl>163594.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="8280" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>1996-05-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
<episode id="167597" update="2015-04-06">
<epno type="5">P1</epno>
<length>6</length>
<rating votes="1">1.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Level C Bullshit Parody</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
