<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7971" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-10-20</startdate>
<enddate>2010-10-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Seikon no Qwaser: Jotei no Shouzou</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">성흔의 퀘이서: 여제의 초상</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Seikon no Qwaser OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">聖痕のクェイサー 女帝の肖像</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The Qwaser of Stigmata: Portrait of the Empress</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6816" type="Parent Story">Seikon no Qwaser</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.qwaser.jp/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="4250" type="Original Work">Yoshino Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="10188" type="Original Work">Satou Ken`etsu</name>
<name id="3097" type="Direction">Kaneko Hiraku</name>
<name id="11225" type="Animation Work">Hoods Entertainment</name>
<name id="3333" type="Character Design">Uno Makoto</name>
<name id="1540" type="Series Composition">Uezu Makoto</name>
<name id="3672" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sugimoto Isao</name>
<name id="1793" type="Chief Animation Direction">Iijima Hiroya</name>
<name id="10106" type="Music">Katou Tatsuya</name>
</creators>
<description>One day, honor-student http://anidb.net/ch26398 [Shiizaki Lulu] observes http://anidb.net/ch11296 [Katya] and http://anidb.net/ch12417 [Hana] together in the science lab preparation room. She is discovered and caught. Katya draws close to her but suddenly stops.
Shortly after, Lulu accompanies her mother to a suspicious ritual being performed by mysterious cult.
~ translated and adapted from official site by Cranston
Note: Bundled with the 10th volume of Seikon no Qwaser manga.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="665">3.15</permanent>
<temporary count="673">5.80</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>55039.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11897</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9202</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4877</identifier>
<identifier>coqkvu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.qwaser.jp/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>The_Qwaser_of_Stigmata</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>聖痕のクェイサー</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="301" parentid="2848" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-10">
<name>lactation</name>
<description>Capable of secreting breast milk, sometimes referred to as Mother`s milk.</description>
<picurl>176139.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3575" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-13">
<name>damsel in distress</name>
<description>The damsel in distress is usually a young, nubile woman placed in a dire predicament by a villain or a monster and requires a hero to dash to her rescue. Often used to unite the cast of a show for this one goal, to make them put differences aside and become a band of nakama. 
Examples: Sakoshita Yanagi from Rekka no Honoo, Yuuki Miaka from Fushigi Yuugi or Higurashi Kagome from Inuyasha.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6083" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>master-servant relationship</name>
<description>To some genres, this would suggest a genuine pairing where one person exists to serve another person, such as in some action/dramas where the pair becomes united by destiny as partners — fighting or battles between different pairs/partners will usually be a dominant part of the story.
In other genres, this suggests a relationship where one person may be occupied as or even forcefully treated as a servant or slave to the other who designates themself the master — these services usually apply anywhere from tsundere/romantic-comedies to ecchi or to the more extreme in hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="11293" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-26">
<rating votes="76">7.41</rating>
<name>Oribe Mafuyu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The titular female character, Mafuyu is the adopted daughter of St.Mihailov`s last dean, and the self-appointed protector of Yamanobe Tomo. Upbeat and cheerful, she is so proficient in kendo that she carries a wooden sword with her all the time. She has to endure hardship on a daily basis in form of her classmates picking harshly on her and especially Tomo. This changes when she encounters Sasha for the first time, where she starts living with him and, little by little, is pitted herself in the fights between Qwasers. Though at odds with Sasha`s coldness, Mafuyu has started to open up to him and the two have formed a stronger bond. A running gag has Mafuyu hit heavily Tomo when the latter makes mistakes.</description>
<picture>46957.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11294" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-26">
<rating votes="71">6.24</rating>
<name>Yamanobe Tomo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Daughter of St. Mihailov`s last dean and currently best friend and roommate of Oribe Mafuyu, Tomo is her exact opposite, both physically and mentally: she herself is very childish and naïve, and while having the largest bust of the whole female cast so far, she is physically weak. Tomo is the spitting image of Sasha`s original protector, Olja, which explains why he took so willingly the role of Tomo`s guardian, much to Mafuyu`s chagrin. Also, sometimes an upside down Eastern Cross (with its third slab being a scar), the symbol of the Adepts, appears between her breasts. This is later revealed to be the presence of the Qwaser of Gold, which apparently inhabits Tomo`s body and, as itself stated, is slowly draining her of her life, which is why she has to replenish herself through Teresa`s Soma.</description>
<picture>46958.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11295" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-26">
<rating votes="41">8.35</rating>
<name>Teresa Beria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Serbian Orthodox nun that serves at St. Mihailov in a variety of ordinary chores, such as taking care of children in the school`s kindergarten or tending to flowers, she is the only survivor of a brutal massacre occurred in Serbia during the Yugoslav Wars, where an expedition led by Croa raped and slaughtered all the inhabitants of Teresa`s church. Due to her assisting at the whole carnage while hidden, she became completely emotionless and stopped smiling, crying or feeling anything, and thus is presented as almost ghostly due to her quietness. Only when Croa reappears and Teresa has to recall the brutalities of her past, does she gain enough courage to face them and begin to show emotions again. She usually provides Sasha with her Soma, but can hold her own in combat by means of martial arts, a bow and huge blades concealed in her skirt.</description>
<picture>46972.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="245" picture="46862.jpg">Chihara Minori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11296" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-26">
<rating votes="107">6.99</rating>
<name>Katya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A little Russian girl, no more than ten years old and with the beauty of a doll, she arrives in Japan shortly after the beginning of the war of the Qwasers. While she is presented as extremely shy and child-like, befitting her age (she has a habit of addressing herself in third person in these instances), her true colours depicts her as a domineering, arrogant, prideful and almost malicious queen, all maintaining a façade of childish innocence. She is a powerful Qwaser who wields the element of copper, which usually makes her gain control and manipulate electrical wires and redirect their flow to electrocute and incinerate her foes. She does not fight herself due to her frailty as a little girl, and this is why she is always guarded by a grim, archaic gynoid dressed in regal attire named Anastasia, which Ekaterina calls mother for reason currently unknown. Currently she attends at St. Mihailov`s primary school, being the subject of admiration and love of her classmates and teachers thanks to her doll-like features, and has Hana serve as her slave and replenish her of Soma. Recently, it has been revealed that she shares heavy connections with the Imperial Family of late Tsar Nicholas II, and it is heavily hinted that she herself is the same Tsarina Alexandra that served as Nicholas` consort, though this is has not been proved, just suggested by Ekaterina herself (although this would also explain why her guardian gynoid is named Anastasia).</description>
<picture>46967.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4" picture="177060.jpg">Hirano Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11297" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-26">
<rating votes="55">6.45</rating>
<name>Sasha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The titular character and male protagonist of the story, Alexander is a young Qwaser of Russian origin that controls the element of Iron, with which he can manipulate the said element on a molecular level, thus being capable not only to morph it in any form he wishes, but also create extreme heat or cold. He was held captive and trained with the other Qwasers into harnessing his powers, and survived the brutal ordeal thanks to the affection received from an older girl named Olja, and whose murder by the Qwaser of Gold he witnessed. He received a large scar on the left side of his face from the same Qwaser. The scar is shaped like an Eastern Cross, and tends to bleed heavily when he draws upon his powers. He appeared out of nowhere on the grounds of St. Mihailov, and was quickly accepted into the school as a student of class 1-A, the same that Mafuyu Oribe and Tomo Yamanobe attend. He became Tomo`s protector because of her resemblance to Olja. Silver-haired with blue eyes, Alexander, or Sasha for short (though he allows only those close to him to call him by this nickname) is usually extremely cold, harsh and serious, although his weakness for borscht, his favourite dish, can soften him. He slowly changed and warmed to those around him, especially Mafuyu, though he remains extremely fierce when fighting other Qwasers. Usually he fights wielding an enormous black scythe that is at least twice his size. Sometimes he tends to comment on things in Russian.</description>
<picture>46956.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="81" picture="41282.jpg">Sanpei Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12417" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-26">
<rating votes="70">6.21</rating>
<name>Katsuragi Hana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A student of class 1-A, she acts as an enforcer on school grounds, but also she is the main architect of the physical abuses that Mafuyu and Tomo have to endure every day, such as regularly throwing the class` garbage can on them or forcing them to fill it after "casually" tripping on it, to covering Tomo`s desk with writings and trash. Being the right hand of Miyuri, she welcomes Ekaterina Kurae when she arrives in Japan, and it`s here that her apparent fondness for lolicon is discovered, as she becomes extremely embarrassed in Ekaterina`s presence and, while the latter fakes to fade out, she kisses her out of lust. These events let her become the unwilling slave of her new mistress, subject to humiliation and erotic torment on a daily basis (which, on a side note, made her very proficient in S&amp;M, such as making extremely complex nodes with little effort). She appears to have some masochistic tendencies, as she derives pleasure from Ekaterina`s abuses.</description>
<picture>46973.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12418" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-29">
<rating votes="66">7.81</rating>
<name>Tsujidou Miyuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The daughter of the current dean at St. Mihailov Academy, who succeeded Tomo`s father. While beautiful and well-endowed, Miyuri is extremely bossy, arrogant and prideful, making nothing to conceal her disrespect for Tomo and Mafuyu and to bully them on a daily basis, supported by Hana. Greatly humiliated by Sasha, who correctly defines her as a leecher of others` powers, she "takes revenge" by welcoming and taking care of Ekaterina Kurae, the Quaser of Copper. It can be noted that Miyuri is very rich and appears to have a sheltered upbringing, based on her drowning Ekaterina with expensive gifts. However, being treated as a fool after Sasha`s arrival made her somewhat of a comic relief character. On a positive note, it can be assumed that she truly cares even for those she bullies, as she stripped naked for a group of terrorists so as to spare the same ordeal to Ekaterina, Mafuyu and the others.</description>
<picture>39436.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12419" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-22">
<rating votes="58">6.77</rating>
<name>Mitarai Fumika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The class president.</description>
<picture>39437.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13999" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-10">
<rating votes="8">6.43</rating>
<name>Yuuri Noda</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41277.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="375" picture="17221.jpg">Chiba Susumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15810" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-14">
<rating votes="6">8.47</rating>
<name>Ootori Shin`ichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44608.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26398" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-03">
<rating votes="15">5.52</rating>
<name>Shiizaki Lulu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61942.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1511" picture="173601.jpg">Akesaka Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26399" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-03">
<rating votes="1">8.85</rating>
<name>Mannyuuken</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61941.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="122397" update="2010-09-15">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OAD</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124607" update="2010-10-25">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-10-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124608" update="2010-10-25">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-10-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129561" update="2011-04-16">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<rating votes="1">1.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Animation Music Clip "Errand"</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
