<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7991" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>3</episodecount>
<startdate>2012-02-04</startdate>
<enddate>2013-02-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Berserk: Ougon Jidai Hen</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Berserk Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">بيرسيرك: فصل العصر الذهبي</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Берсерк: Златният век</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Берсерк. Золота Доба</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ベルセルク 黄金時代篇</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Berserk: The Golden Age Arc</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Berserk: Das goldene Zeitalter</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Berserk : l`Âge d`or</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Berserk - L`epoca d`oro</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Berserk - La Edad de Oro</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Берсерк: Золотой век</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Berserk: Zlatý věk</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="11851" type="Sequel">Berserk</anime>
<anime id="98" type="Alternative Setting">Kenpuu Denki Berserk</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4892" approval="31" total="38">Claymore</anime>
<anime id="13945" approval="9" total="14">Vinland Saga</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="20">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="77536">Personally i liked more the old version, there were a lot more details in the art style although it was old.

for this updated version they took out 40% of the old version in terms of plot, and add a new plot which continue the story a little bit where the old one stopped. 

they both have their advantages and disavantages, but overall have the same plot, so see this if u want the new plot, and see the old one for more plot at the beginning.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="36359">I`d recommend this only for fans that want a comparison point for the old series.
I found it so disappointing and boring that I couldn`t get past the episode 2/3.

Pros: high resolution; modern graphics; old first episode is skipped; the worst comedy scenes were removed; overall fidelity to the old series (for the selection of scenes that was kept in this remake).

Cons: brings nothing new to the story; skips have removed the feeling of the rise of the band of Hawks; most of the screen time is for fights, so characters lack depth; stroboscopic animation in dreams is barely watchable; cheap CGI graphics; bland music everywhere.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="269108">I`ve been waiting for this anime for so many months ... And I`m disappointed, nothing new and poor animation ... only for the biggest fans ;|</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="54971">Can`t do anything wrong with Berserk`s plot, but I would still prefer the series</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="136978">This movie trilogy retells the event of the original 1997`1998 series with some differences and advances the story a bit further.
I`d recommend watching the old Berserk series before, but these movies are also worth watching. Especially, if appreciate the animation quality and the brilliant music composed by Sagisu Shirou of Evangelion fame.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="541020">i really liked this new adaption of berserk. so far after watching the first movie it follows the original berserk series almost 100% by adding some fresh new touch with new cgi/animation. if you are a fan of the series this is a must see, all others very recommended, you can`t go wrong here</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="602201">Overall the movies are great, but they lack character development. If you first read the manga and/or watched the first series, you will have a much easier time understanding what is going on. Personally I find it a great addition to an awesome series.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="243082">The Berserk 1997 anime still remains my all time favourite anime so I`ve been waiting for this one.

Loved the combat, very well done, voice changes didn`t really bother me neither did the CG so many people seem to have a problem with.

Music wasn`t great if I`m honest, which is something I loved about the original, but the second part looks to have better music. As expected it moves pretty fast and crams the first 10 episodes (~200 mins) of the anime into a 76m long movie so it`s going to feel like it`s missing a lot of the feeling.

It`s certainly worth watching but I`ll wait to rate it since it`s not a standalone movie, it needs the other two and I`ll rate it when I`ve seen all three.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="30352">Good stuff.
U will enjoy it there are gores and theres good plot</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="537793">Must see for Berserk fans! Amazing backgrounds and mix of cg\standard animation. Don`t worry about CG, you don`t see it all the time.  If you have a chance to watch it in Movie Theater, don`t miss it. It`s hard to describe how good it`s on the big screen</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="442930">Some of the cg felt unnecessary and strange, but overall, it was really good.  The pacing was good and story is great as expected.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="322646">Loved this first movie. The opening is epic and in true Berserk style. Loved the way the camera swoops and is positioned in action packed sequences. Storywise, it follows the manga closely in my opinion although it races through at some points. The CG is a welcome edition which makes it all more epic (love it or hate). Though, I love it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="241044">Splendide</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="559673">masterpiece!!!!!!!!!!!and the manga... best ever created!!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="398648">Finally watched all the episodes and movies, and now I can say it was one of the most epic anime that I ever watched. It`s impossible to not love it, really enjoyable. Now let`s read the manga :D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="256352">superb ! Just watch it !</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="103542">The Berserk movies had a lot to live up to and somehow they managed to do it. The first Arc is condensed extremely well into three movies and paced to absolute perfection. The animation is simply beautiful and the CGI doesn`t feel gratuitous at all. The gore and brutality remains faithful to the manga. If they decide to animate where the series ended, this may just be the greatest anime film series ever produced. Can`t recommend it enough.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.berserkfilm.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="515" type="Direction">Kubooka Toshiyuki</name>
<name id="2163" type="Chief Animation Direction">Onda Naoyuki</name>
<name id="738" type="Animation Work">Studio 4C</name>
<name id="7260" type="Chief Animation Direction">Iwataki Satoshi</name>
<name id="2163" type="Character Design">Onda Naoyuki</name>
<name id="666" type="Original Work">Miura Kentarou</name>
<name id="1955" type="Music">Sagisu Shirou</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the manga by http://anidb.net/cr666 [Miura Kentarou] serialised in the seinen magazine http://anidb.net/cr30430 [Young Animal].
http://anidb.net/ch650 [Guts], an immensely strong sword-for-hire, has little direction in his life, simply fighting one battle after the next. However, this all changes suddenly when he meets and is bested by http://anidb.net/ch660 [Griffith], a handsome and charismatic young man who leads the Band of the Hawk mercenary army. After Guts joins the Band and the friendship between the two men begins to blossom, http://anidb.net/ch654 [Casca], the tough, lone swordswoman in the Band of the Hawk, struggles to accept Guts and the influence he has on the world around her. While the two men begin to fight together, Griffith continues his rise to power, all seemingly in order to reach his mysterious, prophesied goals. What lengths will Guts and Griffith go to in order to reach these goals, and where will fate take the two men?
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2561">8.00</permanent>
<temporary count="2579">7.85</temporary>
<review count="2">8.50</review>
</ratings>
<picture>80211.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13800</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>13799</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>12397</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12115</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>10218</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>12113</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5150</identifier>
<identifier>wvkqqc</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.younganimal.com/berserk/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.berserkfilm.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.viz.com/berserk</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>List_of_Berserk_films</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>剣風伝奇ベルセルク#.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1.E6.98.A0.E7.94.BB.E7.89.88</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2611</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>341413</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>341412</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>340341</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14209</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>berserk_project</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B00AE2KWYS</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="520" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-14">
<name>nopan</name>
<description>The character foregoes underwear.</description>
<picurl>162753.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1253" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-12-08">
<name>ambitious</name>
<description>having a strong desire for success or achievement; wanting power, money, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1286" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-28">
<name>megalomaniac</name>
<description>Megalomania is a psychopathological condition characterized by delusional fantasies of power, relevance, and omnipotence, and by inflated self-esteem.&#13;
&#13;
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>70559.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1609" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-03-01">
<name>elf</name>
<description>The origin of Elves (Norse; álfar(elves), álfr(elf)) can be found in ancient Norse mythology, in which, elves are described as divine, or near-divine, race of humanoids (Vættir), likened to the Æsir. In common description they are described as sage and immortal beings occupying the threshold between humans and the gods. In some cases humans that were beloved by the gods became elves within their lives. Ancient Elves are delineated into a pair of similar but distinct races; Light Elves (Ljósálfar) and Dark Elves (Svartálfar), each originating from separate homes within the nine worlds of Yggdrasil. Within the Poetic Edda the differences are commonly ascribed as:
"There is one place there that is called the Elf Home (Álfheimr which is the elven city). People live there that are named the light elves (Ljósálfar). But the dark elves (Dökkálfar) live below in earth, in caves and the dark forest and they are unlike them in appearance - and more unlike them in reality. The Light Elves are brighter than the sun in appearance, but the Dark Elves are blacker than pitch." (Snorri, Gylfaginning 17, Prose Edda)</description>
<picurl>63489.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2090" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-17">
<name>trauma</name>
<description>Character with emotional or psychological injury, caused by single or multiple events/experiences in the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2640" parentid="2625" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-06-02">
<name>alternative past</name>
<description>An anime that takes place in an alternative past is an anime that clearly does not belong to the future or the present, and isn`t tied particularly closely to our history, or has ties to our history but only as a premise: there are too many things that don`t make sense for the time-period. In some cases there is futuristic technology present, but the overall setting still feels that of the past. However the setting must still take place on Earth, since we can not know if the history of a fantasy world is an alternate one or not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2647" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>high fantasy</name>
<description>Generally a serious and epic story set in an invented world. The world may be more or less based on real world environments or history. Typical fantastical elements are usually dominating, such as elves, dwarves, magicians, invented languages, quests; just to name a few.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2649" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>dark fantasy</name>
<description>Focus set on darker themes in a fantasy setting, sometimes leaning towards horror elements. Bleak and pessimistic tones often dominate. Dark supernatural beings like vampires may play a significant role.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2709" parentid="4656" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-30">
<name>netorare</name>
<description>Netorare is what happens when the protagonist gets his wife/girlfriend stolen from him by someone else. It is a sexual fetish designed to cause sexual jealousy by way of having the heroine indulge in sexual activity with someone other than the protagonist.
The intent or reason causing the scenario does not have any bearing as to whether the scenario is netorare or netori; perspective is the only differentiating factor.
Netorare is generally caused by, but not limited to: the stealing party has malicious intent to harm the protagonist, or the wife/girlfriend hopes to improve their relationship by causing the protagonist to be jealous.
Netorare Type A
The heroine is willingly cheating on the protagonist with another guy, and enjoys every second of it. No rape, blackmail, drugs etc. involved; it`s consensual sex from the very beginning.
Netorare Type B
Initially, the heroine is raped, blackmailed, drugged, or otherwise tricked to have sex with someone other than the protagonist. However, she eventually starts enjoying it, and the sex becomes fully consensual in the end.
Netorare Type C
The heroine is raped in front of the protagonist, and he can only helplessly watch it. It`s non-consensual from start to finish.
Note: Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t2716 [Netori].</description>
<picurl>150946.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2843" parentid="7220" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-08">
<name>sexual abuse -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is to be split into the following new tags under the http://anidb.net/t7220 [sexual abuse] category. Afterwards, delete this tag.

* http://anidb.net/t7222 [groping / molestation]
* http://anidb.net/t1306 [chikan]
* http://anidb.net/t7221 [psychological sexual abuse]
* http://anidb.net/t2715 [rape / attempted rape]
</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2895" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>dark-skinned girl</name>
<description>The anime features a girl with dark skin. A fetish of sorts, since the other protagonists are usually as white-skinned as porcelain dolls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3322" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-04">
<name>remake</name>
<description>This anime is a remake of a previously released story, anime, or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3327" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-08">
<name>manly</name>
<description>Masculinity is possessing qualities or characteristics considered typical of or appropriate to a man.
Typical characteristics associated with masculinity are: courage, a strong physique, competitive, strong willed, and a sense of honor.
Very important for being considered masculine however is the ability to inspire respect from your fellow brethren and/or being perceived as a virile man by the opposite sex.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3805" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-13">
<name>European stylised</name>
<description>The anime`s setting is crafted in some classic European style. Imagine an architectural and cultural mix of London, Paris, Rome, Berlin, Prague, and other cities as they were at any point in the 19th century or earlier.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4084" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-03-20">
<name>dark atmosphere</name>
<description>Usually metaphorical. Sometimes literal. At times both!
Typically this refers to the fact that the story is set in a grim, dog eat dog milieu — for example a decaying city.
Often the characters are just doing what they need to do to survive, with little or no expectation that their lives can be better. And often characters may feel they do not have any real choice in what they do.
And yes, occasionally the setting is actually dark — be it night or perpetually heavy cloudy sky and rain. It all adds to the oppressive, hopeless feeling of the show.
You probably will not feel uplifted or happy after watching this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4153" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-15">
<name>dark</name>
<description>Describes the overall mood in this anime. Dark colours, a non-happy, often tragic story, dark lighting, many night scenes or constantly dark skies, and continuous rain all contribute to setting this mood.
The anime will often be quite depressing to watch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4226" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>paradise lost</name>
<description>Derived from the Biblical story of the Fall of Man: the temptation of Adam and Eve by the fallen angel Satan and their expulsion from the Garden of Eden.
This tag is used to demonstrate the unbearable loss, the feeling of losing everything along with every single bit of happiness. It prerequisites a small peaceful period of happiness. The main reason for losing "his/her paradise" can either be the death/sacrifice of an important character or even a betrayal. Usually the anime loses a lot of its former glory afterwards.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4516" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>animal abuse</name>
<description>Violence against animals. The humane society will not like this.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4520" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>betrayal</name>
<description>Friends become enemies.
Strong bonds of trust receive violations of confidence while friendships are faithlessly given up or revealed to have been false from the start.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4565" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-08-17">
<name>war-zone realities</name>
<description>War is hell. This tag is for when characters experience the hell of war... not just the exciting stuff blowing up part.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4656" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-06">
<name>infidelity</name>
<description>Infidelity is a violation of a couple`s assumed or stated contract regarding emotional and/or sexual exclusivity, sometimes according to the subjective feeling that one`s partner has violated a set of rules or relationship norms; this violation results in feelings of sexual jealousy and rivalry. What constitutes an act of infidelity is dependent upon the exclusivity expectations within the relationship. In marital relationships, exclusivity expectations are commonly assumed although they are not always met. When they are not met, research has found that psychological damage can occur, including feelings of rage and betrayal, lowering of sexual and personal confidence, and damage to self-image.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>191139.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5571" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-08-27">
<name>Greek mythology</name>
<description>The anime is derived or draws elements from the Greek mythology, and as such features some mythological characteristics of Ancient Greece. Those may be creatures, such as the Centaur or Hydra, tales, such as that of the Trojan War, or even the Gods themselves, like Zeus or Poseidon. More subtle references also count, such as the careful usage of names of places or people that hold significance in the myths.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5890" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-10">
<name>medieval</name>
<description>Setting is placed in the so called "dark ages". It can be either European style, oriental style or Chinese/Japanese style of castles, armour, ways of fighting etc.. 
Also the average education is weak, superstition is high and fights are settled on foot or horseback. Furthermore the level to technology is rather low.
Note: The perceived low level of cultural and technological evolution may be offset by an influx of magic (fantasy stories) or very sophisticated technology that the inhabitants choose to make less obvious to the viewer.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="650" type="main character in" update="2015-05-04">
<rating votes="828">9.33</rating>
<name>Guts</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Guts is the primary protagonist of the story. He is a tall, muscular man who wields the Dragon Slayer, a zweihänder or 2 handed sword about 7` long and 12" wide at its base. Described in the manga as more of a table-sized slab of iron than a blade, the Dragon Slayer`s massive size makes it the ideal weapon for slaying apostles of the God Hand. Guts` left hand is prosthetic, a replacement for the one he lost when Griffith attempted to sacrifice him to the forces of hell; it folds back to expose a hidden cannon within the wrist. Guts also carries throwing knives, miniature bombs, a dagger, and even a repeating crossbow that can be mounted onto his prosthetic arm.</description>
<picture>14962.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28214" picture="49071.jpg">Iwanaga Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="654" type="main character in" update="2008-12-11">
<rating votes="228">7.64</rating>
<name>Casca</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Casca was the only female soldier in the original Band of the Hawk and is behind only Griffith and Guts in swordsmanship. Her ambivalent relationship to both of them makes her moody and capricious. Casca joins the Band of the Hawk after Griffith empowers her to save herself from a sexual assault by a nobleman.</description>
<picture>14964.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20501" picture="186150.jpg">Yukinari Toa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="660" type="main character in" update="2009-06-10">
<rating votes="227">7.07</rating>
<name>Griffith</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Griffith is the founder and leader of the mercenary unit known as the Band of the Hawk. Extraordinarily charismatic, intelligent, and handsome, his skill with his sabre and tactics gives him and his band the reputation of invincibility, making him the favoured choice of the Midland King, who was locked in a century long war with the Empire of Tudor. Griffith is willing to sacrifice everything for his dream of his own kingdom and believes that he is destined for things greater than the average man.</description>
<picture>14967.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2001" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-06">
<rating votes="13">3.22</rating>
<name>Bazuso</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bazuso is one of the earliest named adversaries faced by a young Guts at the beginnings of the Golden Age story arc, almost marking his induction into the Band of the Hawks.</description>
<picture>89134.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29623" picture="78236.jpg">Kendou Kobayashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2002" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="32">5.44</rating>
<name>Rickert</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rickert was the youngest in the old Band of the Hawk; he was just a child.
He is one of the few surviving members of the original Band of the Hawk. After the Eclipse, which he wasn`t present at, he lived with Godo, the smith who created Guts` Dragon Slayer, and became his smith apprentice. For the next two years, Rickert`s talents as a smith grew. He tweaked Guts`s armour and replaced his old crossbow with a repeating crossbow. During his stay with Godo, Rickert had remained completely unaware of what transpired at the Eclipse. He was thus able to put the past behind him. It wasn`t until after Guts, Griffith and Casca were reunited at the Hill of Swords that he learned of the original Band of the Hawk`s fate. Even still, Griffith offered Rickert a position in the new Band of the Hawk. After the death of Godo and the destruction of his mine by Zodd, Rickert travels with Godo`s adopted granddaughter, Erica.</description>
<picture>16792.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1798" picture="20493.jpg">Kotobuki Minako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2003" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-07">
<rating votes="74">7.81</rating>
<name>Judeau</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Judeau was part of the original Band of the Hawk and was a former circus performer, which was the background for his prowess in knife-throwing. He was one of Griffith`s most valued fighters, but his greatest strength came from his ability to read the emotions of other people, as shown by him being the first to notice the growing bond between Guts and Casca, even before the two themselves. Quiet, calm, and practical, Judeau was often the voice of reason when handling the more volatile Hawks like Corkus. Noble and generous, Judeau usually put his companions in the band above him, showing himself to be at ease with understanding matters of the heart and inquiring the true intentions of those who surround him. Judeau himself admitted that he was pretty good at a lot of things but was not a stand-out in any of them. His honesty and down-to-earth personality made him a kind of "average joe" character that people could easily identify with. Throughout his tenure with the Band of the Hawk, he was secretly in love with Casca, but he never acted on it out of respect for Guts and Casca`s feelings for each other.
He died during the Eclipse, sacrificing himself for Casca in order to keep her, the leader of the Hawks, alive. In his final moments, Judeau questions what his last words should be, and settles with telling Casca she cried a lot. As he falls down he mourns over the fact that Casca never saw him as anything other than useful.</description>
<picture>16793.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2004" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="25">5.31</rating>
<name>Pippin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pippin is a massive dark-skinned man who wields an equally massive mace. A former miner who lent his strength to the old Band of the Hawk, his fast reactions and raw strength save the skin of the Hawks on many occasions. Despite his massive physical stature, Pippin proves to be a kind and patient individual, as shown when he dragged Guts to the festivities, keeping his cool even when Guts hit him and made him bleed. A man of few words, which, along with his appearance, might have others wrongly doubt his intelligence. He was often associated with Rickert, who he seemed to share a big-brother relationship with.
During the Eclipse, he held off an Apostle while Casca and Judeau tried to escape. Pippin was seen by Guts one last time before the Count ripped him to shreds.</description>
<picture>16794.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29002" picture="151326.jpg">Fujiwara Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2005" type="appears in" update="2009-01-07">
<rating votes="13">2.86</rating>
<name>Gambino</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Guts` adoptive father, and leader of a mercenary band, Gambino trained Guts to be a mercenary like himself and even gave Guts his first scar (across his nose) during a practice fight. Gambino sold Guts as a sex slave one night to Donovan, a pederast soldier, who anally raped young Guts and whom Guts brutally murders afterwards. Gambino was later hit by a cannon blast in battle and lost his leg and the ability to fight. This incensed his anger towards Guts even further, as he also blamed Guts for the death of his lover, Shizu. Gambino became drunk one night and tried to kill Guts in a fit of rage. He admits he sold Guts to Donovan for three silver coins right before Guts killed him in self-defense. He constantly haunts Guts during his early years before the massacre of the original Band of Hawk.</description>
<picture>16796.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29682" picture="78341.jpg">Iwata Yasunobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2007" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-06">
<rating votes="37">2.55</rating>
<name>Corkus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A loud-mouthed ex-thief, Corkus, was fond of delusions of grandeur and was constantly at odds with Guts. He was the leader of his own band of thieves before he joined the old Band of the Hawk, being one of the longest running members. He was the one who first tried to assault Guts in order to rob him of the money earned defeating Bazuso, but failed miserably, making Casca, followed by Griffith, step in. Because of that, he always held a grudge against Guts and never fully accepted him as a Hawk. Surprisingly, when Casca and Rickert blamed Guts for Griffith`s capture, Corkus refused to agree with them due to his belief that they overestimated Guts` importance to the Band.
Despite his unappealing nature, he was one of the most loyal members of the Band of the Hawk, staying with them until his death during the Eclipse, where he convinces himself that everything had been a dream, since it had been just too good to be true.</description>
<picture>89132.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8994" picture="234982.jpg">Matsumoto Yoshiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2008" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-07">
<rating votes="32">2.92</rating>
<name>Adon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Adon was a principal opponent of the original Band of the Hawk during the war between Midland and Chudor. He commanded the Blue Whale Ultra Heavy Armoured Fierce Assault Annihilation Knight Corps. He regularly bragged about special attacks and defences that he called "Coborlwitz family secrets".</description>
<picture>16799.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2009" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-06">
<rating votes="46">8.02</rating>
<name>Zodd</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Zodd, also known as Nosferatu Zodd, or Zodd the Immortal, an apostle who has lived for three centuries fighting countless battles in search of worthy opponents. Zodd has the ability to transform from his human-like form into a more menacing creature, resembling that of a minotaur with the face and tail of a tiger along with a pair of bat-like wings that he can retract and grow at will.
Zodd first encountered and defeated Guts and Griffith during a castle raid, ultimately deciding to spare them upon realizing Griffith`s crimson behelit and Guts` inevitable fate.</description>
<picture>89133.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2012" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-06">
<rating votes="18">2.09</rating>
<name>Midland no Kokuou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The elderly ruler of Midland who had been fighting a century long war with the neighbouring kingdom of Tudor. Burdened by the demands and responsibilities of his throne, the King`s only comfort was his daughter Charlotte whom to him was the sole source of warmth in his existence. Due to the Band of the White Hawk`s victories on the battlefield, the King supported Griffith despite his common heritage and the disapproval of the nobility and eventually bestowed upon him command over all of Midland`s armies.
However, after Griffith slept with Charlotte, the king became enraged and ordered that Griffith be imprisoned and tortured. He also ordered an attack on the leaderless Band of the Hawk, resulting in the Band`s numbers being drastically reduced over the following two years. Driven to the brink of insanity by the fear of losing his only comfort, the king then proceeded to attempt to rape Charlotte who barely managed to fight him off. Afterwards, the guilt over what he had nearly done caused the King`s health to slowly degrade to the point that his hair turned white and his body wasted away to skin and bones. When Griffith was rescued a year later by Guts and the surviving members of the Hawks; the king sent first a group of five Bakiraka, and then the Black Dog Knights led by Wyald to kill Griffith. Shortly before Griffith was reincarnated on Earth, the King`s health had further faded to the point that he was unable to leave his bed anymore. In his final moments, he demanded to see his daughter, but Charlotte no longer recognised him as her father and refused to see him. Before he died, the King had a final vision of Griffith being reunited with Charlotte whereupon he realised the real reason he had supported Griffith was his hope that Griffith would take his place and free him from the cold loneliness of the throne.</description>
<picture>89126.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3379" picture="24407.jpg">Katsube Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2013" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-06">
<rating votes="19">2.41</rating>
<name>Julius</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yurius was the brother of the king and the leader of the White Dragon Knights. He resented the rise of Griffith and the Band of the Hawk in the favor of the king, especially given Griffith`s common heritage.
As a result, he plotted with Minister Foss to kill Griffith by arranging for a stray arrow to be fired during a hunt. The plan went awry when the arrow struck Griffith`s crimson behelit and the king concluded that the attack was meant for Princess Charlotte, who was accompanying Griffith. In retaliation, Griffith sent Guts to assassinate Julius. Guts managed the deed, but as he was escaping, Julius` son Adonis discovered him. Guts regretfully killed the boy before fleeing into the sewers.</description>
<picture>89127.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2014" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-06">
<rating votes="29">4.33</rating>
<name>Charlotte</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The princess of Midland, Charlotte fell in love with Griffith almost at first sight.
After Guts defeated Griffith in their duel, Griffith slept with Charlotte and was imprisoned and tortured for a year as a result. During that time, Charlotte continued to pine over Griffith and eventually was the one who provided the route for the Hawks to rescue him from prison.</description>
<picture>89131.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2017" type="appears in" update="2017-10-25">
<rating votes="7">2.94</rating>
<name>Laban</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Laban was a high-ranking noble in Midland`s Court. During the One Hundred Year War, Laban led some of the Midland`s forces and was an early supporter of http://anidb.net/ch660 [Griffith]. He agreed with http://anidb.net/ch2012 [the king] that Griffith should be judged on battlefield merit.
Source: Berserk Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>208559.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="297" picture="233915.jpg">Ootsuka Houchuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2019" type="appears in" update="2012-06-06">
<rating votes="16">6.10</rating>
<name>Adonis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Son of General Julius.</description>
<picture>89128.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30648" picture="82105.jpg">Mizuma Maki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2020" type="appears in" update="2009-01-08">
<rating votes="7">2.33</rating>
<name>Hassan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16822.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3384" picture="24411.jpg">Arikawa Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2021" type="appears in" update="2009-01-08">
<rating votes="9">1.89</rating>
<name>Gennon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16826.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="283" picture="17113.jpg">Yao Kazuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2022" type="appears in" update="2009-01-09">
<rating votes="19">6.17</rating>
<name>Boscogn</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16877.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="464" picture="24725.jpg">Sugou Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2042" type="appears in" update="2009-01-08">
<rating votes="14">3.88</rating>
<name>Erica</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16848.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2045" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-08">
<rating votes="16">5.60</rating>
<name>Gaston</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The second in command of the raiding team of the Band of Hawks. Gaston is passionate about his duties and extremely loyal to Guts, even going so far as to suggest breaking off from the Hawks to form a gang of thieves with Guts as the leader.</description>
<picture>16851.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="283" picture="17113.jpg">Yao Kazuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2046" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-08">
<rating votes="36">7.36</rating>
<name>Slan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The female member of the God Hand, Slan takes on the form of a naked woman with black leathery wings and vine-like hair. She is a sadomasochist who thrives on cruelty and the effect it has on those who observe it. She appears to have a fascination with Guts when she manifests in the Qlippoth to confront him and feed on his negative emotions, having as well shown an interest in his incredible strength and survivability when the Count summoned the God Hand. Her interest is probably derived from her sadomasochistic tendencies from how much Guts suffers in his journey.</description>
<picture>16852.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2047" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-08">
<rating votes="12">6.36</rating>
<name>Ubik</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The God Hand Ubik has the form of a small floating demon wearing glasses and having tentacle-like legs. Ubik appears to be a deceiver; he is able to conjure up images from the past to persuade potential Apostles to fulfil the ritual of sacrifice. It is he who convinced Griffith to continue walking towards his dream as a demon.</description>
<picture>16853.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="173" picture="150067.jpg">Chafuurin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2048" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-08">
<rating votes="12">2.82</rating>
<name>Conrad</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Conrad is concerned with inevitability and doom and appears as a puckered human face with the body of a massive wood louse. He summoned the mound that lifted Griffith skyward, above the rest of the Hawks. In a town in Western Midland he is shown as having destroyed the populace with the Black Plague, his head materialising from the plague-carrying rats that infested the town.</description>
<picture>16854.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2049" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="14">4.45</rating>
<name>Void</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Void is a member of the God Hand with a large, exposed brain, eyes stitched shut and lips peeled back. He is the most philosophical God Hand member and is primarily concerned with analysing and controlling the course of destiny. Void is the one who brands the sacrifices made by tortured souls in order for them to become apostles and achieve their dream. His cloak and body seem to be distorted and he has the power to open up a sort of interdimensional mirror portal at his own will. Also notable, he has six fingers on each hand.
Apparently the nemesis of the Skull Knight, who he may have sacrificed himself in a long passed story similar to Guts, he seems to be the leader of the group. In the anime, Void also has the role of narrator, introducing each episode and previewing the next. His appearance is more identical to a Cenobite then the others mainly because he has deformities like one.</description>
<picture>16855.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="544" picture="238510.jpg">Ogawa Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2050" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="39">3.99</rating>
<name>Femto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Femto is the incarnation of Griffith as a member of the God Hand. During the Incarnation Ceremony, he is reincarnated with a human body but given the gift of supernatural charisma and yet other unknown powers, continuing to chase his dream of a kingdom backed up by his new Band of the Hawk. Femto`s body appears as dark armour with cape-like wings on the back, with a demonic version of Griffith`s familiar hawk-beak helmet.
His currently displayed powers are flight via his dark, cape-like wings, a spherical energy shield that protects his body from attacks such as Guts` arm-cannon, and a powerful blast of dark energy that can rip apart even an Apostle in one hit. His first act as a member of the God Hand is to rape Casca, tainting the child she is bearing, which is Guts`.</description>
<picture>16856.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33056" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="8">8.23</rating>
<name>God Hand</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The God Hand are a powerful group of five demons, each corresponding to a finger or thumb, directly below the Idea of Evil in power and authority. All of them were originally humans who were chosen by the Idea of Evil to serve its purpose of giving reason for humanity`s suffering. They used the Crimson Behelit to sacrifice a large group of their followers in order to transcend their humanity. It is unknown whether there are five Crimson Behelits or whether the same one came to each of them in turn.
The God Hand can`t take corporeal form in the mortal plane; if they do appear there, it is a construct, formed by whatever is at hand. They can also appear during an eclipse ceremony where in there is an area that acts as a junction in between the astral realm and the human realm.
Most of the God Hand`s names are inspired by Science-Fiction novels. It is also worth noting that the design of the God Hand characters shows similarity to Cenobites from Hellraiser movie series, based on Clive Barker novella, of which Miura is believed to be a fan.</description>
<picture>72826.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42877" type="appears in" update="2012-03-25">
<rating votes="21">8.05</rating>
<name>Shounen Guts</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>84582.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39784" picture="153564.jpg">Inoue Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43310" type="appears in" update="2012-04-07">
<rating votes="9">2.27</rating>
<name>Goumonkan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85451.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="173" picture="150067.jpg">Chafuurin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43318" type="appears in" update="2012-04-07">
<rating votes="17">5.32</rating>
<name>Shounen Griffith</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85465.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32886" picture="182081.jpg">Takeuchi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43320" type="appears in" update="2012-04-07">
<rating votes="5">3.00</rating>
<name>Rouba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85467.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38157" picture="139873.jpg">Ginpunchou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45687" type="appears in" update="2012-06-06">
<rating votes="3">2.95</rating>
<name>Guillen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>89129.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="35009" picture="130977.jpg">Egami Shingo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45688" type="appears in" update="2017-10-19">
<rating votes="3">2.59</rating>
<name>Anna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Anna is the faithful and loyal servant of http://anidb.net/ch2014 [Charlotte].</description>
<picture>208560.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32886" picture="182081.jpg">Takeuchi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49432" type="appears in" update="2017-10-25">
<rating votes="6">5.85</rating>
<name>Silat</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Silat is a highly skilled and agile Kushan fighter first encountered by http://anidb.net/ch650 [Guts] in the Golden Age Arc. He is the leader of the Bakiraka clan and the impressive http://anidb.net/ch82448 [Tapasa] group are his bodyguards.
He claims to be a man with a "bird`s eye view of things". Though he says that his clan abandoned self esteem when they chose to be assassins, he is shown to be proud of his abilities and also of his clan.
His combat style is similar to Kalarippayattu (a martial arts form existing in South India) and uses many Indian weapons used by Rajput warriors, though Guts has referred to him as a circus performer due to Silat`s exotic appearance, acrobatics and his almost theatrical tendency to call out his attacks. Despite Guts` mockery, Silat is one of the strongest human warriors in Midland and among his race the Kushans too, as he defeated many knights in the tournament and overpowered http://anidb.net/ch654 [Casca] later as well as killing a few trained Hawk members. Silat`s skill only fell short when faced with the overwhelming strength of Guts, who he now considers his rival.
Source: Berserk Wiki</description>
<picture>208620.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49433" type="appears in" update="2017-10-18">
<rating votes="40">7.96</rating>
<name>Dokuro no Kishi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Skull Knight is an enigmatic figure and a self-proclaimed foe of the inhumans, having waged war against demonkind for a millennium.
An ancient being, the Skull Knight is aloof and mysterious with great understanding of the deterministic nature of the world and foreknowledge of the predestined. As such, he possesses a brutally realistic worldview, oftentimes citing the inevitability of causality`s flow. Despite this outlook, he has proven to be quite heroic, saving http://anidb.net/ch650 [Guts] and his comrades on multiple occasions. However, http://anidb.net/ch87815 [Flora] has questioned whether his actions are out of genuine care or merely a means of furthering his own agenda, a query which the Skull Knight turns a deaf ear to. He ultimately values the human will to survive and defy fate, encouraging Guts to contend against causality and aptly naming him "struggler". He is also quite insightful, warning Guts that http://anidb.net/ch654 [Casca]`s true desire might differ from the Black Swordsman`s own.
The Skull Knight has a long-spanning rivalry with Nosferatu http://anidb.net/ch2009 [Zodd], who is always excited to fight the knight, calling him "old friend". He is normally indifferent to Zodd, only showing irritation at the apostle`s efforts to impede him, though he does openly acknowledge their history and rivalry. He has also known and apparently had a close relationship with the witch Flora for at least several hundred years.
Source: Berserk Wiki</description>
<picture>208529.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81092" type="appears in" update="2017-10-18">
<rating votes="8">2.07</rating>
<name>Azan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Azan is an old-fashioned knight who practices a code of honor and loyalty. Formerly a devout Vice-Commander of the Holy Iron Chain Knights, he leaves to become a supporting companion to http://anidb.net/ch650 [Guts] and a member of his party.
Azan is an elder man who is notorious for almost always wearing armor. He`s balding and has a thick mustache. His helmet is reminiscent of a samurai warrior`s kabuto, and his constitution is muscular, but stout. Recently, he was shown to be a bit taller than dwarves.
Since Azan follows old fashioned code of honor. when he fought Guts one on one he ordered the others to stand down. He is shown to care for his fellow knights as shown when he felt ashamed when he fainted and trapped under the rappels and was unable to save them. He is shown to help others whenever he can as when he helped http://anidb.net/ch87813 [Schierke] and her friends against the pirates without being asked.
Source: Berserk Wiki</description>
<picture>208493.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="81094" type="appears in" update="2017-10-18">
<rating votes="19">7.28</rating>
<name>Serpico</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Serpico is one of the main characters of the series. He is a servant and illegitimate son of the noble Vandimion family who would join http://anidb.net/ch650 [Guts]` Traveling Party along with his half-sister http://anidb.net/ch81096 [Farnese]. He is polite in manner, and very loyal, sincere, and protective of Farnese.
He is a slender young man with blond hair. His most notable feature is that his eyes are closed at almost all times, except for when he is very serious. He is often compared to a fox because of this. While a member of the Holy Iron Chain Knights, Serpico wore silvery-white armor around a green shirt with matching scarf and skirt. After leaving the Iron Chain Knights, Serpico wears traveler`s garbs prior to receiving the Sylph Cloak. In combat, Serpico is a deft fencer, very clever and cunning.
From his terrible life on the streets, he has grown to show very little emotion, often hiding his true feelings behind a facade of incompetence or sarcasm. He is scared of fire and dislikes the sight of blood, which makes him an unlikely warrior. He learned from growing up poor that revenge only brings more revenge, and avoids creating these situations. Farnese would sometimes force him into duels with other nobles that insulted his honor, but, though he was always far better than his opponent, he chose to purposefully end it in a draw, as he was well aware that the nobles would want revenge. Serpico views Farnese as his guardian angel for saving him from his miserable life on the streets, and does not hate her, despite that she condemned his demented mother for being a heretic (when she, quite obviously, was not), and forced him to burn her himself. 
Source: Berserk Wiki</description>
<picture>208514.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="81095" type="appears in" update="2017-10-18">
<rating votes="21">5.47</rating>
<name>Puck</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Puck is the first of the companions that http://anidb.net/ch650 [Guts] makes during the latter`s days as the Black Swordsman. He is an elf of the pisky race, descendants of the ancient spirits of wind.
As an elf, Puck is, at first glance, similar to a miniature naked human. Upon closer inspection, Puck`s features as an elf become more distinct; his ears are elongated and pointed, he has insect-like wings on his back, and he lacks any kind of visible genitals. Puck sports blue hair that grows out in all directions at the front (similar to a tomato stem) and uniformly points backward in the back. Puck`s eyes are the same color as his hair, and he has a feminine facial structure, with large eyes and a soft jawline. He often holds a burdock, the closest thing to a weapon the elf possesses.
Puck is a whimsical and lighthearted presence that stands out in the dark and unforgiving world he lives in. Not one to take people`s behavior at face value, Puck prefers to find the inherent good in those he meets rather than dismiss them for what he initially sees. As such, Puck displays a great deal of patience when dealing with less-than-reputable characters, and in some cases (like Guts`) Puck does eventually come to find that they do possess some manner of morality and a reason for their brash actions.
Source: Berserk Wiki</description>
<picture>208516.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="81096" type="appears in" update="2017-10-25">
<rating votes="22">4.56</rating>
<name>Farnese</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Farnese is a noblewoman from the Vandimion family who led the Holy See`s ceremonial guard, the Holy Iron Chain Knights. She later becomes a member of http://anidb.net/ch650 [Guts]` traveling party.
Due to her upbringing and subsequent events, Farnese has a very complex but developing personality. Whenever she wanted she would whip, bite, and otherwise abuse http://anidb.net/ch81094 [Serpico] and even drink his blood. She does not know that he is her half-brother. As a child, she treated him as a possession, and she reminded him frequently of this status. Her lack of empathy due to her poor upbringing along with the praise she received in joining in a witch burning provoked her to hunt down and burn supposed witches and pagans at the stake. This fueled a secret sadistic pleasure that she constantly tried to deny.
Source: Berserk Wiki</description>
<picture>208498.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="122776" update="2010-09-28">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2010-09-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Commercial 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122937" update="2010-10-05">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2010-10-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Commercial 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122938" update="2010-10-05">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2010-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Commercial 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122939" update="2010-10-05">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2010-10-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Commercial 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122940" update="2010-10-05">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2010-09-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Commercial 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131640" update="2014-01-07">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>80</length>
<airdate>2012-02-04</airdate>
<rating votes="35">6.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">覇王の卵</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Egg of the King</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`Oeuf du roi conquérant</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`uovo del re dominatore</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Бехерит Властителя</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haou no Tamago</title>
<summary>Guts, an immensely strong sword-for-hire, has little direction in his life, simply fighting one battle after the next. However, this all changes suddenly when he meets and is bested by Griffith, a beautiful and charismatic young man who leads the Band of the Hawk mercenary army. After Guts joins the Band and the relationship between the two men begins to blossom, Casca, the tough, lone swordswoman in the Band of the Hawk, struggles to accept Guts and the influence he has on the world around her. While the two men begin to fight together, Griffith continues to rise to power, all seemingly in order to reach his mysterious, prophesied goals. What lengths will Guts and Griffith go to in order to reach these goals, and where will fate take the two men?</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="133121" update="2011-09-21">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-07-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Teaser</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134524" update="2011-10-31">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-09-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">36巻発売記念スペシャルCM キス・キス篇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Spot 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">36-kan Hatsubai Kinen Special CM: Kiss Kiss Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134525" update="2011-10-31">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-09-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">36巻発売記念スペシャルCM それどころじゃねぇ! 篇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Spot 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">36-kan Hatsubai Kinen Special CM: Soredokoro Janee! Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134553" update="2011-11-01">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-10-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">予告編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yokokuhen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134916" update="2014-01-07">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>95</length>
<airdate>2012-06-23</airdate>
<rating votes="27">7.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドルドレイ攻略</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Battle for Doldrey</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La bataille de Doldrey</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Битва за Долдрей</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Doldrey Kouryaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134917" update="2012-11-10">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>110</length>
<airdate>2013-02-01</airdate>
<rating votes="28">8.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">降臨</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Advent</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`avent</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Сошествие</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kourin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158393" update="2014-03-09">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2012-02-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
