<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2002-01-11</startdate>
<enddate>2002-03-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Aquarian Age: Sign for Evolution</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">アクエリアンエイジ Sign for Evolution</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Aquarian Age: Sign for Evolution</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Aquarian Age: Sign for Evolution</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">L`âge du Verseau - Signe d`évolution</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2456" type="Same Setting">Aquarian Age: Saga II</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="406" approval="2" total="6">Kachou Ouji: Hard Rock Save the Space</anime>
<anime id="1554" approval="1" total="5">Mai-HiME</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="478723">It wasnt a very well known series but I found it and its concept very enjoyable.  Its at least a good serious watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="361783">A good choice of seinen-romance type anime.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.jvcmusic.co.jp/m-serve/tv/aquarian-age/</url>
<creators>
<name id="704" type="Music">Kajiura Yuki</name>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="3729" type="Character Design">Abe Hisashi</name>
<name id="5532" type="Series Composition">Souma Kazuhiko</name>
<name id="952" type="Original Work">Broccoli</name>
<name id="1921" type="Direction">Oohashi Yoshimitsu</name>
<name id="5751" type="Chief Animation Direction">Muroi Fumie</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch5895 [Kyouta] and his friends http://anidb.net/ch5898 [Shingo] and http://anidb.net/ch5899 [Jun] dream of becoming a big-time http://anidb.net/ch40597 [rock `n` roll band]. Kyouta`s childhood friend http://anidb.net/ch5896 [Yokko] supports them as they work to make their dream come true. Just as things start to turn in their favour, however, Kyouta learns that there are greater forces at work and an Earth-shattering conflict is about to begin. What part will Yokko and Kyouta play in the events to come?</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="712">3.91</permanent>
<temporary count="720">6.33</temporary>
<review count="1">4.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221220.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1147</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1224</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786</identifier>
<identifier>hhtemk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.jvcmusic.co.jp/m-serve/tv/aquarian-age/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Aquarian_Age:_Sign_for_Evolution</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>アクエリアンエイジ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>236841</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5062</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7983</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1876" parentid="2794" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>musical band</name>
<description>A musical ensemble also known as a music(al) group or music(al) band is a group of people who perform instrumental or vocal music, typically known by a distinct name.</description>
<picurl>10249.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2438" parentid="2794" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-16">
<name>idol</name>
<description>In Japanese culture, idols (アイドル) are media personalities in their teens and early twenties who are considered particularly cute and cuddly and who will, for a period ranging from several months to a few years, regularly appear in the mass media, e.g. as singers for J-pop groups, bit-part actors, TV personalities, models in photo spreads published in magazines, advertisements, etc.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>63097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2667" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>university</name>
<description>Since college/university students are typically at least eighteen years old, with stories covering mature everyday life topics, you will find the college setting quite often in seinen and josei anime.
Topics that can now be covered - as compared to High School settings - are higher education (i.e. coping with higher intellectual stress), the more adult party life (i.e. alcohol, smoking, sex), the issues of daily life vs. studying - especially when having to work to pay for bills, and finally the possible friction between those in and out of college.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2886" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>New Year`s Day</name>
<description>It is tradition in Japan to celebrate the new year at a Shinto shrine (hatsumode). The protagonists will offer some money, ring a bell at the end of a thick rope, and then pray for good fortune.
This usually goes along with gorging yourself at the many temporary food stalls, playing various games, and drawing a fortune.
The female characters in the anime will usually dress up in a kimono, to show off their traditional Japanese clothing, while watching the fireworks.</description>
<picurl>161028.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3170" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-10">
<name>occupation and career</name>
<description>The kind of anime which shows the career of a character, usually from the beginning.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3971" parentid="3170" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-07-04">
<name>entertainment industry</name>
<description>The show depicts how the entertainment industry works and how the main protagonists strive to cope with the sudden change to fame. At times this can be a very ugly sight indeed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4304" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-04-26">
<name>anti-climactic end</name>
<description>The story in this anime and the character development were building up so some special point, and the viewer will probably have been looking forward to this resolution. But the ending was a let-down.
This may have several reasons, e.g. it may simply be "bad" story-telling, or the animation studio ran out of money and had to prematurely end the story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="5895" type="main character in" update="2012-01-26">
<rating votes="1">5.14</rating>
<name>Kamikurata Kyouta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kamikurata Kyouta is in a band called http://anidb.net/ch40597 [Traffic Light Signal]. He writes lyrics, sings, and plays harmonica. He lives above http://anidb.net/ch40621 [his] http://anidb.net/ch40620 [family]`s business, Kamiya, a convenience store. He`s a high school student, and he dreams of being a rock star. If the rock star fantasy doesn`t work out he would rather take over his family business than go to college.
(Unbeknownst to him, he is a Mindbreaker with his power lying within his voice.)
Kyouta is calm and accepts what occurs in his life. Some would believe he does not care. Really, he does care but he keeps his concerns to himself. He is new to his rising fame and popularity but still sees things innocently.</description>
<picture>22978.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3060" picture="38602.jpg">Tanaka Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5896" type="main character in" update="2012-01-17">
<rating votes="3">6.99</rating>
<name>Sannou Yoriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sannou Yoriko is the female lead character of this story. She has no siblings but a http://anidb.net/ch40681 [cousin] who cares a lot for her. http://anidb.net/ch5895 [Kyouta] is her best friend; they have known each other since childhood, and she is possibly in love with him. She is two years Kyouta`s senior and already in college (while Kyouta is still struggling with his high school exam). She is a constant cheerleader to http://anidb.net/ch40597 [T.L. Signal] and maintains friendships with all three band members who nickname her "Yokko".
Yoriko is torn between two conflicts within herself. She struggles with the awakening powers in her, and her emerging feelings for Kyouta. It is rumored in her family that she has inherited the powers of the demigod http://anidb.net/ch40649 [Benzaiten]. The http://anidb.net/ch40598 [Arayashiki] are hungry for Yoriko to join their ranks and help them defeat their enemies, but http://anidb.net/ch40610 [other] http://anidb.net/ch5903 [forces] are also seeking Yoriko`s powers for ill. The race for her soul has begun.</description>
<picture>22979.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3061" picture="38603.jpg">Aoki Mayuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5897" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-17">
<name>Sakamoto Rumiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>In her hidden identity, Sakamoto Rumiko is an influential member of the Eastern Faction of http://anidb.net/ch40598 [Arayashiki], acting there as temporary leader-elect until the impending awakening of http://anidb.net/ch40649 [Benzaiten]. For this goal she is trying to sway her cousin http://anidb.net/ch5896 [Yoriko] into embracing her Arayashiki heritage as she`s fully aware of the http://anidb.net/ch40680 [alternative].</description>
<picture>22980.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="551" picture="228658.jpg">Nishimura Chinami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5898" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-21">
<rating votes="1">5.14</rating>
<name>Hirota Shingo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shingo is a bit older than his band mates but tends to be the least mature. He lives with his best friend and band mate http://anidb.net/ch5899 [Jun]. The two are very different and equal one another out. He plays guitar in http://anidb.net/ch40597 [T.L.Signal] and helps write the songs. He is playful and optimistic about the band`s future. Out of the band he is the loudest and most energetic. He likes the ladies and enjoys their attention. He is personable to everyone and never seems to meet a stranger.</description>
<picture>22981.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5899" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-26">
<rating votes="1">5.14</rating>
<name>Kojima Jun`ichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kojima Jun`ichi (nicknamed "Jun") is the keyboardist in http://anidb.net/ch40597 [T.L.Signal]. He lives with http://anidb.net/ch5898 [Shingo], who is his opposite. He enjoys cooking and keeping their apartment. He is short and quiet. He seems to be the most down to earth and insightful member of the band, and mostly keeps to himself. Jun always wears yellow sunglasses. The groupies tend to frighten him a bit, but he still enjoys their attention.</description>
<picture>22982.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5900" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-26">
<rating votes="1">9.37</rating>
<name>Yukimura Misato</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yukimura Misato is head of talent for http://anidb.net/ch40703 [Cosmopop]. She observes http://anidb.net/ch40597 [T.L.Signal] at their New Year`s gig, signs them to the record company immediately afterwards and works to get them a http://anidb.net/ch40661 [debut]. She wears pink glasses often, and is tall.
She is soft spoken but seems quite able to get what she wants when she wants it. She is up on current affairs and may be wiser to http://anidb.net/ch5895 [Kyouta]`s powers than she lets on.</description>
<picture>22983.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="404" picture="151682.jpg">Takashima Gara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5901" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="3">3.92</rating>
<name>Morino Kanae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kanae is a successful singer and is featured in many magazines. She is under the management of Abuto. He seems to keep her prisoner more than anything. Kanae has an interest in Kyouta and often flirts with him under Abuto`s sway.</description>
<picture>22984.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="216" picture="171983.jpg">Takahashi Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5902" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-26">
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<name>Ryuusei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ryuusei is the top pop singer in the country. He is very successful and is also signed to http://anidb.net/ch40703 [Cosmopop]. http://anidb.net/ch5895 [Kyouta] idealized him before meeting him. Ryuusei tends to be egotistic and seems jealous of Kyouta`s emerging success, yet pushes him to do better (through his own methods and for unknown reasons).
Ryuusei is in the know about http://anidb.net/ch5900 [Misato]`s secret plans with Kyouta and appears to be her ally.</description>
<picture>22985.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="375" picture="17221.jpg">Chiba Susumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5903" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-26">
<rating votes="1">7.49</rating>
<name>Abuto Keiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Abuto Keiji is http://anidb.net/ch5901 [Kanae]`s manager for the http://anidb.net/ch40702 [I.J.F.Music Japan] organization. He is violent, possessive and keeps her a prisoner, mentally and physically. He is jealous of http://anidb.net/ch5895 [Kyouta] for his powers and tries to separate him and http://anidb.net/ch5896 [Yoriko] for his own gain.</description>
<picture>22986.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5904" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-17">
<name>Kouno Yui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kouno Yui`s hidden identity is that she is an important member of http://anidb.net/ch40609 [Wiz-Dom]; http://anidb.net/ch5905 [Lemon] is her apprentice in both of her roles.
Yui wants control over http://anidb.net/ch5895 [Kyouta] for his powers as mindbreaker. For this purpose she manipulates http://anidb.net/ch5906 [Asumi] (a member of WIZ-DOM`s rival faction http://anidb.net/ch40611 [E.G.O.]) to gain influence over Kyouta`s future.</description>
<picture>22987.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="206" picture="228617.jpg">Hikami Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5905" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="1">3.07</rating>
<name>Lemon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is a student of the girl`s school and the apprentice to Yui. She seems to be lacking morals.</description>
<picture>22988.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="69" picture="171155.jpg">Itou Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5906" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-17">
<rating votes="2">5.61</rating>
<name>Hougetsu Asumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hougetsu Asumi is http://anidb.net/ch5895 [Kyouta]`s classmate at school. She is a good student and is cool tempered.
Despite not being one of Kyouta`s many groupies she is often dragged to his shows by her unlikely friend http://anidb.net/ch5907 [Kiriko]. Asumi never talked to Kyouta in class before but after Kiriko asked her to get her an autograph of Kyouta the events lead to them getting closer.</description>
<picture>22989.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="186" picture="16999.jpg">Minami Omi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5907" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-17">
<rating votes="2">4.45</rating>
<name>Heguri Kiriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Heguri Kiriko goes to the same school as http://anidb.net/ch5895 [Kyouta] and http://anidb.net/ch5906 [Asumi] but is an underclassman. She is always talking about Kyouta and seems to be one of his greatest fans. She is too scared to talk to him herself but is constantly attending the shows of http://anidb.net/ch40597 [his band].
Asumi and Kiriko hang out often though they are opposites. Kiriko`s personality is often hyper and sometimes childlike but innocent and sweet. She is devastated to find out that Kyouta has a love interest.</description>
<picture>22990.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="603" picture="223012.jpg">Jou Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40597" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-17">
<name>Traffic Light Signal</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>T.L.Signal (short for "Traffic Light Signal") is the band of keyboarder http://anidb.net/ch5899 [Kojima Jun`ichi], guitarist / songwriter http://anidb.net/ch5898 [Hirota Shingo], and vocalist / harmonica player / lyricist http://anidb.net/ch5895 [Kamikurata Kyouta].</description>
<picture>80082.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40598" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-21">
<name>Arayashiki</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Arayashiki (color: red) represent the eastern mages, primarily the onmyouji, who practice magic in theory with the Tao (Yin and Yang). Most of the members of this group seem to primarily represent Japanese mystics, but Chinese (and maybe even Indian) mages are included as well.
Although not as widespread as http://anidb.net/ch40611 [E.G.O.], most Arayashiki members are quite commonly found, even ignored, in modern Asian society. Most of their kind occupy Asia as a whole, with particular concentrations in Japan and China (two of the most socio-politically developed nations in the region). Typical Arayashiki skills include the ability to commune with spirits and nature, all inclined towards the Eastern forms of magic (such as onmyoujitsu). Some are even skilled with martial arts of varying types, as well as Eastern (particularly Japanese) archaic weaponry.
Common types of Arayashiki are: Miko (Japanese shrine-maidens) and other spiritually-inclined occupations. Many martial arts practitioners of the esoteric bent, especially the infamous Ninja, are also surprisingly common among them as bodyguards and spies. Of particular note is that members of the Ainu indigenous tribes of northern Japan also figure quite strongly with them. The remainder of the Arayashiki consist of spirits, especially those of various Asian mythological figures.
The Arayashiki are highly traditionalist, and clash constantly with their direct western opposite, the http://anidb.net/ch40609 [WIZ-DOM].
The name "Arayashiki" most likely comes from the Japanese word for the Buddhist Yogacharan concept of a store consciousness, the idea that karmic occurrences are "stored" in the unconscious and affect our karma and perceptions of the world.</description>
<picture>80264.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40599" type="appears in" update="2012-01-26">
<name>Arayashiki South</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The four Arayashiki leaders represent the Four Symbols of the Chinese constellation, corresponding to the four mythological creatures.
The creature of the South is Suzaku (朱雀), the Vermilion Bird.
Suzaku is hesitant about how to proceed and prefers to wait and see. She considers http://anidb.net/ch40602 [Seiryuu]`s plan of using http://anidb.net/ch5895 [Kyouta] as mindbreaker the perhaps only way of retrieving http://anidb.net/ch40649 [Benzaiten] but fears that the boy would be no match for http://anidb.net/ch40680 [Saraswati] yet, and premature action would only make things worse now.</description>
<picture>80613.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40600" type="appears in" update="2012-01-26">
<name>Arayashiki West</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The four Arayashiki leaders represent the Four Symbols of the Chinese constellation, corresponding to the four mythological creatures.
The creature of the West is Byakko (白虎), the White Tiger.
Byakko accuses http://anidb.net/ch5897 [Rumiko] of being responsible for losing http://anidb.net/ch40649 [Benzaiten]. She demands not to hand over http://anidb.net/ch40719 [Yoriko] to http://anidb.net/ch40610 [Darklore] unopposed but objects http://anidb.net/ch40602 [Seiryuu]`s plan of using http://anidb.net/ch5895 [Kyouta] as Yoriko would then just be under the control of another mindbreaker. Later she performs a sneak attack at Kyouta; when Rumiko intervenes, Byakko secedes from http://anidb.net/ch40598 [Arayashiki].</description>
<picture>80612.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="180" picture="171567.jpg">Saiga Mitsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40601" type="appears in" update="2012-01-26">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Arayashiki North</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The four Arayashiki leaders represent the Four Symbols of the Chinese constellation, corresponding to the four mythological creatures.
The creature of the North is Genbu (玄武), the Black Tortoise.
Genbu objects to twiddling her thumbs about http://anidb.net/ch40719 [Yoriko]`s situation. She agrees with http://anidb.net/ch40602 [Seiryuu]`s plan of using http://anidb.net/ch5895 [Kyouta] as the control by a mindbreaker can only be broken by another mindbreaker. When http://anidb.net/ch40599 [Suzaku] considers this plan too dangerous, Genbu demands action or else she would break away from http://anidb.net/ch40598 [Arayashiki].</description>
<picture>80616.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40602" type="appears in" update="2012-01-26">
<name>Arayashiki East</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The four Arayashiki leaders represent the Four Symbols of the Chinese constellation, corresponding to the four mythological creatures.
The creature of the East is Seiryuu (青龍), the Azure Dragon.
At first, Seiryuu suggests to remain passive; facing http://anidb.net/ch40600 [Byakko]`s allegation she would hand over the already awakened http://anidb.net/ch40719 [Yoriko] to http://anidb.net/ch40610 [Darklore] unopposed, Seiryuu then suggests to use http://anidb.net/ch5895 [Kyouta] as mindbreaker.</description>
<picture>80603.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40609" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-21">
<name>WIZ-DOM</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The members of WIZ-DOM (color: blue) represent western magery, which includes (but is not limited to) pagan, druidic, and even kabbalistic magic. These will be quite familiar to people in the west, as they go by many terms such as witches, warlocks, wizards, and all other European-influenced symbols of magery.
WIZ-DOM members hail from all sects of western magic. Some might even be disguised as clerics of an established religion; although whether they are really part of these religions (WIZ-DOM members have been seen in both Catholic and Protestant denominations), it remains to be seen whether these are genuine alliances or mere cover for their true nature.
WIZ-DOM members seem to be rather isolated from most of society. Since their magic is of the western variety, skilled in a wide variety of occult practices. Common WIZ-DOM archetypes include sorceresses, alchemists, priestesses, knights, spirits and ghosts, and artificial beings (such as elementals and golems) created via magic. There are also a lot of scholars, as well as people proficient in fortune-telling techniques and archaic western weaponry.
Western magic emphasizes control over the magical forces (as opposed to the emphasis on harmony espoused by Eastern magic and shamanism). WIZ-DOM considers the http://anidb.net/ch40598 [Arayashiki] their mortal enemy. They fight for their own ways and their own homelands and care little for anything else. Well, except power, that is.</description>
<picture>80266.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40610" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-21">
<name>Darklore</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Darklore faction (color: yellow; in the anime sometimes written as ダークネス = "Darkness") consists of demi-humans and monsters. Under these are the werewolves and other were-creatures, as well as non-humans such as faeries, mermaids and (possibly) elves. Theoretically, they may be the oldest faction among the five, hinting at a pre-human background, but this is still to be confirmed.
An extremely varied faction, Darklore is a conglomeration of ancient, forgotten races. Elves, lycanthropes (were-creatures), demons, mermaids, vampires, oni, fairies, even undead. Almost every beast or creature recounted in tales and myths can draw their origin from Darklore sightings. Obviously, only the more human members of Darklore (such as lycanthropes, which change from beast to human at will) can assimilate with human society. Everything but angels and dragons can be lumped under Darklore. Some ancient gods including Ba`al are included as Darklore.
Typical skills vary widely, depending on race and disposition, but there`s a lot of magical power to be found here, usually magic inherent to a given species.
The creatures of the Darklore faction want the world that was once theirs back, basically to retake earth from what they see as the human taint. Their principal enemies are the http://anidb.net/ch40609 [WIZ-DOM] and http://anidb.net/ch40598 [Arayashiki], with whom they have fought for centuries.</description>
<picture>80265.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40611" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-21">
<name>E.G.O.</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The group E.G.O. (color: green) is the newest faction to enter the conflict. They claim to be the next level of human evolution, and possess powerful psionic abilities. Also siding with them are androids (artificial humanoids) and cyborgs, the technology of whom might have been taken from http://anidb.net/ch40636 [Eraser]. It`s interesting to note that most E.G.O. members appear to be the youngest among those involved in this fight, most of them barely in their late teens yet possessing extensive psionic abilities, among other skills.
E.G.O. members are in plain sight and never seen. This is because unlike the isolationist http://anidb.net/ch40609 [WIZ-DOM] or the inhuman http://anidb.net/ch40610 [Darklore], they are quite sociable, human, and ordinary for the most part. They can be schoolchildren, celebrities, military personnel, teachers, scientists, police, criminals (!), or even menial laborers (waiters/waitresses, maids, etc.). One would never really know if the person you`re talking to was part of E.G.O. Assorted androids and cyborgs (presumably taken from Eraser) are also among them, well-hidden.
E.G.O. members with occupations tend to be "the best in their fields" (for instance, scientists on the cutting edge of technology—or ahead of it). Typical skills and powers include proficiency with modern or even futuristic (probably more Eraser technology) weapons, knowledge of cybernetics, telekinesis and other psychic powers, and genetic enhancements (Eraser/human hybrids, for example).
The E.G.O. claim to fight for the next generation, for the future of humanity, and they see themselves as the embodiment of that future. They harass the Erasers frequently, and generally take a dim view of the three "old" factions, on account of them being outdated.
NOTE: The name E.G.O. was originally coined for an all-female group, or "Evolutionary Girls Organization". With the Juvenile Orion expansion (of the trading card game) and its all-male additional characters, this just didn`t jibe. As of the second series (http://anidb.net/a2456 [Aquarian Age Saga II]), the group will include both male and female members, and henceforth will be referred to as the "Evolutionary Generation Organization".</description>
<picture>80267.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40620" type="appears in" update="2012-01-16">
<rating votes="1">5.14</rating>
<name>Kamikurata Naoyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kamikurata Naoyuki is the father of http://anidb.net/ch5895 [Kamikurata Kyouta]. He runs a convenience store together with his wife http://anidb.net/ch40621 [Keiko]. Kyouto frequently helps out in the store and has the option of permanently working there in case his musical career won`t work out.</description>
<picture>80097.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3225" picture="24205.jpg">Watabe Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40621" type="appears in" update="2012-01-24">
<rating votes="1">7.49</rating>
<name>Kamikurata Keiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kamikurata Keiko is the mother of http://anidb.net/ch5895 [Kamikurata Kyouta]. She helps her husband http://anidb.net/ch40620 [Naoyuki] run the family`s convenience store. She has good contact to Kyouta`s friends and particularly likes the enthusiastic http://anidb.net/ch5898 [Shingo].</description>
<picture>80442.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2255" picture="38626.jpg">Okamoto Yoshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40636" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-16">
<name>Eraser</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The final faction is known as Eraser, the only non-earth based faction. This is the name assigned to them by the other four factions, due to their sheer power. Despite all this power, and their open hostility towards the other four factions, Eraser`s true origins are unknown, their actions intermittent, and their motives unclear, save for a claim that it plans to eradicate humanity. All that is known is that they are completely alien to the other factions, and for some reason, has decided to involve itself in their power struggles.
Physical descriptions of Eraser vary, but the most notable are the `Angels`, that appear very much like the human interpretation of angels, and their immediate subordinates, a reptiloid race that have been called the `Dragoons`. They have technology advanced enough that androids, cyborgs, and clones have been manufactured, presumably to act as infiltrators studying the human race and are occasionally involved in the battles. http://anidb.net/ch40611 [E.G.O.] has somehow managed to gain access to some of this technology, which may explain the existence of cyborgs and androids among the E.G.O. as well.
Powers and skills among Angel Erasers vary, but they usually rely heavily on advanced science and technology, particularly weapons development. They also seem to possess the power to create "miracles", such as the ability to stop time. The Dragoon Erasers are much simpler (one may say brutish) - they are an out and out warrior race; when they do use high technology, it`s almost always in the form of weapons given to them by the Angels. The androids, cyborgs and clones do whatever the Erasers design them to do, and that covers a wide range of tasks.
There have been many references hinting that Eraser possesses a large battle-fleet and that this is but one of the many planets they have encountered. It is possible that Eraser is studying the other four factions and the Mindbreakers (especially the latter, due to their unique abilities), but as to what reason, one can only hazard a guess.
The Erasers are engaged mostly in fighting the E.G.O. The older factions, occupied with their own battles, take little notice of them; the Erasers pay them little heed in return. But the Erasers wish to destroy humanity, and the E.G.O. - self-proclaimed guardians of humanity`s future - have risen up to stop them.
Towards the end of the first Aquarian Age Saga, Eraser has been driven off by the four Earthbound Factions and Mindbreakers. It is currently unknown whether they will return at a later date.</description>
</character>
<character id="40645" type="appears in" update="2012-01-17">
<rating votes="1">1.78</rating>
<name>Shibuya Gal</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The girl from Shibuya asks where http://anidb.net/ch5895 [Kyouta] is, shortly before the beginning of http://anidb.net/ch40597 [T.L.Signal]`s New Year gig.
But she`s not one of the band`s female followers: She wants to attack Kyouta, and is fended off by http://anidb.net/ch5907 [Heguri Kiriko] in an aerial battle above the concert location until http://anidb.net/ch5897 [Sakamoto Ruriko] barges in and keeps both opponents apart from each other.</description>
<picture>80073.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39836" picture="154839.jpg">Oodaira Izumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40646" type="appears in" update="2012-01-19">
<name>Koumori Darkness</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Shibuya Gal in her hidden identity as member of http://anidb.net/ch40610 [Darklore].</description>
<picture>80083.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39836" picture="154839.jpg">Oodaira Izumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40647" type="appears in" update="2012-01-17">
<rating votes="2">3.43</rating>
<name>Sarashina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sarashina is a leading member of http://anidb.net/ch40598 [Arayashiki], waiting for http://anidb.net/ch40649 [Benzaiten] to awake.</description>
<picture>80104.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40648" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-16">
<name>Mindbreakers</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Mindbreakers are an interesting new group involved in this battle. They are a group of men and women who have an odd ability; the power to unlock the potential powers of the http://anidb.net/ch40598 [Arayashiki], http://anidb.net/ch40609 [WIZ-DOM], http://anidb.net/ch40610 [Darklore], http://anidb.net/ch40611 [E.G.O.], and even http://anidb.net/ch40636 [Eraser] factions, as well as to somehow gain control of them. They are not a faction like the other five, since each Mindbreaker has his or her own goals and purposes to achieve, as well as methods to achieve them. This often leads Mindbreakers to battle each other. The victor of such a battle gains the loser`s power—the members of Arayashiki, WIZ-DOM, Darklore, E.G.O. and Eraser previously under the loser`s control.
Precisely how a Mindbreaker controls one of these factions, much less how they can awaken the new powers within them, is still unknown. Speculation ranges anywhere from advanced psionic powers to emotional attachment. As of yet, there`s no single rule to explain this ability, but the presence of a mindbreaker favoring a member of the previously mentioned factions is often enough to tip the balance in a battle.</description>
</character>
<character id="40649" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-17">
<name>Benzaiten</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Benzaiten is the Japanese name for the Hindu goddess http://anidb.net/ch40680 [Saraswati], god of wealth, music, eloquence and water.
Worship of Benzaiten arrived in Japan during the 6th through 8th centuries, mainly via the Chinese translations of the Sutra of Golden Light, which has a section devoted to her. She is also mentioned in the Lotus Sutra and often depicted holding a biwa, a traditional Japanese lute, in contrast to Saraswati who holds a stringed instrument known as a veena. Benzaiten is a highly syncretic entity with both a Buddhist and a Shinto side.
In http://anidb.net/a8 [Aquarian Age], becoming Benzaiten (and thus the leader of the http://anidb.net/ch40598 [Arayashiki] faction) is one of two possible fates of http://anidb.net/ch5896 [Sannou Yoriko].</description>
<picture>80084.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3061" picture="38603.jpg">Aoki Mayuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40650" type="appears in" update="2012-01-16">
<rating votes="1">1.78</rating>
<name>Tokage Darkness</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lizard Darklore tries to attack the location where http://anidb.net/ch40597 [T.L.System] performs their New Year live gig but is fended off in aerial battle by http://anidb.net/ch5905 [Lemon].</description>
<picture>80085.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40651" type="appears in" update="2012-01-17">
<rating votes="1">3.07</rating>
<name>Tsuukounin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A passerby at the location of the New Year`s gig of http://anidb.net/ch40597 [T.L.Signal]. When the police asks him who caused all the damage there he can only say: "Nobody has seen anything."</description>
<picture>80086.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4821" picture="186259.jpg">Fukushima Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40652" type="appears in" update="2012-01-16">
<rating votes="1">3.07</rating>
<name>Cameraman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The cameraman of a photo shooting for http://anidb.net/ch5901 [Morino Kanae]. Has just two lines of dialog.</description>
<picture>80090.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="294" picture="53586.jpg">Kirimoto Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40657" type="appears in" update="2012-01-16">
<rating votes="1">3.07</rating>
<name>Joshikousei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Several girls from the Girls` School are fawning over photographs from http://anidb.net/ch40597 [T.L.System]`s New Year concert in general and http://anidb.net/ch5895 [Kamikurata Kyouta] in particular, only to get scolded by http://anidb.net/ch5904 [Kouno Yui] who tells them a library is a place to learn in silence.
(Actually there`s several of these girls talking in this scene but only one official credit given.)</description>
<picture>80095.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2344" picture="37361.jpg">Asai Kiyomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40658" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-26">
<rating votes="1">1.22</rating>
<name>Kouno Yui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kouno Yui works as librarian at the Girls` School. The http://anidb.net/ch40657 [girls in the library] are always crowded around pictures, or a boom box talking about or listening to http://anidb.net/ch5895 [Kyouta]. Yui seems interested in Kyouta, but still lectures her students to keep quiet and not enjoy his music in the library.</description>
<picture>80096.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="206" picture="228617.jpg">Hikami Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40659" type="appears in" update="2012-01-16">
<rating votes="1">3.07</rating>
<name>Kyaku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A customer in the convenience store of http://anidb.net/ch40620 [Kamikurata Naoyuki].</description>
<picture>80098.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21259" picture="187131.jpg">Suzuki Urarako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40660" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-17">
<name>Heguri Kiriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Heguri Kiriko in her hidden identity as a member of http://anidb.net/ch40611 [E.G.O.]. She protects http://anidb.net/ch5895 [Kyouta] against attacks from other factions because she wants the boy all for herself.</description>
<picture>80099.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="603" picture="223012.jpg">Jou Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40661" type="appears in" update="2012-01-17">
<rating votes="1">3.07</rating>
<name>Personality</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The radio personality is the host of the radio show where http://anidb.net/ch40597 [T.L.Signal] have their first live performance on air.</description>
<picture>80101.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="68" picture="16675.jpg">Yasumura Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40662" type="appears in" update="2012-01-19">
<rating votes="1">3.07</rating>
<name>Staff</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A staff member of the radio station where http://anidb.net/ch40597 [T.L.Signal] had their live debut. As the front entry is blocked by a large crowd of fangirls he suggests the band members should leave via the back entrance instead.</description>
<picture>80103.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10191" picture="186250.jpg">Hasebe Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40663" type="appears in" update="2012-01-17">
<rating votes="1">1.78</rating>
<name>Darklore no Otome</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Darklore Girl is part of the audience appearing out of nowhere when http://anidb.net/ch40597 [T.L.System] attempts to play their latest song only for their friend http://anidb.net/ch5896 [Yoriko]. She fights against the http://anidb.net/ch40666 [WIZ-DOM girl] as neither of both wants the other to get near http://anidb.net/ch5895 [Kyouta].</description>
<picture>80105.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="94" picture="170799.jpg">Akita Madoka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40664" type="appears in" update="2012-01-17">
<rating votes="1">3.07</rating>
<name>Tannin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Adviser is a teacher at http://anidb.net/ch5895 [Kyouta]`s school who interviews the boy about his career path intentions and warns him about what his future might be like when he won`t be able to go to college.</description>
<picture>80106.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16125" picture="45256.jpg">Hasuike Ryuuzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40665" type="appears in" update="2012-01-19">
<rating votes="1">1.78</rating>
<name>Kyoushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Class Teacher is not too happy to see http://anidb.net/ch5895 [Kyouta] focused on anything but his lesson.</description>
<picture>80107.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="324" picture="223539.jpg">Saitou Jirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40666" type="appears in" update="2012-01-17">
<rating votes="1">1.78</rating>
<name>WIZ-DOM no Otome</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The WIZ-DOM girl is part of the audience appearing out of nowhere when http://anidb.net/ch40597 [T.L.System] attempts to play their latest song only for their friend http://anidb.net/ch5896 [Yoriko]. She fights against the http://anidb.net/ch40663 [Darklore Girl] girl as neither of both wants the other to get near http://anidb.net/ch5895 [Kyouta].</description>
<picture>80109.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21259" picture="187131.jpg">Suzuki Urarako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40668" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-26">
<name>Yukimura Misato</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yukimura Misato in her hidden identity as http://anidb.net/ch40636 [Eraser]. She shows her powers only during two confrontations with http://anidb.net/ch5903 [Abuto Keiji].</description>
<picture>80113.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40679" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-19">
<name>Hougetsu Asumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hougetsu Asumi in her hidden identity as a member of http://anidb.net/ch40611 [E.G.O.]. Manipulated by the spell of http://anidb.net/ch5904 [Kouno Yui] she attempts to begins a relation with http://anidb.net/ch5895 [Kyouta] whom she wasn`t interested in before.</description>
<picture>80133.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="186" picture="16999.jpg">Minami Omi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40680" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-20">
<name>Saraswati</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>In Hinduism Saraswati is the goddess of knowledge, music, arts, science and technology. Her Japanese name is http://anidb.net/ch40649 [Benzaiten].
The name Saraswati came from "saras" (meaning "flow") and "wati" (meaning "she who has ..."), i.e. "she who has flow". So, Saraswati is symbol of knowledge; its flow (or growth) is like a river and knowledge is supremely alluring, like a beautiful woman. She is depicted as beautiful fair Goddess with four arms, wearing spotless white saree and seated on white lotus.
Saraswati is the guardian of earth. She also guides the souls of the deceased to find their way to the afterlife. Her symbolic animal is the cock, whose crowing calls the pious to their religious duties.
In http://anidb.net/a8 [Aquarian Age], becoming Saraswati (and thus the leader of the http://anidb.net/ch40610 [Darklore] faction, and a demon lord rather than a goddess) is one of two possible fates of http://anidb.net/ch5896 [Sannou Yoriko].</description>
<picture>80236.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3061" picture="38603.jpg">Aoki Mayuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40681" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-17">
<rating votes="1">7.49</rating>
<name>Sakamoto Rumiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakamoto Rumiko works part-time at her family`s shrine. She is kind-hearted and only wants the best for her cousin http://anidb.net/ch5896 [Yoriko].</description>
<picture>80134.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="551" picture="228658.jpg">Nishimura Chinami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40701" type="appears in" update="2012-01-19">
<rating votes="1">3.07</rating>
<name>Uketsukejou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Young Woman at Reception Desk works in http://anidb.net/ch5903 [Abuto]`s office when http://anidb.net/ch5907 [Heguri Kiriko] desperately asks for a job there - any job she can get...</description>
<picture>80173.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4958" picture="177897.jpg">Takamori Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40702" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-21">
<name>I.J.F.</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The I.J.F. talent agency is the company that http://anidb.net/ch5903 [Abuto Keiji] works for.</description>
<picture>80268.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40703" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-24">
<name>Cosmopop</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Cosmopop talent agency is the company that http://anidb.net/ch5900 [Yukimura Misato] works for.</description>
<picture>80441.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40704" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-19">
<name>Morino Kanae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Morino Kanae in her hidden identity as a member of http://anidb.net/ch40610 [Darklore]. She is a werecat and hates http://anidb.net/ch5896 [Yoriko] for being more powerful and closer to http://anidb.net/ch5895 [Kyouta] than herself.</description>
<picture>80175.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="216" picture="171983.jpg">Takahashi Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40717" type="appears in" update="2012-01-21">
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<name>Kanzaki Akane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kanzaki Akane was casted for the lead role of the movie "Hiiragi no Toki"; she had dream of this role since her childhood but turns out being unable to perform when http://anidb.net/ch5896 [Sannou Yoriko] is on the set, much to the dismay of http://anidb.net/ch40718 [her manager].
That`s because http://anidb.net/ch40680 [Sarasvati] uses her power to crush Akane`s morale in order to become the star of this movie herself.</description>
<picture>80232.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2810" picture="45903.jpg">Yokote Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40718" type="appears in" update="2012-01-21">
<rating votes="1">1.22</rating>
<name>Akane no Manager</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akane`s manager tries to calm down http://anidb.net/ch40717 [his protégé] during the shooting of the movie "Hiiragi no Toki".</description>
<picture>80233.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="373" picture="191382.jpg">Hamada Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40719" type="main character in" update="2012-01-20">
<name>Sannou Yoriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>After her awakening, Sannou Yoriko changes drastically: She appears older and more mature now, and her character becomes narcissic and ruthless.</description>
<picture>80234.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3061" picture="38603.jpg">Aoki Mayuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40720" type="appears in" update="2012-01-21">
<rating votes="1">3.07</rating>
<name>Kisha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A reporter asking critical questions about the unusual casting for the movie "Hiiragi no Toki" by director http://anidb.net/ch40723 [Tachibana] - only to be dissed by mysterious new actress http://anidb.net/ch40719 [Sannou Yoriko].</description>
<picture>80235.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10191" picture="186250.jpg">Hasebe Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40723" type="appears in" update="2012-01-21">
<name>Tachibana</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Movie director Tachibana plans a special movie feature for his 30th anniversary, named "Hiiragi no Toki" (柊の季節, The Season of the Holly), casting http://anidb.net/ch40717 [Kanzaki Akane] and newcomer http://anidb.net/ch40719 [Sannou Yoriko] for the lead roles, to the bewilderment of http://anidb.net/ch40720 [the press].</description>
<picture>80260.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4683" picture="27279.jpg">Koyama Takehiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40724" type="appears in" update="2012-01-21">
<rating votes="1">3.07</rating>
<name>Pon-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pon-chan is a staff member on location of the movie shooting, responsible for accessories. When http://anidb.net/ch40719 [Yoriko]`s umbrella doesn`t open properly, the actress harshly scolds Pon-chan for not being professional enough for her requirements.</description>
<picture>80269.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6685" picture="31329.jpg">Asano Ruri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40725" type="appears in" update="2012-01-21">
<name>Sadamura</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sadamura is a photographer. He tries to get an arrangement with http://anidb.net/ch5903 [Abuto] about making a photo shooting with the rising star http://anidb.net/ch40719 [Sannou Yoriko]; when Abuto`s new assistant http://anidb.net/ch5907 [Heguri Kiriko] enters the room he shows a certain interest about her as well.</description>
<picture>80270.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="294" picture="53586.jpg">Kirimoto Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40726" type="appears in" update="2012-01-21">
<rating votes="1">3.07</rating>
<name>Staff</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A staff member of the movie crew who tries to give moral support to http://anidb.net/ch40724 [Pon-chan].</description>
<picture>80271.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6039" picture="228632.jpg">Nakamura Toshihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40727" type="appears in" update="2012-01-21">
<name>Jokantoku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Assistant Director of http://anidb.net/ch40723 [Tachibana]`s movie project.</description>
<picture>80272.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40728" type="appears in" update="2012-01-21">
<rating votes="1">3.07</rating>
<name>Kanae no Manager</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kanae`s Manager works for the same company as http://anidb.net/ch5903 [Abuto] who delegates responsibility for http://anidb.net/ch5901 [Kanae] over to her as soon as he managed to get http://anidb.net/ch40719 [Sannou Yoriko] underhis influence.</description>
<picture>80273.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2045" picture="66315.jpg">Yoshida Miho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40797" type="appears in" update="2012-01-23">
<name>Shain</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Company Employee of http://anidb.net/ch40702 [I.J.F. music] answers a phone call requesting http://anidb.net/ch5907 [Kiriko] to attend her first professional photo shooting at http://anidb.net/ch40725 [Sadamura]`s studio.</description>
<picture>80389.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1983" picture="151694.jpg">Murai Kazusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40803" type="appears in" update="2012-01-23">
<name>Guard Man</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A security guard, preventing reporters from following the new film diva http://anidb.net/ch40719 [Sannou Yoriko]. (This scene is only shown on a TV screen where http://anidb.net/ch5900 [Misato] and http://anidb.net/ch5906 [Asumi] are watching the latest development.)</description>
<picture>80435.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10191" picture="186250.jpg">Hasebe Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40814" type="appears in" update="2012-01-24">
<name>Morita</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Morita is the male lead actor of http://anidb.net/ch40723 [Tachibana]`s movie and one target of http://anidb.net/ch40719 [Sannou Yoriko]`s psycho terror.</description>
<picture>80443.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2361" picture="228618.jpg">Kusumi Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40831" type="appears in" update="2012-01-26">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Morino Kanae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Morino Kanae in her hidden identity as a member of http://anidb.net/ch40610 [Darklore], after being released from http://anidb.net/ch5903 [Abuto]`s control: Still a werecat but no longer a wild beast.</description>
<picture>80457.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="216" picture="171983.jpg">Takahashi Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40880" type="appears in" update="2012-01-27">
<name>Cameraman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A cameraman trying to film the final scene of http://anidb.net/ch40723 [Tachibana]`s movie "Hiiragi no Toki", only to notice that http://anidb.net/ch40719 [the lead actress] has suddenly disappeared in a flash of light.</description>
<picture>80651.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="68" picture="16675.jpg">Yasumura Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40881" type="appears in" update="2012-01-27">
<name>Kangofu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A nurse in a hospital informed http://anidb.net/ch5906 [her co-worker] there`s a phone call for her.</description>
<picture>80652.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4958" picture="177897.jpg">Takamori Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="3" update="2012-01-18">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-01-11</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">深青の序曲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Deep-Blue Overture</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Tiefblaue Overtüre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinsei no Jokyoku</title>
<summary>It`s New Year`s Eve, and the musicians of T.L.System are eagerly awaiting their annual live gig on the next day, even more so as Yoriko promised to visit the gig even though her family`s shrine is busy during holidays. Yoriko tries to convince Kyouta to go to college after his school exam but the boy wants to pursuit his dream of becoming a professional singer first. And unnoticed by normal humans, the first battles between the factions are taking place in the sky above the concert location.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="4" update="2012-01-18">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-01-18</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">炎緑の予感</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fire-Green Premonition</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Vorahnung der grünen Flammen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Enryoku no Yokan</title>
<summary>The gig is a success but the invisible battle in the sky causes broken windows all around the place, leaving the police confused. When the band decides to make a demo tape, Misato approaches them and invites them to record it at the CosmoPop studio during the next 48 hours. At this location Kyouta meets his idol Ryuusei, the most popular vocalist of the country, only to be disappointed by this man`s stuck-up attitude. Yoriko has a stunning vision of her imminent awakening, and Rumiko urges her to make the right decision.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="22" update="2012-01-18">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">濁赤の憂鬱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cloudy-Red Melancholy</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Melancholie in trübem Rot</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dakuseki no Yuuutsu</title>
<summary>Misato offers T.L.System a contract which Kyouta`s parents permit; Yoriko`s career at university clashes with the fate Rumiko has in mind for her cousin. Misato has already arranged the band`s debut in a live radio show; Kyouta invites Yoriko to come along but Misato treats her coldly, telling her that she will protect the band from "bad influence and scandals". After the live performance a fan crowd waits in front of the radio station; when they notice the band leaving via the back door Kyouta and Yoriko take a run, only to be dragged into a waiting car by a beautiful woman.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="23" update="2012-01-18">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-02-01</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">潜黒の供物</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Concealment-Black Offering</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Votivgabe in tiefem Schwarz</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senkoku no Kumotsu</title>
<summary>After Kyouta`s career plan interview at school Yoriko tries to talk with him but Misato arrives to pick up the boy for a live performance of Ryuusei and Morino Kanae; disappointed, the girl refuses to tag along. At this gig Kyouta witnesses a supernatural power struggle between Misato and Kanae`s manager Abuto. Yoriko suggests Kyouta they shouldn`t see each other any more; Kyouta then initiates T.L.System to perform a live gig just for Yoriko but when they begin to play lots of female fans appear out of nowhere.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="24" update="2012-01-19">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-02-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">閃白の必然</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sparkling-White Inevitability</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Blütenweiße Notwendigkeit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senpaku no Hitsuzen</title>
<summary>Kiriko asks her senpai Asumi to get her an autograph from Kyouta; Asumi hesitates but then Yui casts a spell on her from afar, and the girl begins to hit on Kyouta herself. Rumiko tells Kyouta she knows about the supernatural battles the boy has seen, and demands he must stay away from Yoriko or else something terrible will happen. Yui`s minions attack Asumi and Kyouta; when Kyouta holds the crying girl in his arms, a photograph of this scene published in the newspapers on the next day causes a scandal.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="25" update="2012-01-19">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-02-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幻緑の救済</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Illusion-Green Salvation</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Grünes Trugbild der Erlösung</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Genryoku no Kyuusai</title>
<summary>Kanae attacks Yoriko; Abuto orders her back and explains Yoriko the choice she has. Misato offers Asumi a career as singer and orders her to accompany T.L.System to learn the basics. Kiriko is fuming; Asumi suggests she should give up on Kyouta. Yoriko has cut her ties with Rumiko and signs a contract as actress with Abuto who claims she can be closer to Kyouta this way. Yoriko observes Kanae kissing Kyouta after dinner - and Sarasvati awakes.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="27" update="2012-01-26">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-02-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">深紅の分蘖</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Deep-Red Offshoot</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Tiefroter Spross</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinku no Bunketsu</title>
<summary>Both Yoriko and Rumiko block Kyouta`s attempts to contact them. The lead role in Yoriko`s first movie was casted with Kanzaki Akane who turns out to be no match for Saraswati. Kanae`s star is sinking. Lemon attacks T.L.System in their band bus, using ice magic to cause a traffic accident; Shingo suffers severe injuries. Jun and Kyouta are stunned when they watch the press conference of Yoriko`s movie on TV. Rumiko tries to stop Yoriko, only to learn how much her cousin has changed.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="28" update="2012-01-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">薄紫の覚醒</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Light-Purple Awakening</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Erwachen in hellem Lila</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakushi no Kakusei</title>
<summary>The Arayashiki disagree about how Benzaiten could be retrieved. Kyouta and Asumi visit the shooting of the movie and observe Yoriko`s diva behavior; Abuto tells Kyouta that this lady is out of his league. Asumi tries to get closer to Kyouta but can`t stop the boy from suddenly running away. An Arayashiki woman attacks Kyouta with a hail of arrows; when Rumiko tries to protect him he instinctively makes use of his power. And at long last, Rumiko explains Kyouta`s role in the war to the confused boy.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="29" update="2012-01-27">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">烈銀の残影</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fierce-Silver Remnants</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Spuren in heißem Silber</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Retsugin no Zan`ei</title>
<summary>Akane resigns from her movie role and is replaced by Yoriko; Abuto suggests Asumi should play Yoriko`s previous role. Tensions amongst Arayashiki members are rising but Rumiko demands neither Yoriko nor Kyouta can be attacked. Sadamura asks Abuto for a photo shooting with Yoriko but gets a deal with Abuto`s new assistant Kiriko instead. Kanae attacks Yoriko again but fails miserably; Asumi challenges Yoriko for a power struggle, getting her hospitalized. And Kyouta plays a song just for Yoriko.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="30" update="2012-01-23">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">萌黄の此岸</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yellow-Green Suffering World</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Leidende Welt in gelbgrün</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moegi no Shigan</title>
<summary>Kyouta`s emotional crisis jeopardizes the scheduling for T.L.System`s debut concert; Jun and Shingo are at their wit`s end. At her photo shooting Kiriko shows her full potential only when Sadamura allows her to listen to Kyouta`s song, much to Abuto`s chagrin. Sarasvati performs a sneak attack at Rumiko. Abuto forces Kanae to attack T.L.System at their photo shooting but Yukimura shows her full power this time.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="31" update="2012-01-24">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">藍碧の渦動</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Indigo-Green Vortex</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Indigoblauer Strudel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ranpeki no Kadou</title>
<summary>T.L.System step up preparations for their debut gig. Yoriko lives out her powers on fellow actor Morita. Asumi attacks Abuto`s car with an ice hail but this time Saraswati doesn`t just play with her. As a result, Kyouta`s performance gets so bad that Ryuusei complains about the waste of studio effort; Kyouta takes this to heart and takes the appropriate action. The boy then runs into Kiriko who is signing autographs for her fans; with her new self-esteem she straightens her idol out.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="32" update="2012-01-25">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-29</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">退紅の葛藤</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Faded-Red Conflict</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Konflikt in verblassendem Rot</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arazome no Kattou</title>
<summary>The day of T.L.Signal`s debut concert has come. But when Benzaiten entreats Kyouta to stop her, the boy makes this his priority. When Abuto loses control over Saraswati and she is running wild, Rumiko reaches a conclusion: She will bring back Yoriko-chan regardless of what it might cost her. But just when an unlikely alliance of several factions is about to defeat their mighty opponent Saraswati suddenly gets an unexpected protector. And Yokko makes up her mind.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="33" update="2012-01-27">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-29</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">純白の抱擁</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pure-White Embrace</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Umarmung in unschuldigem Weiß</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Junpaku no Houyou</title>
<summary>Yokko`s body is reunited but her soul is still wandering around. But when Kyouta has found the girl she`s so afraid of the darkness inside of her that has caused so much pain to her friends that she would rather die than take the risk of putting the boy in danger once again. And there`s not much time left until T.L.Signal`s debut concert is scheduled to begin.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="29908" update="2010-08-05">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36593" update="2011-07-01">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Commercial</title>
</episode>
<episode id="117542" update="2010-08-05">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120772" update="2010-08-05">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="1">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120773" update="2010-08-05">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120774" update="2010-08-05">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="1">2.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
