<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8043" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>5</episodecount>
<startdate>2003-04-20</startdate>
<enddate>2008-12-13</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">There She Is!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">tsi</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">떳다 그녀!!</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="11073" approval="2" total="6">Momokuri</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="314120">This short series of music videos is surprisingly good.  The entire plot of a romance, put into 5 music videos.  Yet it doesn`t feel rushed.  No subs are necessary for this.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="228878">Five brilliant short pieces of animation, which don`t require words to express either the inherent feelings of the protagonists nor the story. Would have scored higher then an eight, if certain aspects of production had been smoother. Also, available on Youtube.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="390549">The music`s good, and there`s very little in the way of talking/text. All the action conveys the story in a wonderful way. I found it to be a very amusing/moving series!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.sambakza.net/works_tsi/tsi_main.html</url>
<description>The plot revolves around Doki, a female rabbit, meeting, falling in love with, and chasing Nabi, a male cat, in a world where love between the two species is socially unacceptable. The theme of the short is that all love can be accepted and has a chance. Nabi attempts to cure Doki`s infatuation for him, but after seeing the extent of her love, he gives in and finds something he can appreciate in her.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="595">7.94</permanent>
<temporary count="597">7.44</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>57827.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6505</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.sambakza.net/works_tsi/tsi_main.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>There_she_is!!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>떳다_그녀!!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4200" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>flash animation</name>
<description>Made in Adobe Flash (formerly known as Macromedia Flash), a software package for rich multimedia and Web animations and applications. Very popular on amateur fanproductions (like the ones found in places such as YouTube)
Sadly, Flash has also earned a bad reputation among the animation purists because it leads to cheap low-quality animation jobs, since anyone with a hint of creativity and a "idea" on its head can easily learn how to produce an animated feature in Flash... and sell it to the masses.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5794" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-01">
<name>forbidden love</name>
<description>This anime contains characters pursuing a romantic interest that their parents, grandparents, the police, the fire department, the neighbourhood watch association and local politicians do not approve of.
Potential relationships defined as such may be ones that are incestuous, violations of caste systems, or socially unsanctioned.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6166" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-23">
<name>South Korean production</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/t6762 [North Korean production]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="23469" type="main character in" update="2010-10-22">
<rating votes="8">8.64</rating>
<name>Nabi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3642.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="23470" type="main character in" update="2010-10-22">
<rating votes="9">8.93</rating>
<name>Doki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3643.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="23471" type="appears in" update="2010-10-22">
<rating votes="2">4.83</rating>
<name>Red-eye</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3648.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="23472" type="appears in" update="2010-10-22">
<rating votes="2">4.20</rating>
<name>Moon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3649.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="23473" type="appears in" update="2010-10-22">
<rating votes="3">7.28</rating>
<name>Jjintta set</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3647.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="23474" type="appears in" update="2010-10-22">
<rating votes="2">3.21</rating>
<name>Pi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3650.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="23475" type="appears in" update="2010-10-22">
<rating votes="4">7.99</rating>
<name>Pizza</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3645.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="23476" type="appears in" update="2010-10-23">
<rating votes="3">6.61</rating>
<name>Hana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3651.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="23477" type="appears in" update="2010-10-22">
<rating votes="2">5.00</rating>
<name>Gray rabbit</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3646.gif</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="124432" update="2010-10-23">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2008-12-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Imagine</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124433" update="2010-10-23">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2008-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Paradise</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124434" update="2010-10-23">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2008-05-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Doki&amp;Nabi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124435" update="2010-10-23">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2005-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Cake Dance</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124436" update="2010-10-23">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2003-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">There She Is!!</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
