<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8069" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-01-07</startdate>
<enddate>2011-04-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Mahou Shoujo Madoka Magica</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Magical Girl Madoka Magika</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Волшебница Мадока Магика</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Büyücü Kız Madoka Magica</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Meduka Meguca</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Mahou Shoujo Madoka Magika</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Дівчина-чарівниця Мадока Маґіка</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Чарівниця Мадока Магіка</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="synonym">مدوکا مجیکا دختر جادویی</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">マドマギ</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">まどマギ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">pmagi</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Madoka Magica</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">MSMM</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">PMMM</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Madoka</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">madomagi</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="short">小圆</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">魔法少女まどか★マギカ PUELLA MAGI MADOKA MAGICA</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Puella Magi Madoka Magica</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Madoka Magica</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Puella Magi Madoka Magica</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Madoka Magica</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Puella Magi Madoka Magica</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">마법소녀 마도카 마기카</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">สาวน้อยเวทมนตร์ มาโดกะ</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">魔法少女小圓</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">魔法少女小圆</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8778" type="Alternative Setting">Gekijouban Mahou Shoujo Madoka Magica</anime>
<anime id="14360" type="Other">Magia Record: Mahou Shoujo Madoka Magica Gaiden</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4861" approval="86" total="115">Bokura no</anime>
<anime id="1554" approval="56" total="92">Mai-HiME</anime>
<anime id="58" approval="53" total="82">Alien 9</anime>
<anime id="10750" approval="43" total="48">Yuuki Yuuna wa Yuusha de Aru</anime>
<anime id="10417" approval="40" total="51">Selector Infected WIXOSS</anime>
<anime id="11572" approval="30" total="38">Mahou Shoujo Ikusei Keikaku</anime>
<anime id="2430" approval="25" total="59">Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha</anime>
<anime id="9736" approval="25" total="28">Gen`ei o Kakeru Taiyou</anime>
<anime id="22" approval="22" total="49">Shinseiki Evangelion</anime>
<anime id="782" approval="21" total="54">Narutaru: Mukuro Naru Hoshi Tama Taru Ko</anime>
<anime id="8584" approval="18" total="39">Black Rock Shooter (2012)</anime>
<anime id="287" approval="10" total="24">Shoujo Kakumei Utena</anime>
<anime id="7729" approval="10" total="24">Steins;Gate</anime>
<anime id="13424" approval="9" total="19">Mahou Shoujo Site</anime>
<anime id="12681" approval="8" total="26">Made in Abyss</anime>
<anime id="2481" approval="8" total="20">Uta Kata</anime>
<anime id="9042" approval="6" total="18">Fate/Kaleid Liner Prisma Illya</anime>
<anime id="10697" approval="5" total="17">Gakkougurashi!</anime>
<anime id="4522" approval="5" total="13">Red Garden</anime>
<anime id="12007" approval="3" total="10">Flip Flappers</anime>
<anime id="8395" approval="2" total="25">Mirai Nikki (2011)</anime>
<anime id="5280" approval="2" total="24">Shugo Chara!</anime>
<anime id="7725" approval="2" total="13">Yumekui Merry</anime>
<anime id="5274" approval="1" total="21">Ef - a Tale of Memories.</anime>
<anime id="9875" approval="1" total="15">Kill la Kill</anime>
<anime id="5113" approval="1" total="15">Mononoke</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="76">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="483032">the words "for fans" does not mean for fans of this specific anime series only, but for those who doesnot hate this genre and fans of japanese anime.This is because the content of the anime would damage the heart of those who not yet watch it XD</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="367864">spectacular, fantastique, suspens</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="458655">Wow, I`m only half way through and I`m enjoying this. I don`t watch MS stuff but this has a more mature, dark feeling to it. So dark, it`s as if this show was meant more for guys than girls!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="544948">Dark magical girl anime has been done before (see Revolutionary Girl Utena) but never before with this much flare. Fantastic characters and riveting drama and a climax that doesn`t let you down mean it`s one of the most solid series.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="317067">Definitely not for everyone. Deliciously fucked up and emotionally intense, this is not what the cover image makes it look like. Very unique, very interesting, and a very good anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="281995">If you`re looking for Sailor Moon X here, you`re in the wrong place. This is a totally different take on mahou shoujo shows. Much deeper and serious. The plot is a bit slow and boring at the beginning, but the second half of the show makes up for it big time.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="177436">An excellent, and original concept, excellent, creative artwork, excellent music... Let down by poor pacing. This series should have worked really well, and been a breath of fresh air for anime. Unfortunately, the story meanders and and fourth for most of the series, and it`s only in the last few episodes that things start to pick up and the story is at it`s strongest. A real shame, perhaps someone else will try the same concept in the future, and learn from the mistakes Madoka made.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="98119">Great anime, can`t agree about the shock factor thing. I watched knowing about episode 3 event yet I still found the series a very intense and entertaining experience.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="479550">Don`t think of this as a just another magical girl show. That`s what lots of people did when it came out and then a few weeks later, all the mahou shoujo fans were like `WTF!? o.0`

In the words of journalist Matt Kamen, "With its...daring approach to a dated genre, Puella Magi Madoka Magica essentially does for magical girls what Neon Genesis Evangelion did for giant robots."
I sometimes refer to it as a subversion of the mahou shoujo genre. That`s how different this is.

great soundtrack, visuals (it`s supposed to look super cutesy, adds to said subversion) especially love the witch world visuals, seiyuu (though madoka`s sounded a little annoying but it was how her character should be anyways)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="318047">Tried like hell to ignore this title. Just couldn`t get the notion of mahou shoujo not adding a saccharin taste to my palette of anime. I was WRONG just plain WRONG. Had to skip most of the intros and a few of the end credits though. They just didn`t encourage my desire to watch a series with more depth than the normal merchandising machines.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="125248">Short  &amp; strong. Ignore "mahou shoujo" thing and watch it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="520752">Pretty deep story. Half of the episodes make you think "what would I do in that kind of situation". Not the average Magical Girl story. Once you get the idea behind the story, you will just love it. Last but not least, this anime doesn`t have a half unfinished ending like the most out there. I definitely recommend watching the whole anime in one go, it`s not even 5hours. :D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="444051">Personally I am absolutely no fan of this genre. I hate almost every aspect of the mahou shoujo genre. Despite my preferences, i watched this and wow. This is one of the darkest anime i`ve seen. I recommend this anime to everyone, even if you don`t like the genre.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="267233">The plot is heavy and interesting, the animation can be pretty unique (which may turn some people off but the animation makes sense if you think about it), and the music is great.   If I had to describe this series, I`d say it is like a base of Magical Lyrical combined with Mokona (CLAMP) and with some Higurashi-like elements.  I can`t say much more (or use better descriptions) without spoiling this great anime!  It is one of the few animes (Like Jigoku Shoujo and Higurashi) that I can actually watch multiple times in a row.

While I wouldn`t give this a 10 (due to the first two episodes being hard to keep watching for many of my friends) and my personal dislike of episode 3, This does get better, especially after episode 7 (halfway through the series).  This is extremely plot filled compared to many other Mahou Shoujo series and is worth the wait in my opinion.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="265326">"Wait what ?! Magical Girl Anime so highly rated ?! and so popular ?!  " 
That was my though process when i heard about this anime . I put if off for quite some time . Card Captor Sakura was ENOUGH FOR ME ! . 

Then one night , i started watching seeing i had it in HDD.............. Ended up finishing in the same night with allot of caffeine to keep me going,
It is just simply , staggering i couldn`t believe that this can be pulled off from the "magical girl" anime genre . 
It`s truly breathtaking the profoundness of this anime.
A must SEE ! !</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="493983">No matter what you think about Mahou Shojou anime, you`ll be shocked by this one.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="154026">A very unique approach to the mahou shojo theme with the usual artistic animation from Shaft. I recommend it especially if you are tired of all the un-inovative anime out there.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="341225">After reading all the "OMG magic lolis!" comments I expected something different. Actually I could expect anything but what I`ve seen here is completely different.
It`s not usual candy series full of sparkles and that stuff. It`s deep story about humanity including psychedelic magical worlds full of what-not.
I`m not able to mark this as must see for some reason, but I can recommend it for sure</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="495882">I would not call this anime "twisted" or "demented" as much as I would call it "shocking." It is definitely a different take on the magical girl genre.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="473323">Started off extremely bad, so bad that i dropped it at first. But i forced myself to watch it and things got alot better. From 1 point to 7. Give it a try! Endure the first episodes, it gets much better after a while!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="745582">Sure it`s not for all Magical Girl fans , but if you`re looking for something darker and more emotional in your life, I point to this</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="221060">dark and moody, there is always that hanging feeling that you know something bad is going to happen at one point. and then one by one, things fall into place and then until at the very end, everything comes full circle and you just realize that that was one heck of a ride.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="249386">As of now,  only 6 eps are broadcasts, but simply this is the best mahou shoujo anime ever. I hope it can last until the very end.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="211996">I just watched all the episodes in one sitting...not much to say here other than WHOA! This was one wacky son of a show, and there was no way anybody was gonna pry me away from the screen til it was over. Good stuff, don`t miss it!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="2975">Just excellent.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="324595">／人 ◕ ‿ _ ◕人＼:  Hallo thar~  Want to make a contract with me?  This world in under invasion of evil, and if you join me, you will be able to kill them.  *smiles*  :]

+98.1%: story, character, art, sound, video
-1.9%: needs more ecchiness and a guy

Beautiful masterpiece... just in awe.....................
.
.
The cover image is very cheap, misleading, and `cute girly girls`..... when u watch this masterpiece, u will be amazed at the graphics, audio, and high technology beyond ours....  :D
.
.
.
.
there are alternate dimensions that are purely artistically awesome.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="596734">Best modern anime ever.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="367615">Good vs. evil. Hope vs. despair. Wonderful designs and unique artwork. Cute girls doing magical things. It`s sort of like a condensed and girlier version of Evangelion. Must see, if you ever get the feels.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="422319">Only one word comes to my mind when i think about this show and that is "EPIC". Now excuse me i`m gonna go and re-watch it a couple of times.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="60478">Forget about card captor sakura, this has only first episodes that can be similar, but becomes dark at the end.
Can`t even say if it has an happy end, watch it and find i t out :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="564967">Even if you don`t like the magical girl genre - don`t get fooled by the overly cute style it has. The first three episodes make it seem as if it`s like any other girly adorable little magical girl anime - but then it drastically changes. I`ve had at least three friends refusing to watch it because it didn`t seem as their style; I don`t blame them, I was the same. But when they saw the rest of it? They ended up LOVING it, just like I do. It completely gets you off guard. The story is great, the characters are great. I highly recommend it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="335602">The greatest anime ever made. This is pure mind fuckery in a usually childish genre where cruel things happen, with an incredibly misleading cover. What Evangelion did for the mecha genre is what this anime will do for the magical girl genre, and possibly even beyond that. You`ll watch this entire series in awe, as you haven`t ever seen something as great as this.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="614621">AMAZING

Must see if you are into visual arts...
Must see if you are into dark magic...
Must see if you are into ANIME...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="478043">If you watch this anime without any prior knowledge of its story like I did, you get pretty blown away as it progresses. A very refreshing take on the traditional "magical girl" genre with great character development.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="212957">I don`t usually like the whole magical girl theme anime, but this, despite its name, is far from being a regular magical girl anime! 

The story is so deep, sad and so touching that it seems to be almost a parody to the whole theme. It is in fact a far cry from what you first think it is.

Also, as usual, Kajiura Yuki (the reason I actually saw this show) did an awesome job with the music.

I highly recommend!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="545305">Looking at the title and character images i though its another girly, overly cute mahou shoujo anime so i ignored it till now. After seeing some episodes i got caught up and watched the whole thing in one go. I never expected something like this. The story is deep and dark, nothing like the usual mahou shoujo.

Highly recommended for anyone who likes dark stories specially people who doesn`t like mahou shojou genre.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="79717">Totally worth the time watching. It was very nicley done, but there might be some plot holes at the end.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="613777">A masterpiece in disguise. 
Watch it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="567315">What can I say? This is truly a masterpiece. As a fan of dark anime, I was pleasantly surprised by this anime`s take on the magical girl theme. It was an absolutely incredible experience and not one that I will forget. One of the best anime I have ever seen. The final episode gets a little existential, but if you can get your brain around what is going on, and you don`t mind a heavy story, then this is THE anime to put at the top of your watchlist.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="758779">Took me a little while to watch this one as while I enjoy the genre, this didn`t look very special on first glance. I was most definitely wrong abou that though and the way this show pulled me in and broke my expectations make it a must see.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="244372">Mahou shoujo anime which really wasn`t one :P
Nice and interesting anime, except they really complicated things at end for no reason... made me use 2 much brain power to figure out what did writer exactly want to say.
Reminds me a bit of noein for some reason.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="31717">Definitely not your typical Mahou Shoujo series. This dark themed take on the category is a must see for all, especially for people who are bored by the typical pace of the Mahou Shoujo series.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="488184">It`s true you don`t have to be a fan of the Mahou Shoujo theme to like this anime. It`s a dark anime that has decent amount of action, but really good storyline. For an original story it`s one of the best. The only people who wouldn`t like this are hardcore action fans who pay no attention to nice character development, good plot twists, and emotional drama (not as much as devoted drama genre, though). Anyone who loves "WTF is going on?!" series that creatively fills in the blanks would instantly put this on their top 10.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="480218">A surprisingly dark show that you just don`t really see in the magical girl genre.  It looks pretty typical (if somewhat bizarre thanks to SHAFT) at first, but give it a couple of episodes and you will see it is not your typical magical girl show at all.
I strongly recommend checking it out, even if you aren`t really into the magical girl genre.  As of time of writing, it`s one of the best new shows I`ve seen in a while.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="352369">I watched this expecting the same old Magical girl cliche, but this show blindsided me by being a totally new take on an old cliche genre. A must see just for the fact that it`s a perfect example of never judging a book by it`s cover.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="350228">This is one of the series which should be recommended for educational purposes, it is simply a cultural phenomen.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="1323">Takes the mahou shoujo genre and completely turns it on its head. A series with a real story - and a roller-coaster ride at that.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="3688">Extremely Dark, Darkness beyond boundaries, endless despair - and Super Nova of Light in the end! This is very charming composition - real Yin&amp;Yang in perfect balance.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="218852">Really interesting deconstruction of the mahou shoujo concept, not only for fans of the genre, but for anyone interested in a anime far deeper than the standard ecchi show we usually are served nowadays.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="240459">The most beautiful plot I`ve seen in years.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="366429">Not your typical mahou shoujo.
This anime twists the genre `conventions` and creates a creepy, menacing atmosphere.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="444838">Sakura Card Captor is dethroned, Lyrical Nanoha lies on the floor and Sailor Moon runs for the hills. Long reign to the new queen of Mahou-Shoujo!!!!
Long have I wanted a darker view on this genre, something that really exploits the really dark themes that surround the genre. Don`t be fooled by the cuteness, this is really tough and psychological.
The best anime from 2010. Period.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="311537">very emotional anime and best mahou shoujo till now, you can enjoy it even if you`re not fan of this genre.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="445322">If you`re not hooked by ep 3 then... No, you will be hooked. A good one for anyone who knows what a trope is. Keep away from young children.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="183526">Even if you are not a fan of mahou shoujo genre, this show is something you ought to see as it is an anime that has surely left a significant mark in the history of anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="367836">An anime with the most consistent high quality, will keep you in place from (almost very) beginning till end. And yet the piece hasnt become what it could be</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="211221">Just a real pleasure to watch.  If you want to get technical, you can definitely pick a bone or 2 with the story and ending.  However, it never got in the way of wanting more.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="447133">The top anime of the winter season 2011 and possibly the best of the whole year. This isn`t supposed to be a funny story ( as some might think ) or moeblobshit. This anime is beautiful, intense and cruel and can rival the likes of Bakemono and NGE.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.madoka-magica.com/tv/</url>
<creators>
<name id="792" type="Animation Work">Shaft</name>
<name id="4147" type="Character Design">Kishida Takahiro</name>
<name id="59" type="Direction">Shinbou Akiyuki</name>
<name id="704" type="Music">Kajiura Yuki</name>
<name id="1512" type="Direction">Miyamoto Yukihiro</name>
<name id="14125" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takahashi Mika</name>
<name id="7866" type="Chief Animation Direction">Taniguchi Jun`ichirou</name>
<name id="39802" type="Original Work">Magica Quartet</name>
</creators>
<description>Having a loving family, close friends, experiencing times of joy and times of sadness. These are the things that make up an ordinary life.
http://anidb.net/ch24746 [Kaname Madoka] is a normal 2nd year middle-schoolgirl who lives such an ordinary life. Until, that is, a strange encounter occurs. She does not know if this encounter is coincidence, or the vagaries of fate, but two things are certain...
This is the moment when her destiny changes...
This is the start of a new magical girl story!
~ translated and adapted from the official site by Cranston
Note: Won the Television Award at the 16th Animation Kobe Awards (2011), 12 NewType Anime Awards, including Best Anime Series, Director, Screenplay, and Design, and the Grand Prize in the animation category at the 15th Japan Media Arts Festival.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="7653">8.55</permanent>
<temporary count="7745">8.28</temporary>
<review count="14">7.48</review>
</ratings>
<picture>224383.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12120</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9756</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4825</identifier>
<identifier>jfgkkh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.madoka-magica.com/tv/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Puella_Magi_Madoka_Magica</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>魔法少女まどか★マギカ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2077</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>338502</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13247</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2728</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>madoka_magica</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>puella-magi-madoka-magica</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14810</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B01N4MCXTZ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="55" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-11">
<name>awards</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1018" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-25">
<name>middle school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2649" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>dark fantasy</name>
<description>Focus set on darker themes in a fantasy setting, sometimes leaning towards horror elements. Bleak and pessimistic tones often dominate. Dark supernatural beings like vampires may play a significant role.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3013" parentid="55" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-10">
<name>Newtype Anime Award</name>
<description>This anime has won 1 or more Newtype Anime Award(s)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3088" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-31">
<name>manipulation</name>
<description>When someone else is pulling the strings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3267" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>everybody dies</name>
<description>Not necessarily everyone, but a good portion of the characters kick the bucket.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3276" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>plot twists</name>
<description>The plot and story of this anime may seem to be going along a quite predictable path, when suddenly there is a jarring unexpected twist in the plot, taking the viewer by surprise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3278" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false">
<name>deception</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3314" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-10">
<name>fate</name>
<description>Fate — The predestined path of all things. The outcome is inevitable and the consequences predetermined. Whether or not the protagonist ultimately decides to follow this path shall weigh heavily on their soul.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3316" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-08-10">
<name>despair</name>
<description>Involves characters that may be lost in negatively emotional atmospheres created through feelings of hopelessness and suffering.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3435" parentid="2851" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>eating of humans</name>
<description>The eating of humans, also called man-eating, is the practice of some species to prey on human beings for nourishment. Examples of possible hunters may include Earth animals, alien species, zombies or other undead, and so forth. Eating of humans is not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t3815 [human cannibalism]; the former is about other species eating people, while the latter is about humans eating fellow humans.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3696" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-28">
<name>off-model animation</name>
<description>Anime shows tend to most often run on an already tight budget; some have even tighter ones. Thus, over the years it became a norm to invest more time and money into the first and last episode, leaving many episodes in the middle to stand severe budget restrictions. This sometimes results in episodes which particularly stand out due to the drop in artwork or animation quality; bar some basic framework, they often have little in common with the rest of the series.
One clue to upcoming off-model animation is the noticeable addition of many Korean names in the production credits, as farming out more animation to Korean artists is a nearly universal indicator of a production company trying to save money in all possible ways.
This effect is often called yashigani, after the infamous http://anidb.net/e4682 [fourth episode] of http://anidb.net/a403 [Lost Universe], Yashigani Hoburu. Another prominent term describing the same effect is "QUALITY animation", with capital letters meant to show contrast to actual quality. http://anidb.net/a4531 [Yoake Mae yori Ruriiro na: Crescent Love] is another legendarily terrible offender: the TV airing of its http://anidb.net/e63752 [third episode] had a perfectly spherical ball in place of what should be a cabbage; the "cabbage" was so egregious that it became closely associated with the anime itself, to a point the show would henceforth be nicknamed "Cabbage Love" among Western viewers.
One should not confuse the yashigani effect with art shifts that stem from guest staff, changes in main staff, intentional art shifts, and similar effects. Another effect one shouldn`t confuse this one with is the so-called DVD/BD enhancement, which is when a studio scrambles to meet the deadline for a TV airing and airs a half-finished episode but eventually fixes it for a disk release; for example, http://anidb.net/cr792 [Shaft] is particularly infamous for its disk enhancements, to a point it has become known as "Shafting", and they prominently feature intentionally weird character models, but they don`t often leave bad artwork on the disk release. Additionally, it should also not be confused with intentional lack of detail on background plane characters; this effect is instead when even the foreground has art quality shifting over time due to the aforementioned budget restrictions.</description>
<picurl>29532.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3815" parentid="2851" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>human cannibalism</name>
<description>Cannibalism is the practice of an individual of a species eating parts or the whole of another individual of the same species; as such, human cannibalism is when a human eats the flesh, organs, or other parts of another human being.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3834" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-11-24">
<name>impending death -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>At least one character in this show is going to or very likely to die soon because of a http://anidb.net/t2574 [terminal illness], of a http://anidb.net/t2874 [disaster] such a http://anidb.net/t2925 [war], an http://anidb.net/t5466 [epidemic] (including the zombie apocalypse), or of other life-threatening reasons. Please assign the appropriate disaster tags to the anime, the terminal illness tag to the relevant characters, and any other relevant or necessary replacement tags to the corresponding entities, and then remove this tag from the anime in question. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3898" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-11">
<name>science and magic coexist</name>
<description>In this anime science and magic do not exclude each other. Magic here is actually very advanced, artefact- and/or ritual-based science.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3934" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-10">
<name>non-linear</name>
<description>The story is told achronologically.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4057" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-19">
<name>magical creatures</name>
<description>Magical creatures are beings associated with a fantasy setting, thus do not exist in reality. Apparently they were "created of" or "powered by" magic. An incantation may have brought them into existence.
Examples: A legendary creature, a mythological or folkloric creature, a fairy or demon, ...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4062" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-10-14">
<name>deja vu</name>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4153" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-15">
<name>dark</name>
<description>Describes the overall mood in this anime. Dark colours, a non-happy, often tragic story, dark lighting, many night scenes or constantly dark skies, and continuous rain all contribute to setting this mood.
The anime will often be quite depressing to watch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4196" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-01-23">
<name>fate worse than death</name>
<description>If you think death is the worst that can ever happen to someone, you had better think again: at least one character in this show is sure to end up in such a terrible way that many people would likely have preferred death if they had the choice. The fate of such characters is normally not for the faint of heart, and the audience is expected to at least sympathise with the poor character`s fate, and at times even be horrified at the shocking turn of events that led to their demise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4217" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-02-11">
<name>nightmares</name>
<description>One or more characters in the anime are plagued by bad dreams.
Possible causes: A traumatic experience in the past or induced by an external "presence".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4225" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-02-16">
<name>symbolism</name>
<description>Representation of a more complex concept by a simple thing. Like a red flower for love or a flag for a nation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4228" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-09">
<name>subtle OP ED sequence change</name>
<description>A (small) part of the opening or ending sequence changes after a certain episode, usually to reflect a plot milestone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4280" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-02">
<name>surreal</name>
<description>Refers to things or occurrences that are generally bizarre or dreamlike, with the relentless capability of replacing reality through the eyes of the beholder. Surrealism is boundless, limited only by thought itself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4314" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-04-11">
<name>psychological</name>
<description>Directed toward dealing with or affecting the mind, especially as a function of awareness, feeling, or motivation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4327" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-18">
<name>be careful what you wish for</name>
<description>Be careful what you wish for... your wish may actually come true. This is an age-old philosophical problem of what human beings think they want and what is actually good for them. The power to wish for anything can be very dangerous and usually — as a moral lesson — yields unexpected / unwanted results.
A contract with the devil is a specific case of this; receiving great power, especially from a devil, is usually a double edged sword.</description>
<picurl>230309.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4340" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-26">
<name>suicide</name>
<description>One or several characters in this anime commit suicide.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4386" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-19">
<name>eating Pocky</name>
<description>Pocky (ポッキー) is a Japanese snack food produced by the Ezaki Glico Company of Japan. Pocky was first sold in 1966, and consists of a biscuit stick coated with chocolate. It was named after the Japanese onomatopoetic word for the sound Pocky makes when bitten, pokkin (ポッキン). The original was followed by "Almond Pocky" in 1971, with an almond coating, and "Strawberry Pocky" in 1977. Today, the product line includes such variations as milk, mousse, green tea, honey, banana and coconut flavored coatings, and themed products such as "Decorer Pocky," with colourful decorative stripes in the coating, and "Men`s Pocky," a dark (bittersweet) chocolate and "mature" version.
Source: Wikipedia
It`s marketed in Germany under the name Mikado (Note: NOT the game, the snack).</description>
<picurl>73630.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4388" parentid="2611" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-16">
<name>deconstruction</name>
<description>In the context of fiction, a deconstruction is the act of taking storytelling devices and exploring their real-life consequences, commonly in dark and cynical ways. Deconstructions often reveal the dark and terrifying aspects of some of the themes and elements that appear recurrently in fictional works.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4499" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-07-28">
<name>some weird shit goin` on</name>
<description>Scenes of this show point to insanely strange events which seem to be taking place; throughout its episodes, the show may or may not explain what is going on. Either way, many viewers will find that a succinct and accurate way to describe the show is "WTF?", and the show`s explanations (or lack thereof) to the events will often be subject of heated debate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4663" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-31">
<name>tone changes</name>
<description>The anime switches quickly, often rather drastically between different moods or tones, sometimes even on the same scene.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4729" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-07-06">
<name>colour coded</name>
<description>Every single character on the main cast has a unique hair colour to help less perceptive viewers distiguish between them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5335" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-10">
<name>dreams and reality</name>
<description>This genre of anime is typically set in both the world as we know it (reality) and a world of dreams, mythology or imagination.
Sometimes this dreamworld is actually real, sometimes it is not. Other times what we think is the real world is the dreamworld, and vice versa. They are not always easy to distinguish from each other, neither by the characters nor the viewer.
Whatever is real, and whatever is reality, both worlds are integral in shaping both the plot of this anime and the development of the characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5384" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-15">
<name>put right what once went wrong</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5417" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>mind fuck</name>
<description>A `mind fuck` is a slang term which describes a work that uses literary devices such as nonlinear storytelling and plot twists in order to present convoluted, yet not conflicting, themes.
A creation is usually considered a mind fuck when a casual observer is not able to discern the true meaning of a work without making a serious attempt to unravel the themes presented or when the plot is incredibly difficult to follow.
Special examples of mind fucks involve a single plot twist which completely changes the viewer`s understanding of the events in a film or novel as well as the ideas it presents.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5651" parentid="3314" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-06-22">
<name>against destiny</name>
<description>Screw destiny and all the others who try to discourage them; they`re not going to fulfill the prophecy of world destruction because they`re the Big Bad`s descendant, or become a sacrificial magician. They`re going to become who they want to be. (source: TV Tropes)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5768" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>intact family</name>
<description>The main character`s family is a so-called "nuclear family". Wherein both parents are alive and present in his or her life. This is actually relatively rare for anime, where "parental abandonment" is the norm.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5888" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>power gives you wings</name>
<description>It is not Red Bull that gives you wings, but power, most often even the power of love.
Whether it`s an android, a mecha, mons, a mahou shoujo, or basically any super powered individual, once they start powering up and become REALLY powerful, it will be indicated by them getting a pair of wings.
Specifically, feathery white angelic wings, sometimes also wings made of Hard Light or Pure Energy. These wings will of course allow the character to fly, float, and glow, all without needing to flap them!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5952" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-25">
<name>end of the world</name>
<description>The imminent end of the world may range from the total destruction of the planet Earth, to the destruction of Earth`s surface, or to the point where human life on the planet is no longer possible, aka the end of humanity.
In any case it looks grim, and the protagonists battle to preserve what they can.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5980" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-24">
<name>live-action imagery</name>
<description>This anime incorporates still images and/or video footage of real-world objects and locations into the animation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5984" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-09-10">
<name>girly tears</name>
<description>Usually girly tears are the ones not shed by men (duh). 
Like when a (stereotypical) girl watches something and cries her makeup out, a (stereotypical) dude just says, proclaiming his masculinity: "Meh, yet another soap opera bulls..t, I`ll be in my garage fixing my ride while playing heavy metal on a burning guitar ...with my teeth! And where`s my beer, woman?".
So that`s how it goes: girly tears are for girls and sissies! Chuck Norris forbid a guy would weep watching something that has this tag! Now 20 push-ups!
P.S. The opposite of "manly tears". Or is it? Let`s face it - it`s all subjective (and relative, and context-dependent).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5991" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-07-04">
<name>dark mood</name>
<description>Similar to `Dark Atmosphere`, but more focused on the actual characters rather than the setting. A dark mood can easily result from a dark atmosphere.
A dark mood is more than just occasionally feeling angry or down, it`s usually a permanent character trait that sours the character`s relationships with others.
However it arises, at least one character in this anime can see little good in the world or the people in it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6055" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-15">
<name>time loop</name>
<description>A time loop is a common plot device in science fiction (especially in universes where time travel is commonplace). Events in the story repeat themselves a number of times with or without some variation with each pass. Most characters either do not realise this is occurring or are attempting to break the cycle in some way. 
One well-known example of this is in the 1993 film Groundhog Day, in which the main character is the only one aware of the time loop, although time loops had appeared in many fictional works prior to that. Stories with time loops commonly center on correcting past mistakes or on getting a character to recognise some key truth; escape from the loop may then follow.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6062" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-05">
<name>heroic sacrifice</name>
<description>"In order to save the many, the few will need to sacrifice their lives..." or so this character may think. 
In a seemingly hopeless situation, against impossible odds, the character does not choose the path of the coward and run, he or she chooses to bravely face the enemy, fully aware that this will mean death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6070" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>mystery</name>
<description>The mystery film is a sub-genre of the more general category of crime film. It focuses on the efforts of the detective, private investigator or amateur sleuth to solve the mysterious circumstances of a crime by means of clues, investigation, and clever deduction. (Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="24746" type="main character in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="200">4.68</rating>
<name>Kaname Madoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>58514.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25024" type="main character in" update="2011-07-30">
<rating votes="239">8.87</rating>
<name>Akemi Homura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akemi Homura is a smart, graceful, athletically-talented girl. Cool if not chilly, her personality can even be seen in her posture.
She seems to be a magical girl, but there are a lot of mysteries surrounding the way she acts. Her fighting style is also unidentified.</description>
<picture>60588.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25163" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-05-01">
<rating votes="101">5.59</rating>
<name>Tomoe Mami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tomoe Mami is a Puella Magi contracted to http://anidb.net/ch25645 [Kyuubee] and a third year student at Madoka`s school, living alone in a penthouse after her parents`s deaths. She has the ability to produce a near-infinite amount of flintlock rifles, can use ribbons to suspend her enemies, and is also able to perform healing magic. Due to being involved and seriously injured in a car accident (which also claimed the lives of her parents) at the time Kyuubey approached her, she was forced to use her wish to save herself. Unlike other Puella Magi, who mostly focus on obtaining valuable Grief Seeds, Mami is particularly focused on saving those around her. Though she often has a cheery disposition, she is also often lonely and scared due to the nature of her work and is pleased when Madoka offers to become her partner.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>60589.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="591" picture="226209.jpg">Mizuhashi Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25315" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-01">
<rating votes="115">4.87</rating>
<name>Miki Sayaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miki Sayaka is Madoka`s classmate who, after helping Madoka rescue Kyubey, ends up getting an offer to become a Puella Magi herself. She cares deeply for her friends, and wants to help an ill boy named Kyousuke Kamijou, whom she has a crush on. She becomes a Puella Magi after using her wish to cure Kyousuke`s hand, which was damaged in an accident which robbed him of his ability to play the violin. Sayaka`s weapon of choice is a sword and, like Mami, she can produce multiple swords at a time. She also has regenerative powers stronger than anyone else due to the nature of her wish. Sayaka hates people that only think of themselves at the cost of hurting others and is easily provoked into a fight.</description>
<picture>60591.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25641" type="main character in" update="2011-03-01">
<rating votes="387">8.74</rating>
<name>Akemi Homura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akemi Homura is a Puella Magi who first appears in Madoka`s dream, and then transfers into her school the day after the dream. A beautiful yet mysterious individual who performs exceptionally well in school, be it academically or athletically, making her popular at school despite her awkward personality. It is unknown whom she is contracted to, with Kyuubey identifying her as an irregular. Homura has extensive knowledge concerning different Puella Magi and is well aware of the dark sides of becoming one, believing those with kind hearts are unfit to become one. As such, she tries to keep other girls from making contracts, particularly Madoka, whom she seems to know well before their meeting. Though she is seen as something of a rival, she often strives to protect Madoka and the others from life-threatening danger. Homura has a small discus-like object strapped to her left forearm and uses it like a shield, and is able to produce various military weapons such as grenades and pistols. It is later revealed that she is from another timeline, as she has the ability to temporarily stop time, allowing her to travel quickly and get an advantage on her opponents.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>60587.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25642" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-12-10">
<rating votes="122">6.87</rating>
<name>Tomoe Mami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60590.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="591" picture="226209.jpg">Mizuhashi Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25643" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-01">
<rating votes="104">5.11</rating>
<name>Miki Sayaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Magical Girl form of Miki Sayaka.</description>
<picture>60592.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25644" type="main character in" update="2013-04-18">
<rating votes="154">4.53</rating>
<name>Kaname Madoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A 14-year-old girl whose life changes when she encounters the Puella Magi Homura and the familiar Kyubey, who offers to transform her into a Puella Magi herself. She sees herself as a person without special qualities or talents, and after seeing Mami fighting against witches, wants to help people as a Puella Magi the same way Mami does. Madoka becomes uncertain about becoming a Puella Magi after Mami`s death in battle, though she still accompanies her friend, Sayaka, on witch hunts. She is averse to fighting and wishes that everyone would get along. She is implied to have large amount of magical potential within her, and Kyubey is particularly interested in forming a contract with her; however, she has yet to take him up on the offer.</description>
<picture>60593.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25645" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="170">6.37</rating>
<name>Kyuubee</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kyuubee is a familiar who can grant any wish to a certain girl, on the condition that she become a Puella Magi and fight against witches.
When someone makes a contract with him, he extracts their soul and places it inside a Soul Gem, replacing their body with a shell that`s more resilient to fighting witches. He has so far made contracts with Mami, Kyouko and Sayaka, and shows particular interest in making Madoka a magical girl. It is yet to be revealed if there are other familiars besides him. As a magical creature, he can only be seen or heard by Puella Magis and those with magical potential. He is shown to consume used Grief Seeds, though for what reason is unknown. His true motives are unknown, and he constantly tries to find chances to persuade girls with magical potential to form a contract with him despite knowing the dangers that a Puella Magi faces. He tends to have little understanding of human values and doesn`t believe what he`s doing is cruel. If he is killed, another Kyuubee takes his place and consumes the previous one. Homura recognizes his true identity as Incubator.</description>
<picture>60594.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26540" type="appears in" update="2011-01-07">
<rating votes="5">3.01</rating>
<name>Nakazawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62418.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20249" picture="186289.jpg">Matsuoka Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26541" type="appears in" update="2011-03-01">
<rating votes="29">5.97</rating>
<name>Kaname Junko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaname Junko is Madoka`s mother, an executive who wears a lot of make up and sometimes comes home drunk, making it hard to wake her up in the morning. Other than this, she is a caring and gentle person and often gives Madoka advice whenever she is troubled.</description>
<picture>62416.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26542" type="appears in" update="2011-03-01">
<rating votes="5">3.47</rating>
<name>Kaname Tomohisa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaname Tomohisa is Madoka`s father, who seems to be the one in charge of the house.</description>
<picture>62419.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2044" picture="21387.jpg">Iwanaga Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26543" type="appears in" update="2011-03-01">
<rating votes="10">5.16</rating>
<name>Saotome Kazuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saotome Kazuko is Madoka`s teacher, who constantly has trouble keeping a boyfriend.</description>
<picture>62420.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2068" picture="28743.jpg">Iwao Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26544" type="appears in" update="2020-02-05">
<rating votes="31">2.65</rating>
<name>Shizuki Hitomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shizuki Hitomi is http://anidb.net/ch25644 [Madoka] and http://anidb.net/ch25315 [Sayaka]`s classmate and friend, quite popular with the boys. She seems to believe Sayaka and Madoka are in a relationship and often feels she is being left out. In episode seven, she tells Sayaka that she loves http://anidb.net/ch27647 [Kyousuke] and that she plans to confess to him if Sayaka does not.</description>
<picture>244313.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="357" picture="32000.jpg">Shintani Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26545" type="appears in" update="2020-02-05">
<rating votes="11">4.28</rating>
<name>Kaname Tatsuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaname Tatsuya is http://anidb.net/ch25644 [Madoka]`s younger brother.</description>
<picture>244314.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="591" picture="226209.jpg">Mizuhashi Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27647" type="appears in" update="2020-02-05">
<rating votes="20">1.92</rating>
<name>Kamijou Kyousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kamijou Kyousuke is a disabled boy whom http://anidb.net/ch25315 [Sayaka] constantly visits in hospital. He used to be a violin player, but an accident crippled him and destroyed the feeling in his fingers, making him unable to play an instrument again, which causes him a lot of grief and despair. Sayaka uses her wish to cure his hand, allowing him to play the violin once more.</description>
<picture>244312.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5641" picture="228630.jpg">Yoshida Seiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27945" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-23">
<rating votes="133">7.40</rating>
<name>Sakura Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244587.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="347" picture="41555.jpg">Nonaka Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28165" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-28">
<rating votes="114">7.54</rating>
<name>Sakura Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakura Kyouko is a rival Puella Magi who comes to the city after Mami is killed by a witch. A girl with red-colored long hair and an equally fiery personality to match. Amusingly, she is always seen eating something, even while she is battling Sayaka. When Kyouko learns Sayaka had become a Puella Magi just before she arrived, she becomes Sayaka`s enemy for allegedly stealing her territory, although she later tries to help her after learning the truth about Soul Gems. She comes from a poor church family and used her wish so that people would listen to her father`s preachings. However, when her father learned of this, he went mad and killed his entire family. As such, Kyouko decided only to use her magic for herself, since using it for others will only cause despair. Having grown up in a poor family, she often has to steal food and hates wasting it, a logic she also applies to Grief Seeds, as she only goes after fully grown witches. Kyouko wields a spear which can extend itself, split into multiple sections, and produce a ball at the end of the chain, which can constrict and hit others at the same time.</description>
<picture>64987.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="347" picture="41555.jpg">Nonaka Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28261" type="appears in" update="2011-02-04">
<rating votes="6">2.94</rating>
<name>Kyousuke no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65119.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1630" picture="1887.gif">Tasaka Hideki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29575" type="appears in" update="2011-03-17">
<rating votes="11">4.02</rating>
<name>Oktavia von Seckendorff</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Oktavia von Seckendorff is the witch form of Miki Sayaka. She briefly appears at the end of Episode 8 and battles with Sakura Kyouko in Episode 9. Her Labyrinth is filled with calls for attention -- probably to Kamijou Kyousuke. Initially, the outer areas of her Labyrinth are filled with train tracks, perhaps a reflection of the train station where she became a witch. Later on, the entrance area becomes a long corridor filled with concert posters. The center of the Labyrinth appears to be a distorted concert hall, where the seats fill the domed ceiling. Her weapons appear to be manifested wheels, and the concert hall is populated with a spectral string orchestra.
Source: Puella Magi Wiki</description>
<picture>68010.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="30153" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="5">3.93</rating>
<name>Gertrud</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gertrud is a witch born from negative emotions, who loves roses more than anything else--her barrier is full of them. She uses humans` life energy to feed her roses and hates humans entering her barrier. Her minions are Anthony and Adelbert. She and her barrier are presented in a surreal manner with bizarre cut-and-paste-style photo collages. She also seems to like mustaches as both of her minions have some. The special page has confirmed that the mustaches are set by the witch herself. Her "body" has parts from a butterfly, and butterflies are seen in her barrier at many points.
Source: Puella Magi Wiki</description>
<picture>68011.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="30154" type="appears in" update="2014-04-06">
<rating votes="5">3.93</rating>
<name>Anthony</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Anthony is Gertrud`s minion. His duty is landscaping. His mustache is set by the witch.</description>
<picture>68012.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="30155" type="appears in" update="2011-03-17">
<rating votes="5">3.93</rating>
<name>Adelbert</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Adelbert is the rose garden witch`s minion. His duty is to act as lookout. Upon seeing a human, he will sound a warning bell and headbutt him mercilessly. They have 2.5 (20/8) vision. The smaller type can change into rose vines to hinder intruders.</description>
<picture>68013.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="30156" type="appears in" update="2014-05-21">
<rating votes="13">6.34</rating>
<name>Charlotte</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The dessert witch, with a tenacious nature. She desires everything. She will never give up. Though she is capable of creating infinite amounts of any dessert she desires, she is unable to make the cheese that she loves most. One could easily catch her off-guard with a piece of cheese.
The head of her first form is shaped like piece of candy in wrap. In her fight against Mami, after it looks like she is defeated, she suddenly transforms into her second form, a huge caterpiller, and kills Mami.
Source: Puella Magi Wiki</description>
<picture>68014.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="30157" type="appears in" update="2011-03-17">
<rating votes="5">3.93</rating>
<name>Pyotr</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The dessert witch`s minion. His duty is to search for cheese. However, one shouldn`t expect much from him.</description>
<picture>68015.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="30158" type="appears in" update="2011-03-17">
<rating votes="5">3.93</rating>
<name>H.N. Elly (Kirsten)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The box witch with a covetous nature. She is a staunchly reclusive witch. Anything she covets she locks away within glass. The thoughts of her prisoners are laid bare, but one can strike her without thought without problems.</description>
<picture>68016.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="30159" type="appears in" update="2011-03-17">
<rating votes="5">3.93</rating>
<name>Daniyyel + Jennifer</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The box witch`s minions with the duty of transportation. Anything they touch becomes easy to carry.</description>
<picture>68017.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="30160" type="appears in" update="2011-03-17">
<rating votes="4">3.89</rating>
<name>Gisela</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gisela is a witch who battles Kyouko within the flashback scene in Episode 7.
The silver witch, with a liberal nature. She dwells in a barrier where everything moves at high speed, but the witch herself is dull. She unfortunately can not use any sort of scientific power. Her body was once dazzling with silver, but her body has rusted as she gazes upon the coastal sunset.</description>
<picture>68018.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="30161" type="appears in" update="2011-03-17">
<rating votes="4">4.17</rating>
<name>Dora</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The silver witch`s minion, whose duty is to declare her opinion. She makes a nuisance of herself with the roaring from the pipes extending from her body as she moves about like a freak sandstorm. She hates magnets.</description>
<picture>68019.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="30162" type="appears in" update="2011-03-17">
<rating votes="5">4.63</rating>
<name>Elsa Maria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Elsa Maria is a witch who battles Sayaka at the end of Episode 7. Her barrier is full of dark shadows with a white background. Her symbolism includes Christian crosses, and the terrain forms a large arm holding either a torch or a monstrance. Elsa Maria appears to be praying before this object when Sayaka engages her. She fights with fanged snake-like minions and tree branches that extend from her body.
The shadow witch with a self-righteous nature. She continually prays for all of creation. She drags all life equally into her shadow without breaking her posture. One hoping to defeat her must know the blackest anguish.
Source: Puella Magi Wiki</description>
<picture>68020.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="30176" type="appears in" update="2011-03-17">
<rating votes="9">2.73</rating>
<name>Kriemhild Gretchen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kriemhild Gretchen is the witch form of Kaname Madoka. She appears in the fourth timeline of Episode 10 as a mountain-sized creature. Her name was not shown during initial broadcast, but was added in a Nicovideo broadcast version one week later.
Nothing is known about the specifics of her powers or personality, but her formation in the second timeline involves thunderclouds coalescing into a giant humanoid (the name is not shown then, however, and thus it is not known whether that witch is also called Kriemhild Gretchen). According to Kyuubey, her strength in the fourth timeline is of such a magnitude that she could obliterate the planet within ten days.
Source: Puella Magi Wiki</description>
<picture>68045.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="31463" type="appears in" update="2013-08-27">
<rating votes="75">6.18</rating>
<name>Kaname Madoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141993.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70742" type="appears in" update="2014-10-19">
<rating votes="4">2.24</rating>
<name>Charlotte</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Charlotte`s second forme.</description>
<picture>162919.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="70743" type="appears in" update="2014-10-19">
<rating votes="2">4.13</rating>
<name>Sebastian</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sebastian is the shadow witch`s minion. His duty is to blindly believe. He is the aggregate of the lives who have found salvation thanks to the shadow witch. He continually seeks out companions.</description>
<picture>162920.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="70745" type="appears in" update="2014-10-19">
<rating votes="2">4.13</rating>
<name>Walpurgis Night`s Minions</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>They are the stage-constructing witch`s minions. Their duty is to be clowns. Countless souls drawn to her vast magical power. Nobody knows whether Walpurgis Night was initially a single person, or if it was a phantom born from the gathering of many spirits.</description>
<picture>162922.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="70746" type="appears in" update="2014-10-19">
<rating votes="2">4.13</rating>
<name>Walpurgis Night</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Walpurgis Night is the stage-constructing witch. Her nature is helplessness. She symbolizes the fool who continuously spins in circles. The witch`s mysteries have been handed down through the course of history; her appellation is "Walpurgis Night." She will continue to rotate aimlessly throughout the world until she completely changes the whole of this age into a drama. When the doll`s usual upside-down position reaches the top part of the witch, she completely roils the civilization on the ground in a flash through her gale-like flight.</description>
<picture>162923.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="126544" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-01-14</airdate>
<rating votes="45">6.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それはとっても嬉しいなって</title>
<title xml:lang="en">That Would Be Really Nice</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Pensavo che sarebbe molto bello</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Bu Harika Olurdu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sore wa Tottemo Ureshii Natte</title>
<summary>While rescuing Kyubey from being attacked by Homura, Madoka and Sayaka lose their way in a mysterious space. They find themselves in a desperate situation and are rescued by Mami Tomoe, a magical girl. Afterward, Mami invites them to her room.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>591737</identifier>
<identifier>puella-magi-madoka-magica</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="126545" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-01-07</airdate>
<rating votes="51">6.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢の中で会った, ような.....</title>
<title xml:lang="en">As If I Met Her in My Dream...</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Come se fossimo incontrate in sogno</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Onunla Bir Rüyada Falan Tanıştım</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume no Naka de Atta, You na.....</title>
<summary>She has a loving family and best friends. She laughs and cries from time to time. Madoka Kaname - an eighth grader who lives such a peaceful life. One night, she has a strange dream. It was supposed to be an usual routine day, but the arrival of Homura Akemi - a transfer student who came to Madoka`s class, changed that.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>591735</identifier>
<identifier>puella-magi-madoka-magica</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="126624" update="2011-01-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-01-07</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126963" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-01-21</airdate>
<rating votes="57">8.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">もう何も恐くない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m Not Afraid Anymore</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Ormai non ho più paura di nulla</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Artık Hiçbir Şeyden Korkmuyorum</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mou Nanimo Kowakunai</title>
<summary>Madoka and Sayaka are getting used to Mami`s witch hunting trial run. Yet their wishes remain undecided. Mami reveals her past to the anxious two girls. Sayaka asks, "Does my wish have to be for myself?"
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>591739</identifier>
<identifier>puella-magi-madoka-magica</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="127599" update="2014-05-26">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-01-21</airdate>
<rating votes="4">9.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="127600" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-01-28</airdate>
<rating votes="39">6.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">奇跡も, 魔法も, あるんだよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">There Are Miracles and Magic</title>
<title xml:lang="it">I miracoli e le magie esistono</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Mucizeler Ve Büyü Gerçek</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiseki mo, Mahou mo, Arun Da yo</title>
<summary>The day after the fierce battle between Mami and the witch was a normal peaceful day. After what they witnessed, Madoka and Sayaka fully realize the demands of being involved in the magical world, and give up becoming on magical girls.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>591741</identifier>
<identifier>puella-magi-madoka-magica</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="127759" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-02-04</airdate>
<rating votes="38">6.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">後悔なんて, あるわけない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">There`s No Way I Would Regret It</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Io non ho alcun rimpianto</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Bundan Asla Pişman Olmayacağım</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koukai Nante, Aru Wake nai</title>
<summary>As a magical girl, Sayaka rescues Madoka and Hitomi from a witch. Now that her wish has come true by signing Kyubey`s contract, her mind is clear and she doesn`t seem to regret becoming a magical girl.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>591743</identifier>
<identifier>puella-magi-madoka-magica</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="127938" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-02-11</airdate>
<rating votes="39">8.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">こんなの絶対おかしいよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This Just Isn`t Right</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Non è per niente giusto tutto questo</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Bu Doğru Olamaz</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Konna no Zettai Okashii yo</title>
<summary>Homura appears suddenly on Sayaka and Kyoko`s battlefield. She intervenes and knocks Sayaka unconscious with a single blow. After seeing this, Kyoko is on her guard against Homura, and leaves, putting an end to the battle.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>591745</identifier>
<identifier>puella-magi-madoka-magica</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="128178" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="37">7.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">本当の気持ちと向き合えますか?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Can I Face My True Feelings?</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Sai affrontare a volto aperto i tuoi sentimenti?</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Gerçek Hislerinle Yüzleşebilir Misin?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hontou no Kimochi to Mukiaemasuka?</title>
<summary>Sayaka discovers the truth about her own body as a magical girl. She wavers between the wish that came true by accepting the destiny to fight and the high price she paid for it. Sayaka is in low spirits at home when Kyoko Sakura shows up.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>591747</identifier>
<identifier>puella-magi-madoka-magica</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="128265" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="40">9.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あたしって, ほんとバカ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m Such a Fool</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Sono davvero una stupida</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Salaktım, Çok Salaktım</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atashitte, Honto Baka</title>
<summary>Despite her own injury, Sayaka keeps shredding the witch in front of her. Thanks to healing magic, she wins without a scratch at the end. But she seems extremely exhausted.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>591749</identifier>
<identifier>puella-magi-madoka-magica</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="128355" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-03-04</airdate>
<rating votes="37">8.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そんなの, あたしが許さない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Can`t Forgive That Kind of Thing</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Io non lo permetterò</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Buna Asla İzin Vermezdim</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sonna no, Atashi ga Yurusanai</title>
<summary>Sayaka`s Soul Gem turns into a jet-black grief seed, which hatches and a new witch emerges. Carrying Sayaka`s body, Kyoko focuses on defending against the approaching witch`s attacks. Homura cuts into the witch`s labyrinth and leads Kyoko to escape.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>591751</identifier>
<identifier>puella-magi-madoka-magica</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="128508" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-03-11</airdate>
<rating votes="69">9.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">もう誰にも頼らない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Can`t Depend on Anyone Anymore</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Ormai non conto più su nessuno</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Artık Kimseye Güvenmeyeceğim</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mou Dare ni mo Tayoranai</title>
<summary>A scene depicting a female transfer student. The timid girl is so nervous and meek. She introduces herself shyly while feeling the eyes of all the students in the class. At recess, other girls gather around her and ask questions curiously.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>591753</identifier>
<identifier>puella-magi-madoka-magica</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="128584" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="45">7.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">わたしの, 最高の友達</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Best Friend</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La mia migliore amica</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">En Yakın Arkadaşım</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi no, Saikou no Tomodachi</title>
<summary>Homura challenges Walpurgisnacht alone and is seriously wounded. She despairs because she can`t win no matter how many times she tries. Her actions are making Madoka suffer even more, and she becomes despondent. Her Soul Gem begins to turn black.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>591757</identifier>
<identifier>puella-magi-madoka-magica</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="128585" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="43">8.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最後に残った道しるべ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Final Sign Left</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`ultima via rimasta</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Bana Rehberlik Edecek, Kalan Tek Şeyim</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo ni Nokotta Michishirube</title>
<summary>Sayaka`s funeral was held in the rain. Madoka returns home with vacant eyes. She barely says anything to Junko who met her at the front door, and goes into her room. Kyubey appears in front of Madoka, who is lost in her grief, alone.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>591755</identifier>
<identifier>puella-magi-madoka-magica</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="135087" update="2011-12-01">
<epno type="4">T10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2010-12-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">CM動画10</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 10 (30sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135088" update="2011-12-01">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2010-12-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">CM動画9</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 9 (15sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135089" update="2011-12-01">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2010-12-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">CM動画8</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 8 (OP &amp; ED)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135090" update="2011-12-01">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">CM動画7</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 7 (Kyubey)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135091" update="2011-12-01">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">CM動画6</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 6 (Sayaka)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135092" update="2011-12-01">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">CM動画5</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 5 (Mami)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135093" update="2011-12-01">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">CM動画4</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 4 (Homura)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135094" update="2011-12-01">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">CM動画3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 3 (Madoka)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135095" update="2011-12-01">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">CM動画2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 2 (Staff)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135096" update="2011-12-01">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">CM動画1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1 (Staff)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="143857" update="2012-09-15">
<epno type="4">T12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">BD CM 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="143858" update="2012-09-15">
<epno type="4">T11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">BD CM 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145527" update="2012-11-20">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-08-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145528" update="2014-05-26">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-04-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="184694" update="2017-02-17">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
