<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8073" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-05-07</startdate>
<enddate>2011-05-07</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hoshi o Ou Kodomo</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Children Who Chase Stars</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Journey to Agartha</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">별을 쫓는 아이</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Децата, които преследваха загубените гласове</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Hoshi wo Ou Kodomo</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Діти, що женуться за зорями</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">星を追う子ども</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Children Who Chase Lost Voices</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Die Reise nach Agartha</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Voyage vers Agartha</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Viaje a Agartha</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Ловцы забытых голосов</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">별을 쫓는 아이:아가르타의 전설</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Děti, které následují hvězdy</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="official">Vaikai, kurie vijosi žvaigždes</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">เด็กสาวกับเสียงเพรียกแห่งพิภพเทวา</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="331" approval="53" total="58">Tenkuu no Shiro Laputa</anime>
<anime id="7" approval="23" total="37">Mononoke-hime</anime>
<anime id="112" approval="8" total="21">Sen to Chihiro no Kamikakushi</anime>
<anime id="4193" approval="5" total="14">Ged Senki: Tales from Earthsea</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="10">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="109384">very good art, bad story, thats it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="314120">I agree with the rest.  The art is absolutely top notch.  The story wasn`t awful, but is certainly wasn`t good.  It was just... lacking.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="437695">great art and animation... full of nature but the plot doesn`t seem to be quenching enough... for fans i say and a good attempt to compete ghibli</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="77972">For those who like beautiful, vivid and detailed visual you will not be disappointed. But don`t expect much about the story.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="210496">This film is closer to a Ghibli film than Shinkai Makoto`s previous works. Stunning visuals and a great story as always. General dialogs and story flow are much easier to understand than past Shinkai works, but unfortunately lacks the powerful monologues that Shinkai is so good at writing.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="57112">Excellent visuals, most notably sky, sunset, and night scenes, which is much of the same if you`re used to Makoto Shinkai. He changes things up a bit by showing a lot of northern lights to great effect. However, his unmatched, almost photo-realistic detail found in 5 Centimeters Per Second is not found here due to the fantasy setting.

The story is interesting but only serves to create scenarios where Shinkai can showcase his visual talent. This tries to be like a studio Ghibli movie, but falls way short in both character and story. The music is quite good, but not Tenmon`s best.

Overall, watch this for the visuals even though 5 Centimeters Per Second does it better.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="501846">Beautiful. The animation is stunning. Very close to Miyazaki`s work. I enjoyed thoroughly. That radio-beautiful beginning of the story.. No doubt, Miyazaki effected the work of Shinkai Makoto. Go and see this movie ;). You won`t regret it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="626968">A great film that explores (albeit not enough) the hollow earth civilization, Agartha.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>https://www.cwfilms.jp/hoshi-o-kodomo/top.php</url>
<creators>
<name id="445" type="Original Work">Shinkai Makoto</name>
<name id="445" type="Direction">Shinkai Makoto</name>
<name id="3546" type="Music">Tenmon</name>
<name id="1810" type="Character Design">Nishimura Takayo</name>
<name id="10345" type="Work">CoMix Wave Films</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch25887 [Asuna] lost her father and lives a lonely life listening to mysterious music coming from her father`s crystal radio. One day she sets out for a journey to see a boy again. Through the adventure, she experiences a parting and finds the cruelty and the beauty of the world.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2368">6.85</permanent>
<temporary count="2378">7.45</temporary>
<review count="3">7.77</review>
</ratings>
<picture>232317.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12141</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9760</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4931</identifier>
<identifier>elzbag</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.cwfilms.jp/hoshi-o-kodomo/top.php</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Children_Who_Chase_Lost_Voices</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>星を追う子ども</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2553</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>338303</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13449</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2820</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>별을_쫓는_아이</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>追逐繁星的孩子</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14898</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3606" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-11">
<name>family without father</name>
<description>For some reason the protagonists father is no longer among the living. The much too early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family: Possibly the grieve-stricken mother and children barely function as humans. Or adding emphasis to the overall financial predicament of the family, should the father have been the money earner.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3870" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2016-09-11">
<name>resurrection</name>
<description>At least one character in this anime is brought back from the dead or from a near-death experience. This is achieved by either very advanced technology or simply magic.</description>
<picurl>191152.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4510" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-10-05">
<name>desolate ruins</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="25887" type="main character in" update="2010-12-22">
<rating votes="17">6.04</rating>
<name>Watase Asuna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61210.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12266" picture="56026.jpg">Kanemoto Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25888" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-12-22">
<rating votes="7">5.03</rating>
<name>Shun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61208.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="470" picture="17419.jpg">Irino Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25889" type="main character in" update="2010-12-22">
<rating votes="11">3.62</rating>
<name>Morisaki Ryuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61209.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25892" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-02">
<rating votes="1">5.03</rating>
<name>Asuna no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>82646.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25893" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-02">
<rating votes="1">2.14</rating>
<name>Mana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>82647.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="430" picture="246278.jpg">Hidaka Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25894" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-09">
<rating votes="7">7.74</rating>
<name>Mimi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79690.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="302" picture="17134.jpg">Takeuchi Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25895" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-02">
<rating votes="2">1.88</rating>
<name>Morisaki Risa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>82648.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="508" picture="140061.jpg">Shimamoto Sumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47118" type="main character in" update="2012-07-22">
<rating votes="7">4.90</rating>
<name>Shin Canaan Preases</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91286.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="470" picture="17419.jpg">Irino Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47119" type="appears in" update="2012-07-22">
<name>Yazaki Yuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91297.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2227" picture="73301.jpg">Inamura Yuuna</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47121" type="appears in" update="2012-07-22">
<name>Ikeda-sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91296.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="613" picture="155849.jpg">Mizuno Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47122" type="appears in" update="2012-07-22">
<name>Asuna no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91295.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="76" picture="16684.jpg">Maeda Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47123" type="appears in" update="2012-07-22">
<name>Chourou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91294.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33513" picture="172673.jpg">Katsukura Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47124" type="appears in" update="2012-07-22">
<name>Souhei Taichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91292.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="373" picture="191382.jpg">Hamada Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47125" type="appears in" update="2012-07-22">
<name>Seri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91291.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47126" type="appears in" update="2012-07-22">
<name>Amorout no Roujin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91289.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2366" picture="203225.jpg">Ooki Tamio</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="124740" update="2011-05-12">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>120</length>
<airdate>2011-05-07</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125089" update="2010-11-09">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2010-11-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132086" update="2011-07-27">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-03-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135832" update="2011-12-28">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>7</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Makoto Shinkai Filmography</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135833" update="2011-12-28">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>45</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Making Of</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135834" update="2011-12-28">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Hello Goodbye and Hello PV -Anri Kumaki-</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135835" update="2012-08-02">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Director and Cast Interview -Short Ver</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135836" update="2012-08-02">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>55</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Director and Cast Interview -Long Ver</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135837" update="2011-12-28">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Spot 15sec</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
