<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8085" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-02-23</startdate>
<enddate>2011-03-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Baka to Test to Shoukanjuu: Matsuri</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Глупаци, тестове и странни същества: Празник</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Baka to Test to Shoukanjuu OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">bakatest ova</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">バカとテストと召喚獣 ~祭~</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Baka and Test: Summon the Beasts - OVA</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8235" type="Sequel">Baka to Test to Shoukanjuu Ni!</anime>
<anime id="6747" type="Prequel">Baka to Test to Shoukanjuu</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="343071">Actually , it`s not necessary to watch this , but in case you wonder the event which play on the Ni , ep5 , then watch it , it`s maybe not so funny then the series , but it a great OVA.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.bakatest.com/ova/</url>
<creators>
<name id="2900" type="Animation Work">Silver Link</name>
<name id="3779" type="Character Design">Ooshima Miwa</name>
<name id="2836" type="Series Composition">Takayama Katsuhiko</name>
<name id="7052" type="Original Work">Inoue Kenji</name>
<name id="1564" type="Direction">Oonuma Shin</name>
<name id="2931" type="Music">Nijine</name>
<name id="3779" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ooshima Miwa</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a light novel series by http://anidb.net/cr7052 [Inoue Kenji] with illustrations by http://anidb.net/cr7051 [Haga Yui].
The school festival ("Seiryousai") at Fumizaki Academy is upon the colourful high school Class 2-F. Though, attracting visitors to their Chinese Cafe "European" can be quite exasperating, especially with rivals from another class publicly badmouthing their cafe. Thus it is time for class 2-F`s secret weapon: http://anidb.net/ch11106 [Yoshii Akihisa] cross-dressing in a cute maid outfit.
But to finally be able to buy new classroom desks they will have to win the Summoned Being Tournament on day two of the school festival.
— written by foo2</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2080">6.49</permanent>
<temporary count="2096">7.31</temporary>
<review count="1">5.50</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221074.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11847</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>31298</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>9471</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>10431</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.bakatest.com/ova/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Baka_to_Test_to_Shōkanjū</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>バカとテストと召喚獣</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2145</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>339798</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13366</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15123</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="28" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-16">
<name>baseball</name>
<description>Baseball is like a complicated version of Rounders. It involves hitting a ball with a stick, then running around several bases placed in the form of a diamond on a field. Big in the US, and also in Japan.</description>
<picurl>29801.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="618" parentid="2565" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>trap</name>
<description>A trap is a plot device where a male character is mistaken for a female, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the male (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the male, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the male character as a female; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through his behaviour, and/or language. A male character misinterpreted by others as female, without action from the male (explicitly feminine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t1637 [reverse trap].
Note: the tag image is from http://anidb.net/a10475 [Himegoto].</description>
<picurl>161537.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1244" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>summoning</name>
<description>Ability to call/materialize some kind of creature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1471" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-19">
<name>bad cooking</name>
<description>The character is hopelessly terrible at cooking, and any attempts he or she makes at making even the simplest dishes are spectacular failures.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2069" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-15">
<name>delinquent</name>
<description>Delinquents - Every school has them, but not all anime with school setting make delinquents a central topic. There are several versions of these delinquents, though some are grounded on a misunderstanding:
* The student with a really bad image and attitude, based on his real criminal actions outside of the school and is even feared by teachers.
* The primitive "class bully" that pushes around ("clobbers") his classmates for no apparent reason, possibly extorting lunch money.
* The student with an sinister complexion or "evil eye", but is actually a "good" student (unfoundedly feared character).
* The rebellious student, who does not care for studying, but is otherwise docile. Called a "delinquent" as a joke.</description>
<picurl>243713.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2072" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>maid</name>
<description>A maid is a female employed in domestic service. They usually wear uniforms. Since their nature is to be obedient and serve their goshujin-sama (master), they are one of the most desired types of women in Japan, a dream of every Japanese man, particularly http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku]. Often seen in so-called Maid Cafes in Akihabara, where male customers can for a little time enjoy the feeling of being served by a woman. The male gender opposite is the butler.</description>
<picurl>4954.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2670" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>school festival - TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>THIS TAG NEEDS TO BE SPLIT:
into http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=tag&amp;tagid=6119&amp;reltb=eptb [school culture festival]
and http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=tag&amp;tagid=2665&amp;reltb=eptb [school sports festival]
The obligatory school festival (or cultural fair) with cosplay cafe, haunted house, theatre performance, and food booths cannot be missing in any school setting.
For good measure there may also be an athletics or sports festival in this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2863" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>proxy battles</name>
<description>In our terms, a proxy battle is a battle where humans use creatures/robots to do the fighting for them, either by commanding those creatures/robots or by simply evolving them/changing them into battle mode. Often the training aspect is also involved, or in some cases the proxies are nothing more than holographic representatives of some other variation of competition (like for example a card game). While many popular shounen anime fit under this category, it`s not limited to shounen anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3094" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-16">
<name>befriend attack</name>
<description>A befriend attack is a pounce performed by someone in an attempt to hug someone else. This is an exuberant display of affection, often used for comedic effect. Sometimes, the target of such attacks learn to dodge them, usually by simply sidestepping them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3150" parentid="4522" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>social class issues</name>
<description>A character`s standing in society is cause of many issues. More generally, the society`s class structure is the source of many problems in the anime.
A common example is class division; a strong and rigid class division between rich/elite and poor/commoners, with the elites having disproportionately more privilege than the common class.
This can be applied not only when royalty and nobility are present, but also dystopian societies display often these divisions.
Another example is a division between employees and management, with employees akin to the common class, and management akin to the elite class.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4151" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-07-04">
<name>German suplex</name>
<description>A wrestling move commonly used in a slapstick manner by one of the more unique characters in a series. The move typically signals a strong and coordinated individual (who may or may not actually be a wrestler). Often the move will be deployed on the same person over and over again as part of a running gag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6029" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-04-08">
<name>mundane made awesome</name>
<description>Sometimes normal just doesn`t cut it. Eating: you put food in your mouth and chew. Playing sports: you throw a ball around. You need to make it awesome, no matter how mundane it is.
Let`s throw in some gripping orchestral music, lighting changes, different camera angles, something! Don`t write like a man, write like an evil overlord! Exaggerate your expressions and gestures, speak with excessive intonation, and if all else fails, throw in some close-ups, slow motion, and ominous Latin chanting! With practice, even you can turn something like eating chips into an epic battle of light and dark, blinding the viewer with sheer awesomeness.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>149443.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="5085" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-03-16">
<rating votes="9">8.91</rating>
<name>Gargoyle</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A masterpiece of highly skilled alchemists, it protects the entrance to the Yoshinaga household.</description>
<picture>21455.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="5086" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-03-16">
<rating votes="6">5.70</rating>
<name>Yoshinaga Futaba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The only daughter and youngest member of the household. She is a boyish troublemaker who loves wrestling.</description>
<picture>21454.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="9672" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-03-12">
<rating votes="29">7.97</rating>
<name>Midarezaki Kyouka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The `mother` of Midarezaki family. She is twenty years old, however, she has an appearance of a little girl with cat`s ear and tail. Her real name is `Kyoukya Eaeriaea`, and she used to be worshiped by the people of an underground kingdom named `Shangri-la`, however, she ran away because she felt something was missing from her life.</description>
<picture>44559.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="11106" type="main character in" update="2009-08-12">
<rating votes="142">5.54</rating>
<name>Yoshii Akihisa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>33035.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11107" type="main character in" update="2009-08-12">
<rating votes="170">5.10</rating>
<name>Himeji Mizuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>33036.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5878" picture="45926.jpg">Harada Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11108" type="main character in" update="2009-08-12">
<rating votes="209">6.93</rating>
<name>Shimada Minami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>33037.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="591" picture="226209.jpg">Mizuhashi Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11109" type="main character in" update="2009-08-12">
<rating votes="123">6.43</rating>
<name>Sakamoto Yuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>33038.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="644" picture="205640.jpg">Suzuki Tatsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11110" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="162">7.36</rating>
<name>Kinoshita Hideyoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hideyoshi Kinoshita is a very feminine-looking bishounen and is the younger twin brother of Yuuko Kinoshita of class A. Despite being a fraternal twin, except for his male body, he looks almost identical to his twin sister. Because of that, his male peers, and many of his female peers, see him as a female, which upsets him though he doesn`t express it strongly. In the Anime, his feminine looks are often the subject of fanservice, going so far as to make him his own gender. Hideyoshi has a helpful personality and is willing to support any activity his friends embark on. He uses the term `Washi`, used by old venerable men to describe himself. While he is bad in academics, he has unquestionable talent in acting, and can not only replicate the behavior and mannerisms of other people but also their voices as well. In volume 2, he was instigated by Akihisa to mimic Yuuji`s voice to propose to Shouko during their tournament, confusing her and ultimately setting up the stage for a win for Akihisa-Yuuji Team, but this move caused Yuuji all manner of problems later on. His Shoukanjuu is clad in Hakama and wields a Naginata.</description>
<picture>33039.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11111" type="main character in" update="2009-08-12">
<rating votes="148">6.66</rating>
<name>Tsuchiya Kouta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>33040.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="689" picture="170354.jpg">Miyata Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11112" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-28">
<rating votes="226">8.39</rating>
<name>Kirishima Shouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shouko Kirishima is the childhood friend of Yuji Sakamoto. She is the top student in her level and the class representative for class A. In the story, she is portrayed as a soft-spoken, but highly assertive and intelligent girl. In the novel, her dialog always starts with ellipses. She is described as elegantly beautiful and very popular, but yet has no boyfriend, which initially created the impression to others that she is a lesbian. Later, it was revealed that the reason for this is because she is crazily infatuated with Yuji since childhood and acts possessively towards him. Despite being tricked multiple times, she still shows a trusting nature towards Yuji and practically believes everything he says. Shouko is also shown to be someone who is very long-term thinking, and has already decided on her children`s names (Shoyuu for a girl, and Koshou for a boy). She is also a gadget moron, and is known to spoil any electronic gadget that falls into her hands. Her Shoukanjuu is clad in Samurai armor and wields a Japanese longsword.</description>
<picture>33041.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10361" picture="38073.jpg">Isomura Tomomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11667" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-12-25">
<rating votes="128">8.81</rating>
<name>Amano Tooko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40614.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13271" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-26">
<rating votes="68">6.85</rating>
<name>Shimada Hazuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39321.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12352" picture="130106.jpg">Hirata Mana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14006" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-10">
<rating votes="71">4.50</rating>
<name>Kinoshita Yuuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The attractive elder twin sister of Kinoshita Hideyoshi. Due to their disparity in academic abilities, she feels superior to her younger brother, whom she thinks is trash. During the classroom wars in volume 1, Hideyoshi, while acting on a strategy of Yuuji, masqueraded as his sister and branded the whole of class C as filthy pigs, sowing discord between class C and class A, saving F from a potential alliance between class C and class B. And the proud Yuuko bears a deep grudge against Hideyoshi and class F for the incident.</description>
<picture>42794.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14009" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-10">
<rating votes="55">5.06</rating>
<name>Nishimura Souichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>42791.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14010" type="appears in" update="2010-02-10">
<rating votes="11">2.99</rating>
<name>Fukuhara Shin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>42792.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="592" picture="170729.jpg">Tsuda Kenjirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14012" type="appears in" update="2010-01-11">
<rating votes="18">4.42</rating>
<name>Takahashi Youko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41307.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="223" picture="228520.jpg">Kakazu Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14125" type="appears in" update="2010-02-10">
<rating votes="52">3.47</rating>
<name>Kubo Toshimitsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A calm and cool man with glasses and the second ranked student in his level. He lives in a relatively tight and structured schedule which is reflected in his high grades. However, he easily misinterprets situations and because of this, he thinks that Akihisa was trying to hit on him. As a result, he ends up having a crush on him despite being another man.</description>
<picture>42793.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="202" picture="25743.jpg">Terashima Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14236" type="main character in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="94">8.67</rating>
<name>Kinoshita Hideyoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hideyoshi Kinoshita is a very feminine-looking bishounen and is the younger twin brother of Yuuko Kinoshita of class A. Despite being a fraternal twin, except for his male body, he looks almost identical to his twin sister. Because of that, his male peers, and many of his female peers, see him as a female, which upsets him though he doesn`t express it strongly. In the Anime, his feminine looks are often the subject of fanservice, going so far as to make him his own gender. Hideyoshi has a helpful personality and is willing to support any activity his friends embark on. He uses the term `Washi`, used by old venerable men to describe himself. While he is bad in academics, he has unquestionable talent in acting, and can not only replicate the behavior and mannerisms of other people but also their voices as well. In volume 2, he was instigated by Akihisa to mimic Yuuji`s voice to propose to Shouko during their tournament, confusing her and ultimately setting up the stage for a win for Akihisa-Yuuji Team, but this move caused Yuuji all manner of problems later on. His Shoukanjuu is clad in Hakama and wields a Naginata.</description>
<picture>41754.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14924" type="appears in" update="2011-07-24">
<rating votes="5">6.13</rating>
<name>Sugawa Ryou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sugawa Ryou is a minor supporting character in class F. He is the only class F student outside of the `inner circle` whose Shoukanjuu is described in the novel. His Shoukanjuu wears a martial-arts robe and wields a staff.</description>
<picture>42795.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12661" picture="42798.jpg">Gotou Keisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15546" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-16">
<rating votes="76">7.29</rating>
<name>Yoshii Akira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akihisa`s elder sister. 23 years old. Harvard graduate. Has E-Cup breasts and is horrible at cooking, evident in Episode 9 when Yoshii finds all the attempted Paella dishes in the fridge and when all the band-aids are shown on her hand. Seems to have a huge brother complex as she really tries to seduce Yoshii into a kiss, reducing his allowance by her own volition such as deducting 100 for every girl that Akihisa encounters and blushes extremely red when Yoshii admits he loves her as a brother.</description>
<picture>73599.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15818" type="appears in" update="2010-03-14">
<rating votes="11">2.68</rating>
<name>Nemoto Kyouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44628.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3787" picture="25815.jpg">Miyazaki Hiromu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15925" type="appears in" update="2011-08-07">
<rating votes="20">4.53</rating>
<name>Koyama Yuuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76609.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5663" picture="228631.jpg">Igarashi Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17526" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-04-21">
<rating votes="1020">8.54</rating>
<name>Gokou Ruri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kuroneko (a.k.a. Gokou Ruri) was one of the anime otaku girls Kirino had met in a gathering organized by Saori. Though their tastes in anime and games greatly differ, they nevertheless began to be good friends. She also became a good friend to Kyousuke, and it is hinted that she may have feelings for him. As befits the Kuroneko epithet, she is usually seen wearing a black Gothic Lolita-style dress, and is sharp-tongued and antisocial.
She enters Kyousuke`s high school later in the series, and joins the Game Club at his urging, displaying her considerable talents at writing and graphic design.</description>
<picture>55756.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="21862" type="appears in" update="2010-09-25">
<rating votes="5">6.31</rating>
<name>FFF Dan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>A group in class F who once punished Akihisa for getting attention from the girls, to the extent of `sentencing him to death`. They also seem to be Hideyoshi`s fans. When agitated, like when they learned of Class B`s representative having a girlfriend, they would turn into "Messengers of Genocide", using their Shoukanjuu as sacrifice, suicide-bombing their opponents effectively.</description>
<picture>55447.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="29128" type="appears in" update="2011-03-05">
<rating votes="6">1.69</rating>
<name>Natsukawa Shunpei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67188.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3155" picture="24137.jpg">Ono Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29129" type="appears in" update="2011-03-05">
<rating votes="4">2.71</rating>
<name>Tsunemura Yuusaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67187.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="389" picture="56097.jpg">Okano Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30767" type="appears in" update="2011-04-03">
<rating votes="4">5.97</rating>
<name>Iwashita Ritsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69022.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12352" picture="130106.jpg">Hirata Mana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30768" type="appears in" update="2011-04-03">
<rating votes="3">3.62</rating>
<name>Kikuiri Mayumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69023.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11003" picture="126729.jpg">Nakagami Ikumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30769" type="appears in" update="2011-04-03">
<name>A Class</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="30770" type="appears in" update="2011-04-03">
<name>F Class</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="30771" type="appears in" update="2011-04-03">
<name>B Class</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="30772" type="appears in" update="2011-04-03">
<name>C Class</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="30773" type="appears in" update="2011-04-03">
<name>D Class</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="30774" type="appears in" update="2011-04-03">
<name>E Class</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="126334" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2011-02-23</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">1日目「僕とメイドと新たなる旅立ち」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Day 1: Me, Maids, and a New Start</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Dia 1 - Eu, As Maids E O Início De Uma Nova Jornada!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ichinichi-me: Boku to Maid to Aratanaru Tabidachi</title>
<summary>When Class 2-F has to pick a project for the school’s annual festival, the gang decides to run a restaurant! If they can make some money, they might get to upgrade their gear. Unfortunately, deadly dumplings and a kidnapping could cut into their profits.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="126335" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2011-03-30</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">2日目「バカと花火と召喚大会」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Day 2: Idiots, Fireworks and the Summoner Tournament</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Dia 2 - Idiotas, Fogos E Torneios De Seres Invocados!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ninichi-me: Baka to Hanabi to Shoukan Taikai</title>
<summary>Thanks to their restaurant profits, things are looking up for Class 2-F. But if they hope to score some better gear - and keep Mizuki from transferring to another school - there’s one more challenge to be faced: a Summoner Tournament!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="128310" update="2011-02-24">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-02-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128311" update="2011-03-05">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-02-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128394" update="2018-07-30">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2011-02-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">選択肢以降のみ: もちろん秀吉だよね.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kinoshita Hideyoshi Ending (Episode 1)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sentakushi Ikou nomi: Mochiron Hideyoshi Da yo ne.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128395" update="2018-07-30">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2011-02-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">選択肢以降のみ: いやいや, 瑞希でしょ.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Himeji Mizuki Ending (Episode 1)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sentakushi Ikou nomi: Iyaiya, Miki Desho.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128396" update="2018-07-30">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2011-02-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">選択肢以降のみ: 美波に決まってるだろ. 常考.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shimada Minami Ending (Episode 1)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sentakushi Ikou nomi: Minami ni Kimatteru Daro. Tsunekou.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128397" update="2018-07-30">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2011-02-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">選択肢以降のみ: やっぱりアキちゃん.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yoshii Akihisa Ending (Episode 1)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sentakushi Ikou nomi: Yappari Aki-chan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128527" update="2011-06-09">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-08-29</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">プロモーション映像1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Promotional Video 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Promotion Eizou 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128528" update="2011-06-09">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">プロモーション映像2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Promotional Video 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Promotion Eizou 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129146" update="2018-07-30">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-03-30</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">選択肢以降のみ: あなたは3次元派?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Live Action Ending (Episode 2)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sentakushi Ikou nomi: Anata wa 3 Jigen Ha?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129147" update="2018-07-30">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-03-30</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">選択肢以降のみ: あなたは2次元派?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Animated Ending (Episode 2)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sentakushi Ikou nomi: Anata wa 2 Jigen Ha?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138181" update="2012-03-26">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">プロモーション映像3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Promotional Video 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Promotion Eizou 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="181636" update="2016-10-30">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-02-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
