<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8087" restricted="false">
<type>TV Special</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-02-20</startdate>
<enddate>2011-02-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Mai no Mahou to Katei no Hi</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">まいかて</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">maikate</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">マイの魔法と家庭の日</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.pref.toyama.jp/sections/1201/anime/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="3037" type="Character Design">Yoshihara Masayuki</name>
<name id="17953" type="Character Design">Makino Hiromi</name>
<name id="3037" type="Direction">Yoshihara Masayuki</name>
<name id="1385" type="Animation Work">P.A. Works</name>
<name id="2238" type="Music">Eufonius</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch27947 [Mai] is an 8-year old grade-schooler. She uses "magic" (empathy) to understand the feelings of her family members. However, her http://anidb.net/ch27948 [elder brother] is going through a difficult period due to the onset of puberty and is cutting himself off. In order to deepen the bonds within the family, http://anidb.net/ch27949 [Mai`s father] has decreed that every Saturday will be a "Family Day".
~ translated and adapted from official site by Cranston</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="115">4.18</permanent>
<temporary count="115">5.60</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>64877.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12164</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9940</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4858</identifier>
<identifier>qdywak</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.pref.toyama.jp/sections/1201/anime/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>マイの魔法と家庭の日</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>339003</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13381</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="775" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-29">
<name>pregnant</name>
<description>A pregnant character carries developing offspring within the body.
A character only shown pregnant for a small segment of their total appearance(s) should not be tagged. For example, a character shown pregnant in the epilogue of the last episode in a series generally would not qualify for the tag.
For porn entries, a pregnant character can be tagged when any of the following conditions are met:

* The character is pregnant for a material portion of their total appearance(s); for example, a mother that is known to be pregnant in the series/arc/episode

Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t2935 [stomach bulge] or http://anidb.net/t2727 [stomach stretch]. Engaging in at least 1 pregnant sex scene is not sufficient for this tag; tag http://anidb.net/t6999 [pregnant sex] at the anime level instead. For porn entries, pregnancy typically follows after an http://anidb.net/t3976 [impregnation] scene.
If the human character is http://anidb.net/t7148 [impregnated with larvae], use the http://anidb.net/t7151 [pregnant with larvae] tag instead.</description>
<picurl>161878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2378" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-02">
<name>hard-working</name>
<description>Describes someone, who is constantly, regularly, or habitually active or occupied.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2616" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>mina</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word mina refers to a broad audience, which can be said to be "the entire family", from the grumpy grandpa to the newborn baby. In Japanese, the word means simply "everyone", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic. Mina works are deliberately targeted at a range of people as wide as possible, and are commonly associated with high-budget releases that require a very large audience to be financially viable. They usually bring mildly philosophical themes so that the adults can be interested, but do so without bringing objectionable content so that the children can be allowed to watch, and indeed also feature content specifically geared to spark their interest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3697" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-05">
<name>particularly suitable for children</name>
<description>No sex or drugs, but probably rock and roll. Very watchable for children.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4577" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-19">
<name>family values</name>
<description>Family values are traditional or cultural values, generally conservative in nature, that pertain to the family`s structure, function, roles, beliefs, attitudes, and ideals. They encompass a set of beliefs, the most common of which is the classical "traditional family" involving a middle-class family with a breadwinner father and a homemaker mother, raising their biological children.
According to Merriam-Webster, family values are "values especially of a traditional or conservative kind which are held to promote the sound functioning of the family and to strengthen the fabric of society."
Source: English Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5768" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>intact family</name>
<description>The main character`s family is a so-called "nuclear family". Wherein both parents are alive and present in his or her life. This is actually relatively rare for anime, where "parental abandonment" is the norm.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="27947" type="main character in" update="2011-01-29">
<name>Tatsumi Mai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64649.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10757" picture="81678.jpg">Miyamoto Kanako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27948" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-29">
<name>Tatsumi Hikaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64650.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20249" picture="186289.jpg">Matsuoka Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27949" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-29">
<name>Tatsumi Mamoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64651.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="478" picture="17453.jpg">Nakamura Daiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27950" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-29">
<name>Tatsumi Yuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64652.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="508" picture="140061.jpg">Shimamoto Sumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27951" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-29">
<name>Tatsumi Hotaru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64653.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="407" picture="17254.jpg">Koyama Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27952" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-29">
<name>Tatsumi Raizou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64654.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="282" picture="223615.jpg">Houki Katsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27953" type="appears in" update="2011-01-29">
<name>Koshimaru</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64655.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="127872" update="2011-04-16">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2011-02-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Special</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
