<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8090" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-07-02</startdate>
<enddate>2011-07-02</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hagane no Renkinjutsushi: Milos no Seinaru Hoshi</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Fullmetal Alchemist the Movie: The Sacred Star of Milos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Fullmetal Alchemist Milos no Seinaru Hoshi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Hagaren the Movie (2011)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">FMAB Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">鋼の錬金術師 嘆きの丘[ミロス]の聖なる星</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Fullmetal Alchemist: The Sacred Star of Milos</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Full Metal Alchemist - The Sacred Star of Milos</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Fullmetal Alchemist le film: L`étoile sacrée de Milos</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Fullmetal Alchemist, la estrella sagrada de Milos</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Fullmetal Alchemist - Święta Gwiazda Milos</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Fullmetal Alchemist: Milos szent csillaga</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">钢之炼金术师 叹息之丘的圣星</title>
<title xml:lang="mn" type="official">Цул Металлан Алхимич: Милосын ариун од</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6107" type="Parent Story">Hagane no Renkinjutsushi (2009)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="331" approval="3" total="17">Tenkuu no Shiro Laputa</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="8">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="554678">For fans only. Not a phenomenal movie.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="112916">While i was expecting something more along the line of direct sequel, like "The Conqueror of Shambala", "The Sacred Star of Milos" certainly did not dissapoint as a movie.
It has a refreshing environment caused by the never-before-seen country of Crete/Milos but the story maintains a very familiar feel, even if it`s not written by Hiromu Arakawa-sensei.
In the end, even if it doesn`t quench my thirst for a proper sequel to the manga/Brotherhood series, it is a wonderfully animated film and can stand as a very good movie on its own right.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="242736">Great watch. Just watched this today and I`m really happy I did :) Top notch animation, good story with some interesting twists and action+adventure for the taking. 

You may find some shallow areas as this could have been a much bigger story.. but hey, they had to fit it in the 2 hours limit ^^ *sigh, longing for some great action-adventure fantasy series*
Now you go watch this! ;)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="229364">If you liked Brotherhood then you will love this. its not a piece of crap like Conqueror of Shamballa was. The story is very much along the lines of that which was found in Brotherhood so it is a must watch for fans.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="436636">WOW! I didn`t except it to be so great! Wonderful artwork,music,fights etc.Trully must watch.It was so epic it made me weep.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="465354">I saw this movie in theaters during its limited US screening. This is a very entertaining action/drama anime with AMAZING animation quality and production value, probably the most some of the most well done fights I`ve ever seen.

Despite this being simply a "filler episode" for the FMA:B series, I felt that the story was very well done with a surprising amount of plot twists, there was one moment when my mouth was hanging open from surprise.

Do yourself a favor and see it. Must see.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.hagaren-movie.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1007" type="Original Work">Arakawa Hiromu</name>
<name id="5748" type="Chief Animation Direction">Konishi Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="755" type="Animation Work">Bones</name>
<name id="1496" type="Direction">Murata Kazuya</name>
<name id="15765" type="Chief Animation Direction">Oshiyama Kiyotaka</name>
<name id="5748" type="Character Design">Konishi Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="8344" type="Music">Iwashiro Tarou</name>
</creators>
<description>After http://anidb.net/ch29808 [a mysterious prisoner] with only a few weeks left on his sentence breaks out of prison in Central City, the Elric brothers attempt to track him down. The search leads them to Table City in the southwestern country of Creta, where http://anidb.net/ch5908 [Alphonse] rescues a young alchemist named http://anidb.net/ch29807 [Julia] from the very man they are trying to capture. In the thick of the fight, they literally tumble into Julia`s home turf, the slums of Milos Valley, and are embroiled in the grassroots rebellion of her people.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2149">6.07</permanent>
<temporary count="2160">7.15</temporary>
<review count="1">6.83</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221057.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12180</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10842</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>9135</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.hagaren-movie.net/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.bones.co.jp/fullmetal-alchemist-milos</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Fullmetal_Alchemist_the_Movie:_The_Sacred_Star_of_Milos</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>鋼の錬金術師_嘆きの丘の聖なる星</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2664</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>338428</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13544</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2633" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>prison</name>
<description>A building used to house convicted criminals and accused persons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2866" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>slavery</name>
<description>Someone is owned by somebody else. In anime this usually affects body (slaves in a fantasy setting) or mind (the evil villain brainwashes a sidekick, creates an obedient minion or places a spell on some poor bloke). Slavery is also a common element of hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2870" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-17">
<name>steampunk</name>
<description>Steampunk is a sub-genre of science fiction that typically features steam-powered machinery, especially in a setting inspired by industrialized Western civilization during the 19th century. Steampunk works are often set in an alternative history of the 19th century`s British Victorian era or American "Wild West", in a post-apocalyptic future during which steam power has regained mainstream use, or in a fantasy world that similarly employs steam power.
Noteworthy attributes of the theme include large amounts smoke pollution from wood or coal burning, the affinity to metal constructs like cogs and metal tubing, and the mechanization of everyday objects.
Steampunk perhaps most recognisably features anachronistic technologies or retro-futuristic inventions as people in the 19th century might have envisioned them, and is likewise rooted in the era`s perspective on fashion, culture, architectural style, and art.
Such technology may include fictional machines like those found in the works of H. G. Wells and Jules Verne, or the modern authors Philip Pullman, Scott Westerfeld, Stephen Hunt and China Miéville. Other examples of steampunk contain alternative history-style presentations of such technology as lighter-than-air airships, analog computers, or such digital mechanical computers as Charles Babbage`s Analytical Engine.
Steampunk can also exemplify everything that is bad about unrestrained technological progress (dead matter), when compared to life and nature. The anime usually makes a point to propound the latter.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162830.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2871" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>anti-war</name>
<description>The anime portrays the insanity of war.</description>
<picurl>70855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2877" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>revenge</name>
<description>A primary factor that drives the plot forward, is the almost obsessive desire of one of the characters to get back at someone else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3192" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2013-02-26">
<name>hidden base</name>
<description>Someone wants to be secretive when he plans to take over the world...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3276" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>plot twists</name>
<description>The plot and story of this anime may seem to be going along a quite predictable path, when suddenly there is a jarring unexpected twist in the plot, taking the viewer by surprise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3278" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false">
<name>deception</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3805" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-13">
<name>European stylised</name>
<description>The anime`s setting is crafted in some classic European style. Imagine an architectural and cultural mix of London, Paris, Rome, Berlin, Prague, and other cities as they were at any point in the 19th century or earlier.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3898" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-11">
<name>science and magic coexist</name>
<description>In this anime science and magic do not exclude each other. Magic here is actually very advanced, artefact- and/or ritual-based science.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4085" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-17">
<name>unlikely duo</name>
<description>Comedy element: There is usually not only a difference in gender but also in appearance, character, and background concerning the main characters of this anime. Making it very unlikely for them to appear in the same context. Non-the-less they share the same adventure, as in "opposites attract".
These differences are exploited to come up with all sorts of wacky situations.
Examples: A demon-killer or Hero and the daughter of the Demon King. A girl from a normal family and a very intelligent and attractive boy from a very rich background (Shoujo). A very energetic outgoing girl and her very calm almost introverted best friend.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4196" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-01-23">
<name>fate worse than death</name>
<description>If you think death is the worst that can ever happen to someone, you had better think again: at least one character in this show is sure to end up in such a terrible way that many people would likely have preferred death if they had the choice. The fate of such characters is normally not for the faint of heart, and the audience is expected to at least sympathise with the poor character`s fate, and at times even be horrified at the shocking turn of events that led to their demise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4203" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>rebellion</name>
<description>Rebellion, uprising, or insurrection is a refusal of obedience or order. It may, therefore, be seen as encompassing a range of behaviors aimed at destroying or taking over the position of an established authority such as a government, governor, president, political leader, financial institution, or person in charge. On the one hand the forms of behaviour can include non-violent methods such as the (overlapping but not quite identical) phenomena of civil disobedience, civil resistance and nonviolent resistance. On the other hand it may encompass violent campaigns. Those who participate in rebellions, especially if they are armed rebellions, are known as "rebels".&#13;
&#13;
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>163803.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4217" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-02-11">
<name>nightmares</name>
<description>One or more characters in the anime are plagued by bad dreams.
Possible causes: A traumatic experience in the past or induced by an external "presence".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4565" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-08-17">
<name>war-zone realities</name>
<description>War is hell. This tag is for when characters experience the hell of war... not just the exciting stuff blowing up part.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4762" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>philosopher`s stone</name>
<description>The philosopher`s stone, reputed to be hard as stone and malleable as wax, is a legendary alchemical tool, supposedly capable of turning base metals into gold; it was also sometimes believed to be an elixir of life, useful for rejuvenation and possibly for achieving immortality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5095" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-23">
<name>slums</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5459" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>poverty</name>
<description>It refers to the condition of not having the means to afford basic human needs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5818" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2013-01-21">
<name>out-of-place artefact</name>
<description>Out-of-place artefact (OOPArt) is a term coined by American naturalist and crypto-zoologist Ivan T. Sanderson for an object of historical, archaeological, or palaeontological interest found in a very unusual or seemingly impossible context that could challenge conventional historical chronology.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5821" parentid="5826" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>sibling rivalry</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5843" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>sibling yin yang</name>
<description>In real life, siblings hardly ever act the same. Fiction sometimes takes this to an extreme.
Enter Sibling Yin Yang, the occurrence of siblings that are nearly polar opposites. If he`s cool and reckless, she`s responsible and thoughtful. If she`s a spiky-haired hooligan, he`s the nerdy wimpy one. If he`s an immature brat, she`s... well, you get the picture.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5981" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-10-12">
<name>seeking protagonist</name>
<description>The main character has a main objective that is referenced to through the whole series; he is in search of something, or someone
Should it be treasure, friends, money, power or all of the above nothing will stop our lead character in his quest to find his passion</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="5885" type="main character in" update="2009-05-02">
<rating votes="872">8.35</rating>
<name>Edward Elric</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Edward, the "Fullmetal Alchemist", is the youngest State Alchemist in history of the country and the main character of the series. He and his younger brother, Alphonse Elric, scour the world in search of the Philosopher`s Stone in the hopes of restoring their bodies.</description>
<picture>24292.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5908" type="main character in" update="2009-05-02">
<rating votes="521">6.18</rating>
<name>Alphonse Elric</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is a human child who lost his body during an alchemic experiment to bring his deceased mother back to life, and had his soul "attached" to a suit of armor by his brother, Edward Elric.
Al`s blood seal lies just below the base of the neck at the back of the suit, on the inside. It is drawn with Ed`s blood. According to Edward, he needs to be careful whenever he reconstructs Alphonse`s body because he must keep the blood seal intact during the transmutation. If the blood seal is removed, Al`s soul will be lost.</description>
<picture>24291.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6586" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-05">
<rating votes="646">8.49</rating>
<name>Roy Mustang</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Roy Mustang, the Flame Alchemist, is a State Alchemist and officer in the Amestrian State Military. A hero of the Ishval Civil War and http://anidb.net/ch5885 [Edward Elric]`s superior officer, Colonel Mustang is a remarkably capable commander who plans one day soon to become the next Führer of Amestris.</description>
<picture>24234.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6587" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-06">
<rating votes="432">8.12</rating>
<name>Riza Hawkeye</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lieutenant Riza Hawkeye is an officer in the Amestrian State Military as well as the personal adjutant and bodyguard of http://anidb.net/ch6586 [Colonel Roy Mustang]. A sharpshooter and weapons specialist, Lt. Hawkeye is an invaluable asset to the Colonel both in office and on the battlefield and serves as his closest and most supportive subordinate.</description>
<picture>24235.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6588" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-16">
<rating votes="480">7.31</rating>
<name>Winry Rockbell</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Winry Rockbell is a close childhood friend of http://anidb.net/ch5885 [Edward] and http://anidb.net/ch5908 [Alphonse] Elric since their young life in Resembool, she is almost like a sister to the two and essentially their only family. An amateur surgeon and mechanical repair specialist/enthusiast, Winry acts as Edward`s rear line support as his personal automail engineer and mechanic, making sure his prosthetic right arm and left leg are always in good working order. Additionally, she provides a great deal of emotional support for the pair and somewhat plays the role of the love interest in the story.</description>
<picture>24236.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1445" picture="33610.jpg">Takamoto Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6589" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="371">7.07</rating>
<name>Alex Louis Armstrong</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Alex Louis Armstrong, the "Strong Arm Alchemist," is a large and comically emotional State Alchemist who will burst into tears or joyous praise, given the right situation, and embraces others in an effort to console them. Because he is an extremely strong character, this usually causes great personal injury to others. Armstrong is very proud of his strength and of his muscular physique, frequently taking off his shirt so that he can flex for the benefit of others. As a final element of his comedic properties, he has the tendency to "sparkle"; when first appearing in a scene or taking off his shirt, pink stars radiate from his body. Despite his humorous tendencies, Armstrong can be very serious when the situation calls for it. He is not fond of violence and will try to end conflicts peacefully, and will break down and cry if an innocent person is killed.
Armstrong comes from a wealthy family of aristocrats who have earned renown in most professions. He has mastered many of his family`s talents for himself, and when displaying such a talent, he remarks it to have been "passed down the Armstrong line for generations." His alchemical skills also represent a remnant of his family`s history; by using a unique kind of brass knuckles, Armstrong can reshape any solid object that he punches. Armstrong is a valuable ally of http://anidb.net/ch6586 [Roy Mustang] and the Elric brothers, even if they are not always happy to be in his emotional company. He takes his honor as a soldier and as a leader seriously, and always looks out for his peers` and subordinates` best interests.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>24237.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23" picture="188505.jpg">Utsumi Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10884" type="appears in" update="2010-04-06">
<rating votes="48">5.18</rating>
<name>Vato Falman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Warrent Officer Vato Falman is one of http://anidb.net/ch6586 [Roy Mustang]`s most trusted subordinates. He was recruited by Mustang for his innate ability to remember almost every detail, allowing him to act as a sort of recording device that does not leave any physical evidence. Because his intellect is his area of expertise, he does not have much experience in the field, causing him to make rookie mistakes when in a combat situation. He is overly formal, causing some of his comrades to wish he would lighten up.</description>
<picture>45813.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="14598" type="appears in" update="2018-01-07">
<rating votes="52">5.50</rating>
<name>Heymans Breda</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Second Lieutenant Heymans Breda is one of http://anidb.net/ch6586 [Roy Mustang]`s most trusted subordinates. He was recruited by Mustang for his high level of intelligence, indicated by his talent with chess and other strategy games. Despite his intelligence, he still has an irrational fear of dogs. Breda is usually tasked by Mustang with jobs that require he travel abroad. He is transferred to Western Headquarters when Mustang`s group is broken up by the homunculi.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>211701.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4424" picture="170949.jpg">Satou Biichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29807" type="main character in" update="2011-05-20">
<rating votes="5">6.06</rating>
<name>Julia Crichton</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Julia Crichton is a 16 years old girl who was born in Milos. Her parents, who were both Alchemists, were murdered. She is a member of an organisation called Black Bat and is working to restore the country.</description>
<picture>71924.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="227" picture="205854.jpg">Sakamoto Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29808" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-20">
<rating votes="3">2.16</rating>
<name>Melvin Voyager</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Melvin Voyager is a 26 years old man who was about to be paroled after serving a sentence at the Central prison for robbery. But after he read something on the newspaper he immediately made an escape from the prison.</description>
<picture>71925.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32523" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-20">
<rating votes="5">6.39</rating>
<name>Miranda</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71921.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="471" picture="242052.jpg">Tamagawa Sakiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32524" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-20">
<rating votes="2">3.46</rating>
<name>Tony</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71922.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="60" picture="171602.jpg">Kawada Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32525" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-20">
<rating votes="3">1.95</rating>
<name>Alan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71920.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="177" picture="170981.jpg">Hoshino Takanori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32526" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-20">
<rating votes="3">1.85</rating>
<name>Ookami Chimera</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71923.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5978" picture="170983.jpg">Hayashi Yuuki</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="4039" picture="91415.jpg">Mogami Tsuguo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32527" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-20">
<name>Santos</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="30457" picture="81402.jpg">Kosugi Ryuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32528" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-25">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Carlos</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="30458" picture="81403.jpg">Yoshida Taka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45128" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-05-23">
<rating votes="2">1.29</rating>
<name>Peter Soyuz</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88351.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="469" picture="17418.jpg">Umezu Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45129" type="appears in" update="2012-05-24">
<rating votes="2">5.32</rating>
<name>Pedro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88352.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2364" picture="151724.jpg">Furushima Kiyotaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45130" type="appears in" update="2012-05-24">
<rating votes="2">8.54</rating>
<name>Gonzales</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88353.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3317" picture="24700.jpg">Kishino Yukimasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45131" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-05-24">
<rating votes="3">2.16</rating>
<name>Herschel Chuusa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88354.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="280" picture="170840.jpg">Kiuchi Hidenobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45132" type="appears in" update="2012-05-24">
<rating votes="2">5.66</rating>
<name>Vatanen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88355.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2026" picture="21352.jpg">Yara Yuusaku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45133" type="appears in" update="2012-05-24">
<rating votes="2">4.34</rating>
<name>Karina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88356.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45134" type="appears in" update="2012-05-24">
<rating votes="3">3.66</rating>
<name>Ashley Crichton</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88357.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="280" picture="170840.jpg">Kiuchi Hidenobu</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="2225" picture="192115.jpg">Kimura Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="126613" update="2012-03-12">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer (30s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130959" update="2018-07-29">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>110</length>
<airdate>2011-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135873" update="2012-03-12">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137709" update="2017-03-24">
<epno type="4">T13</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Trailer 5 (1m20)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137710" update="2012-03-10">
<epno type="4">T12</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Trailer 4 (4m30)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137711" update="2012-03-10">
<epno type="4">T11</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Trailer 3 (4m50)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137712" update="2012-03-10">
<epno type="4">T10</epno>
<length>6</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Trailer 2 (5m40)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137713" update="2012-03-10">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Promo (18s) 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137714" update="2012-03-10">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Promo (18s) 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137715" update="2012-03-10">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Promo (18s) 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137716" update="2012-03-10">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer (30s) 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137717" update="2012-03-10">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer (1m30s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137718" update="2012-03-10">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer (30s) 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137719" update="2012-03-10">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer (1m)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="203600" update="2018-07-29">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>2011-07-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="203601" update="2018-07-29">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>55</length>
<airdate>2011-07-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
