<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8113" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-04-09</startdate>
<enddate>2011-06-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sekaiichi Hatsukoi TV</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">World`s Greatest First Love TV</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Лучшая в мире первая любовь</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Sekai-ichi Hatsukoi TV</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">世界一初恋 TV</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Sekai Ichi Hatsukoi: The World`s Greatest First Love</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8567" type="Sequel">Sekaiichi Hatsukoi 2</anime>
<anime id="5532" type="Same Setting">Junjou Romantica</anime>
<anime id="7921" type="Side Story">Sekaiichi Hatsukoi</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="5532" approval="55" total="56">Junjou Romantica</anime>
<anime id="6073" approval="44" total="44">Junjou Romantica 2</anime>
<anime id="10049" approval="3" total="3">Hybrid Child</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="188990">On shounen-ai side, it`s awesome, found it even more enjoyable than Junjou Romantica. Way of telling the story is exactly same as Junjou - so it`s more like watch it all in one go anime. Cause the cliffhangers are frustrating.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="558328">I absolutely fell in love with these series. It has everything - beautiful animation, nice plot and characters, funny moments which are actually FUNNY (not like those wanna-be-funny quotes which happen to be in many animes trying to save the boring plot and are in fact not funny at all) and.. it`s soo romantic! I got pretty disappointed it ended when I finished the last episode.. Definitely must see for any shounen-ai fans! ♥</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://sekai-ichi.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="10226" type="Original Work">Nakamura Shungiku</name>
<name id="19268" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yasuda Takahiro</name>
<name id="1752" type="Character Design">Kikuchi Youko</name>
<name id="4302" type="Series Composition">Nakase Rika</name>
<name id="1482" type="Direction">Kon Chiaki</name>
<name id="9943" type="Music">Anze Hijiri</name>
<name id="730" type="Animation Work">Studio Deen</name>
<name id="1752" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kikuchi Youko</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch29552 [Ritsu Onodera] quit working for his father`s company and transferred to work at the publishing company, Marukawa Shoten. To his dismay, he`s assigned to edit shojo manga in which he has no interest or experience. He works with a strict boss, http://anidb.net/ch29558 [Takano Masamune], that he has trouble getting along with from the beginning. But, Onodera later discovers that he knows Takano from his past...
Source: crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="655">6.35</permanent>
<temporary count="663">7.27</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>67874.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12218</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9926</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4846</identifier>
<identifier>ipzvcm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.deen.co.jp/works/sekaiichi/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://sekai-ichi.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>世界一初恋</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2136</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>338564</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13386</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B06VYJK4Y8</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2614" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>josei</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word josei refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 15 and 44. In Japanese, the word means simply "woman", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2779" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>multiple couples</name>
<description>More than one couple is developed in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2788" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-21">
<name>confession</name>
<description>Someone confesses his/her love to someone else.</description>
<picurl>160903.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3103" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-11">
<name>first love</name>
<description>Ah… first love. The love that is remembered the most fondly by the participant, as this is commonly what people experience when they first have a first crush, but it is also the love before the Second Love, if that should ever happen, and for a guy, he usually holds her memory very close to him if he is a widower whereas for young girls, the memory of the First Love they ever had is a special memory to them, especially if he later becomes the boyfriend they`ve longed for.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>204995.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3170" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-10">
<name>occupation and career</name>
<description>The kind of anime which shows the career of a character, usually from the beginning.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4198" parentid="5604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-14">
<name>hard work and guts</name>
<description>One of the character`s motto in the anime. Because there is nothing that cannot be achieved by hard work and guts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4537" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-15">
<name>time skip</name>
<description>The plot features at least one skip or jump in time.
Example: A skip from the present into the past, or time skips in increments, e.g. every hour there is a time skip by a day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5865" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>manly tears</name>
<description>Somewhere down the line, it became the "norm" that boys don`t cry. The scenario does not matter; shedding tears is the ultimate no-no in terms of what you can and cannot do as a man (at least in the West, anyway). But there comes a time when a man`s emotions do get the better of him, and they pour forth - as prerequisite an impassioned speech may or may not be present - by cascading down his cheeks. These are what we like to call "manly tears". Extremely powerful. Not limited but often used in hot-blooded / super robot shows. Examples include Yuusha Ou GaoGaiGar, Getter Robo and Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann.
The opposite of manly tears are "girly tears".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5943" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-14">
<name>misunderstanding</name>
<description>Suggests that a large portion of storyline revolves around a rather large misunderstanding between two or more characters, usually forming long lasting situations of separation or hostility between all those involved.
A large portion of the story may be dedicated to gradually working all parties into a mutual understanding to true intentions or changes of heart.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="9519" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-06-17">
<rating votes="68">4.69</rating>
<name>Usami Akihiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29091.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="29550" type="appears in" update="2011-08-13">
<rating votes="6">4.01</rating>
<name>Isaka Ryuuichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Isaka Ryuuichirou is the senior managing director of Marukawa Publishing. He is acquainted with Sekaiichi Hatsukoi`s Ritsu`s parents and is a childhood friend of Junjou Romantica`s Haruhiko. He is 32 years old in the main time line. Isaka aspired to be a novelist, but his real talents lay in finding future best-sellers.
He appears in both Sekaiichi Hatsukoi and Junjou Romantica and is together with his assistant Asahina the main character of the short comics released with the Junjou Romantica DVDs, Junjou Mistake. Junjou Mistake takes place ten years before the main Romantica storyline.</description>
<picture>74519.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29551" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-05">
<rating votes="24">3.75</rating>
<name>Yoshino Chiaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60774.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1680" picture="132752.jpg">Tachibana Shinnosuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29552" type="main character in" update="2011-03-27">
<rating votes="39">6.57</rating>
<name>Onodera Ritsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68563.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="616" picture="18138.jpg">Kondou Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29553" type="main character in" update="2011-07-13">
<rating votes="24">6.52</rating>
<name>Kisa Shouta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74513.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29554" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-25">
<rating votes="17">5.93</rating>
<name>Yanase Yuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72214.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29555" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-26">
<rating votes="16">5.99</rating>
<name>Yokozawa Takafumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70539.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29556" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-26">
<rating votes="2">4.70</rating>
<name>Mino Kanade</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70537.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29557" type="main character in" update="2011-04-26">
<rating votes="27">5.72</rating>
<name>Hatori Yoshiyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70541.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29558" type="main character in" update="2014-11-16">
<rating votes="50">8.50</rating>
<name>Takano Masamune</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68564.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32707" type="appears in" update="2011-05-24">
<name>Mutou Yukina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72212.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1528" picture="223648.jpg">Kawaragi Shiho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32708" type="appears in" update="2011-05-25">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Ichinose Erika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72218.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32709" type="appears in" update="2011-05-25">
<name>Saeki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72216.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34075" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-12-13">
<rating votes="16">5.12</rating>
<name>Yukina Kou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He works in a bookstore and is taking charge of the Shoujo section there. He`s really good with his (female) customers and practically makes them buy new manga with his really good looks.
"I thought you could buy this so next time you come in we can bond over how good this manga is."</description>
<picture>74512.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="612" picture="79531.jpg">Maeno Tomoaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34078" type="appears in" update="2014-11-01">
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<name>Otoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A stalkerish guy that had a one-night-stand with Kisa. He seems to be unable to let go of the unwanted attention towards Kisa.</description>
<picture>74516.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34079" type="appears in" update="2011-07-01">
<name>Sumi Ryouichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74517.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="26" picture="170737.jpg">Chijiwa Ryuusaku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34080" type="appears in" update="2011-07-01">
<name>Hasegawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74518.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="198" picture="202893.jpg">Kusao Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75807" type="appears in" update="2016-01-31">
<rating votes="2">1.63</rating>
<name>Ijuuin Kyou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A mangaka working for Marukawa.
He went through a very hard time, until one day meeting Misaki.</description>
<picture>175851.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="366" picture="17212.jpg">Gouda Hozumi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="128717" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">First impressions are the most lasting.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Impressions Are the Most Lasting</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">First Impressions Are the Most Lasting.</title>
<summary>Ritsu Onodera hated the fact that people claimed he only got into his father`s company because he was the son and promptly quits. He starts his new job at Marukawa Publishing house but ends up in a department for shojo manga, something he`s neither interested nor experienced in. To make matters worse, the first impression he gets from the high handed editor in chief Masamune Takano is terrible...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="129280" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">A man has free choice to begin love but not to end it.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Man Has Free Choice to Begin Love But Not to End It.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">A Man Has Free Choice to Begin Love But Not to End It.</title>
<summary>The Emerald Editing team has started the task of releasing a magazine. Ritsu Onodera, a rookie shojo manga editor, is forced to go to the office of an author with the editor in chief, Masamune Takano. However, when Ritsu sees the author panic because of the looming deadline, he accidentally...?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="129384" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Love is lawless.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love Is Lawless.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Love Is Lawless.</title>
<summary>Chiaki Yoshino is a popular shoujo manga author under the pen name "Chiharu Yoshikawa". His friends include his childhood friend and editor Yoshiyuki Hatori, and the chief assistant Yuu Yanase they know since middle school. But one day, Yoshino happens to witness Hatori and Yanase kiss...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="129385" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Adversity makes a man wise.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Adversity Makes a Man Wise.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Adversity Makes a Man Wise.</title>
<summary>Late at night, Ritsu has a run in with Yokozawa at Takano`s apartment.
He tries to stay calm, but the confusion and agitation have him too rattled.
Then one day, it becomes apparent that the manuscript of one of the author`s Ritsu
is responsible for won`t make it for the printing deadline.
Yokozawa suggests to "drop it this time".
However, when Ritsu insists that he wants to get it in, Takano says...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="129386" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">In love there is both dotage and discretion.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In Love There Is Both Dotage and Discretion.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">In Love There Is Both Dotage and Discretion.</title>
<summary>Ritsu can`t calm down after finding out Takano`s true identity. On top of that, when he`s about to immerse himself in the work for the author he`s in charge for, he encounters Takafumi Yokozawa, the wild horse of the sales department. He makes a terrible first impression on Ritsu by accusing him of "riding [his] father`s coat tails". To top it off, he seems to be quite friendly with Takano in and outside work...?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="129716" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">After a storm comes a calm.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">After a Storm Comes a Calm.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">After a Storm Comes a Calm.</title>
<summary>Meeting Ryouichi Sumi and the advice from Hasegawa have put doubt into Ritsu Onodera`s heart. He remembers the reason he transferred to Marukawa and wonders if he can continue to work as a manga editor. 
While he is struggling, Takano asks him if he wants transfer to the literature department and...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="129717" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">It never rains but it pours.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Never Rains but it Pours.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">It Never Rains but it Pours.</title>
<summary>One day Ritsu Onodera runs into the author Ryouichi Sumi who he had
worked with at his old company. Ritsu also gets introduced to Ryouichi Sumi`s
new editor and gets in contact with the literary world again after a 
long hiatus, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="129718" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Absence makes the heart grow fonder.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Absence Makes the Heart Grow Fonder.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Absence Makes the Heart Grow Fonder.</title>
<summary>Right after Yoshino announces that he is going to a hot spring resort with his chief assistant and friend Yanase, Hatori says "Do you even remember what`s on that day?".
While he is still confused, Hatori throws him out of his apartment. Yoshino does not understand Hatori`s problem and indignantly goes to the hot springs with Yanase, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="129719" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">The die is cast.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Die Is Cast.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Die Is Cast.</title>
<summary>Kisa can`t concentrate on his work due to not being able to keep Yukina out of his mind. He tries to convince himself that he`s only visiting the store to check out the comic display that Yukina made for him; however, the fact that Yukina isn`t acting any different confuses him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="129720" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Looks breed love.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Looks Breed Love.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Looks Breed Love.</title>
<summary>Kisa has a crush on one of the staff members at the book store he frequents.  He silently watches until Yokozawa forces an introduction.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="129721" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Coming events cast their shadows before them.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Coming Events Cast Their Shadows Before Them.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Coming Events Cast Their Shadows Before Them.</title>
<summary>Ritsu is having trouble writing up the proposal for his first manga project. 
Amidst his trouble, Takano`s friend from the sales department, Yokozawa, declares that "Masamune is mine". Ritsu can`t hide that he`s shaken, but then he runs into Takano at a bar he ended up with his friend...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="129722" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Go to the sea,if you would fish well.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Go to The Sea, if You Would Fish Well.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Go to The Sea, if You Would Fish Well.</title>
<summary>Yoshino`s childhood friend and editor Hatori confesses his love to him.
But Yoshino suspects that his friend and chief assistant Yanase is actually secretly in love with Hatori.
Yoshino`s so preoccupied with the relationship between those two that he can`t focus on his work...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="131079" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163638" update="2014-10-20">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-04-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163639" update="2014-10-20">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-04-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
