<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8132" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>9</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-04-15</startdate>
<enddate>2016-12-16</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Fairy Tail (2011)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">フェアリーテイル (2011)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Fairy Tail OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Приказна история (2011)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">FAIRY TAIL (2011)</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6662" type="Parent Story">Fairy Tail</anime>
<anime id="9980" type="Parent Story">Fairy Tail (2014)</anime>
<anime id="125" type="Other">Groove Adventure Rave</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="639219">I just LOVE it! Fairy Tail has SO much in it, and it takes a while for parts of it to fully blossom and come to fruition. Fairy Tail has not only magic and awesome combat, but it also speaks to the human condition and overflows with moments of heartfelt joy (for those who can still be so moved)!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="373440">the final ova is amazing. really glad I watched this :D</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://kc.kodansha.co.jp/fairytail/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="1043" type="Animation Work">Satelight</name>
<name id="17096" type="Character Design">Yamamoto Midori</name>
<name id="5571" type="Direction">Ishihira Shinji</name>
<name id="2754" type="Music">Takanashi Yasuharu</name>
<name id="1303" type="Animation Work">A-1 Pictures</name>
<name id="7578" type="Original Work">Mashima Hiro</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the manga by http://anidb.net/cr7578 [Mashima Hiro], serialised in http://anidb.net/ch17160 [Weekly Shounen Magazine].
Story 1: The Fairy Tail mage guild member http://anidb.net/ch11720 [Lucy] comes across a mysterious written request on an odd-job noticeboard. The client is looking for an object that is hidden somewhere in Fairy Tail`s female dormitory, Fairy Hills. To verify the request, Lucy visits Fairy Hills, and discovers that the client is http://anidb.net/ch31116 [Hilda], the dormitory head who is looking for a shining treasure. Meanwhile, http://anidb.net/ch11801 [Natsu] and the other guild members are cleaning their pool. (Source: ANN)
Story 2: Lucy just transferred to the Fairy Academy, but with http://anidb.net/ch12250 [Gray] and Natsu as wannabe delinquent classmates, http://anidb.net/ch12249 [Erza] as strict student council president, and http://anidb.net/ch11802 [Happy] the cat as homeroom teacher, no school day will be normal.
Story 3: An accident with a mysterious book, Memory Days, opens a portal into the past, where Erza, Gray, Lucy, Natsu and Happy meet their younger selves, hopefully being careful not to cause a time paradox six years in the past...
Story 4: http://anidb.net/ch40291 [Mavis] is bored staying alone on Tenrou Island, so she decides to pay the guild a visit, unaware that the Fairy Tail members are going to the beach for a training camp. She decides to tag along. The group faces a lot of trouble that is caused by Natsu and Gray. What would happen if the girls got drunk? (Source: Fairy Tail Wikia)
Story 5: After the third day of the Grand Magic Games, the gang heads off to the summer resort known throughout Fiore: Ryuzetsu Land. Poolside high jinks ensue.
Story 6: Natsu and http://anidb.net/ch31610 [Haru] (from http://anidb.net/a125 [Rave]) are lost, so Lucy and http://anidb.net/ch9818 [Elie] (also from Rave) embark on a search for them.
Story 7: Due to the bet they made during the Grand Magic Games, the time has finally come for Team Fairy Tail A and B to decide who will have the privilege to make the other team do whatever they desire, leading to a day`s worth of antics from the two parties.
Story 8: Natsu vs. Mavis
Story 9: Fairies` Christmas
Note: Released with the 26th, 27th, 31st, 35th, 38th, 39th, 55th, 58th and 59th manga volumes. Each OAD features a different side story taken from the manga.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1327">5.13</permanent>
<temporary count="1343">6.79</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>60535.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12322</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>15504</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18393</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>9982</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>32930</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://kc.kodansha.co.jp/fairytail/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.shonenmagazine.com/special/ftoad/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>List_of_Fairy_Tail_episodes</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>Fairy_Tail#Original_video_animations</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>FAIRY_TAIL#.E5.90.84.E8.A9.B1.E3.83.AA.E3.82.B9.E3.83.88.EF.BC.88OAD.EF.BC.89</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13412</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4052" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-23">
<name>treasure hunting</name>
<description>A significant part of the anime centres on the protagonists` search for some obscure artefact or other treasure, an epic adventure and wild goose chase for something unusual and quite valuable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4474" parentid="2655" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-04">
<name>self-parody</name>
<description>The anime is a parody of itself. 
I.e. the authors make fun of the genre they are portraying, and take the actions of their characters and story lightly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4537" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-15">
<name>time skip</name>
<description>The plot features at least one skip or jump in time.
Example: A skip from the present into the past, or time skips in increments, e.g. every hour there is a time skip by a day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="9818" type="appears in" update="2009-06-24">
<rating votes="8">7.55</rating>
<name>Elie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Elie is very lively and optimistic girl with a hot temper. She also has no memories of who she is, which is why she sets out to look for someone who could tell here what is her real name and where are her parents. While travaling Elie meets Haru Glory who promises her that they will find her memories together.</description>
<picture>29814.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11720" type="main character in" update="2014-02-20">
<rating votes="397">6.68</rating>
<name>Lucy Heartfilia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lucy Heartfilia is the main female protagonist and viewpoint character of Fairy Tail.
According to http://anidb.net/cr7578 [Mashima Hiro], her given name was inspired by The Beatles song "Lucy in the Sky with Diamonds".
She is a 17-year-old wizard who specializes in summoning celestial spirits from another realm using a set of keys called Gatekeys, and treats them like her friends. She also carries a whip as her personal weapon, which she wields on occasion to fight alongside her spirits.
As one of the saner members of the guild, Lucy regularly gawks at the odd habits of her guildmates, who frequently show up uninvited inside her house.
Source: wikipedia</description>
<picture>150493.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4" picture="177060.jpg">Hirano Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11801" type="main character in" update="2014-02-20">
<rating votes="406">7.59</rating>
<name>Natsu Dragneel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Natsu Dragneel, also known by the nickname "Salamander" (火竜), is the main male protagonist of Fairy Tail.
Aside from performing missions for his guild, Natsu travels with his partner http://anidb.net/ch11802 [Happy] in search of Igneel, a dragon who raised Natsu in his youth before disappearing seven years prior to the start of the series.
He is a Dragon Slayer (滅竜魔導士), a wizard who can perform an ancient form of magic, or "Lost Magic", that grants him the physical properties of a dragon. He specializes in a particular form of this magic called Fire Dragon Slayer magic (火の滅竜魔法), which gives him powers such as breathing fire, emitting flames from any part of his body to attack his opponent, being physically immune to fire, and ingesting any flame besides his own for nourishment.
Natsu is generally carefree and reckless in nature, and causes most of the collateral damage Fairy Tail is blamed for. However, he is extremely loyal to his guildmates and attacks anyone who tries to harm or insult them. Although he comes across as thick-headed to several other characters, he is a perceptive tactician in battle and can quickly deduce his opponents` strengths and weaknesses.
He suffers from motion sickness when riding on vehicles of any sort (trains, carriages, boats, etc.), as well as when carried by others. The only exception to this rule is Happy, who Natsu claims is his friend and not a "moving object".
Source: wikipedia</description>
<picture>150492.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="174" picture="41158.jpg">Kakihara Tetsuya</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="98" picture="172032.jpg">Mako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11802" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-20">
<rating votes="166">6.31</rating>
<name>Happy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Happy is a 6-year-old talking cat with blue fur who serves as Natsu`s best friend and initial partner before Lucy`s inclusion in the Fairy Tail guild.
http://anidb.net/cr7578 [Mashima Hiro] originally planned to name him "Freyr" after the Norse god, but found the name did not fit his character.
Happy possesses a magical ability called Aera (翼), which allows him to temporarily grow white feathered wings on his back and fly. He is only able to carry up to one person at a time in this form.
He is generally cheerful as per his name, and often utters the catchphrase "Aye!" (あい) or "Aye, sir!" (あいさ).
Source: wikipedia</description>
<picture>150498.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12248" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-12-02">
<rating votes="79">6.28</rating>
<name>Makarov Dreyar</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165350.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2021" picture="187129.jpg">Tsuji Shinpachi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12249" type="main character in" update="2014-02-20">
<rating votes="606">8.25</rating>
<name>Erza Scarlet</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Erza Scarlet, also known by the nickname "Fairy Queen, Titania" (妖精女王 ティターニア), is one of the primary female protagonists of Fairy Tail. She is a 19-year-old S-Class wizard, who is usually tasked with performing extremely dangerous missions, and considered by many to be the most powerful female member of the guild.
Her name was derived from Eru, a character from the one-shot manga created by http://anidb.net/cr7578 [Mashima Hiro] that served as a pilot for Fairy Tail.
Having specialized in the re-equip magic "the Knight" (騎士), Erza can summon and equip different weapons, armor, and clothing from a hammerspace at will. Erza usually hauls along a large number of suitcases while traveling.
Source: wikipedia</description>
<picture>150491.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12250" type="main character in" update="2014-02-20">
<rating votes="213">6.96</rating>
<name>Gray Fullbuster</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gray Fullbuster is one of the main male protagonists. He is an 18-year-old wizard who uses a form of magic called Ice Make (氷の造形魔法), which allows him to instantaneously create ice and mold it into various kinds of weapons, shields, and other inanimate objects.
He has a habit of stripping down to his underwear, often without realizing it, which he developed as a result of his training to withstand the freezing temperatures.
While normally calm and collected, Gray has a fierce rivalry with http://anidb.net/ch11801 [Natsu] due to their opposing magic types, which constantly leads the two to bicker and insult each other.
Source: wikipedia</description>
<picture>150490.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13713" type="appears in" update="2010-01-07">
<rating votes="29">5.53</rating>
<name>Plue</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Plue`s body is a pure white creature with a yellow horn-like nose. It`s always trembling, and it can only say "puun". Its favorite food is candy. When it`s hungry or enters a bath, its body and nose become shrivelled. Hiro Mashima, the author of the manga, has said that Plue feels close to a stuffed animal. It`s age and gender are a mystery.
In Groove Adventure Rave, Plue is a strange creature that Haru discovered, Plue is the Rave Bearer, and is able to sense the presence of the other Rave Stones. Plue`s nose also has the ability to destroy Dark Bring. It has the ability to utilise the Rave of Combat, which powers itself and Haru up.
In Fairy Tail, Plue is a Silver Key Celestial Spirit officially called "Nicola the Canis Minor", but named Plue by its summoner Lucy. Its only unique ability is magic cancellation, and so serves more as a pet for Lucy.</description>
<picture>3894.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="355" picture="71573.jpg">Gotou Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13894" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-12-02">
<rating votes="181">7.59</rating>
<name>Mirajane Strauss</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165351.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="594" picture="156858.jpg">Ono Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13895" type="appears in" update="2010-01-04">
<rating votes="41">7.83</rating>
<name>Loki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3897.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="63" picture="186695.jpg">Kishio Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13896" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-12-02">
<rating votes="114">6.46</rating>
<name>Elfman Strauss</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165353.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13897" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-12-02">
<rating votes="91">6.29</rating>
<name>Kana Alberona</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165352.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13898" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-12-02">
<rating votes="93">6.90</rating>
<name>Levy McGarden</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165354.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="101" picture="16709.jpg">Ise Mariya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13899" type="appears in" update="2010-01-04">
<rating votes="66">5.70</rating>
<name>Jellal Fernandes</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3901.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13900" type="appears in" update="2011-09-15">
<rating votes="40">7.08</rating>
<name>Aquarius</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aquarius "The Water Bearer" is a Celestial Spirit that is one of the 12 Golden Zodiac Keys.</description>
<picture>55742.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13901" type="appears in" update="2010-01-05">
<rating votes="9">3.98</rating>
<name>Horologium</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Celestial Spirit of Lucy Heartfilia</description>
<picture>41063.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13902" type="appears in" update="2010-01-05">
<rating votes="15">6.65</rating>
<name>Taurus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Celestial Spirit of Lucy Heartfilia</description>
<picture>41065.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2001" picture="228614.jpg">Sekiguchi Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13903" type="appears in" update="2010-01-05">
<rating votes="13">5.19</rating>
<name>Cancer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Celestial Spirit of Lucy Heartfilia</description>
<picture>41067.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16987" picture="86303.jpg">Shimoyama Yoshimitsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13926" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-05">
<rating votes="78">7.70</rating>
<name>Virgo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Became Celestial Spirit of Lucy Heartfilia in episode 7.</description>
<picture>41123.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13928" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-09-07">
<rating votes="26">5.14</rating>
<name>Bisca Moulin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60467.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13929" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-06">
<rating votes="14">4.85</rating>
<name>Alzack Connell</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41126.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16987" picture="86303.jpg">Shimoyama Yoshimitsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13930" type="appears in" update="2012-10-14">
<rating votes="45">7.67</rating>
<name>Mystogan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126882.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17607" type="appears in" update="2010-05-14">
<rating votes="6">4.24</rating>
<name>Sarusuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jet is a member of the Fairy Tail Guild`s team Shadow Gear, along with Levy and Droy. His magic, God`s Leg, is a type of magic which dramatically increases his speed.
His real name is Sarusuke, with his nickname `Jet`, presumably coming from his type of magic.</description>
<picture>47924.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11101" picture="40055.jpg">Namekawa Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17608" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-25">
<rating votes="130">6.51</rating>
<name>Lisanna Strauss</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lisanna was the younger sister of both Elfman and Mirajane, and was also a member of Fairy Tail, like her siblings her magic is take over. Her member stamp was on her upper left shoulder.
It is also very possible that Lisanna, Elfman and Mirajane operated in a three man group similar to Shadow Gear. She lost her life while trying to revert Elfman after his full-body Take Over went awry. He quickly lost control of himself and went on a rampage. Lisana gave her life trying to calm him down and stop his rampage (actually she didnt die, but was transported to Edolas). How she actually was able to do this is unknown. The mental and emotional trauma that Elfman and Mirajane both experienced after Lisana`s supposed death crippled their powers considerably. Mirajane lost her S-class rank and has not fought since. Elfman suffered major emotional damage and was incapable to cast his full body takeover spell for some time. When he did try casting it, a flashback to Lisana caused him to lose concentration. When Lisanna was younger, she seemed to be very kind like Elfman and unlike Mirajane. She wanted to help Natsu Dragneel raise an unknown egg to see what comes out of it, being a little more knowledgable in it then Natsu. After seeing a softer side of the usually flamboyant Natsu, she stated that he was a lot like her sister and joked that perhaps later she should become his bride which predictably freaked him out. It is shown that while the Edolas version of Lisanna is deceased, the Eathland version of Lisanna is still alive. Like her Earth land counterpart, she seems just as friendly and caring, as seen when she scolds Lucy for bullying Natsu and tells Jet and Droy not to pick on Elfman. When Natsu and Happy see her they both shed tears and tried to hug her in joy, this freaked her out. She doesn`t seem to have the massive crush her Earth Realm counterpart has on Natsu.</description>
<picture>78974.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1918" picture="225099.jpg">Sakurai Harumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17609" type="appears in" update="2019-04-29">
<rating votes="40">7.38</rating>
<name>Ultear Milkovich</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ultear is introduced as a member of the Magic Council who apparently works for Siegrain. When the members of Fairy Tail go to Galuna Island they encounter a cloaked wizard named Zalty. Zalty helps Reitei Lyon try to revive Deliora (a demon trapped in ice by Ur) and uses "Lost Magic" to manipulate time`s effects on inanimate objects. After Deliora is discovered to be long dead, Zalty is revealed to be Ultear, the daughter of Ur. Unsuccessful in the attempt to gain Deliora, Ultear later helps Siegrain manipulate the Magic Council in order to activate the Tower of Paradise.</description>
<picture>233198.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="17611" type="appears in" update="2010-06-12">
<rating votes="4">4.31</rating>
<name>Droy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Droy is a member of Fairy Tail Guild`s team Shadow Gear, along with Levy and Jet.
Droy controls Rapid-Growing Plants to battle. He wears something called "Live-Coal" containers holding seeds for his magic.</description>
<picture>49541.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32215" picture="223325.jpg">Sasamoto Natsue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17615" type="appears in" update="2010-05-14">
<rating votes="2">2.20</rating>
<name>Sol</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sol is part of the Element 4 group. He along with Jubia were sent to capture Lucy to bring her back to their master, Jose. He is nicknamed Sol of the earth, as shown by his name his magic consists of controlling and creating the different forms of earth (sand, rocks, etc.) he has also been shown to be able to wrap his body around a persons arm maybe even their whole body. Sol often uses French linguistics in his speech as well as talking in a rhythmic pattern, he also gives his attacks musical names mix with the French names of different kinds of earth (Roche[rock] Concerto, Plâtre[plaster] Sonata, etc). Sol is also French for "ground".</description>
<picture>47932.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2001" picture="228614.jpg">Sekiguchi Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17616" type="appears in" update="2010-05-14">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Aria</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aria is part of the Element 4 group as well as it strongest member. He is a very large man that towers over the other members. Despite his large appearance he seems to cry a lot. Aria`s magic is called Drain which drains it`s opponent of his or her magic power. Once it`s drained it floats in the air and eventually disappears. The greater the magic power of the opponent the more damage Drain causes. His power is so great that he has to keep his eyes closed to contan it and only opens them for the strongest of opponents. His nickname within the guild is Aria of the Sky. Aria is Italian for "air".</description>
<picture>47933.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21" picture="170939.jpg">Taira Katsui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17617" type="appears in" update="2010-05-14">
<rating votes="2">2.78</rating>
<name>Totomaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Totomaru is part of the Element 4 group. He`s a fire mage and can manipulate it to the point where he alters the state of fire even making it cold or extremely smelly. He carries a sword which he uses for close-combat. His nickname within the guild is The Great Fire.</description>
<picture>47934.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2474" picture="228619.jpg">Endou Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17622" type="appears in" update="2010-05-14">
<rating votes="8">4.27</rating>
<name>Sagittarius</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sagittarius, despite how people would view him, is a tall, black-haired lanky man wearing a horse costume. He has rustic, almost medieval clothing. His weapon is a bow and he has a giant quiver on his back.</description>
<picture>47939.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1999" picture="21304.jpg">Kawanabe Masaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17623" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="1">5.25</rating>
<name>Max Alors</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Max Alors is a lesser member of the Fairy Tail Guild but apparently he is in charge of all the social activities, given his love for talking to people. He specializes in sand based magic.</description>
<picture>47940.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12623" picture="151646.jpg">Iguchi Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17626" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="5">4.70</rating>
<name>Macao Conbolt</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Macao Conbolt is one of the older mages of the Fairy Tail Guild, being 36. He uses a special flame, the purple flare, which cannot be blown off by wind or water. He`s also very skilled in transformation magic, an ability which can even deceive an equal expert such as Mirajane. He`s divorced and is dating a younger girl. It`s said that he`s very popular among young girls and he even had Cana Alberona falling for him in the past. He has one son, Romeo whom he cares a lot about.</description>
<picture>47943.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1999" picture="21304.jpg">Kawanabe Masaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17627" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-20">
<rating votes="162">7.58</rating>
<name>Laxus Dreyar</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Laxus Dreyar was an S-Class mage of the Fairy Tail Guild, as well as the grandson of Fairy Tail master Makarov and the son of dark Raven Tail Guild master Ivan Dreyar.</description>
<picture>150489.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17628" type="appears in" update="2010-05-14">
<rating votes="2">4.12</rating>
<name>Vijeeter Ecor</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vijeeter Ecor is a member of the Fairy Tail guild.
Vijeeter serves mostly as a back-ground character, and is seen most of the time dancing. However he has been seen in all of the manga`s arcs along with the rest of the guild during there celebrations. He participated in the war against Phantom Lord and had a a fight against Nab Lasaro during the Fighting Festival arc. It is presumed that Nab defeated Vijeeter since he wasn`t among the members who Bixlow took down, but Nab was.</description>
<picture>47945.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="17629" type="appears in" update="2010-05-14">
<rating votes="7">3.12</rating>
<name>Reedus Jonah</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Reedus Jonah is one of the mages of the Fairy Tail Guild.
Reedus doesn`t seem to be very brave seen when he stated he was "afraid" of Laxus Dreyar when Makarov noticed him hiding in the building, however he will do important jobs if asked, like protecting Lucy in the Phantom Lord Arc and finding help in the Fighting Festival Arc. He loves to draw happy scenes like when Happy was first born. Reedus also likes to portray other people, like drawing Mirajane and Fried just for having good looks.</description>
<picture>47946.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="17630" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-14">
<rating votes="5">4.22</rating>
<name>Nab Lasaro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nab Lasaro is one of the many mages of Fairy Tail.
Not much is known about Nab Lasaro, except that he seems to hang around the Request Board often, even though he dosen`t get much jobs or missions to do. He shouts at Natsu when he breaks the Mission board, knowing Natsu Dragneel was going to do something bad. He also says he prefers solo missions when Lucy asked him to go on a mission with her.</description>
<picture>47947.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2474" picture="228619.jpg">Endou Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17631" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-20">
<rating votes="213">7.54</rating>
<name>Juvia Lockser</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Juvia made up 1/4th of the Phantom Lord`s elite group, Element 4. She was sent by the guild master Jose, along with Sol, to go and capture Lucy and bring her back to him safely. Her magic seems to deal with water as she is able to control rain and other large bodies of water. In addition, her body seems to be formed from the rain that surrounds her, leaving her intact and able to reform herself after attacks. Her nickname is also Juvia of the Sea, which correlates with her water controlling magic. When angry she can also control hot water. Juvia also often refers to herself in the 3rd person. Juvia has developed a crush on Gray, and due to a misunderstanding, views Lucy as her rival in love. After being defeated by Gray, the rain above her finally clears up which she thought was beautiful.
After the fight, her deep infatuation with Gray continues, secretly following him wherever he goes. In the current arc, she mentions to Gray that she is now an independent mage once more, but Gray notes that she has probably has her eyes set on Fairy Tail. She is quite willing to do anything for him.
She is one of the few Phantom members to be shown after the Phantom Guild arc. The Spanish word "lluvia", which is pronounced like her name, means rain.</description>
<picture>150495.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17632" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-11">
<rating votes="19">4.30</rating>
<name>Lyon Vastia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lyon Vastia, first introduced as Reitei Lyon, is one of three ice mages shown in the series, as well as a rival of Gray Fullbuster. He was the main antagonist of the Galuna Island arc and later appears as a member of the Lamia Scale Guild.</description>
<picture>126868.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17635" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-14">
<rating votes="5">5.32</rating>
<name>Wakaba Mine</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wakaba Mine is a 36-year-old veteran mage who uses smoke magic. He has been in the Fairy Tail Guild for a very long time and has made many memories with many of the older guild members like Reedus Jonah and his rival Macao Conbolt. He also has a wife, but he doesn`t like her at all.</description>
<picture>47952.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8357" picture="174120.jpg">Kageura Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17636" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-27">
<rating votes="25">7.19</rating>
<name>Lucky Ollietta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lucky Ollietta is an 18-year-old mage who uses wood-based magic, and can instantly reshape wood into a form of her choice. Due to this ability, she helped a lot with the rebuilding of the Fairy Tail Guild after it was vandalized by the Phantom Lord Guild. She likes glasses and wears them as well, and she has a dislike for perverts. Lucky also has funny ways of expressing herself, for example she refers to getting a haircut as "chopping hair", eating as "feeding your stomach", and sleeping as "whittling away the defenseless hours".</description>
<picture>84718.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9124" picture="186845.jpg">Hayama Ikumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17638" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-20">
<rating votes="117">7.47</rating>
<name>Gajeel Redfox</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gajeel is an intimidating-looking young man around the age of Natsu Dragneel. He has a wing-like sleeve on his right arm (right above his Phantom Lord tattoo) and various body piercings, usually in sets of three or five. His usual outfit consists of a ragged-looking black tunic with studded edges, studded wristbands, and studded boots (somewhat resembling Punk style). His hair style is a heavy metal, long, black hair.
He doesn`t seem to care at all about Fairy Tail, and seems to think that Phantom Lord is a stronger and more worthwhile guild. Gajeel bears his Phantom Lord symbol marked at the top off his right shoulder (note the same place were Natsu has his Fairy Tail emblem). Gajeel and Natsu seem to be opposites as Gajeel has more of dark personality and appearance unlike Natsu who is a larger affinity to light. However, he seems to have a short temper, seen when Natsu Dragneel constantly makes him angry.</description>
<picture>150494.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18743" type="appears in" update="2010-06-12">
<rating votes="2">2.99</rating>
<name>Spetto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49551.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1617" picture="19642.jpg">Tanaka Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18745" type="appears in" update="2010-06-12">
<rating votes="8">2.24</rating>
<name>Crux</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Crux is a Celestial Spirit owned by Lucy Heartfilia. It is unknown if Crux can be used for combat purposes. However, it is known that Crux has the ability to search for information about Celestial Spirits and their owners by sleeping. His nickname is Crumudgeon.</description>
<picture>49552.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2586" picture="233442.jpg">Kimura Masafumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18746" type="appears in" update="2010-06-12">
<rating votes="22">6.20</rating>
<name>Aries</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aries is a Celestial Spirit and one of the 12 Golden Zodiac Keys. Her key is currently owned by Lucy, formerly owned by Angel and Karen Lilica.</description>
<picture>49554.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1927" picture="21136.jpg">Narita Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20956" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-20">
<rating votes="9">4.79</rating>
<name>Warren Rocko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Warren Rocko is a member of the Fairy Tail Guild. Although he may not look it, he is classified as one of the more powerful wizards in the guild, and he has gone on a huge number of jobs alone. His fear of heights causes him many problems. At one point he took a girl on a date, but as they were crossing a bridge, his mental shouts of "Help, save me!!! I`m scared!!!" were heard by everyone in the town.</description>
<picture>53643.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8357" picture="174120.jpg">Kageura Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20957" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-26">
<rating votes="53">5.84</rating>
<name>Fried Justine</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fried Justine is a member of the Fairy Tail Guild who doesn`t show his face often. He is the captain of the Raijinshuu and is known as Fried the Dark by Laxus Dreyar.</description>
<picture>78972.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20958" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-26">
<rating votes="41">5.00</rating>
<name>Evergreen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Evergreen is a member of the Fairy Tail guild and the only female of Laxus Dreyar` bodyguard, the Raijinshuu which are the main antagonists of the Fighting Festival arc. Her Fairy Tail stamp is located on her right bosom.</description>
<picture>78971.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="314" picture="10231.jpeg">Seto Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20959" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-26">
<rating votes="28">3.33</rating>
<name>Bixlow</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bixlow is a 22 year-old member of the Fairy Tail Guild and, along with Fried Justine and Evergreen, makes up Laxus Dreyar`s team Raijinshuu. His member`s stamp is on his tongue.</description>
<picture>78969.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5040" picture="88977.jpg">Kawahara Yoshihisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22290" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-20">
<rating votes="218">6.87</rating>
<name>Wendy Marvell</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wendy Marvell is a young female Dragon Slayer mage, formerly belonging to the Cait Shelter Guild. After the events surrounding Nirvana unfold, she officially joins the Fairy Tail Guild. She learned her Dragon Slayer abilities from Grandine.</description>
<picture>150499.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="162" picture="23208.jpg">Satou Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24712" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-20">
<rating votes="78">2.67</rating>
<name>Charles</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Charle is an Exceed, similar to Happy, and the daughter of Queen Shagotte and apparent chaperon to Wendy Marvell. Both she and Wendy belonged to the Cait Shelter Guild before joining Fairy Tail.</description>
<picture>150496.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24713" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-10-14">
<rating votes="27">2.83</rating>
<name>Ichiya Wanderlei Kotobuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ichiya Wanderlei Kotobuki (Which means One Night to go along with the others) is one of the top mages of the Blue Pegasus Guild, as well as the leader of The Trimens (composed of Hibiki Laytis, Ren Akatsuki and Eve Thylm).</description>
<picture>126876.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27" picture="26123.jpg">Hayami Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24714" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-10-14">
<rating votes="11">3.63</rating>
<name>Hibiki Leytis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hibiki Laytis (known as Hundred Night Hibiki) is one of the mages who belong to the Blue Pegasus Guild`s team The Trimens.</description>
<picture>126871.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="616" picture="18138.jpg">Kondou Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24715" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-10-14">
<rating votes="15">6.62</rating>
<name>Eve Tilm</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Eve Thylm (known as Holy Night Eve) is one of the mages who belong to the Blue Pegasus Guild`s team The Trimens.</description>
<picture>126870.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="142" picture="68482.jpg">Ooura Fuyuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24716" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-10-14">
<rating votes="13">2.02</rating>
<name>Ren Akatsuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ren Akatsuki (known as Empty Night Ren) is one of the mages who belong to the Blue Pegasus Guild`s team The Trimens.</description>
<picture>126872.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="263" picture="186711.jpg">Matsukaze Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25737" type="appears in" update="2010-12-16">
<rating votes="10">5.58</rating>
<name>Scorpio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Scorpio is a Celestial Spirit that is one of the 12 Golden Zodiac Keys. His key is currently owned by Lucy. He is also Aquarius`s boyfriend with which he has a happy relationship. His weapon appears to be a large, strange gun shaped like a scorpion`s tail.</description>
<picture>60870.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27935" type="appears in" update="2012-08-19">
<rating votes="3">3.89</rating>
<name>Klodoa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Klodoa is the seventh member of the Oración Seis, although he is more usually Brain`s staff.</description>
<picture>64631.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="369" picture="223406.jpg">Aoyama Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31116" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-12">
<rating votes="1">1.35</rating>
<name>Hilda</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69668.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1801" picture="146194.jpg">Asou Miyoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31610" type="appears in" update="2011-04-27">
<rating votes="3">7.32</rating>
<name>Haru Glory</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haru Glory is the current Rave Master. He lives with his sister, Cattleya Glory on Garage Island. Haru was entrusted with the responsibility of finding all the Rave Stones and bringing peace to the world when he was chosen as the second generation Rave Master. He is in love with Elie.</description>
<picture>70603.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31612" type="appears in" update="2011-04-27">
<rating votes="2">4.52</rating>
<name>Griffon Kato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Called Griff by his friends, he mostly praises Plue and calls him `Master Plue`. He looks like a strange blue eggplant, with eyes and arms. He is close to Plue in size but with the ability to speak. Griff has limited shape-shifting abilities; such as inflating portions of his body and elongating his limbs. He is also a voyeuristic character, and in a couple of episodes he is seen spying on Elie. He is the cartographer of the group.</description>
<picture>1595.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20322" picture="186181.jpg">Shiga Katsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31613" type="appears in" update="2011-04-27">
<rating votes="2">1.32</rating>
<name>Tanchimo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70620.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="31614" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="2">4.52</rating>
<name>Let Javad Dahaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Let is a Dragonrace, a race of dragon people who reside in the Mystic Realm. When Let was first introduced, he was an evil warrior who worked for Demon Card as a guardian for King. He only wanted to fight until Haru defeated him and showed him the path of justice. His initial appearance in the story is of a human with a lizard like face. In the fight against Jegan he performs Dragon trial and takes the appearance of a human. Soon, he joined Haru in hope of bringing peace to the world. He uses Dragon roar of the gods to defeat Jegan which consumes ones life in return for the power. He manages to defeat Jegan and turn Julia back to normal using a potion given by Alice. He is saved by Julia using the same potion.</description>
<picture>78648.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5650" picture="30095.jpg">Murozono Takehiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31615" type="appears in" update="2011-04-27">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Julia Line Dragoon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Julia is Let`s girlfriend, somewhat of a feisty one who`s loud, rowdy, and not above beating people up to get her way, which is a polar opposite to the cool and calm Let. Initially in the story Julia is shown to have become a dragon as she had failed to pass the dragon trial. Julia is saved by Let and turned back to normal using a potion given by Alice. She can usually be found at a bar. A sisterly figure to Haru`s party. She was first thought to be a kind and shy girl in Let`s flashbacks. In the anime her hair is green.</description>
<picture>70622.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11101" picture="40055.jpg">Namekawa Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32922" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-26">
<rating votes="32">6.56</rating>
<name>Panther Lily</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pantherlily is an Exceed, that used to work for the kingdom of Edolas as the Magic Militia`s First Division Commander of the Royal Army. He is currently a member of the Fairy Tail Guild.</description>
<picture>78975.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="451" picture="17347.jpg">Touchi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36681" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-19">
<rating votes="19">5.18</rating>
<name>Kinana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kinana is one of the newest members of the Fairy Tail Guild,and the former pet of Oracion Seis Member, Cobra.
Unlike most other members of Fairy Tail, she joined the guild as an employee rather than as a Mage.</description>
<picture>154186.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32215" picture="223325.jpg">Sasamoto Natsue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39725" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="2">4.52</rating>
<name>Ruby</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ruby is a pink penguin sentinoid who owns a massive floating casino. Ruby likes to use his wealth to buy rare treasures. When he learns Doryu is using his cash for evil ends, he is almost killed by Doryu, but Haru saves him, and he decides to join his side. He is the only person to know who would be the third Rave Master if Haru dies. Ruby also has a tendency to blab out plans that the Rave Warriors have decided on during battle, making them entirely useless. He recently learned how to use "Wind" magic from the bell given to him by his father. The bell was actually named "the Holy Bell" and it was a weapon used by Dalmatian of Knights of the Blue Sky. It can turn into a magic sword, and use "Magic Reflection", "Twister", and "Air Ball" (from the videogame). In Chapter 75 the characters of Fairy Tail go to casino owned by Ruby.</description>
<picture>78650.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10410" picture="223211.jpg">Izawa Shiori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39772" type="appears in" update="2012-03-12">
<rating votes="2">1.32</rating>
<name>Nakajima</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nakajima is a strange lifeform that lives stuck to the outside wall of Cattleya and Haru`s house. He looks like a flower, but claims that the petal-looking things ringing his round face are feathers. His favorite (and perhaps only) hobby is "golling".</description>
<picture>83445.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="389" picture="56097.jpg">Okano Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39779" type="appears in" update="2012-05-07">
<rating votes="5">1.56</rating>
<name>Wonderful Gotche</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wonderful Gocche is the leader of the Jiggle Butt Gang. He and his gang meet Haru while attempting to rob a train.</description>
<picture>87378.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="39780" type="appears in" update="2012-05-07">
<rating votes="5">1.49</rating>
<name>Karen Borg</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87379.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="39781" type="appears in" update="2012-05-07">
<rating votes="5">2.13</rating>
<name>Marco Berunju</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87380.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40291" type="appears in" update="2019-04-29">
<rating votes="119">7.88</rating>
<name>Mavis Vermilion</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mavis Vermilion was the first master and the founder of the Fairy Tail Guild.</description>
<picture>233184.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40587" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-15">
<rating votes="13">5.86</rating>
<name>Romeo Conbolt</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>80002.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="101" picture="16709.jpg">Ise Mariya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42931" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-27">
<rating votes="23">6.49</rating>
<name>Alzack Connell</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Alzack Connell is a Mage from the West. He came to Fairy Tail as an immigrant and joined the Guild.
Source: Fairy Tail Wikia</description>
<picture>84705.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16987" picture="86303.jpg">Shimoyama Yoshimitsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42932" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-27">
<rating votes="4">4.52</rating>
<name>Sarusuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>84706.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1999" picture="21304.jpg">Kawanabe Masaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42933" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-05">
<rating votes="6">4.07</rating>
<name>Macao Conbolt</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Macao Conbolt is a Mage of Fairy Tail, and the fourth Guild Master following the disappearance of Makarov and the guild`s S-Class Mages.
Source: Fairy Tail Wikia</description>
<picture>152755.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1999" picture="21304.jpg">Kawanabe Masaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42934" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-27">
<rating votes="6">3.95</rating>
<name>Wakaba Mine</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wakaba Mine is a veteran Mage of the Fairy Tail guild. He`s a long-time friend of Macao Conbolt, and was his advisor during the latter`s time as the guild`s Fourth Guild Master.
Source: Fairy Tail Wikia</description>
<picture>84709.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2001" picture="228614.jpg">Sekiguchi Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42935" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-27">
<rating votes="9">6.28</rating>
<name>Max Alors</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Max Alors is a Mage of the Fairy Tail guild who is apparently in charge of most of the guild`s social activities, given his love for talking to people. He specializes in Sand Magic.
Source: Fairy Tail Wikia</description>
<picture>84710.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12623" picture="151646.jpg">Iguchi Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42936" type="appears in" update="2012-03-27">
<name>Vijeeter Ecor</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vijeeter Ecor is a Mage of the Fairy Tail Guild.
Source: Fairy Tail Wikia</description>
<picture>84711.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42937" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-27">
<rating votes="5">3.66</rating>
<name>Droy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>84715.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2001" picture="228614.jpg">Sekiguchi Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42938" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-27">
<rating votes="11">5.67</rating>
<name>Warren Rocko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>84716.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8357" picture="174120.jpg">Kageura Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42939" type="appears in" update="2012-03-27">
<rating votes="5">2.34</rating>
<name>Nab Lasaro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>84717.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="44138" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-05-01">
<rating votes="12">4.57</rating>
<name>Asuka Connell</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Asuka Connell is the daughter of Fairy Tail Mages, Alzack and Bisca Connell.
Source: Fairy Tail Wikia</description>
<picture>86971.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="44418" type="appears in" update="2012-05-07">
<rating votes="1">1.34</rating>
<name>Ketsupuri-dan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>87377.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="45765" type="appears in" update="2012-06-11">
<rating votes="2">7.39</rating>
<name>Hamrio Musica</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>89325.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="143" picture="23260.jpg">Morikubo Shoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49736" type="appears in" update="2012-10-08">
<rating votes="26">5.52</rating>
<name>Sting Eucliffe</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sting Eucliffe is a Mage of the currently strongest Guild in Fiore, the Sabertooth Guild.
Source: Fairy Tail Wikia</description>
<picture>126626.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49738" type="appears in" update="2012-10-08">
<rating votes="10">4.12</rating>
<name>Lector</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lector was an Exceed and a Mage of the currently strongest Guild in Fiore, the Sabertooth Guild.
Source: Fairy Tail Wikia</description>
<picture>126627.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49867" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-10-14">
<rating votes="27">6.14</rating>
<name>Flare Corona</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126855.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49873" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-10-14">
<rating votes="19">8.13</rating>
<name>Jenny Realight</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126874.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49874" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-10-14">
<rating votes="10">5.86</rating>
<name>Chelia Blendy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126875.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49879" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-10-14">
<rating votes="2">4.79</rating>
<name>Risley Law</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126889.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4717" picture="186206.jpg">Narahashi Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49881" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-10-14">
<rating votes="7">4.82</rating>
<name>Bacchus Groh</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126891.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="592" picture="170729.jpg">Tsuda Kenjirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49882" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-10-14">
<rating votes="1">2.42</rating>
<name>Rocker</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126892.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2145" picture="82117.jpg">Miyashita Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49884" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-10-14">
<rating votes="2">2.10</rating>
<name>Yeager</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126894.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2001" picture="228614.jpg">Sekiguchi Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49885" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-27">
<rating votes="1">3.61</rating>
<name>Novali</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126895.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1999" picture="21304.jpg">Kawanabe Masaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49886" type="appears in" update="2012-10-14">
<rating votes="3">3.17</rating>
<name>Semmes</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126896.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="50201" type="appears in" update="2012-10-29">
<rating votes="21">6.87</rating>
<name>Meredy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Meredy was a member of Grimoire Heart and one of the Seven Kin of Purgatory. Currently, she`s a member of Crime Sorcière, an Independent Guild.
Source: Fairy Tail Wikia</description>
<picture>127397.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="58262" type="appears in" update="2014-01-02">
<name>Lazenby</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148025.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16987" picture="86303.jpg">Shimoyama Yoshimitsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62777" type="appears in" update="2014-01-02">
<name>Jackpot Mark II</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148024.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="369" picture="223406.jpg">Aoyama Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77271" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-11-28">
<rating votes="34">5.57</rating>
<name>Bisca Connell</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bisca Connell, nee Mulan, was originally an immigrant from the West, who moved to Magnolia and joined the Fairy Tail Guild. Currently in year X791, she is the wife of Alzack Connell.
Source: Fairy Tail Wikia</description>
<picture>177178.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="128220" update="2011-05-06">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2011-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ようこそ フェアリーヒルズ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to Fairy Hills!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bienvenue à Fairy Hills!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youkoso Fairy Hills!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128221" update="2011-04-12">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-17</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖精学園 ヤンキー君とヤンキーちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fairy Academy: Yankee-kun and Yankee-chan!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yousei Gakuen Yankee-kun to Yankee-chan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129615" update="2011-04-23">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-04-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129616" update="2020-03-01">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-04-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133039" update="2012-02-25">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-02-17</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">メモリーデイズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Memory Days</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Memory Days</title>
</episode>
<episode id="141574" update="2012-12-02">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-11-16</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖精たちの合宿</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fairies` Training Camp</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yousei-tachi no Gasshuku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145939" update="2012-12-13">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-11-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145940" update="2020-03-01">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-11-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147475" update="2013-02-15">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドキドキ・リュウゼツランド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Exciting Ryuzetsu Land</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dokidoki Ryuuzetsu Land</title>
</episode>
<episode id="149673" update="2013-11-04">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-08-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フェアリーテイル x レイヴ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fairy Tail x Rave</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fairy Tail x Rave</title>
<summary>In the Fairy Tail x Rave crossover story, Fairy Tail`s main character Natsu and Rave`s main character Haru are lost, so Lucy and Elie - the heroines of both series - embark on a search for them.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="152227" update="2013-11-04">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-07-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">PV (Volume 6 - Fairy Tail x Rave)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="177800" update="2016-09-30">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖精たちのクリスマス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fairies` Christmas</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yousei-tachi no Christmas</title>
</episode>
<episode id="177801" update="2016-09-30">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナツvs.メイビス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Natsu vs. Mavis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu vs. Mavis</title>
</episode>
<episode id="177802" update="2016-05-25">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖精たちの罰ゲーム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fairies` Penalty Game</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yousei-tachi no Batsu Game</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227302" update="2020-03-01">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-05-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227303" update="2020-03-01">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-05-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
