<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8139" restricted="false">
<type>Other</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-08-01</startdate>
<enddate>2010-08-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Pikachu no Fushigi na Fushigi na Daibouken</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pikachu`s Big Mysterious Adventure</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pikachu`s Really Mysterious Adventure</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pokemon: Movie 13 Short</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Pikachu no Fushigina Fushigina Daiboken</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ピカチュウのふしぎなふしぎな大冒険</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4728" type="Parent Story">Pocket Monsters: Diamond and Pearl</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="727" type="Animation Work">OLM</name>
<name id="7914" type="Character Design">Yamada Shun`ya</name>
<name id="27525" type="Character Design">Matsumiya Toshinobu</name>
<name id="27643" type="Character Design">Nishino Kouji</name>
<name id="27526" type="Character Design">Matsushima Kenji</name>
<name id="2841" type="Work">Shogakukan-Shueisha Productions</name>
<name id="7914" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yamada Shun`ya</name>
<name id="5780" type="Original Plan">Tajiri Satoshi</name>
<name id="10185" type="Original Plan">Masuda Jun`ichi</name>
<name id="10181" type="Original Plan">Sugimori Ken</name>
<name id="4235" type="Direction">Yuyama Kunihiko</name>
<name id="2822" type="Music">Tada Akifumi</name>
<name id="6897" type="Music">Tanaka Hirokazu</name>
<name id="5660" type="Music">Miyazaki Shinji</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch8091 [Pikachu], http://anidb.net/ch24156 [Piplup] and a http://anidb.net/ch953 [Skitty] help an http://anidb.net/ch611 [Unknown] find its herd through an alternate dimension.
Source: ANN
Note: Aired on ANA (All Nippon Airways) flights starting from 01.08.2010 to 29.08.2010 to promote the movie http://anidb.net/a7257 [Pocket Monsters Diamond &amp; Pearl: Gen`ei no Hasha Zoroark]. It was released on DVD on 16.07.2011.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="96">3.25</permanent>
<temporary count="99">5.27</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>143974.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15659</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11069</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2024</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>339737</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1846" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>kodomo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word kodomo refers to a children`s audience roughly for the ages 12 and younger. In Japanese, the word means simply "child", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="567" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Maril</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Marill is an aquatic mouse Pokémon. Marill`s tail floats like a buoy because it is filled with oil, which is less dense than water. When fishing at a fast-running stream, Marill wraps its tail around a tree. Since the tail is stretchy and flexible, it allows the Pokémon to get food and still stay safely anchored. Otherwise, when in a lake, it uses the buoy-qualities of its tail to keep itself suspended as the rest of its body dives underwater to feed on aquatic plants. Its fur is impermeable, which keeps it dry, and that allows it to swim through water at high speed without being slowed by the water`s resistance.
In the Pokémon Anime, Tracey, the Pokémon Observer from the Orange Islands, has a Marill which he uses on multiple occasions.</description>
<picture>243067.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="70" picture="171604.jpg">Kanai Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="611" type="main character in" update="2020-01-05">
<name>Unknown</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Unown is a hieroglyph-like symbol with 28 different forms, based on the letters of the Latin alphabet, a question mark, and an exclamation point. They always have the similarities of a flat body with black color and one medium-size eye. They always reside in mysterious chambers, only with other Unown, always stuck on walls.
Unown is featured in Spell of the Unown as the main antagonists. The Unown create an Entei to befriend a young girl and grant all of the girl`s wishes: in the girl`s case, turning the town she lives in into crystal. Ash and friends convince the girl that Entei is not her true father, since her father was lost on an archeological dig in an Unown temple. The Unown, overpowered by the girl`s current thoughts, became unable to control their powers and larger areas were turning into crystal. Entei saves them all by attacking the Unown, sending them all back to their dimension. It has also been revealed that Dialga and Palkia live in the same dimension as the Unown.</description>
<picture>64433.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="953" type="main character in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Eneco</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Skitty is a basic Pokémon species found in the Hoenn region. Skitty is a "cute" Pokémon, according to the Pokédex. It loves things that it can chase. Some times it even chases its own tail. Many people in the Pokémon world have them as pets.
In the Pokémon anime, trainer May has a Skitty that she uses for Contests. It can juggle and perform a variety of attacks, for which it also is useful in battle, when it is not chasing its own tail. May`s Skitty (like Jessie`s Wobbuffet, Misty`s Psyduck and Brock`s Croagunk) has a knack for coming out of its Poké Ball at some inappropriate moments, which may make May`s opponent think it`s her next battle Pokémon.
In Pokémon Mystery Dungeon: Blue Rescue Team and Red Rescue Team, Skitty is one of the sixteen available starter Pokémon.Skitty is also playable in the game`s sequel and is one of three normal types.(the others being Meowth and Munchlax)</description>
<picture>243264.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1098" type="appears in" update="2020-01-07">
<name>Deoxys</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Deoxys (pronounced /di`ɑks.ɪs/) is a Pokémon formed from a mutation of a extraterrestrial virus exposed to a laser beam. It has psychokinetic powers and a high intelligence along with a crystalline organ on its chest that acts as its brain and shoots lasers. It has the ability to transform into four different forms, each with a specific purpose: Normal, Attack, Defense, and Speed. In the third generation of games, the form is based upon the game the Deoxys is contained within. As of Pokémon Diamond and Pearl, it can freely change by interacting with the four meteorites in Veilstone City.
Deoxys` name is based on "Deoxyribonucleic acid", or DNA, which is the base of all life and contains instructions for every part of it.
Deoxys first appeared in the seventh Pokémon film, http://anidb.net/a2371 [Pokémon: Destiny Deoxys]. In the film, it demonstrated the ability to switch between its forms, create shadow copies for use as drones, regenerate missing body parts, launch an aurora into the sky, and erect a city-size force field which keeps nearly every sort of machine within from operating. The film also demonstrated that Deoxys is not a one-of-a-kind unique species like Rayquaza; more than one Deoxys is seen.
In early 2005, NASA began a cross-promotion with Nintendo and the Pokémon Company to provide an "edutainment" program for children across the United States by Internet, teaching the science behind various Pokémon characters as they appear in Trading Card Game expansions. In the first segment of the program, based on the newly-released EX: Deoxys Trading Card Game expansion, they used the character of Deoxys to teach children about outer space, anatomy of a virus, the meaning of DNA, the existence of the ozone layer, and a definition of an extraterrestrial. Since then the program has had two other segments covering the next two expansions: EX Emerald and EX Unseen Forces.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>64386.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="1268" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Yuxie</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Uxie, known as the Knowledge Pokémon, has a yellow and round head with a jewel (probably a ruby), embedded in its forehead, and in its Sugimori art it appears to be sleeping, or closing its eyes in deep thought. Uxie`s name comes from the word pixie, a small mythical creature, and "you", U being short for it. The other members of the Psychic-type, Mew like Lake Trio, Mesprit and Azelf, represent "me" and "us", respectively. It is also a possibility that these three Pokémon are inspired from a trio of Arabian goddesses, Al-Lat (Azelf), Manat (Mesprit), and Al-Uzza (Uxie). This is further supported by their moniker as Mirage Pokémon (as mirages are something associated with the Arabian desert), and that the three appear to be wearing jeweled turbans, which are associated with Arabic royalty. Uxie`s eyelids are also yellow, although they are obviously not part of the top of the head where the other yellow is. Uxie also resembles a religious monk. Its head resembles a human brain, since it is the Knowledge Pokémon. Like Mesprit and Azelf, its partners in the legendary trio, it has two tails with jewels embedded in them, and the only major difference between them is their heads and their faces. It is also believed that the mystic trio was all hatched from the same egg.
Uxie is referred to as "The Being of Knowledge". It is said that the wisdom that enriches the lives of humans was brought with the birth of Uxie. Similar to the legend of the basilisk where the basilisk could cause death by a single glance, Uxie can cause a complete loss of memory by a single glance of its open eyes; hence, its eyes are always closed, even when it is in battle.</description>
<picture>243415.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1269" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Emrit</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mesprit, known as the Emotion Pokémon, is a legendary Pokémon that is part of the Psychic-type Lake Trio along with Uxie and Azelf. Mesprit`s name comes from the word sprite, a tiny fairy found in fantasy and fairy tales, or spirit, as its spirit often exits its body, leaving it on the bottom of Lake Verity. It has a small blue body about the size of Mew, and is identical to Uxie and Azelf except for its head. It has a pink head with a jewel embedded in its forehead, and four long ears drooping down its head looking like those of Lucario.
Mesprit is referred to as "The Being of Emotion," and said to have taught humans to sense emotions such as sorrow, pain and joy. If a human touches it, three days after the touch, the person will lose their emotions. Cyrus is one example. When you attempt to capture it, it will roam around Sinnoh. It is thought to have come from the same egg as Uxie and Azelf.</description>
<picture>243416.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1270" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Agnome</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Azelf, known as the Willpower Pokémon, is a legendary Pokémon that is part of the Psychic-type trio along with Uxie and Mesprit. It has a small blue body about the size of Mew, and is identical to Uxie and Mesprit except for its head. It has a blue cone shaped head with a jewel embedded in its forehead and also two blue dropping ears, yellow eyes, and eyelids the same dark blue as its head.
Referred to as "The Being of Willpower", it can either make people give up on an activity or cause them to attempt the activity repeatedly. Also, if a human is to harm Azelf, in a scant five days, the offender would be immobile for all eternity. Residing and sleeping at the base of Lake Valor, it keeps the world in balance. It`s believed to have come from the same egg as Uxie and Mesprit.</description>
<picture>243417.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1938" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-13">
<rating votes="420">5.46</rating>
<name>Nyarth (Rocket-dan)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Meowth is a very unique Pokémon as it has many of the characteristics of a human. It walks on two feet, talks and is as smart as any human. Meowth is currently a member of Team Rocket and he travels around with Jessie and James trying to capture Pikachu and other rare Pokémon for Giovanni.
Meowth generally finishes his sentences with "Nyaa (ニャー)" which is the equivalent of "meow" in English. This helps people remember that despite his ability to talk like a human, he still has cat character traits.
Meowth is also known for coming up with his many schemes to try to capture Pikachu. While Jessie and James always agree with Meowth and think his plans are brilliant, they are generally foiled by Ash and his friends.
Long Con to Access Raimon City Pokémon Center
Meowth schemed with Jessie, James and Doctor Zager to figure out a way for them to infiltrate the Raimon City Pokémon Center where high-leveled Pokémon are stored in a vault that is protected by a security machine scan system that would only open if Nurse Joy (Isshu) or Nurse Joy`s Audino were scanned. Meowth pretended to be no longer part of Team Rocket making up a story that his made an error while executing a certain operation and when headquarters hear of his mistake, they told him he was fired.
Ash, Iris and Cilan believed him and allowed Meowth to travel with him. Pikachu though didn`t trust Meowth even though Meowth proved on numerous occasion that it should be trusted. Meowth`s plan was put into action when they arrived at the Raimon City Pokémon Center and as soon as Nurse Joy`s Audino was scanned to open the door, Meowth turned on Pikachu and the other and captured all the Pokémon in the vault. The long con had been a success and Meowth met up with Jessie and James below the Pokémon Center. Unfortunately, they weren`t able to get away as Ash and his friends realized that Meowth had just been conning them and they were able to stop Team Rocket.</description>
<picture>56344.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3832" picture="170554.jpg">Inuyama Inuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8091" type="main character in" update="2017-10-30">
<rating votes="989">3.91</rating>
<name>Pikachu (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Beginning
On the morning that Ash was to start his Pokémon journey, he woke up late and by the time he reached Professor Samual Oak`s laboratory, all of the beginner Pokémon were already taken. However, Professor Samual Oak did have one Pokémon left, a wild Pikachu. At first, Pikachu did not like Ash and would refuse to enter his PokéBall. He would often laugh at Ash`s failures and refused to listen to him. However, after Ash proved his loyalty to Pikachu by protecting him from a flock of Spearow, and thus began to earn Pikachu`s trust and respect. The two have since become best friends and Pikachu never leaves Ash`s side.
Since the day Team Rocket first encountered Pikachu, it has been their sole goal to capture it. Day after day, their plan to capture Pikachu has been thwarted mainly due to Pikachu`s amazingly powerful Thunderbolt that keeps on blasting them off.
On numerous occasions, Pikachu has made it evident that he is happy being a Pikachu and has no desire to evolve into a more powerful Raichu. It has proven time and time again that it is a powerful and worthy opponent to any Pokémon that dares to battle it.
Gym Battle against Burgh`s Leavanny
Pikachu was then sent out to battle Burgh`s Leavanny. Burgh`s Leavanny managed to tie up Pikachu with String Shot but unlike Ash`s Swadloon who was able to break free, Pikachu ended up getting hit with a couple of Leaf Storm attacks and a Hyper Beam before it rolled into another of Burgh`s Leavanny`s Leaf Storm attacks to break the string off its body so it could attack. Freed from the String Shot, Burgh`s Leavanny tried to tie it up again but Pikachu managed to avoid it with its speed and then knocked Burgh`s Leavanny out with a combination of Iron Tail and Electro Ball.
Gym Battle against Elesa
Elesa`s Emolga knocked out Ash`s Snivy and was then matched up with Pikachu. Pikachu made quick work of Elesa`s Emolga and knocked it out with one attack, its Iron Tail.
Elesa`s Tynamo was the last Pokémon that she used in her gym battle against Ash. It was matched up against Pikachu who had just defeated her Emonga. Pikachu had a hard time defending against the fast Tackle attack that Elesa`s Tynamo kept hitting it with but Pikachu used its Thunderbolt to create a large dust cloud leaving only a small corridor for Pikachu to focus on it and so Elesa`s Tynamo couldn`t maneuver out of the way. Pikachu one hit K.O`d Elesa`s Tynamo with a Iron Tail. The loss gave Ash the overall victory.
Battle against Alder`s Bouffalant
Ash challenged Alder to a battle and he accepted though he had been walking all night and was actually quite tired. Alder sent out his Buffron to battle Pikachu but just as the battle started, Alder fell asleep standing up and didn`t give any orders to his Buffron. Alder`s Bouffalant stood still as Pikachu began hitting it with attack after attack until it Alder`s Bouffalant finally got mad at Alder and charged at him and set him flying into a tree. After that, Alder`s Bouffalant no longer wished to battle and Alder conceded the battle.
Gym Battle against Skyla
In Skyla air battle simulation, Ash`s Tranquill was matched up against Skyla`s Unfezant and since her Pokémon was the highest evolved form, she determined that her Pokémon would be the winner in that match-up. In the actual gym battle, Ash`s Tranquill was up against Skyla`s Unfezant which was the match-up just after Ash`s Tranquill had defeated Skyla`s Swoobat. Skyla`s Unfezant proved to be stronger and faster than Ash`s Tranquill, so Ash recalled it and set out Pikachu. Pikachu had a definite advantage over Skyla`s Unfezant with its electric attacks and it quickly knocked it out with its Electro Ball attack.
Ash Just after Pikachu ended up knocking out Skyla`s Unfezant, Skyla`s Swanna was sent out to battle against it. Skyla had been watching her grandpa`s battle videos and noticed that he used the move Aqua Ring to defend against Electric attacks. She used that same defense against Pikachu which nullified its Electric attacks. It`s Iron Tail also couldn`t hit it so high in the air. Ash then noticed the rings in the air and Pikachu jumped up on them and managed to hit Skyla`s Swanna but not directly. Pikachu was now up in the air though and Skyla`s Swanna had the advantage there and it quickly knocked Pikachu out with a powerful Brave Bird attack.
Battle Against Trip`s Serperior at the Isshu League
Pikachu participated in the Isshu League in the preliminary match where it is was matched up against Trip`s Serperior. Cilan noted that Trip`s Serperior speed and its attack power had leveled up quite a bit too since the last time they saw it. The match was pretty one sided for a long time as Pikachu wasn`t able to counter its speed and ended up getting wrapped up. After using Iron Tail on the ground to get loose, Pikachu used a combination attack of Iron Tail and Electro Ball to one hit KO Trip`s Serperior. As a result, Trip was eliminated from the Isshu League and Ash advanced to the next round.</description>
<picture>88041.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7" picture="186500.jpg">Ootani Ikue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8135" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-12">
<rating votes="73">8.01</rating>
<name>Sonans (Musashi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>While Wobbuffet is technically Jessie`s Pokémon, it has been around so long that it has become a main character, appearing in almost every episode of the series since it debut.
Wobbuffet was first seen walking around with Benny, his previous trainer. Jessie traded her Lickitung for Wobbuffet and it has been with her ever since that day.
Wobbuffet rarely battles but when he does, his Counter and Mirror Coat moves have proved to be very effective. Unfortunately, Jessie`s tactics aren`t always sufficient to master Wobbuffet`s superior defensive skills.
Wobbuffet also randomly comes out of his Pokeball, especially during the Team Rocket motto. He is also seen blasting off with Jessie regardless if he was actually part of the action.</description>
<picture>56350.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8150" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-12">
<name>Manene (Kojirou)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mime Jr. previously resided with the old couple who took care of an old vacation castle that James`s family owns.</description>
<picture>56367.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="24147" type="appears in" update="2012-10-27">
<name>Buoysel (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>When Ash and co. were traveling towards Daybreak Town for Dawn`s next Pokémon Contest, a mysterious Pokémon Trainer specializing in martial arts, named Clayton, challenged Ash and his Buizel to a battle after seeing how Buizel saved Gible who had fallen into a river. Clayton`s Mr. Mime proved to be a really strong opponent, though, as it managed to dodge Buizel`s Aqua Jet and SonicBoom attacks by skillfully using its Psychic and Double Team moves, eventually knocking Buizel out with a powerful ThunderPunch. Ash and Buizel, determined to make up for the loss by getting stronger, started training with Clayton`s help so that Buizel could learn a new move; Ice Punch. He told them that, in order to master the move, they had to work on improving their speed and concentration.
At first, the progress of Ash`s Buizel`s training seemed to be really slow. However, after training overnight using unstable and light objects as targets for its punches, like floating leaves, Buizel managed to master the move completely. After the completion of Buizel`s training, Ash challenged Clayton to a rematch, and Clayton accepted. Ash`s Buizel proved to be more of a challenge for its opponent, Mr. Mime, this time and after activating its ability, Swift Swim, in the midst of the battle due to a sudden rain, Buizel managed to increase its speed and finish Clayton`s Mr. Mime off with a powerful Ice Punch. Clayton then acknowledged Ash`s Buizel`s improvement and praised its skills, but also put emphasis on the fact that Buizel still had a long way to go and had to keep on training.</description>
<picture>58893.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2364" picture="151724.jpg">Furushima Kiyotaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24149" type="appears in" update="2012-10-27">
<name>Usokkie (Takeshi)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Brock`s Bonsly evolved into Sudowoodo after it escaped from a cage that Team Rocket caught it in.</description>
<picture>58869.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="24150" type="appears in" update="2011-01-15">
<name>Pinpuku (Takeshi)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Brock won Happiny`s egg in a Pokémon cosplay contest by entering his Croagunk dressed up as a Politoed. While traveling on Cycling Road, the egg began to glow. After taking it to a Pokémon Center, the egg hatched into Happiny.</description>
<picture>58870.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6925" picture="201846.jpg">Itou Miyako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24151" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-08">
<rating votes="11">9.08</rating>
<name>Gureggru (Takeshi)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Team Rocket recruited Croagunk while they were running their fake Gym in the Sinnoh region.</description>
<picture>58871.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24156" type="main character in" update="2011-06-08">
<rating votes="12">7.27</rating>
<name>Pochama (Hikari)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dawn`s first Pokémon that she got from Professor Rowan.</description>
<picture>58876.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2046" picture="186581.jpg">Kozakura Etsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24183" type="appears in" update="2011-06-08">
<name>Mimirol (Hikari)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dawn battled many wild Buneary before she captured captured this Buneary.</description>
<picture>58877.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="271" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24198" type="appears in" update="2010-11-08">
<name>Pachirisu (Hikari)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dawn captured Pachirisu which has a very hyperactive and mischievous personality.</description>
<picture>58878.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="551" picture="228658.jpg">Nishimura Chinami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24232" type="appears in" update="2010-11-08">
<name>Manmoo (Hikari)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mamoswine evolve after being attacked by Team Rocket.</description>
<picture>58881.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24438" type="appears in" update="2012-10-27">
<name>Mukuhawk (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ash`s Staraptor evolved during the PokéRinger competition held in Wind Town.</description>
<picture>59101.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="24495" type="appears in" update="2010-11-08">
<name>Hinoarashi (Hikari)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dawn received her Cyndaquil as an egg after she defeated Kotone in a battle during the Johto Festa in Suiren Town. Team Rocket noticed the egg while they were flying away and Meowth used his extender arm to capture the egg.
While escaping from a wild Ursaring, James noticed that the egg was glowing, signifying that it was close to hatching. Dawn was able to recover the egg in time to watch it hatch.
Dawn`s Cyndaquil didn`t get along with her Pilpup just after it hatched as they fought a lot.</description>
<picture>58883.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="24527" type="appears in" update="2012-10-27">
<name>Fukamaru (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>While heading to Asatsuki Town for Hikari`s next contest, Satoshi and his friends got lost once again in a forest. They see Grandma Tatsu`s Altaria`s Draco Meteor in the air and quickly go to see where it was coming from.
Grandma Wilma introduces herself to the group. Grandma Wilma is based off the Route 210 Dragon type Pokémon tutor who teaches Draco Meteor to trainers Pokémon. A Gible appeared on the field as Altaria was practicing and tried to use Draco Meteor as well. It had a hard time getting the move to work properly and it kept hitting Hikari`s Pochama.
After leaving Grandma Tatsu, Gible followed Satoshi and his friends and Satoshi later captured it after a battle with his rival Jun.</description>
<picture>59103.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="336" picture="17172.jpg">Sakaguchi Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24536" type="appears in" update="2010-11-10">
<name>Dodaitose (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ash`s Torterra was revealed during the Japanese opening `The Greatest-Everyday!`. It evolved during a battle against Rocket Gang when they commandeered Nagisa Tower. Denji`s Raichu and Satoshi`s Pikachu were injured by Rocket Gang and in order to protect them it used its new move Leaf Storm which it learned after evolving.</description>
<picture>59104.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24537" type="appears in" update="2012-10-27">
<name>Togekiss (Hikari)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dawn`s Togekiss was revealed during the Japanese opening `The Greatest-Everyday!". Princess Salvia gave her Togekiss to Dawn to help her in the Grand Festival as thanks for trading places with her so she could participate in the Katakuri Town Pokémon Contest.</description>
<picture>58886.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24538" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<name>Goukazaru (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ash`s Infernape was revealed during the Japanese opening `The Greatest-Everyday!`. It evolved a few episodes after the airing of opening in DP163.
During a battle against Barry, Monferno was hit by Empoleon`s Hydro Cannon and was sent flying into the nearby forest. When Team Rocket captured the Pokémon and were about to get away, Monferno returned in rage and began destroying their mecha.
Ash managed to stop Monferno, but while Paul`s Electabuzz was holding the broken mecha up, it couldn`t hold it any longer and Monferno came to the rescue. While it was rescuing Piplup, Empoleon and Pikachu, it evolved into Infernape.</description>
<picture>59105.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="316" picture="25472.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="126083" update="2011-10-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2010-08-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
