<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8142" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>147</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-04-03</startdate>
<enddate>2014-03-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Toriko (2011)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">トリコ (2011)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Toriko</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="official">Торико</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8009" type="Prequel">Toriko 3D: Kaimaku! Gourmet Adventure!!</anime>
<anime id="7227" type="Alternative Setting">Toriko</anime>
<anime id="9671" type="Side Story">Gekijouban Toriko: Bishokushin no Special Menu</anime>
<anime id="7735" type="Other">Toriko: Barbarian Ivy o Hokaku Seyo!</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="1530" approval="11" total="19">Dragon Ball Z</anime>
<anime id="10901" approval="2" total="8">Shokugeki no Souma</anime>
<anime id="8550" approval="2" total="6">Hunter x Hunter (2011)</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="335704">Good anime to watch if you like to watch thing about food (if you tend to watch cooking progams alot etc).</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="460550">Overall average shounen anime. It does not compare to manga at all, but it can be a good watch at some parts (It can even make you hungry sometimes.)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="478945">Toriko is very good.
CLASSIC.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.fujitv.co.jp/b_hp/toriko/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="2803" type="Character Design">Kagawa Hisashi</name>
<name id="15768" type="Direction">Zako Akifumi</name>
<name id="20514" type="Series Composition">Murayama Isao</name>
<name id="1834" type="Work">Toei Animation</name>
<name id="21534" type="Original Work">Shimabukuro Mitsutoshi</name>
<name id="2803" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kagawa Hisashi</name>
<name id="2753" type="Music">Mizutani Hiromi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a shounen manga by http://anidb.net/cr21534 [Shimabukuro Mitsutoshi] serialised in http://anidb.net/cr5372 [Weekly Shounen Jump].
In a world where the taste and texture of food is extremely important there exist individuals known as Bishoku-ya (luxury food providers) who specialize in the acquisition of rare ingredients and animals. http://anidb.net/ch19496 [Toriko] is one of these hunters and it is his dream to find the most precious foods in the world and create the ultimate dinner course. As one of the most skilled hunters in the world he is regularly hired by restaurants and the rich to seek out new ingredients and rare animals. A man with inhuman ability, he utilizes his incredible strength and knowledge of the animal kingdom to capture ferocious, evasive and rare beasts to further his final goal, the ultimate dinner course composed of the most delicious food in the world. He is currently accompanied by a weak and timid chef who, inspired by Toriko`s ambition, travels with him to improve his culinary skills and find rare ingredients.
Note: The first episode is actually a 2 part special called Toriko x One Piece Collabo Special - a crossover with http://anidb.net/a69 [One Piece]. The first part aired on Toriko`s timeslot at 9:00 and the second part aired on One Piece`s timeslot at 9:30. That is also the reason why the second Toriko episode doesn`t continue where the first one left off.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="725">4.86</permanent>
<temporary count="733">6.58</temporary>
<review count="1">4.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>67308.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12306</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10033</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4863</identifier>
<identifier>kzkuld</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/tv/toriko/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.fujitv.co.jp/b_hp/toriko/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>トリコ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2162</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>339078</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13446</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2765</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3327" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-08">
<name>manly</name>
<description>Masculinity is possessing qualities or characteristics considered typical of or appropriate to a man.
Typical characteristics associated with masculinity are: courage, a strong physique, competitive, strong willed, and a sense of honor.
Very important for being considered masculine however is the ability to inspire respect from your fellow brethren and/or being perceived as a virile man by the opposite sex.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3394" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-25">
<name>environmentalism</name>
<description>Environmental protection is a practice of protecting the natural environment on individual, organizational or governmental levels, for the benefit of both the natural environment and humans. Due to the pressures of population and technology, the biophysical environment is being degraded, sometimes permanently. This has been recognized, and governments have begun placing restraints on activities that cause environmental degradation. Since the 1960s, activity of environmental movements has created awareness of the various environmental issues.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3896" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-23">
<name>bloodless wounds</name>
<description>No matter what weapon is used in what way to attack, hurt or kill somebody, there won`t be blood. You may see ripped clothes and smoke coming from the deadly wounds, but that`s it.
So if you have an aversion towards the red liquid but still love some action going on - this is the anime for you!</description>
<picurl>39189.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4418" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-12-04">
<name>evil organization</name>
<description>The main enemy in this show is an evil organization, that starts off with a small number of unknown goals/powerful members that you learn about as the story goes on.
Examples:
1 - Akatsuki from Naruto.
2 - Demon Cards from Rave Master.
3 - Gung-Ho Guns from Trigun.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5151" parentid="3394" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-31">
<name>man vs nature</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5863" parentid="2798" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-06">
<name>Weekly Shounen Jump</name>
<description>The Weekly Shounen Jump is a Japanese manga magazine released on a weekly basis. Its main target audience consists of young males and it features several manga titles. The magazine was created by http://anidb.net/cr780 [Shueisha] in July, 1968, and was originally only called Shounen Jump, because it was not published every week at the time. A number of very famous shounen manga were or are published in it, such as http://anidb.net/a386 [Hokuto no Ken], http://anidb.net/a231 [Dragon Ball], http://anidb.net/a942 [City Hunter], http://anidb.net/a826 [Saint Seiya], http://anidb.net/a590 [Slam Dunk], http://anidb.net/a312 [Yuu Yuu Hakushou], http://anidb.net/a69 [One Piece], http://anidb.net/a239 [Naruto], http://anidb.net/a2369 [Bleach], http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], http://anidb.net/a3468 [Gintama], to name a few of the most well-known.</description>
<picurl>66685.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5981" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-10-12">
<name>seeking protagonist</name>
<description>The main character has a main objective that is referenced to through the whole series; he is in search of something, or someone
Should it be treasure, friends, money, power or all of the above nothing will stop our lead character in his quest to find his passion</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="474" type="cameo appearance in" update="2019-03-01">
<rating votes="4175">8.53</rating>
<name>Monkey D. Luffy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Monkey D. Luffy is a fictional character and the main protagonist in the anime and manga series http://anidb.net/a69 [One Piece] created by http://anidb.net/cr4013 [Oda Eiichiro]. He is a boy whose body is made of rubber after he ate a http://anidb.net/t2518 [devil`s fruit] and acquired the accursed ability.
In the anime and manga, Luffy is captain of the http://anidb.net/ch1954 [Straw Hat Pirates], a group of pirates he assembles himself as he quests to find the "One Piece" and become the King of the Pirates. His primary motivation throughout the series is to reach the goal with all of his comrades, a task he pursues no matter what stands in his way. While he is goofy and reckless, he gets quite serious when anyone is in serious danger, notably his crew, whom he considers his friends. Luffy has additionally appeared in all of the featured movies in the series and other media relating to the series, including several video games and specials.
His blood type is F in XFS blood group system used in his world. It is equivalent to B in ABO blood group system.</description>
<picture>77294.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="322" picture="17159.jpg">Tanaka Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="475" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-01-19">
<rating votes="3991">8.67</rating>
<name>Roronoa Zoro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Roronoa Zoro is a pirate, former bounty hunter and one of the main protagonists of http://anidb.net/a69 [One Piece]. He was the first member to join the http://anidb.net/ch1954 [Straw Hat Pirates], and to date is widely acknowledged as the largest threat and the most dangerous member in the crew after http://anidb.net/ch474 [Luffy]. He is famed as a master swordsman, user of the Santouryuu style, and his great strength sometimes leads others to believe he must be the true captain. Being labeled as one of the "Monster Trio", he`s one of the top three fighters in the crew. Zoro is currently one of eleven pirates who have been referred to as "The Eleven Supernovas", having a bounty of 120,000,000 beli.</description>
<picture>80181.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="259" picture="17082.jpg">Nakai Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="476" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-01-19">
<rating votes="2401">7.24</rating>
<name>Nami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nami, nicknamed Thief-Cat Nami, is the crew`s 18-year-old navigator and thief. She has the ability to recognize and analyze even the slightest changes in the weather up to the point of sheer intuition. She is also an excellent pickpocket. Her dream is to draw a complete map of the world. Throughout the series, Nami fights using a bou-like staff that is made up of three connectable segments. http://anidb.net/ch478 [Usopp] later provides her with a version of this weapon capable of controlling weather, called the Clima-Takt ("Climate Baton" in the English manga and as "Weather Forcer" in the 4Kids dub). Even later, Usopp augments the Clima-Takt with dials, making it more powerful. Nami ranked in the Top 10 of all three Shounen Jump character popularity polls. Her backstory has been found to be a "touching story" as it "unfolds with a lot of emotion" by Mania Entertainment writer, Jarred Pine. Pine also mentioned Nami was his favorite character from the series, and satisfied with how the manga showed her past. While reviewing the 8th DVD from Viz Media, Activeanime mentioned Nami is one of the best characters from the series as "She`s got guts, smarts, and can heft a mean punch when needed". Like Pined, Activeanime liked Nami`s background and added that his "itty bitty heart went out to her".
When a reader asked http://anidb.net/cr4013 [Oda] who Nami is in romantic love with, Oda answered that there will not likely be any romance among the http://anidb.net/ch1954 [Straw Hat Pirates]. Oda explained that he does not portray romance in http://anidb.net/a69 [One Piece] as the series is a shounen comic, and the young boys who read the comic are not interested in romance.</description>
<picture>80179.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="319" picture="228606.jpg">Okamura Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="478" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-01-19">
<rating votes="1329">4.40</rating>
<name>Usopp</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Usopp, nicknamed "Sogeking", "King of Snipers Sogeking" (Sogeki no Ou-sama; "Sniperking" (Viz manga) is the 17-year old marksman of the http://anidb.net/ch1954 [Straw Hat Pirates]. His name comes from Uso, which means liar in Japanese, and Aesop, the author of The Boy Who Cried Wolf. He is a liar, talented inventor, as well as a skilled painter and sculptor. His primary weapon is a slingshot, which he uses to fire various kinds of ammunition, ranging from rotten eggs and shuriken to hot sauce, flaming, and exploding projectiles. Later, he creates himself a large, dial-powered slingshot he calls Kabuto, with which he is able to out range even guns. Usopp`s father, http://anidb.net/ch688 [Yasopp], left his family to become a pirate when Usopp was still very young. Some time after this, Usopp`s mother, http://anidb.net/ch648 [Banchina], fell ill. Usopp started telling lies, stating that his father had returned and would be taking them with him. His mother eventually died, but Usopp, in his sadness, continued to lie. Despite all this, he does not blame his father for leaving him, but takes pride in his heritage. He is inspired by http://anidb.net/ch474 [Luffy], http://anidb.net/ch475 [Zoro], and http://anidb.net/ch476 [Nami] and decides to go out to sea, following his dream of becoming a "brave warrior of the sea". His weakness as a fighter weighs heavily upon him and when after the crew is defeated and almost destroyed by http://anidb.net/ch3168 [Admiral Aokiji], Luffy decides to replace the badly damaged http://anidb.net/ch2028 [Going Merry], the Straw Hats` first ship, which is given to them by Usopp`s friend http://anidb.net/ch643 [Kaya], a girl from his village that he used to cheer up with his lies, Usopp goes so far as to temporarily leave the crew.
Usopp ranked in the Top 10 of all three Shounen Jump character popularity polls. In a 2007 Oricon poll, Usopp was voted the 10th most wanted character to receive a spin off amongst all respondents, and the 5th most popular amongst males. In a review of Funimation Entertainment`s second DVD release for Mania Entertainment, Bryce Coulter notes that Usopp "brings lots of comic relief to the series", but also comments that he "can be down right annoying at times".</description>
<picture>80183.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="479" type="cameo appearance in" update="2017-08-18">
<rating votes="1397">6.86</rating>
<name>Vinsmoke Sanji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sanji is a pirate and the chef of the Straw Hat Pirates. He is the fifth member of the crew and the fourth to join. Since he was born in North Blue, he is the first Straw Hat not to originate from East Blue. His dream is to find the rumoured All Blue, which is where East Blue, West Blue, North Blue, and South Blue meet along with their wildlife; a chef`s paradise. He has a bounty of 77,000,000 Berry.
Source: onepiece.wikia.com</description>
<picture>80184.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="323" picture="211661.jpg">Hirata Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="487" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-01-18">
<rating votes="889">5.23</rating>
<name>Tony Tony Chopper</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tony Tony Chopper is the doctor of the Straw Hat Pirates. Chopper is a reindeer that consumed the Devil fruit, Hito Hito no Mi. He comes from Drum Island, which makes him the only member of the Straw Hat Pirate Crew who was born on the Grand Line. He is the sixth member of the crew and the fifth to join, as well as being the youngest member on board. He has a bounty of 50 Berry, due to being mistaken for the crew`s pet.</description>
<picture>80146.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7" picture="186500.jpg">Ootani Ikue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="488" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-01-19">
<rating votes="1489">7.47</rating>
<name>Nico Robin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nico Robin, nicknamed "Demon Child" (悪魔の子, Akuma no Ko) by the http://anidb.net/ch1974 [World Government] is the 28 years old archeologist of the http://anidb.net/ch1954 [Straw Hat Pirates] Growing up alone on the island Ohara, home of the world`s largest and oldest library, she became an archeologist at age eight and learned how to decipher the writings on the ancient stones called Poneglyph, which are scattered around the world. After the World Government destroyed Ohara for housing archeologists along with her returning mother, http://anidb.net/ch2887 [Nico Olivia], researching these stones, Robin spent twenty years on the run, cooperating with various pirates and other outlaws and became a member of http://anidb.net/ch2939 [Baroque Works] nicknamed as "Ms. All-Sunday"; Ms. Sunday (4Kids dub) at the time, being briefly an antagonist to the Straw Hat Pirates before joining them. Like the scholars of Ohara before her, it is her dream to find and decipher the Rio Poneglyph, which is said to tell the world`s lost history. Her devotion to history and its preservation goes so far that she will even risk her life to protect ancient artefacts and buildings. She ate the Flower-Flower Fruit, allowing her to create copies of any of her body parts on any surface that she can see. However, if her replicated parts are hurt, she feels the pain on her actual body.</description>
<picture>80187.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1900" picture="156922.jpg">Yamaguchi Yuriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="490" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-01-19">
<rating votes="461">6.17</rating>
<name>Franky</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Franky is the shipwright for the http://anidb.net/ch1954 [Straw Hat Pirates]. He is a 34 year old cyborg from Water 7, and was introduced in the story as the leader of the http://anidb.net/ch3252 [Franky Family], a group of ship dismantlers. He is also so far one of the two "true" cyborgs so far shown in the series, with the other being the http://anidb.net/ch2135 [Shichibukai], http://anidb.net/ch3841 [Bartholomew Kuma], and was the first one to be introduced. He was originally named Cutty Flam until he threw away his original name for his nickname per the request by http://anidb.net/ch3264 [Iceburg] to hide his identity. Franky and followers were originally introduced as antagonists of the Water 7 Arc against the Straw Hats until circumstances forced them to become allies. Per the request of the Franky Family, Franky was allowed to join the Straw Hats to fulfill his dream. He is the eighth member of the Straw Hat crew and the seventh to join http://anidb.net/ch474 [Luffy]`s crew. He is also the second member to have been a former villain (the first being http://anidb.net/ch488 [Nico Robin]).</description>
<picture>80182.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="283" picture="17113.jpg">Yao Kazuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="491" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-01-19">
<rating votes="404">5.60</rating>
<name>Brook</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Brook is the musician of the Straw Hat Pirates. He is a skeleton the Straw Hats found on board a ghost ship after drifting into the Florian Triangle. He is a Devil Fruit user who ate the Yomi Yomi no Mi and is an undead being brought back into a pseudo-immortal state because of its powers. He is the ninth member of the Straw Hat crew and the eighth to join Luffy`s crew. He is also one of the two swordsmen onboard their current ship with the other being Zoro. He fills the role of the long awaited musician that Luffy wanted for his crew since his journey began. He has a bounty of 33,000,000 Berry.</description>
<picture>80188.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="694" picture="52187.jpg">Choo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2085" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-04-18">
<rating votes="689">8.50</rating>
<name>Kame Sennin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kame Sennin is an ancient and wise martial arts master and the first Earthling to wield the Kamehameha. Though he seems frail, he is a mighty warrior, having trained Grandpa Gohan, Gyuumaou, Son Gokuu, and others.</description>
<picture>135368.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2279" picture="23207.jpg">Satou Masaharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2103" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-06-16">
<rating votes="2804">8.56</rating>
<name>Son Gokuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Son Gokuu is a Saiyajin warrior who was sent to Earth when he was a child.</description>
<picture>135352.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="386" picture="187997.jpg">Nozawa Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2105" type="cameo appearance in" update="2019-02-25">
<rating votes="1212">8.57</rating>
<name>Vegeta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vegeta is the prince of the Saiyajin race and http://anidb.net/ch2103 [Gokuu]`s most fearsome rival. He is a very prideful person and, as a full-blooded saiyajin, loves the prospect of a good battle.</description>
<picture>230630.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6917" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-04-18">
<rating votes="56">4.03</rating>
<name>Puar</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Puar is a soft-spoken shapeshifting blue creature and the constant companion of Yamcha. He uses his abilities to shapeshift into anything to help Yamcha rob passersby in the desert. Afterwards, he travels with Yamcha and Goku during Dragon Ball, and continues to live with Yamcha afterwards.</description>
<picture>135370.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="9002" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-06-21">
<rating votes="56">7.11</rating>
<name>Super Saiyajin Gokuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>During the events of Dragon Ball Z, Gokuu becomes the first Super Saiyajin in a millennium after being overcome with rage by the murder of Krillin by the hand of Frieza.</description>
<picture>28447.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="386" picture="187997.jpg">Nozawa Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9915" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-04-17">
<rating votes="187">5.58</rating>
<name>Son Gohan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gohan is introduced as the first son of the primary protagonist, Son Goku, and his wife, Chi Chi, in volume #17 of the original manga, or the premiere episode of its animated adaptation, Dragon Ball Z. Gohan is the first Saiyan/Human hybrid in the series.
As opposed to full-blooded Saiyans, whose hair stays the same from birth, Gohan`s is drawn at varying lengths, and changes markedly in style. Many of Yamcha`s hairstyles are used by Gohan at various points in his life.
Initially, Gohan is illustrated garbed in a Hanfu-like surcoat with the Chinese character 孫, fixed on the front and the four-star Dragon Ball fitted on top of his hat. Piccolo later supplies him with a keikogi fashioned after Goku`s, but substitutes it with the demon character "魔" as a sign of his admission into the Demon Tribe. Normally thereafter, Gohan is drawn with a keikogi modeled after Piccolo`s own, with the anime recoloring his wristbands from blue to red and, during the Cell Games tournament, his obi from red to blue, despite reverting to the original colors for the former. On Namek, Gohan is portrayed in battle armor worn by Frieza`s henchmen, having been given it by Vegeta in preparation for their encounter with Frieza. Prior to his second fight with Majin Buu, Gohan asks Kibito for an outfit resembling his father`s, and is then drawn in a keikogi identical to Goku`s.</description>
<picture>135354.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="386" picture="187997.jpg">Nozawa Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11405" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-08-30">
<rating votes="18">6.47</rating>
<name>Bubbles</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bubbles is the monkey pet of Kaiou. He serves a special purpose during Kaiou`s training lessons, particularly one of two endurance tests, where trainees are instructed to chase after Bubbles in an effort to catch him.
His name is a reference to Michael Jackson`s pet monkey, who is also named Bubbles.</description>
<picture>34057.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3998" picture="33313.jpg">Fujimoto Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11407" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-06-16">
<rating votes="37">5.44</rating>
<name>Kaiou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaiou is the kaiou of the northern quadrant of the galaxy. His companion is a pet monkey named http://anidb.net/ch11405 [Bubbles] and in anime adaptation, http://anidb.net/a1530 [Dragon Ball Z], he also has a flying cricket companion named http://anidb.net/ch11406 [Gregory]. If a fighter that was allowed to keep his body manages to reach his small planet at the end of Hebi no Michi (Snake Way in the English adaptations), Kaiou trains them. Before training any students though, he forces them to appeal to his strange sense of humor, catch Bubbles, and hit Gregory with a mallet.</description>
<picture>135374.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3241" picture="24745.jpg">Yanami Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11408" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-04-18">
<rating votes="105">3.10</rating>
<name>Chaozu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chaozu is a small human that resembles a doll with white skin, red cheeks, and one hair under his hat. Though he is not physically strong, he is skilled with psychokinesis and telepathy</description>
<picture>135367.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="11411" type="cameo appearance in" update="2015-02-20">
<rating votes="17">3.43</rating>
<name>Gyuumaou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Despite his threatening sounding name, Ox-King is really quite harmless and fun loving. He was somewhat demonic when his castle became engulfed in flames on Fire Mountain during a picnic with his daughter, and wreaked havoc through the village at the foot of the mountain. He is Chichi`s biological father and thus, Gokuu`s father-in-law. He is very strong and trained alongside Grandpa Gohan under Kame Sennin`s tutelage.</description>
<picture>135372.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="11413" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-02-28">
<rating votes="81">6.86</rating>
<name>Karin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Karin is a Senbyou (immortal cat) and is at least 800 years old when introduced in Dragon Ball. He is a deity who lives at the top of Karin Tower. The tower is located right underneath Kami`s palace.</description>
<picture>34067.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="11416" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-06-16">
<rating votes="557">7.67</rating>
<name>Piccolo</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Piccolo, whose full name is Piccolo Jr., was first introduced as the reincarnation of the evil http://anidb.net/ch22168 [Piccolo Daimaou] in http://anidb.net/a231 [Dragon Ball], making him a demon and arch-rival of the primary protagonist, http://anidb.net/ch2103 [Son Gokuu]. However, it is later revealed that he is from the race of alien beings called Namekians and he decides to team up with http://anidb.net/ch2103 [Gokuu] and his friends in order to beat newer, more dangerous threats.</description>
<picture>135357.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="11417" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="67">6.16</rating>
<name>Mr. Popo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is an immortal genie who tends the grounds of Kami`s Lookout and is bound there eternally as the gardener and caretaker. He uses a magic carpet for Instant Transportation. Though he may not appear to physically age, Mr. Popo is very old; having served Kami, the Guardian of Earth for hundreds of years, he also served Kami`s predecessor, as well as every other guardian of the Earth in the past. Being the loyal and faithful servant that he is, his purpose consists mainly of tending to Kami`s Palace, keeping the Lookout clean, helping to reconstruct Shenron if needed, and most importantly, taking care of Kami. He also tends to the ancient butterfly garden that he planted thousands of years ago, and enjoys the more simple things in life.</description>
<picture>34072.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="11420" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-04-17">
<rating votes="85">5.23</rating>
<name>Tenshinhan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Initially an enemy of Goku who was trained by Kame Sennin`s rival Tsuru Sennin, Tenshinhan soon makes peace with Goku and becomes a Z Fighter along with his friend Chaozu.</description>
<picture>135362.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="11421" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-08-30">
<rating votes="85">5.16</rating>
<name>Yajirobe</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yajirobe is an overweight samurai that Goku meets in Dragon Ball. He is often considered to be rude, unmannered, timid, lazy, and cowardly. He helps Goku prepare for the battle against Piccolo Daimao, and continues to support Goku and his companions, though often from the sideline</description>
<picture>34076.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12210" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-06-21">
<rating votes="108">2.27</rating>
<name>Mr. Satan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mr. Satan (known as Hercule in the English adaptations) is a flamboyant martial artist. After http://anidb.net/ch2103 [Gokuu] and his companions stop attending the Tenkaichi Budoukai, Mr. Satan starts winning them and becomes the reigning champion for many years.
On a Q&amp;A with mangaka http://anidb.net/cr1902 [Toriyama Akira] published in Super Exciting Guide - Character Volume on April 3, 2009, it is revealed that Mr. Satan is just a stage/ring name and that his actual first name is "Mark". While it seems like a common name, it is actually written out in katakana as マーク (maaku). If you rearrange the syllables, as you would with many names in the series to derive their puns, you end up with akuma (meaning "devil" or "demon"), which is in concordance with his daughter`s name being a pun on the English word "devil".
During the Cell Games, he attempts to fight http://anidb.net/ch24822 [Cell], but even after being swatted away, he is given credit for Cell`s death by the media. He is soon called a world hero, gaining great wealth and a city named after him. Though Gokuu and his companions find his inflated ego and arrogance very annoying, he becomes close to them after befriending the good http://anidb.net/ch41758 [Majin Buu] and by helping defeat Kid Buu by using his appeal to the people of Earth to get energy for the Genki Dama. His daughter, http://anidb.net/ch12209 [Videl], marries http://anidb.net/ch9915 [Gohan].</description>
<picture>135363.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18382" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-04-17">
<rating votes="137">4.77</rating>
<name>Trunks</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135355.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="198" picture="202893.jpg">Kusao Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19496" type="main character in" update="2011-06-14">
<rating votes="72">7.09</rating>
<name>Toriko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Gourmet Hunter with an abnormally large appetite (A food serving for 500 people could only get him 1/10 full). He is known as one of the "Four Heavenly Kings", and his nickname is "The Glutton". Despite having a huge appetite and massive power, he doesn`t indiscriminately kill and eat any animal; he only kills those animals he decides to eat. He has immunity to seventy different poisons, created by injecting himself with a near fatal dose of each poison and causing his body to create antibodies. He also has an animal-like sense of smell. He has adopted the Battle Wolf`s new born pup and named it Terry Cloth. Like the other Kings, Toriko started of as a chain animal.</description>
<picture>73363.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19497" type="main character in" update="2011-06-14">
<rating votes="27">3.32</rating>
<name>Komatsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A six-star, (initially five), chef who works for Hotel Gourmet, part of the prestigious IGO (International Gourmet Organization). He is timid, but greatly interested by what he finds in his travels with Toriko. As a result, he tries to overcome his fear and does his best to help. He is a highly skilled and competent chief and has a large knowledge of foods that he knows which foods would work well together. Because he is otherwise normal, he`ll write a will whenever he come along on Toriko`s hunts. Currently, he is the only chef in the world who knows the complete recipe of the Century Soup. He keeps a Wall Penguin as a pet, which is also a key element of the soup.</description>
<picture>73364.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19498" type="appears in" update="2011-06-14">
<rating votes="6">4.45</rating>
<name>Tom</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A ship captain and old friend of Toriko`s, he can tell how much someone weighs the moment they set foot on his ship. He sells ingredients captured by Toriko.</description>
<picture>73370.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="174" picture="41158.jpg">Kakihara Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19619" type="cameo appearance in" update="2016-09-22">
<rating votes="219">7.16</rating>
<name>Jinzouningen 18 Gou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jinzouningen 18 Gou (Android #18 in the English adaptations) is a fictional character who first appears in the Dragon Ball manga created by http://anidb.net/cr1902 [Toriyama Akira], followed by the shows http://anidb.net/a1530 [Dragon Ball Z] and http://anidb.net/a233 [Dragon Ball GT]. She is a mass murderer in http://anidb.net/ch13302 [Future Trunks]` timeline.
Originally a human, she and her brother were modified into cyborgs by http://anidb.net/ch18381 [Dr. Gero].
On a Q&amp;A with mangaka http://anidb.net/cr1902 [Toriyama Akira] published May 2nd, 2014 it was revealed that her human name was Lazuli.
After http://anidb.net/ch20915 [Cell] is defeated, http://anidb.net/ch11414 [Kuririn] uses the Dragon Balls to wish for her and her brother to be turned into humans; http://anidb.net/ch7015 [Shenron] is unable to perform this task because of the unfathomable differences in power between him and the duo, so he wishes instead for their self destruct devices to be removed. Kuririn pursues her and, at some point, they marry and have a daughter named http://anidb.net/ch30874 [Marron].
To clear up the heavily espoused misconception that she is a pure android and therefore could not have a child, Kuririn went on to explain to http://anidb.net/ch2103 [Son Gokuu] during the Tenkaichi Budoukai Saga that she was originally human but that Dr. Gero just "remodeled her a little bit."</description>
<picture>135365.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="229" picture="152363.jpg">Itou Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22251" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-04-17">
<rating votes="169">5.69</rating>
<name>Son Goten</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Goten is first introduced at age 7, basically appearing out of nowhere. He is the second son of Goku and ChiChi, and it is said he was born shortly before Goku died. There is no explanation as to why he was never shown or mentioned earlier.</description>
<picture>135356.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="386" picture="187997.jpg">Nozawa Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25795" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-14">
<rating votes="25">6.96</rating>
<name>Coco</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The "Gentleman" of the "Four Heavenly Kings," he is good friends with Toriko. While Toriko mostly relies on his brute strength, Coco prefers using stealthy techniques and cunning strategy to subdue aggressors. He is also strong defensively. He is immune to five hundred different kinds of poison. He earns most of his living by working as a fortuneteller; his fortunes have a 97% accuracy rating, which also makes him extremely popular with women and as a result he is mobbed by costumers when he is in public. He also has the ability to see non-visible spectrums of light and can read electromagnetic auras in order to predict an animal`s next action. He and the other Four Heavenly Kings were trained by Ichiryuu, the president of the IGO.</description>
<picture>73365.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25797" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-14">
<rating votes="23">5.77</rating>
<name>Sunny</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the "Four Heavenly Kings," he is first shown to have great strength, like Toriko, carrying a Regal Mammoth with one arm (although this was merely a clever trick from using his monstrously strong hair, each one of its strings being strong enough to lift nearly 500 pounds). He is Rin`s older brother. He is a calm and collected pretty boy who judges the beauty of people`s actions and speaks in an elegant, almost flirting manner. He has a way of knocking without touching the target, mostly related to his "sensor" talent which allows him to know the physical state of those around him. His sensor is actually thousand upon thousands of super thin hairs that can reach a maximum of 25 feet (7.6 m) in length. Sani`s body has a very high body temperature and powerful sense of touch, being touched by his hair or any part of his body can only be described as Sani tasting whatever he is touching. He seeks "harmony" in his dishes, defined as the perfect use of ingredients, perfect handling of the food, and most importantly producing the prefect taste. He seems to be slightly in love with Komatsu (or at least his skills since they seem to produce the "harmony" Sani looks for in meals). When he sees Rin his calm personality disappears and is replaced by that of an over-protective older brother, shocked by how much weight she gained from eating too many sweets, leading to a comical sibling spat between them. He also expresses a great sense of disgust towards the Bishoku-kai, displaying anger after seeing the slaughtered creatures with a bite taken out of them that followed a GT Robo`s path of destruction. He and the other Four Heavenly Kings were trained by Ichiryuu, the president of the IGO.</description>
<picture>73369.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="554" picture="244340.jpg">Iwata Mitsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25830" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-14">
<rating votes="17">6.73</rating>
<name>Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A tomboyish pheromone and other odor composition user who acts as a beast handler at the gourmet Coliseum, a fighting ring run by IGO that pits beast against each other to both validate the accuracy of CLVL rankings and as entertainment for world officials, her nickname is "the wild beast tamer." She has a crush on Toriko as shown when she heard he was at the Coliseum she busily began applying makeup. She is the younger sister of one of the Four Heavenly Kings, Sani. She blushes whenever Toriko talks to her (even if he just says her name) or does something kind. She seems to have a weakness for sweets. She is protective of Toriko, as shown when Sani touches his cheek and comments on his skin and Rin gets flustered and tells Sani not to touch Toriko. She also seems to have been implanted with Gourmet Cells.</description>
<picture>73372.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24068" picture="224929.jpg">Tano Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25831" type="appears in" update="2011-08-18">
<rating votes="2">8.72</rating>
<name>Mansam</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>IGO`s Development Bureau Director and Gourmet Research Facility Chief, he holds IGO`s third position, with authority below the CEO and President. He is an old friend of Toriko`s and has the same body type. He runs IGO`s Garden One, a facility where 30% of the world`s gourmet foods are made. It also clones long extinct animals and performs selective breeding. He has an incredibly high pain tolerance, able to live through being stabbed in the gut and a hole blown through his throat, and he heals himself by drinking alcohol. He appears to be able to use the same muscle enhancing abilities that Jirou the Knocking master uses. When someone says his name he thinks they are calling him handsome; this is a pun as his name sounds similar to the English word "handsome." He seems to be always drunk or just in a really happy state most of the time, only when someone mentions a job that needs doing or when he is gets angry does he change to a more serious manner.</description>
<picture>46478.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25833" type="appears in" update="2011-08-23">
<name>Zonge</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A very arrogant and annoying Gourmet Hunter who wields a large axe to hunt. He is very self-centered and boasts about his completed full course menu which is made of dishes that probably don`t have a capture level of more than three, the only really dangerous dish being Garara Gator he had just killed (it was also a newborn making it no where near as strong or as tasty as the one Toriko fought). Despite all his boasting he is a very big coward using other as shields and making excuses when confront by a beast he can`t take down.</description>
<picture>48734.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25834" type="appears in" update="2011-08-18">
<rating votes="2">7.25</rating>
<name>Terry Cloth</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A newborn Battle Wolf pup that has been adopted by Toriko, it sees Toriko as a parental figure, a big surprise since Battle Wolves never become attached to humans. Terry got his name from how Toriko described his fur. Only few foods suit its taste, such as Gourmet World`s foods.</description>
<picture>46470.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="29692" type="appears in" update="2011-08-18">
<name>Stajun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vice Head Chef of the Bishoku-kai, has a currently unexplained ability to roast things by touching them. His name is sometimes pronounced Star-Jun, he is not one to mince words and will admit his mistakes. He appears to be noble, or at least respectful to those he considers strong, since in his fight with Toriko he set the GT Robo`s pain sensors to 100% to test and feel Toriko`s maximum power. Later he claims that it would be difficult to not test Toriko. He has a habit of scratching his head with one finger. He is one of the few Bishoku-kai members that Alfaro says are capable of entering the Gourmet World.</description>
<picture>46477.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29693" type="appears in" update="2011-09-05">
<name>Grinpatch</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vice Head Chef of the Bishoku-kai. He can suck up large amounts of food with his giant straw and has an extra pair of arms. He has the same eyes as Kuromado and Yuu except he has three pupils in each eye instead of just one. For transportation and food collection, he has a pet Jack Elephant (CLVL 85), which is large and strong enough to cut down an entire ear of BB Corn and carry it. He seems to be very lazy as he does not fulfill his mission of retrieving the GT Robos because he does not feel like fighting the Gourmet Association`s second and third. Another example of his laziness is that he does not finish the full names of places and things, calling the Regal Plateau the "Regal-whatever" and the Devil`s Athletics the "Athletics-looking place." He agrees with Stajun that it is hard to not test Toriko`s strength. He is one of the few Bishoku-kai members that Alfaro says are capable of entering the Gourmet World.</description>
<picture>52296.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3270" picture="30153.jpg">Mitsuya Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29694" type="appears in" update="2012-01-05">
<name>Tommyrod</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vice Head Chef of the Bishoku-kai. Having a bug-like appearance, complete with wings, Tommy raises "parasite bugs" inside his body and can spew them out at will. His lack of emotion allows him to fight at complete efficiency, focusing solely on the goal at hand. It is also revealed that his armbands allow him to limit his strength. He is the first Bishoku-kai to seriously fight Toriko head-to-head (without using a GT Robo) with the intent to kill him. He is one of the few Bishoku-kai members that Alfaro says are capable of entering the Gourmet World.</description>
<picture>79492.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29695" type="appears in" update="2011-08-18">
<name>Joejoe</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An old man in a black robe who works for the Bishoku-kai and monitors the GT Robos for them. He also appears to be the one who made Grinpatch`s Straw. His mouth is stitched closed.</description>
<picture>46509.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="199" picture="23218.jpg">Shimada Bin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29696" type="appears in" update="2011-08-18">
<rating votes="2">8.26</rating>
<name>Jirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Known as the Knocking Master, he is a legendary retired Gourmet Hunter and master of Knocking. He is able to Knock to not only stun animals but expand his muscular size to become a giant, and to revive the recently deceased. He is old and a heavy drinker; when introduced he asked Toriko for some sake. As a Bishoku-ya, the chef he was paired with as a combo was the legendary chef and Gourmet Living Treasure Setsuno. Jirou is also the discoverer of the original Century Soup in Ice Hell. He is the grandfather of the famous Saiseya Teppei, who has also inherited his grandfather`s Knocking talent. Seeing his grandfather`s emotional reaction to seeing certain Gourmet ingredients depleted is also what inspired Teppei to become a Saiseya instead of a Bishoku-kai. He is one of the three disciples of the legendary Bishoku-ya, Acacia, along with Ichiryuu and the boss of the Bishoku-kai, of the three he is the only one that does not the head of an organization, as well as being the only one in retirement.</description>
<picture>46495.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29697" type="appears in" update="2011-10-01">
<name>IGO</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The International Gourmet Organization, a group in charge of creation and development of new foods and flavors. They responsible for mainting order in the Gourmet age, and defending civilians against dangerous animals and gourmet criminals. They are shown to hold more weight than the United Nations and have many well renown members in the organization.</description>
<picture>61888.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="29698" type="appears in" update="2011-10-01">
<name>Bishoku-kai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Bishoku-kai (literally: Beautiful Food Organization), a rival organization to the IGO, their headquarters are Castle Shokuyokubou (Appetite`s Desire) located in the Forest of Sorrow, "Thorn Wood."</description>
<picture>61889.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="29699" type="appears in" update="2011-05-08">
<name>GT Robo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Gourmet Telexistence Robot (a.k.a GT Robo) is a type of robot used mainly by the Bishokukai. The operator can control the movements of the robot from far away and the robot transmits back the senses of sight, touch, hearing, smell and sometimes taste.</description>
<picture>71198.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="29700" type="appears in" update="2012-03-01">
<rating votes="3">9.07</rating>
<name>Ichiryuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The President of IGO, he has the appearance of an old man with dark skin and white hair, along with a long white mustache. Despite his old age, he is not yet retired, although seems to vacation frequently, spending time on a private island resort. Ichiryuu used to be a very powerful Bishoku-ya and is one of the three disciples of the legendary Bishoku-ya, Acacia, along with Jirou and the boss of the Bishoku-kai. Even in his old age, he is powerful and can defeat Toriko effortlessly in a fight and perform inhuman actions, such as running on water. He appears to have strange mannerisms, like eating the cork of a bottle of liquor, and making the names of dishes Toriko collects. He trains all of the Four Heavenly Kings since their childhood.</description>
<picture>82619.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29701" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-05-28">
<rating votes="14">6.98</rating>
<name>Zebra</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Described by Toriko as the most powerful of the "Four Heavenly Kings" for his pure destructive capabilities, Zebra is a very large and well-built man with scars that cover most of his body, one of the more striking ones being the half Glasgow smile on the left side of his face. His personality is very angry and small-tempered, he enjoys fighting the most out of all the Heavenly Kings and has a self-professed hatred for anyone or anything acting "cocky". He is incredibly strong, having single handily caused all the scars on Match`s body, killing dozens of prisoners in "Honey Prison" in the matter of minutes, and destroying many beasts with a capture level above 60, including the Magma Tortoise (CLV 70). He is held in "Honey Prison". He and the other Four Heavenly Kings were trained by Ichiryuu, the president of the IGO.</description>
<picture>88638.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34211" picture="126923.jpg">Matsuda Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29702" type="appears in" update="2013-03-29">
<rating votes="3">7.47</rating>
<name>Midora</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The leader of the Bishoku-kai who has so far only been shown as a silhouette with very long, dark hair. He is extremely powerful and has an insatiable appetite, which Kuromado and Alfaro both comment on.</description>
<picture>134411.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3185" picture="171529.jpg">Terasoma Masaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29703" type="appears in" update="2011-08-29">
<name>Acacia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The greatest Bishoku-ya in human history, he discovered countless ingredients all over the world, including the Phantom Jellyfish from which he discovered the Gourmet Cells, and is the first and only person to find the ingredient GOD. Using GOD, he manages to end a centuries-long war between all the nations of the world, and bring about the current Gourmet Age. Acacia took three disciples: Ichiryuu, the current president of the IGO, the "Knocking Master" Jirou, and the boss of the Bishoku-kai. Little else is known about Acacia, but he seems to have formed a combo with the chef Frohze.</description>
<picture>50476.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1733" picture="25839.jpg">Tanaka Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30015" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-14">
<rating votes="13">4.84</rating>
<name>Tina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tina is a television reporter who appears in the anime series. She is also the news anchor for Gourmet News.</description>
<picture>73371.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31080" type="appears in" update="2012-02-29">
<rating votes="3">7.04</rating>
<name>Teppei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A top level Saiseiya, Teppei is a considered an expert Knocker, able to deal with numerous hybrid insects birthed by Tommyrod as well as the Bishoku-kai Vice Chef himself. Teppei has been under the tutelage of the "Knocking Master" Jirou (his relative), the fruits of which are shown through his adept Knocking ability as well as his pompadour. Teppei also carries with him supplies such as Forest Seeds and liquids capable of instantly growing these sturdy plants.</description>
<picture>82528.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="183" picture="16992.jpg">Onosaka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31081" type="appears in" update="2012-05-28">
<name>Alfaro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The waiter (Garcon) of the Bishoku-kai and Kuromado`s personal aide. He has a very large nose and eight arms, giving him the appearance of a spider. He also has been seen to resist the intense cold of Ice Hell while wearing just a tuxedo and cape. His attacks are all based on the plates he keeps hidden in his tuxedo. He is one of the few Bishoku-kai members capable of entering the Gourmet World.</description>
<picture>88637.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="469" picture="17418.jpg">Umezu Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31341" type="appears in" update="2011-08-18">
<name>Johannes</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>IGO Development Office, Food Development Manager.</description>
<picture>46491.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="60" picture="171602.jpg">Kawada Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32296" type="appears in" update="2011-09-18">
<name>Uumen Umeda</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>IGO Business Bureau Director</description>
<picture>56817.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32297" type="appears in" update="2011-05-15">
<name>Wain</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>IGO Administration Bureau Director</description>
<picture>71581.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2501" picture="191381.jpg">Yoshikai Kiyohito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32298" type="appears in" update="2011-05-15">
<name>Gras</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>IGO Judicial Affairs Bureau Director</description>
<picture>71582.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20286" picture="52973.jpg">Koike Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32299" type="appears in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="1">7.76</rating>
<name>Sedoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Sixth Branch Chef, the operator of the GT Robo that Sani defeats. He uses the skulls of animals as shoulder pads and has some kind of interest with eyeballs since he wears a necklace of them, which he collects from the animals he kills and throws them away when they rot and stop moving.</description>
<picture>54740.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="399" picture="17244.jpg">Suyama Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32300" type="appears in" update="2011-09-26">
<name>Gido</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gido is from Bishokukai and was one of the main antagonists of the Regal Mammoth Arc. He is never actually seen in person as throughout the story he was piloting a GT Robo and only his voice was heard.</description>
<picture>60031.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32301" type="appears in" update="2011-09-26">
<name>Bei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The man responsible for the GT Robo attacks. Mansam seems to know him. A member of the Bishoku-kai, Stajun claims he has bad taste. He looks like a sort of goblin, and is a major glutton.</description>
<picture>60028.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="340" picture="17176.jpg">Yabe Masahito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32302" type="appears in" update="2011-05-15">
<name>Buru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>IGO Financial Affairs Bureau Director</description>
<picture>71583.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="32303" type="appears in" update="2011-05-15">
<name>Naroid</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>IGO Public Relations Bureau Director</description>
<picture>71584.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="32304" type="appears in" update="2011-05-15">
<name>Director</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71585.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10401" picture="38335.jpg">Kojima Kazunari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32305" type="appears in" update="2011-08-18">
<name>Kruppou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kruppou is Tina`s Carrier Balloon Pigeon and her constant companion when doing outdoor news.</description>
<picture>46469.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3132" picture="223652.jpg">Kikuchi Kokoro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32306" type="appears in" update="2011-05-15">
<name>Manager</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71587.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="468" picture="17383.jpg">Kikuchi Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32307" type="appears in" update="2011-05-15">
<name>Keeper</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71588.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3395" picture="24474.jpg">Sonobe Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32312" type="appears in" update="2011-05-15">
<name>Market Man</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71594.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3801" picture="171533.jpg">Sakamaki Manabu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32313" type="appears in" update="2011-05-15">
<name>Guard</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71595.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29680" picture="78339.jpg">Ise Fumihide</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32314" type="appears in" update="2011-05-15">
<name>Teshita A</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71596.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10772" picture="38752.jpg">Shirakawa Shuusaku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32315" type="appears in" update="2011-05-15">
<name>Teshita B</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71597.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3801" picture="171533.jpg">Sakamaki Manabu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32316" type="appears in" update="2011-05-15">
<name>Bishokuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71598.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12575" picture="203221.jpg">Watanabe Hideo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32902" type="appears in" update="2011-05-29">
<name>Marilyn</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gourmet Coliseum Commander-in-Chief</description>
<picture>72504.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2230" picture="21782.jpg">Iwasaki Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33063" type="appears in" update="2011-09-26">
<name>Zaipa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60032.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9912" picture="65378.jpg">Oobayashi Youhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34417" type="appears in" update="2011-08-23">
<name>Kiss</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kiss is said to be the last remaining Emperor Crow and lives with Coco. He considers him family, having raised him from an egg. Though the species is classified as extinct, rumors still circulate that somewhere in this vast Gourmet World they live on.</description>
<picture>48693.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35076" type="appears in" update="2011-08-29">
<name>Shigematsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Vice-President of IGO, he is a very large, muscular man with a big, black beard and mustache and thick, black hair with a stripe of white hair down the middle. He keeps one eye closed at all times, as well as a nose plug over the bridge of his nose. When these are removed, which he does when preparing to fight Grinpatch, he becomes more beastly and his muscles bulge and his clothes begin to tear. When Grinpatch comes to the First Biotope, he is disappointed that Stajun or Tommyrod had not come, showing not only his delight in fighting, but also his knowledge of the Bishoku-kai.</description>
<picture>50481.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="67" picture="25195.jpg">Ishii Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36323" type="appears in" update="2011-09-12">
<name>Kuromado</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Head Chef of the Bishoku-kai, he has black eyes with white pupils, a thin yet long mustache, and he wears a black chef`s uniform with a very tall, black chef`s hat. He is one of the few Bishoku-kai members that Alfaro says are capable of entering the Gourmet World.</description>
<picture>54739.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3094" picture="50367.jpg">Kanao Tetsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36324" type="appears in" update="2012-05-28">
<name>Yuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Second Branch Chef, he has the same kind of eyes as Kuromado, dresses in renaissance-like clothes, and is somewhat of a blond pretty boy. He appears to be the politest of the Chefs. He is the only member of the Bishoku-kai to be able to pilot the "Micro-Model" GT Robo, for unknown reasons. With this GT Robo, he attacks and incapacitates Komatsu and is able to take the last bits of Century Soup that he collected away.</description>
<picture>88636.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="612" picture="79531.jpg">Maeno Tomoaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36325" type="appears in" update="2011-09-04">
<name>Jerry Boy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Third Branch Chef, a tan blond man who greatly resembles Toriko in appearance and clothes, save for his fanged teeth and his veins that show from his nose to his forehead as well as extended earlobes with multiple piercings.</description>
<picture>51768.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12637" picture="130507.jpg">Takahashi Hidenori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36326" type="appears in" update="2012-01-05">
<name>Barrygamon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Fourth Branch Chef, a stocky, bearded man with protruding tusks. He wears very little clothing, even in frigid conditions, and displays incredible resilience to these temperatures. The Fourth Branch is the cookware supply team for the Bishoku-kai, which explains Barry`s unique armor: made from the shell of the Crush Turtle, a level 60 beast. This shell is several times superior to steel, and is also used by master craftsmen to manufacture the best pans and utensils in the gourmet world. He also produces naturally occurring antifreeze, allowing him to survive arctic conditions and use the same slick to deflect gunfire. It is shown he also has very effective healing abilities, after being cut several times by Match his organs are able to paste themselves back together until he is fully healed.</description>
<picture>79490.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2586" picture="233442.jpg">Kimura Masafumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36327" type="appears in" update="2012-01-05">
<rating votes="1">4.46</rating>
<name>Bogie Woods</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Fifth Branch Chef, he wears a jogging suit, sport shades, and some kind of shell with a mask made from the body of an IGO agent that he used his ability on. He has approximately 4,000 bones and 4,600 joints, which he can easily detach and manipulate to allow him complete mobility and flexibility. He uses this quirk for his Lodge, a technique which allows him to inhabit another creature, assuming its form. Even if his bones are broken and removed, he can manipulate the rest of his unnatural capacity to compensate, barring the sacrum. However, even if the sacrum would happen to be removed or dislocated, his body will adjust in time and repair the nervous system, this process takes time but will be fully healed afterwards.</description>
<picture>79491.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2796" picture="23212.jpg">Takemoto Eiji</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="12646" picture="155098.jpg">Nakaya Kazuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36328" type="appears in" update="2011-09-18">
<rating votes="3">6.99</rating>
<name>Setsuno</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Gourmet Living National Treasure, Setsuno is Jirou`s long-time partner, and has the same Full-Course Meal as him. She has the skill and capability of easily doing the work of eight top-level chefs. Setsuno attempts to recreate the legendary Century Soup Jirou gave to her at some point; however, it is incomplete and she requests Toriko and Komatsu to find the missing ingredient after being impressed by their relationship and strong knowledge and respect of the gourmet ingredients. Although an old woman, she still has incredible power, breaking all of Alfaro`s Plate Shuriken from far away without seeming to move, and is one of the few people brave enough to call the Bishoku-kai boss an "idiot." However, she has still lost some of her power since her early days, losing some of her ability to let her Gourmet Cells "adapt." This is characterized by her having "White Breath" in Ice Hell, meaning her Cells did not adapt to the cold environment and warm her body accordingly. Melk the First said that the knife of Setsuno is one of the few knives he got a shock from after seeing.</description>
<picture>56802.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1827" picture="55501.jpg">Uran Sakiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36378" type="appears in" update="2011-09-05">
<name>Dohem</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is President of the Republic of Roto and a member of the National Security Council.</description>
<picture>52293.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1683" picture="223030.jpg">Kanemitsu Nobuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36642" type="appears in" update="2011-09-26">
<name>Colonel Mokkoi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is very rich man and President of Company Gourdarake.</description>
<picture>60023.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4731" picture="27599.jpg">Saitou Shirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36713" type="appears in" update="2012-01-05">
<rating votes="1">4.40</rating>
<name>Takimaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A new member of Gourmet Knights and highly skilled in martial arts, he joins Toriko`s party as they enter the Ice Hell in search of Century Soup, as he needs money to buy medicine for Aimaru. There he faces off against Bogie Woods. He once suffers a disease from the Gourmet World, which are referred to as curses because known science has no cure for them. Aimaru consumes the disease and leaves only one of his eyes infected, at great personal expense.</description>
<picture>79498.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="367" picture="17213.jpg">Kenn</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36714" type="appears in" update="2012-07-12">
<rating votes="1">7.76</rating>
<name>Aimaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leader of the Gourmet Knights, nothing more is known except that he is afflicted with an illness that he gained from Takimaru when he tries to cure him of a disease from the Gourmet World. He is capable of eating bacteria and viruses, which enables him to devour diseases. He is one of Toriko`s old friends and they have a friendly rivalry to see who can obtain GOD first.</description>
<picture>79496.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36715" type="appears in" update="2013-06-30">
<name>Ryuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The boss of the Gourmet Yakuza, not much is known about him other than he is a good friend of Yosaku and that he has never been arrested.</description>
<picture>139319.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="36716" type="appears in" update="2012-01-05">
<rating votes="2">5.32</rating>
<name>Match</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vice Boss of the Gourmet Yakuza, he is completely covered in scars received at the hands of Zebra of the Four Heavenly Kings. He wields a single sword and is adept in the art of Iai, unsheathing, striking and sheathing the sword in a single movement. His ability allows his strength to be proportionate to his exhaustion, so the more tired he is, the more powerful he becomes. The sword he uses is made from a fang of the king of aquatic dragons, the Leodragon. This beast hunts and is capable of crushing the shell of a Crush Turtle with its jaws. Match takes advantage of this fact to cut through Barrygamon`s armor made of the same shell.</description>
<picture>79497.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36717" type="appears in" update="2012-02-29">
<rating votes="1">5.89</rating>
<name>Yosaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An expert Saiseiya and Teppei`s master. He is nicknamed "Blood-stained Yosaku" due to his seemingly brutal methods of healing. He wears a blood-soaked doctor`s coat (befitting to his nickname), a black bandanna worn over his hair and is always seen smoking a cigar branch. He hates following rules of any kind, be it simple rules such as to not smoke in a restaurant or go against rules of life itself. He has been described as a very strong person able to take down one of the Four Heavenly Kings, with Teppei`s assistance (though Teppei notes that Yosaku had fully restrained him), a testament to his power. Despite his rough appearance he is a master in healing. He has been to the Gourmet World and knows the location of the dessert Sunny is looking for, EARTH.</description>
<picture>82529.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2782" picture="23189.jpg">Ginga Banjou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36718" type="appears in" update="2011-09-14">
<name>Gourmet Knights</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Gourmet Knights follow "gourmet doctrine": to entrust one`s life completely to nature. This means shunning man-made medicines.</description>
</character>
<character id="36719" type="appears in" update="2011-09-14">
<name>Gourmet Yakuza</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>An organization much hated by the constitutional countries, seemingly made up completely of orphans and slum dogs from the crime slum Nerg, a non-IGO affiliated city. 10% of the prisoners in Gourmet Prison come from this city, giving it the nickname "Criminal-Producing Factory." The Yakuza, seemingly altruistic, are told by the Boss upon joining to repay their debt not to him, but to the "hungry children of the slums."</description>
</character>
<character id="36720" type="appears in" update="2011-09-14">
<name>Saisei-ya</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Saisei-ya are a gourmet police, given the power of judgment to arrest anyone dealing with illegal gourmet products, in both procurement and black market trading. Their powers also extend to those who break the law by over-fishing and poaching certain species.</description>
</character>
<character id="37033" type="appears in" update="2011-09-26">
<name>Morijii</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Morijii is the owner of the Bar Heavy Lodge located in Gourmet Town, where many Bishoku-ya gather and look for work. He`s got discerning eyes that can see through a Bishoku-ya to know his true power and talent.</description>
<picture>60029.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1987" picture="225435.jpg">Egawa Hisao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37034" type="appears in" update="2012-01-05">
<name>Drunker</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Drunker is Eating Champion of the Southern Islands. He goes with other Bishoku-ya to Ice Hell, seeking the Century Soup.</description>
<picture>79495.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3186" picture="171957.jpg">Tone Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37035" type="appears in" update="2012-01-05">
<name>Brubo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Brubo is Gourmet Bounty Hunter and seems to have a good Full Course Menu, but is not hired because of his temperament. He goes with other Bishoku-ya to Ice Hell, seeking the Century Soup.</description>
<picture>79493.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="37036" type="appears in" update="2012-05-28">
<name>Ram</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the subordinates of Match.</description>
<picture>88642.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9912" picture="65378.jpg">Oobayashi Youhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37037" type="appears in" update="2012-05-28">
<name>Shin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the subordinates of Match.</description>
<picture>88640.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10772" picture="38752.jpg">Shirakawa Shuusaku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37038" type="appears in" update="2012-05-28">
<name>Louis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the subordinates of Match.</description>
<picture>88641.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3801" picture="171533.jpg">Sakamaki Manabu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37949" type="appears in" update="2012-03-28">
<name>Yun</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Baby Wall Penguin which was found by Komatsu in Ice Hell. When Komatsu first found it he hoped to return it to its parents, however they were horribly killed by the Tommyrod and was left orphaned, however Komatsu decided to adopt the little guy and keep it as a pet. Later he names him Yun.</description>
<picture>71767.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="553" picture="170553.jpg">Kaneda Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37950" type="appears in" update="2012-05-28">
<name>Ricky</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ricky is a large Hayanpanther Mansam keeps as a pet. Ricky is surprisingly obedient to Mansam. Ricky`s favorite food is Horohoro Parfait. Its capture level is 35 and lives at the 1st Biotope.</description>
<picture>88639.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40692" type="appears in" update="2012-01-18">
<name>Gourmet 7</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Gourmet Seven are seven "Taste Masters" chosen from the chief member nations of the IGO. They are an organization of members who hold a miraculous sense of taste, said to be able to recognize the taste of a single grain of sugar in a twenty-five meter pool. They take part in important decisions of the Gourmet Age, such as assigning the number of stars to hotels and restaurants, and the rank of cooks, these important people also serve as inspectors for the IGO.</description>
</character>
<character id="40693" type="appears in" update="2012-10-25">
<name>Patch</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>127197.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="469" picture="17418.jpg">Umezu Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40694" type="appears in" update="2014-01-04">
<name>Elg</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The First Branch Chef. According to Alfaro, Elg is capable of entering Gourmet World. Not much is know about him, except he seems to be centaur (it is unknown if it`s natural or body modification).</description>
<picture>148129.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52" picture="19811.jpg">Takahashi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40695" type="appears in" update="2014-01-04">
<name>Limon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Not much is known about her, except she is the Sommelier of Bishokukai and is capable of entering Gourmet World according of Alfaro.</description>
<picture>148128.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40932" type="appears in" update="2012-02-29">
<name>Bono</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>82525.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="81" picture="41282.jpg">Sanpei Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41758" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-04-18">
<rating votes="46">6.05</rating>
<name>Majin Buu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135364.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="41938" type="appears in" update="2012-03-02">
<name>Smile</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Smile is a top class Gourmet Architect. He is famous for designing the Gourmet Tower. Despite his name, he is a man who rarely smiles and finds very little happiness in his stressful life. He is also the architect of Toriko`s Sweets Houses.</description>
<picture>82685.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="592" picture="170729.jpg">Tsuda Kenjirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42061" type="appears in" update="2012-03-04">
<name>Tacchino Kawagoe</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>82877.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41709" picture="10221.jpeg">Kawagoe Tatsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43508" type="appears in" update="2012-05-28">
<rating votes="2">7.49</rating>
<name>Melk (Nidaime)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Melk the Second is the adopted daughter of the famous knife sharpener, Melk the First. She took the title of The Second, after Melk the First decided to retire and focus on making the knife that Ichiryuu requested.</description>
<picture>88635.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43509" type="appears in" update="2012-05-28">
<rating votes="1">8.72</rating>
<name>Melk (Shodai)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Melk is the most famous knife sharpener in the world. He was previously known as the "Demon Gourmet" for his great strength and intimidating appearance. Living and working as a hermit atop his mountain, Melk raised an orphaned girl as his daughter and apprentice, who later took on the mantle of Melk the Second. It`s believed he is shy and silent, but in reality his voice is so tiny, that most people can`t hear him and he thinks he gets ignored.</description>
<picture>88634.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2340" picture="151335.jpg">Naka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45286" type="appears in" update="2012-06-04">
<name>Love</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Love is the warden of Honey Prison. Her body is able to produce a large amount of pheromones that she uses to control prisoners and execution beasts. The only person her pheromones do not work on is Zebra, against whose discharge she objected because she has a crush on him.</description>
<picture>88968.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="291" picture="17122.jpg">Matsui Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45288" type="appears in" update="2012-05-27">
<name>Honey Prison</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The largest land-based prison located in the Human World and is one of the Three Great Gourmet Prisons. It houses over 100,000 A-class criminals who violated the IGO laws and hangs from a cliff behind the Gates of the Underworld. The Prison is administered by the IGO Legal Affairs Bureau.</description>
<picture>88548.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="45289" type="appears in" update="2012-06-04">
<name>Ouban</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ouban is the Assistant Warden of Honey Prison.</description>
<picture>88967.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="177" picture="170981.jpg">Hoshino Takanori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45290" type="appears in" update="2012-05-27">
<name>Chupaly</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chupaly is the receptionist at Honey Prison.</description>
<picture>88550.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23806" picture="66170.jpg">Shimada Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45291" type="appears in" update="2012-05-27">
<name>Pricom</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pricom is the Captain of the Guard and a commanding officer stationed at Honey Prison.</description>
<picture>88551.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2230" picture="21782.jpg">Iwasaki Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45292" type="appears in" update="2012-05-27">
<name>Elbou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Elbou is an officer of IGO`s Bureau of Defense and the Surveillance Chief of the 18th Barrier entrance to the Gourmet World.</description>
<picture>88552.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4706" picture="171561.jpg">Takaguchi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45561" type="appears in" update="2012-06-04">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Love</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pheromone form.</description>
<picture>88969.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="291" picture="17122.jpg">Matsui Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47751" type="appears in" update="2012-08-28">
<name>Rapp</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93130.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10750" picture="186166.jpg">Takeuchi Ryouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47752" type="appears in" update="2012-08-28">
<name>Rei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rei is the IGO Defense Chief. He is one of the higher-ups within the IGO, shown from the fact that he both knows of the existence of the 0th Biotope and can command its staff.</description>
<picture>93129.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2090" picture="151718.jpg">Toochika Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47753" type="appears in" update="2013-06-30">
<name>0th Biotope</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Unlike the rest of IGO`s Biotopes, the 0th Biotope is located in the Gourmet World and its existence is a secret from the world at large. It is located on the Cloud Tree in Gourmet World. Curently its members are either trying to locate or prepare Acacia`s Full Course Menu, or preparing for a possible war against the Bishokukai.
It is also unusual in that its staff, who number less than 20, are not IGO employees, but are all private citizens who have other professions when not at the Biotope. They are called "the best of the best," and are all chosen by the IGO president, Ichiryuu.</description>
<picture>139332.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="47912" type="appears in" update="2012-08-28">
<name>Kumin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93128.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1663" picture="23213.jpg">Takato Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47913" type="appears in" update="2012-08-28">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Safura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93127.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1932" picture="65403.jpg">Sendai Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47914" type="appears in" update="2012-08-19">
<name>Ryoutei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92644.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47915" type="appears in" update="2012-08-19">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Koryou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92645.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48432" type="appears in" update="2012-09-30">
<name>Meria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Meria is the owner of Bar Meria. She is never seen in person as she uses a GT Robo to run her bar which is located in the dangerous region.</description>
<picture>48779.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2972" picture="186915.jpg">Nagano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48433" type="appears in" update="2012-10-25">
<name>Guemon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Guemon, also known as the "Gourmet Gang Leader," is a member of the 0th Biotope. He spends most of his time guarding the Wak Continent`s Three-Way Road, one of the few entrances to the Gourmet World from the Human World.</description>
<picture>127196.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4841" picture="55063.jpg">Iwasaki Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48434" type="appears in" update="2013-07-19">
<rating votes="1">1.67</rating>
<name>Starjun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vice Head Chef of the Bishoku-kai, has a currently unexplained ability to roast things by touching them. His name is sometimes pronounced Star-Jun, he is not one to mince words and will admit his mistakes. He appears to be noble, or at least respectful to those he considers strong, since in his fight with Toriko he set the GT Robo`s pain sensors to 100% to test and feel Toriko`s maximum power. Later he claims that it would be difficult to not test Toriko. He has a habit of scratching his head with one finger. He is one of the few Bishoku-kai members that Alfaro says are capable of entering the Gourmet World.</description>
<picture>140214.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49271" type="appears in" update="2012-09-23">
<name>Tsurara Mama</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94802.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2089" picture="151696.jpg">Morota Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49272" type="appears in" update="2012-09-30">
<name>Apollon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48778.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2230" picture="21782.jpg">Iwasaki Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49512" type="appears in" update="2012-10-09">
<name>Quin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Quin is a Mother Snake and Sunny`s animal partner. She is a juvenile Mother Snake who was tamed by Sunny during a trip to the Gourmet World. An adult Mother Snake is said to be around the Circumference of the Earth, but since Quin is still a child, her length is only 25km right now and with weight of 50,000t.</description>
<picture>126387.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49513" type="appears in" update="2012-09-30">
<name>Yocchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48900.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3280" picture="24278.jpg">Ishida Tarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49514" type="appears in" update="2012-09-30">
<name>Papo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49083.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3395" picture="24474.jpg">Sonobe Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49516" type="appears in" update="2012-09-30">
<name>Smith</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49192.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3186" picture="171957.jpg">Tone Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49517" type="appears in" update="2012-09-30">
<name>Nitro</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nitro are humanoid creatures with a bird-like face that possess incredible physical abilities and high intelligence. According to Chief Mansam the Nitro know how to obtain "GOD", and it is said that Acacia discovered GOD by observing the Nitro. Bishokukai`s GT Robos are based on the looks of this creature.</description>
<picture>49567.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="50830" type="appears in" update="2012-11-28">
<name>Ootake</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128726.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1925" picture="21115.jpg">Yuuki Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50831" type="appears in" update="2012-11-28">
<name>Niceny</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128727.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2231" picture="235895.jpg">Kusunoki Taiten</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51030" type="appears in" update="2013-05-05">
<name>Chiru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128968.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3382" picture="24410.jpg">Fuchizaki Yuriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51031" type="appears in" update="2012-12-02">
<name>Damala Sky the XIII</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128970.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9114" picture="201075.jpg">Kikumoto Taira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51032" type="appears in" update="2012-12-02">
<name>Sumire</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128971.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="553" picture="170553.jpg">Kaneda Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52048" type="appears in" update="2013-01-21">
<name>Livebearer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Livebearer is the boss of the Underground Cooking World and theowner of Gourmet Casino. He is one of the top 100 chefs in the world, holding the 17th spot on the IGO Chef Ranking.</description>
<picture>131144.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54455" type="appears in" update="2013-03-29">
<name>Kaitora</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134418.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10772" picture="38752.jpg">Shirakawa Shuusaku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54456" type="appears in" update="2013-03-29">
<name>Dores</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134419.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3395" picture="24474.jpg">Sonobe Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54457" type="appears in" update="2013-03-29">
<name>Bile</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134420.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5021" picture="188516.jpg">Taki Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54458" type="appears in" update="2013-03-29">
<rating votes="3">5.95</rating>
<name>Nono</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134421.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3132" picture="223652.jpg">Kikuchi Kokoro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54459" type="appears in" update="2014-03-29">
<name>Joa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152479.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3282" picture="24710.jpg">Nanba Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54460" type="appears in" update="2013-03-29">
<name>Darnil Khan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134423.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55086" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-04-17">
<rating votes="2">1.50</rating>
<name>Yamucha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135361.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="55095" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-04-18">
<rating votes="8">2.22</rating>
<name>Marron</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135382.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="57295" type="appears in" update="2013-06-20">
<name>Monchy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138761.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2016" picture="240331.jpg">Yanaka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57296" type="appears in" update="2013-06-20">
<name>Akimaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138762.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9114" picture="201075.jpg">Kikumoto Taira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57297" type="appears in" update="2013-06-20">
<name>Tsukimaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138763.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32333" picture="131863.jpg">Kanemoto Ryousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57298" type="appears in" update="2013-06-20">
<name>Raimaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138765.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2071" picture="74324.jpg">Oohata Shintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57299" type="appears in" update="2013-06-20">
<name>Kagemaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138766.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12637" picture="130507.jpg">Takahashi Hidenori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57300" type="appears in" update="2013-06-20">
<name>Yukimaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138767.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10772" picture="38752.jpg">Shirakawa Shuusaku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57301" type="appears in" update="2013-06-20">
<name>Nonchy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138768.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2016" picture="240331.jpg">Yanaka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57302" type="appears in" update="2013-06-20">
<name>Chirin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138769.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="140" picture="170306.jpg">Noda Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57303" type="appears in" update="2013-06-20">
<rating votes="1">4.40</rating>
<name>Chin Chinchin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138770.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2026" picture="21352.jpg">Yara Yuusaku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57304" type="appears in" update="2013-06-20">
<name>Shuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138771.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="375" picture="17221.jpg">Chiba Susumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57305" type="appears in" update="2013-06-20">
<name>Koppowo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138772.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3395" picture="24474.jpg">Sonobe Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57306" type="appears in" update="2013-06-20">
<name>Wagon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138773.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="60" picture="171602.jpg">Kawada Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57307" type="appears in" update="2013-06-20">
<name>Ootake</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138774.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1925" picture="21115.jpg">Yuuki Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57308" type="appears in" update="2013-06-20">
<name>Chiyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138775.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="548" picture="186185.jpg">Sakamoto Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57309" type="appears in" update="2013-06-20">
<name>Shokurin Temple</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Chowlin Temple (食林寺 Shokurin Tera "Food Forest Temple") is a temple located in the Lost Forest. Its precise location is unknown even to big-name bishokuya, hence it`s nickname of the Disappearing Temple. The master of the temple is Chin Chinchin, one of the Gourmet National Treasures. The assistant masters are Shuu, Koppowo and Wagon.
Like the Disappearing Cuisine the temple is made by materials that disappear if the visitors don`t pray respect at the building, but unlike the Disappearing Cuisine the materials attack the people without enough respect.
The temple is also a prison where the gourmet criminals are sent to learn respect for food. If the criminals try to escape they become lost in the forest. Unlike Honey Prison, where the criminals remain for the rest of their lives, if a criminal completes the training he become free again.</description>
<picture>138776.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="57456" type="appears in" update="2013-06-24">
<name>Ayame</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139007.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38118" picture="139627.jpg">Maya Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57457" type="appears in" update="2013-06-24">
<name>Girim</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139008.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34374" picture="127853.jpg">Kitaooji Kin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57590" type="appears in" update="2013-06-30">
<name>Tack</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tack is a warrior of the Goro Tribe and a member of 0th Biotope.</description>
<picture>139320.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="57591" type="appears in" update="2013-06-30">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Malisman</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Malisman is a Gourmet Human National Treasure and a member of the 0th Biotope. She is a Gourmet Literary Master.</description>
<picture>139321.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="291" picture="17122.jpg">Matsui Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57592" type="appears in" update="2013-06-30">
<name>Malee</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Malee is a Knocking Artisan and a member of the 0th Biotope. He is also a master of Seitai therapy.</description>
<picture>139322.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10750" picture="186166.jpg">Takeuchi Ryouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57593" type="appears in" update="2013-06-30">
<name>Manan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Manan is a Bishokuya known as the "Gourmet Magician" and is a member of the 0th Biotope.</description>
<picture>139324.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="57594" type="appears in" update="2013-06-30">
<name>Goblin Ramon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Goblin Ramon is known as the "Gourmet Mountain Bandit" and is a member of the 0th Biotope.</description>
<picture>139325.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3801" picture="171533.jpg">Sakamaki Manabu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57595" type="appears in" update="2013-06-30">
<name>Megarodras</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Megarodras is an assassin and a member of the 0th Biotope.</description>
<picture>139326.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="57596" type="appears in" update="2013-06-30">
<name>Sakura</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakura is a martial artist Bishokuya and a member of the 0th Biotope.</description>
<picture>139327.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="375" picture="17221.jpg">Chiba Susumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57597" type="appears in" update="2013-06-30">
<name>Rala</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rala is known as the "Gourmet Astronomer" and is a member of the 0th Biotope.</description>
<picture>139328.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2586" picture="233442.jpg">Kimura Masafumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57598" type="appears in" update="2013-06-30">
<name>Atashino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Atashino is a skilled doctor and chef well known as the "Gourmet Surgeon" and is a member of the 0th Biotope.</description>
<picture>139329.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3132" picture="223652.jpg">Kikuchi Kokoro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57599" type="appears in" update="2013-06-30">
<name>Kousairou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kousairou, also known as the "Gourmet Hermit" was a former member of the 0th Biotope.</description>
<picture>139330.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39" picture="16629.jpg">Mugihito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57600" type="appears in" update="2013-06-30">
<name>Kuribou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kuribou aka the Ultimate Pot Artisan, is the world`s most famous and greatest pot artisan.</description>
<picture>139331.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2405" picture="23217.jpg">Shioya Kouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59279" type="appears in" update="2013-08-30">
<name>Janpin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142133.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2976" picture="234380.jpg">Tanaka Kazunari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59280" type="appears in" update="2013-08-30">
<name>Yuda</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142134.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1688" picture="19873.jpg">Ishizumi Akihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60831" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>Lulubuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144888.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16987" picture="86303.jpg">Shimoyama Yoshimitsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60832" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>Tairan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144889.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9114" picture="201075.jpg">Kikumoto Taira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60833" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>Kitt</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144890.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60834" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>Painomi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144891.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60835" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>Ahmon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144893.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60836" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>Nomarch</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144894.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60837" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>Toppo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144895.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60838" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Pukin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144896.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2972" picture="186915.jpg">Nagano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60839" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>Wabutora</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144897.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="60" picture="171602.jpg">Kawada Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60840" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>Zaus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144898.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="373" picture="191382.jpg">Hamada Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60841" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>Nakaume</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144899.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60842" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>Munage</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144900.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="694" picture="52187.jpg">Choo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60843" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>Mahmai Moi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144901.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="282" picture="223615.jpg">Houki Katsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60844" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>Yuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144902.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60845" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>Ahn</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="60846" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>Anyo Jr.</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144903.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60847" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>Appolo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="60848" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>CM Goron</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144904.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60849" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>Darin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144905.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60850" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>Pippi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144906.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60851" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>Kurakage</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144907.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60852" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>Mitsurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144908.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60853" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>Klaraman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144909.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60854" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>Horis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144910.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60855" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>Reishun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144911.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60856" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>Gen-chan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144912.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="469" picture="17418.jpg">Umezu Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60857" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Kopuriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144913.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24068" picture="224929.jpg">Tano Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60858" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>Koyubi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144914.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60859" type="appears in" update="2014-01-04">
<name>Mami</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148127.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60860" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>Rikiya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144915.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60861" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>Moh</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144916.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60862" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>Ton</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144917.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60863" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>Kamizaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144918.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="694" picture="52187.jpg">Choo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60864" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>Makubee</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144919.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3801" picture="171533.jpg">Sakamaki Manabu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60865" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>Granny Kama</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144920.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="553" picture="170553.jpg">Kaneda Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60866" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<name>Nerimaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144921.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60867" type="appears in" update="2013-10-27">
<rating votes="2">4.97</rating>
<name>Buranchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>"Bizarre Cooking" Tengu Buranchi is a genius chef and somewhat of a problem child, who, in the chef world, is a delinquent comparable to Zebra of the Bishokuya world. He has appeared only once in a Cooking Festival, but won it by a good margin. He currently holds the Number 3 spot in the IGO Chef Ranking, making him the third greatest chef in the world. He is from the "Bewitching Food World" located in the Gourmet World and is the head chef and owner of the Bizarre Dining Hall "Tengu Castle".</description>
<picture>144922.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3264" picture="24262.jpg">Dan Tomoyuki</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62828" type="appears in" update="2014-01-04">
<name>Dosa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148130.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="62829" type="appears in" update="2014-01-05">
<name>Zaragira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148147.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9114" picture="201075.jpg">Kikumoto Taira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62830" type="appears in" update="2014-01-05">
<name>Gur</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148146.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4665" picture="27220.jpg">Takahashi Naozumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65679" type="appears in" update="2014-03-16">
<name>NEO</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="66137" type="appears in" update="2014-03-29">
<name>Boneless</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152475.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="66138" type="appears in" update="2014-03-29">
<name>Kariu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152477.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="66139" type="appears in" update="2014-03-29">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Froese</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152478.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="129132" update="2013-11-25">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">秘境の巨獣! トリコ, ガララワニを捕獲せよ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Undiscovered Giant Beast! Toriko, Capture a Gararagator!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hikyou no Kyojuu! Toriko, Gararawani o Hokaku Seyo!</title>
<summary>The series begins with a chef named Komatsu discovering a Gourmet Hunter named Toriko, who catches a Pincer Fish, much to Komatsu`s amazement. After Toriko stops an attack on the fish by defeating a Five-Tailed Eagle, he is informed about a local Gararagator and accompanies Komatsu on his journey to the Baron Archipelago, a swamp where the animal lives. While there, Toriko scares off a Baron Tiger. Later, while eating Snake Frogs at dinner, a Swamp Snake suddenly appears but dies because of a large bite wound. However, they discover Baron Leeches on his body and is quickly eaten by the Gararagator, who reveals itself to be an oversized alligator. While fighting the Gararagator, Toriko discovers that it smells the scent of blood from the Baron Leeches. He eventually kills the Gararagator with his Fork and Knife technique. Toriko tells Komatsu of his intention to have a full-course menu while eating the Gararagator, while Komatsu tells his dream of becoming a world-renowned chef. Komatsu offers to come with Toriko, which he accepts.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651517</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129141" update="2018-09-03">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-03</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">上陸, グルメの島! 美食屋トリコ現る!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Landing, Gourmet Island! The Gourmet Hunter Toriko Appears!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jouriku, Gourmet no Shima! Bishoku-ya Toriko Arawareru!</title>
<summary>As Monkey D. Luffy and his crew are running low on food supplies, they discover an island known as the Gourmet Island. As Luffy, Nami, Sanji and Tony Tony Chopper explore the island and discover everything to be made of food, they encounter Toriko travelling with Komatsu, who initially mistake Chopper as potential food. After encountering some Roasted Boars and clearing up their misunderstandings, the two groups search for a large bird which Toriko and Luffy manage to beat. They spend the night sampling their spoils. However, Nami and Komatsu are kidnapped by a group of Cocoalas. As the gang head towards a mountain where a delicious fruit is said to exist and where the Cocoalas have taken Nami and Komatsu, the gang end up against a fierce group of lions, but are aided by Toriko`s allies: Sunny, Coco &amp; Rin. They later find Nami and Komatsu being held captive by a giant Cocoala and work together to defeat it. Afterwards, an eruption occurs, revealing the entire island to be one giant dessert. After Luffy and crew gather the provisions they need, they set off on their journey as Toriko continues his search for his Full Course menu.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651515</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129239" update="2013-12-02">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">芳醇なる七色の果汁! 虹の実をとれ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Well Mellowed 7-Colored Fruit Juice! Pick the Rainbow Fruit!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Houjun Naru Nanairo no Kajuu! Niji no Mi o Tore!</title>
<summary>Toriko is commissioned by the International Gourmet Organization to obtain the Rainbow Fruit, which is guarded by powerful Troll Kongs. As he and Komatsu make their way into the enclosed Biotope, news reporter Tina sneaks in to try and get footage of Toriko in action. Toriko encounters a scout and knocks him out with a stun gun, since he does not kill what he does not intend to eat, though gets licked with its scent. Toriko soon encounters a group of Troll Kongs guarding the Rainbow Fruit tree. As Toriko confronts them, the rain washes off the scent from the underling, allowing him to use his intimidation against the others and gain dominance over its leader. Toriko takes a single fruit, though Tina is caught and her footage is confiscated. Moved by the ever-changing flavors of the Rainbow Fruit, served in a jelly by Komatsu, Toriko declares the Rainbow Fruit as the dessert for his full-course menu. Meanwhile, various shady figures become interested in Toriko`s movements.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651519</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129412" update="2014-01-22">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-08</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ノッキングの達人! フグ鯨, 実食の時!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Knocking Master! Time to Taste the Puffer Whale!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nokkingu no Tatsujin! Fugukujira, Bishoku no Toki!</title>
<summary>As the kidnapper leaves Komatsu at the mercy of the Demon Devil Snake only to be killed by some other creatures, Komatsu uses a special firecracker given to him by Toriko, but the sound from it causes Komatsu`s heart to stop. However, he is rescued by an old man they had met on the train named Jirou, who is a Knocking Master, knocking out the snake and reviving Komatsu. After reuniting with Komatsu, Toriko`s group reach a sandy beach in the cave, where they find a school of small Puffer Whales. After Coco uses his technique of hiding his presence to catch one whale, Toriko is able to copy it and catch more. After catching a few, Coco has Komatsu prepare the whales to have their poisonous glands removed and, despite poisoning all but one of the whales, Komatsu manages to save the last one, preparing it into sashimi and sake. Afterwards, they spot a strange creature with a fearsome aura emerge from the water, leaving with some more Puffer Whales.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651525</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129413" update="2014-01-22">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-01</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">洞窟(どうくつ)の死闘! 打て, 5連釘パンチ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Deadly Cave Battle! Fire, Five-Fold Spiked Punch!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Doukutsu no Shitou! Ute, Go Ren Kugi Panchi</title>
<summary>The Devil Snake`s cries cause the entrance to the cave to cave in, and its acid spitting and regenerative abilities prove difficult for Toriko and Coco. Meanwhile, Komatsu is taken captive by another hunter looking for the Puffer Whale. As Coco tries to distract the Devil Snake so Toriko can gather power, he is injected with its venom. However, he manages to make some antibodies for it and inject them into the snake along with his own poison, allowing Toriko to unleash his 5-Fold Spiked Punch on it. As Toriko contemplates what to do with the meat, Komatsu and his kidnapper encounter another Demon Devil Snake.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651523</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129414" update="2014-01-14">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さばけ猛毒フグ鯨! 四天王ココ登場!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Prepare It! The Poisonous Puffer Whale! The Heavenly King Coco Appears!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sabake Moudoku Fugu Kujira! Shitennou Koko Toujou!</title>
<summary>As the rare Puffer Whale makes its appearance once in every ten years, Toriko and Komatsu go to meet the chefs that prepare its meat. Upon arriving at their destination, they meet one of the Four Heavenly Kings, Coco, to request his help in capturing and preparing the Puffer Whale. Together they enter a cave labrynth in search of the Puffer Whale, though Coco predicts Komatsu might die. It is revealed that Coco`s body contains several types of poison which ward away beasts, but has also made him a target for those interested in the antibodies he produces. As they approach the beach, Komatsu goes missing and Toriko and Coco are approached by the fearsome Devil Snake.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651521</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129737" update="2011-05-01">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode T1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129794" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最強の助っ人! 激突, ココ対GTロボ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ultimate Backup! Clash, Coco Vs. GT Robot!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikyou no Suketto! Gekitotsu, Coco tai GT Robo!</title>
<summary>Toriko`s quick thinking saves Sunny and Komatsu from being crush by a mammoth, but there are greater threats looming. A giant GT Robot is ready to rumble, and the Gourmet Hunters are all out of strength!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651539</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129795" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔のゲーム! デビルアスレチックをクリアしろ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Devils` Game! Clear the Devils` Playground!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ma no Game! Devil Athletic o Clear Shiro!</title>
<summary>Toriko`s daring attempt to navigate the Devils` Playground brings him face-to-face with a Soldier Frog, an Axeox, and an Avian Beast with hallucinogenic breath! Meanwhile, a GT Robot stalks the Regal Mammoth!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651537</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129796" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">疾走, リーガル島! ジュエルミートを目指せ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Regal Isle Dash! Search for the Jewel Meat!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shissou, Regal-tou! Jewel Meat o Mezase!</title>
<summary>While the villainous GT Robots continue their search for mammoth meat, Torkio has his hands full battling an ornery Obasaurus, and Komatsu learns the powerful secrets of the Gourmet Cells!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651535</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129797" update="2014-01-22">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">無敵の領域を持つ男! その名はサニー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Man Who Has an Invincible Domain! His Name Is Sani!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Muteki no Ryouiki o Motsu Otoko! Sono Na wa Sunny!</title>
<summary>After defeating the GT Robot, Toriko, Mansem, Tina and Komatsu discover a Regal Mammoth. The Gourmet Hunter says that the Mammoth has been called a food treasure. However, a stranger defeats a group of Gang Hoods when they try to steal the Regal Mammoth. The stranger reveals that his name is Sunny and is a member of the Four Heavenly Kings. Mansem tells the group that the Regal Mammoth is a child and their parents are somewhere on the island. At Mansem`s request, Toriko and the others search for the adult Regal Mammoth. Meanwhile, the Gourmet Corps learn of Bei`s failure to defeat Toriko and steal the Regal Mammoth. Toriko and the others discover Black Grass and Sunny tells the group his full course meal. Toriko tells Komatsu that the IGO has 8 worlds with different environments and beasts. However, the group discovers the giant Rock Drums. Toriko uses his Five-Folt Spiked Punch technique on the beasts and Sunny eventually the last one with the Hair Net: Spatula technique. Mansem learns that a GT Robot has invaded the island.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651533</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129798" update="2014-01-22">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">受け継がれるもの! 活性, グルメ細胞!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">That Which Is Passed Down! Activate, Gourmet Cells!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uketsugareru Mono! Kassei, Gourmet Saibou!</title>
<summary>Komatsu discovers that Mansem can heal himself by disinfecting his wounds. Bei tries to attack the Battle Wolf and her cub, but Rin uses the Endorphin Smoke technique on him. Mansem informs Komatsu that the Battle Wolf has given love to her cub which has been passed down for generations, and that a GT Robot can be manipulated by a human. Enraged at the near-death of the Battle Wolf, Toriko activates his gourmet cells and confronts the GT Robot. Toriko uses his Five-Fold Spike Punch and Ice Pick techniques on the GT Robot in a futile attempt to destroy it. The GT Robot attempts to kill Toriko, but he uses the Five-Fold Ice Pick Spiked Punch technique on the GT Robot - destroying its head. Mansem orders his men to fire the laser cannons on the robot, revealing its core antenna. The antenna flees from the attacks, but is obliterated by the beast Ricky. The Battle Wolf dies while standing up and Toriko, having befriended the cub, names him Terry Cloth. While eating, Toriko and Komatsu discovers that the Regal Mammoth has been stolen. Rin tells them that her brother has captured a Regal Mammoth on an island.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651531</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129799" update="2014-01-22">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">現れた脅威! 波乱, グルメコロシアム!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Threat Appears! Rumble at the Gourmet Coliseum!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arawareta Kyoui! Haran, Gurume Koroshiamu!</title>
<summary>As Toriko confronts the Battle Wolf, the crowd is shocked to discover Toriko`s appearance. Mansam discovers that Toriko entered the arena through the glass walls. Meanwhile, Tina discovers Komatsu and Mansam while filming the fight. Toriko frightens the other beasts away. The Battle Wolf collapses from exhaustion, but Toriko continues to fight the beasts. Mansem orders Rin to shut down the Battle Fragrance machine, but it continues to pour out Battle Fragrance as the machine malfunctions. Toriko manages to defeat a beast with his 5-Fold Spiked Punch technique, destroying most of the dome. Toriko announces the arrival of a new Battle Wolf. Meanwhile, Rin tries to tranquil a Demon Devil Python, but she is chased by the beast. Mansem tells Komatsu that the Battle Wolf has the Gourmet Cells, which can produce a clone of a beast. Rin leads the Demon Devil Python to the arena, where Toriko confronts the beast. Mansem confronts Dohem, whose true form is Bei. Bei defeats Mansem, while the Battle Wolf easily defeats the Demon Devil Python. Toriko then confronts Bei, who tells him that he will not be interested in eating a Battle Wolf and incapacitates the Battle Wolf with a single blast from the GT Robot.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651529</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129800" update="2014-01-22">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最大最強の狼! バトルウルフ, 復活!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Strongest Wolf That Ever Lived! The Battle Wolf Is Reborn!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saidai Saikyou no Ookami! Battle Wolf, Fukkatsu</title>
<summary>Toriko, Komatsu and Coco exit the cave and find the creature had beaten up all the other hunters. Later, Tina is suspended from her job as her camera had been confiscated by the IGO due to footage on the strange creature, known as a GT Robo, which has also been attacking Biotopes and stealing Rainbow Fruit. As the IGO prepare the release of a Gourmet Hunter named Zebra in preparation for a certain enemy, Toriko and Komatsu travel to one of the Biotopes to capture the Regal Mammoth. They meet up with Chief Mansam, who tells about the Gourmet Corps, the evil organisation trying to take control of the world`s ingredients and is targeting the Regal Mammoth. They then head to the Gourmet Colloseum where they view the main event, a battle royale between various creatures, including the legendary Battle Wolf. However, something goes wrong and the colloseum is filled with Battle Fragrance that causes the beasts to go wild and attack the Battle Wolf. Toriko decides to enter the arena and appears before the Battlewolf.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651527</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="130772" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-07-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">脅威の猛毒! ココ, 勝利への方程式</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Threat of Deadly Poison! Coco`s Formula for Victory!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoui no Moudoku! Coco, Shouri e no Houteishiki</title>
<summary>While Toriko searches for the priceless Jewel Meat, Sunny and Coco wage separate battles against deadly GT Robots! Will Sunny`s hair leash and Coco`s poison rifle be enough secure victory?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651541</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="131124" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">超トリコ, 怒りの拳! これが最強の釘パンチ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Toriko, the Fists of Anger! This Is the Strongest Spike Punch!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chou Toriko, Ikari no Kobushi! Korega Saikyou no Kugi Panchi!</title>
<summary>A bite of the delicious Jewel Meat energizes Torkio, who uses a vicious Ten-Fold Spike Punch to put the hurt on a GT Robot! When the dust finally settles on the battlefield, dinner will be served!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651547</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="131125" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">リン, 最期の願い! 覚醒せよ, 超(スーパー)トリコ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rin`s Final Wish! Awaken, Super Toriko!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rin, Saigo no Negai! Kakusei Seyo, Chou (Super) Toriko!!</title>
<summary>Rin`s tragic end sends Toriko into a rage, but the price of fueling his passionate attack may cost him his life. Meanwhile, Komatsu takes a heroic stand when the GT Robot tries to rob the chef of his favorite knife!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651545</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="131126" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">強靭なる美学! サニー, 男の闘い!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Unyielding Aesthetic! Sunny`s Manly Battle!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoujin Naru Bigaku! Sunny, Otoko no Tatakai!</title>
<summary>Sunny`s battle with the GT Robot is complicated by the arrival of a Mega Octopus, and something extremely evil hunts Toriko and his famished friends!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651543</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="131708" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-08-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">DNAに刻まれた味! トリコ, BB(ブルーブラッド)コーンを探せ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Taste Written in His DNA! Toriko, Search for the BB Corn!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">DNA ni Kizama Reta Aji! Toriko, BB (Blue Blood) Koun o Sagase!</title>
<summary>Komatsu must find an exquisite sauce to top a dish of very rare fish, and Toriko prepares to venture deep into the deadly Wu Jungle in search of food fit for a Battle Wolf!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651549</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="132186" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">美食屋軍団の挑戦! 上陸, 極寒の地獄!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Challenge of the Gourmet Hunter Army! Disembarking at Freezing Hell!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bishokuya Gundan no Chousen! Jouriku, Gokkan no Jigoku!</title>
<summary>Tundra Dragons and killer icicles are just a few of the obstacles standing between Toriko and the Century Soup. If the elements don`t kill him, there is a mean, green, GT Robot waiting to finish the job!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651565</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="132187" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">出会いの酒場! 群雄割拠の美食屋達!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Meeting at the Saloon! Rivalry Between Gourmet Hunters!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Deai no Sakaba! Gunyuukakkyo no Bishokuya-tachi!</title>
<summary>Toriko, Komatsu, and a ravenous army of Gourmet Hunters set off in search of the legendary Century Soup. Their journey will take them to Ice Hell, but they`ll have to survive a Sharkrocodile attack to arrive in one piece!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651563</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="132188" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢の時間! 節乃のセンチュリースープ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dreamtime! Setsuno`s Century Soup!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume no Jikan! Setsuno no Century Soup!</title>
<summary>Komatsu and Toriko are treated to an ultra-exclusive tour of Setsuno`s kitchen, including the top secret area where she prepares Century Soup! Inspired, they set off in search of the genuine article, but trouble lies ahead!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651561</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="132189" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">食事の遊園地! 満腹都市グルメタウン!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Amusement Park of Eating! The Bellyfull City, Gourmet Town!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shokuji no Yuuenchi! Manpuku Toshi Gourmet Town!</title>
<summary>Toriko and Komatsu travel to the city of culinary dreams for a special dinner with a living gourmet legend! Elsewhere, the sinister Gourmet Corps reveal the secrets behind their desperate desire for the Jewel Meat!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651559</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="132190" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-09-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狂気の圧力! グリンパーチ対トリコ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pressure of Madness! Grinpatch Vs. Toriko!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyouki no Atsuryoku! Grinpatch Tai Toriko!</title>
<summary>Toriko continues his battle with the corn-stealing, straw-wielding villain known as Grinpatch, and Komatsu desperately races to make it home before a rare dish of fish becomes nothing more than bubbles!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651557</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="132191" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">美食會(びしょくかい)の刺客! トリコの技, 進化の瞬間!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Gourmet Corp. Assassin! The Moment Toriko`s Techniques Evolve!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bishokukai no Shikaku! Toriko no Waza, Shinka no Shunkan!</title>
<summary>Toriko must take his powers to the next level if he hopes to defeat a ravenous assassin from the Gourmet Corps. Elsewhere, Komatsu learns of the legendary ingredient with the power to stop - or start - wars!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651555</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="132192" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">テリーの為に! 灼熱(しゃくねつ)で弾けろ, BBコーン!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">For Terry`s Sake! Burst by Broiling Heat, BB Corn!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Terii no Tame ni! Shakunetsu de Hajikero, BB Koun!</title>
<summary>Toriko and Terry finally find the deliciously elusive BB Corn, and Komatsu must depend on a special blend of spices to survive an encounter with a giant lizard!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651553</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="132193" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-08-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">闘いの才能! 見せろテリー, 王者の素質!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Talent of Battle! Show Me, Terry, King in the Making!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tatakai no Sainou! Misero Terry, Ouja no Soshitsu!</title>
<summary>Time is running out for Komatsu to complete his fishy dish, and Toriko watches as Terry faces off against a beastly Zombie Wood. Will the Battle Wolf show his true power - or fall to his ferocious foe?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651551</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="132984" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">膳は急げ! 氷土[ひょうど]のサバイバルレース!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hurry While It`s Hot! A Survival Race on Ice!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zen wa Isoge! Hyoudo no Survival Race!</title>
<summary>Zonge stumbles upon a group of angry Growlruses, Toriko and company go head-to-head with a herd of ferocious Freezer Bison, and a villainous vice chef unleashes an army of beastly insects!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651567</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="133083" update="2013-04-07">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-04-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133084" update="2011-09-19">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-04-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133617" update="2013-04-07">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133817" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">氷山揺るがす爆炎! 覆面男の正体!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Explosive Fire Shakes Ice Mountain! The Identity of the Masked Man!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hyouzan Yurugasu Bakuen! Fukumen Otoko no Shoutai!</title>
<summary>Toriko and Komatsu team up to turn a deadly Silver Grizzly into a scrumptious soup. A villainous member of the Gourmet Corps is hot on their trail, but help is on the way in the form of a Heavenly King!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651569</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="133897" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決着! マッチと滝丸捨て身の大技!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Settled! Match and Takimaru`s Desperate Attacks!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ketchaku! Match to Takimaru Sutemi no Oowaza!</title>
<summary>Takimaru relies on lessons from his past to settle the score with his flexible foe, and Match puts his blade to the ultimate test against an opponent clad in Crash Turtle armor!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651575</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="133898" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">感謝と誇り! 滝丸, 渾身の栓抜きショット!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gratitude and Pride! Takimaru`s Full-Out Corkscrew Shot!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kansha to Hokori! Takimaru, Konshin no Sennuki Shot!</title>
<summary>Toriko fights to survive a deadly swarm of insects, and Takimaru fights for his life against an unbreakable opponent. Meanwhile, Komatsu`s quest to collect the Century Soup is monitored by GT Robot!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651573</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="133899" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">爛漫なる蟲使い! トミーロッド対トリコ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Glorious Bug Tamer! Tommyrod vs Toriko!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ranmannaru Mushi Tsukai! Tommyrod tai Toriko!</title>
<summary>When Toriko`s hand is frozen solid during a deadly encounter with a Gourmet Corps bug tamer, the burden of collecting the Century Soup falls squarely on the small shoulders of Komatsu! Is the little chef up to such a big task?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651571</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="134797" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">食の再生屋と伝説のスープの行方!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Gourmet Reviver and the Legendary Soup`s Location!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoku no Saisei-ya to Densetsu no Soup no Yukue!</title>
<summary>Toriko heats things up in a heroic attempt to end the insect onslaught! Elsewhere, Komatsu finally reaches the location of the Century Soup - only to find that there is no soup!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651577</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="134888" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真っ向勝負! 激闘トリコ対トミーロッド!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Head-on Fight! Fierce Battle! Toriko vs. Tommyrod!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Makkou Shoubu! Gekitou Toriko tai Tommyrod!</title>
<summary>Komatsu learns the amazing truth about his mysterious new friend, and Toriko relies on the power of his Gourmet Cells to even the odds in his brutal showdown with Tommyrod!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651579</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="134982" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶体絶命! トミーロッド本気モード炸裂!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ultimate Desperation! Tommyrod`s Full-Power Mode Explodes!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zettai Zetsumei! Tommyrod Honki Mode Sakuretsu!</title>
<summary>Toriko attempts to end his epic battle with Tommyrod by unleashing a Thirteen-Fold Spike Punch, but the bug tamer counters by revealing the true depths of his devious strength!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651581</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="135038" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">驚異の力! 再生屋鉄平参戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wondrous Power! Gourmet Reviver Teppei Joins the Battle!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoui no Chikara! Saisei-ya Teppei Sansen!</title>
<summary>The sudden arrival of a powerful Gourmet Reviver prompts Tommyrod to shed his skin, giving birth to a monstrous Parasite Emperor! The buggy beast is big and bad, but will he survive a bout with Hellboros, the ruler of Ice Hell?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651583</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="135253" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最後の一滴! センチュリースープは誰の手に!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Last Drop! Who Will Get the Century Soup?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo no Itteki! Century Soup wa Dare no Te ni!?</title>
<summary>Komatsu is crushed by his failure to capture the Century Soup, but Teppei has one more amazing trick up his sleeve. With evil forces bearing down on them, will any our heroes live to tell of their adventure?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651585</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="135264" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらばアイスヘル! セツ婆の秘めたる力</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell, Ice Hell! Granny Setsu`s Hidden Power!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saraba Ice Hell! Setsu-baa no Himetaru Chikara</title>
<summary>After being rescued by Granny Setsu, the weary and wounded adventures set a course for the healing country known as Life. Toriko has an arm to regenerate, and Komatsu is eager to recreate the Century Soup!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651587</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="135390" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">競争! トリコの完治か小松のスープか!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Race to Finish! Will It Be Toriko`s Recovery, or Komatsu`s Soup?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyousou! Toriko no Kanchi ka Komatsu no Soup ka!?</title>
<summary>Toriko`s recovery progresses faster than expected, but the strain of growing a new arm may cost him his life. Meanwhile, Komatsu struggles to find the final ingredient for his Century Soup!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651591</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="135391" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">豪快治療! 再生屋・与作登場!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Splendid Healing! Here Comes the Gourmet Reviver, Yosaku!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Goukai Chiryou! Saisei-ya Yosaku Toujou!</title>
<summary>Toriko`s gang arrives in the healing country of Life, an amazing land of curative creatures that can treat almost any ailment. After a chance meeting with Sunny, the group visits Teppei`s master, a renowned - and rowdy - Reviver.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651589</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="135567" update="2012-04-08">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-04-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">驚異の助っ人登場! パートナーの真の意味</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Enter the Astounding Ringer! The True Meaning of a Partner!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoui no Suketto Toujou! Partner no Shin no Imi</title>
<summary>Toriko is in the edge of danger by meeting animals which have immesureable capture level - currently - in the Underground Forest. He also meets tons of new ingredients that will be explained by his savior, Knocking Master Jirou. Jirou also tells him that he cannot rush on the training process for entering the Gourmet World, and he also tells that Komatsu is the one that requests his aids. Toriko begins to realize and regret regarding his actions for trying to conquer Gourmet World alone. He meets Komatsu to tell him that he is fine, and Komatsu cries out of joy. He begins for his next training - From Comics will be Melk`s Stardust.
Source Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651613</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="135568" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トリコ突入! グルメ界の真実!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Toriko Rushes In! The Truth of the Gourmet World!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toriko Totsunyuu! Gourmet-kai no Shinjitsu!</title>
<summary>Eager to test his new abilities in the Gourmet World, Toriko ignores the warnings of his closest friends and goes in search of adventure! Meanwhile, Komatsu is shocked by an unexpected visitor!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651611</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="135569" update="2012-04-08">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-03-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">衝撃の出会い! 謎の生物現る!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shocking Encounter! A Mysterious Life Form Appears!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shougeki no Deai! Nazo no Seibutsu Arawaru!</title>
<summary>Toriko realizes that there is a unique wild beast that learns quickly by looking from others. After fulfilling the request from IGO`s president, he comes back and Ichiro realizes Komatsu`s ability to hear ingredients voice. Toriko also asks regarding the creature that he found in the sky garden but Ichiro ignores him. Ichiro also requests tons of other ingredients to prepare Toriko for entering gourmet world. Meanwhile other four heavenly kings have received their assignments accepts for Zebura in which currently in prison. Ichiro tells Toriko that it is OK to invite other heavenly kings to capture the requested ingredients as for training. Ichiro invites them to go to Gourmet World to enjoy unknown ingredients.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651609</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="135570" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-03-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大空の告白! 不滅のコンビ結成!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Confession in the Heavens! The Formation of the Invincible Duo!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oozora no Kokuhaku! Fumetsu no Combi Kessei!</title>
<summary>Toriko and Komatsu finally reach the Ozone Grass, but the legendary ingredient proves challenging to harvest. As the culinary adventurers struggle to satisfy their appetites, something sinister watches the scene unfold!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651607</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="135571" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">発見! 野菜の王様オゾン草!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Discovery! The King of Vegetables, Ozone Grass!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakken! Yasai no Oosama Ozon-sou!</title>
<summary>Toriko and Komatsu continue their quest to collect the Ozone Grass, but their journey only grows more difficult. Before they arrive at the garden in the sky, they must pass through a deadly thunderstorm!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651605</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="135572" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-02-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天空の野菜畑・ベジタブルスカイ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Vegetable Garden in the Heavens! Vegetable Sky!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenkuu no Yasaibatake Vegetable Sky!</title>
<summary>Toriko begins his training with a mission to collect the delicious Ozone Grass. Komatsu is along for the ride, but is the little chef ready for brutal battles against Flying Sea Lions, Air Gorillas, and a Killer Bean Tree!?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651603</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="135573" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-02-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">白熱! トリコ対IGO会長!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">White Hot! Toriko vs. the IGO President!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakunetsu! Toriko tai IGO Kaichou!</title>
<summary>Toriko tests out his new battle techniques - and his brand new arm - in a ferocious fistfight with the IGO President! Though his strength has improved, Toriko will need more training before he`s ready for the Gourmet World!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651601</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="135574" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-02-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絆の一品! パートナーは永遠に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bonding Dish! Partners Are Forever!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kizuna no Ippin! Partner wa Eien ni</title>
<summary>Sharkbox Turtles, Honey Dragons, and a Chomp Urchin plague the Heavenly Kings in their mission to feed the Seven-Colored Nellie. Can they survive this perilous quest and satisfy the starving beast?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651599</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="135575" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-01-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">美食王決定戦! 究極のスイーツを探せ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Gourmet King Championship! Search for the Ultimate Sweets!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bishoku Ou Ketteisen! Kyuukyoku no Sweets o Sagase!</title>
<summary>Toriko, Sunny, and Coco set out on a death-defying quest to see who can track down the most irresistible sweets for a starving Seven-Colored Nellie!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651597</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="135576" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新築祝! スイーツハウスに全員集合!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Housewarming Party! Everyone Gather at the Sweets House!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinchiku Iwai! Sweets House ni Zen`in Shuugou!</title>
<summary>Toriko returns home only to discover that his house has been eaten! Looks like it`s time to call the candy architect and start gathering delicious ingredients for a new place to rest his head!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651595</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="135577" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-01-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">至福の世界へ! 実食センチュリースープ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the World of Ultimate Bliss! Taste the Century Soup!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shifuku no Sekai e! Jisshoku Century Soup</title>
<summary>With the help of an unusual ingredient, Komatsu finally completes the Century Soup! Thanks to the little chef`s big accomplishment, Toriko may get his arm back - and add an ingredient to his Full Course Menu of Life!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651593</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="136226" update="2013-04-07">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-01-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137610" update="2018-09-03">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-04-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">再会トリコとルフィ! 海鮮の実を探せ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Reunion of Toriko and Luffy! Find the Seafood Fruit!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikai Toriko to Luffy! Kaisen no Mi o Sagase!</title>
<summary>After catching a Spring Shark, Toriko and Komatsu are surprised to see Luffy come tumbling out its mouth.  Luffy needs the gourmet hunter help to save a valuable crew member.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>666089</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138354" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">62</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-06-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">小松失踪! 魔のデザートラビリンス!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Komatsu Disappears! Devilish Desert Labyrinth!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Komatsu Shissou! Ma no Desert Labyrinth!</title>
<summary>A dangerous encounter with Desert Sharks leads to Komatsu`s disappearance, which leads Toriko and Zebra to the foot of the Gourmet Pyramid!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651635</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138355" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">61</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-06-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">警報発令! ゼブラ サンドガーデンに上陸!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Warning! Zebra Has Disembarked at the Sand Garden!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Keihou Hatsurei! Zebra Sand Garden ni Jouriku!</title>
<summary>Komatsu voices his concerns about travelling with such a dangerous criminal, and Zebra makes some new friends after a slugfest with a savage scorpion!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651633</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138356" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">60</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-06-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">爆音解放!! 死刑囚ゼブラの出所!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unleashed Roar! Death Row Zebra`s Release!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bakuon Kaihou! Shikeishuu Zebra no Shussho!</title>
<summary>The one they call Zebra is released from prison just in time for Monster Season and a showdown with the horrifying Forrest Goblin! After he eats lunch, of course!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651631</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138357" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">59</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-06-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">遂に登場! 最後の四天王ゼブラ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Finally, He Appears! The Last of the Four Kings, Zebra!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsui ni Toujou! Saigo no Shitennou Zebra!</title>
<summary>Toriko and Komatsu explore the despicable depths of Honey Prison as they make their way to the one called Zebra. Dare they hope to survive such a deafening encounter!?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651629</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138358" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">58</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-05-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">超セレブ! グルメ馬車の夢の旅!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Celeb! Once-in-a-Lifetime Gourmet Carriage Journey!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chou Celeb! Gourmet Basha no Yume no Tabi!</title>
<summary>Toriko and Komatsu take a trip on the luxurious Gourmet Carriage, but there`s more to this vacation than sight-seeing and fine food. The adventurous duo is headed for the gates of hell!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651627</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138359" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">57</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-05-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">渾身の一作! 完成メルク包丁!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Work Made with All Her Might! The Completed Melk Knife!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Konshin no Issaku! Kansei Melk-bouchou!</title>
<summary>While Melk`s apprentice works tirelessly to craft a special knife for Komatsu, the little chef and Toriko wait eagerly for the job to be finished - and the feast to begin!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651625</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138360" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">56</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-05-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">御披露目! 二代目襲名とメルクの星屑!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Debut! The Second Generation`s Succession and Melk Stardust!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ohirome! Nidaime Shuumei to Melk no Hoshikuzu!</title>
<summary>Toriko delves into the various mysterious of Cutler Melk, including his unusual voice, and Komatsu uses his culinary skills to give Melk`s apprentice a confidence boost!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651623</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138361" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">55</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-05-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">隠された真実! 初代メルク現る!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hidden Truth! The First Melk Appears!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakusareta Shinjitsu! Shodai Melk Arawaru!</title>
<summary>The intense gravity of Heavy Hole pushes Toriko`s body to the breaking point. Back on the surface, Komatsu makes a shocking discovery about Culter Melk`s apprentice!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651621</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138362" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">54</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">超重力! ヘビーホールを攻略せよ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Supergravity! Conquer Heavy Hole!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chou Juuryoku! Heavy Hole o Kouryaku seyo!</title>
<summary>Komatsu spends some quality time with Cutler Melk`s apprentice, and Toriko delves deeper into the depths of Heavy Hole, where the gravity is intense and the Barbamoths are fierce!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651619</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138363" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">53</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">緊迫! トリコのナイフ対メルク包丁!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tension! Toriko`s Knife vs. Melk`s Knife!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kinpaku! Toriko no Knife tai Melk-bouchou!</title>
<summary>Toriko and Komatsu are shocked by who they find waiting at the home of Cutler Melk, and the legendary Gourmet Hunter`s brash nature quickly leads to a knife fight!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651617</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138364" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">衝撃! 折れた包丁と研ぎ師メルク!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shock! The Broken Kitchen Knife and Cutler Melk!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shougeki! Oreta Houchou to Togishi Melk!</title>
<summary>When Komatsu breaks his favorite knife, he and Toriko set out to find a famed craftsman who is said to forge the strongest blades imaginable. Their journey - plagued by Rock Wolves and Scale Kongs - will not be easy.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651615</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138857" update="2013-04-07">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-04-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139653" update="2013-04-07">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-05-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="140358" update="2012-06-24">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-06-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="140516" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">63</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-07-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">封印された声! 異空間グルメピラミッド!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sealed Voice! The Other-Dimensional Gourmet Pyramid!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuuinsareta Koe! Ikoukan Gourmet Pyramid!</title>
<summary>Komatsu is trapped within the labyrinthine Gourmet Pyramid, and only Zebra and Toriko can save him. Unfortunately, a deadly Gorgonclops and a hideous Unicorn Cerberus are standing in their way!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651637</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="140632" update="2013-04-07">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-07-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="140810" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">64</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-07-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">奇々怪々! 謎の古文書と棺の中の生物!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Astounding! The Mysterious Ancient Manuscript and the Creature Inside the Coffin!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikikaikai! Nazo no Komonjo to Hitsugi no Naka no Seibutsu!</title>
<summary>Zebra and Toriko must eat everything in their path in order to regain the strength needed for their daring rescue mission! Meanwhile, Komatsu struggles to survive on his own!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651639</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="140869" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">73</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-09-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ウワーッ! 仰天ビックリアップル!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Uwaaa! Astonishing Stun Apple!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uwaa! Gyouten Bikkuri Apple!</title>
<summary>Toriko and Komatsu hope to have the element of surprise on their side as they travel to the explosive Battle Island in search of the legendary Stun Apple!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651657</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="140870" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">72</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-09-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">あふれる食運! 巡礼グルメ神社!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Food Luck Runneth Over! Pilgrimage to the Gourmet Shrine!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Afureru Shokuun! Junrei Gourmet Jinja!</title>
<summary>Toriko and Komatsu visit the legendary Gourmet Shrine where they seek to increase their food luck! After sampling many delicacies and taking in the sights, Komatsu takes center stage for a surprising feat of strength!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651655</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="140871" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">71</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-09-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">新局面! トリコの決意と"奴"との再会!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">New Phase! Toriko`s Decision and the Reunion with `Him`!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinkyokumen! Toriko no Ketsui to "Yatsu" to no Saikai!</title>
<summary>Toriko`s quest to get stronger leads the dynamic culinary duo to a remote cafe in the middle of a jet black lake. The food is fantastic, but the clientele is deadly!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651653</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="140872" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">70</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">つながる絆! 絶品ガツカツカレー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ties That Bind! Superb Gobbling Katsu Curry!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsunagaru Kizuna! Zeppin Gatsu Katsu Curry!</title>
<summary>Toriko continues his heated battle with powerful Water Tiger, and Komatsu helps a heartbroken chef find the amazing curry cooking skills locked inside him!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651651</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="140873" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">69</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-08-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">父を超えろ! 真夏のガツカツカレー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Surpass Dad! Midsummer Gobbling Katsu Curry!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chichi o Koero! Manatsu no Gatsu Katsu Curry!</title>
<summary>Toriko`s trip to the beach turns into an adventure when he agrees to help his favorite curry shop track down some much needed - and very dangerous - ingredients! First on the list: Water Tiger!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651649</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="140874" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">68</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-08-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">明かされる真相! 小松の意志と謎の生物の正体!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Truth Revealed! Komatsu`s Will and the Identity of the Mysterious Creature!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akasareru Shinsou! Komatsu no Ishi to Nazo no Seibutsu no Shoutai!</title>
<summary>Komatsu must find the courage to stand up to Zebra and tell the truth about who he wants to be his partner. Later, the horrifying identity of the mysterious monster from the Gourmet Pyramid is finally revealed!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651647</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="140875" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">67</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-08-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">合体技炸裂! 世界一のコーラいただきます!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Explosion of Combination Techniques! We Get the World`s Best Cola!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gattai Waza Sakuretsu! Sekaiichi no Cola Itadakimasu!</title>
<summary>Toriko and Zebra must work together to defeat the mysterious monster that attacked Komatsu. There`s just one problem: the two warriors are completely out of energy!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651645</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="140876" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">66</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-07-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">連携調理! 小松が操るトリコとゼブラ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cooperative Cooking! Komatsu Manages Toriko and Zebra!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Renkei Chouri! Komatsu ga Ayatsuru Toriko to Zebra!</title>
<summary>Zebra and Toriko carry out Komatsu’s brutal orders as the little chef tells them exactly how to harvest the Mellow Cola. Their mission is on the verge of success when an unseen evil emerges!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651643</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="140877" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">65</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-07-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">衝撃対決! サラマンダースフィンクス!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shocking Showdown! Salamander Sphinx!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shougeki Taiketsu! Salamander Sphinx!</title>
<summary>Zebra and Toriko finally reunite with Komatsu, but their troubles are only just beginning. To acquire the Mellow Cola, they must defeat a ferocious Salamander Sphinx, but they have no idea how to kill it!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651641</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="143774" update="2013-04-07">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-10-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144032" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">76</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-10-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">衝撃の激流! 巨大滝デスフォール!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shocking Rapids! Giant Waterfall, Death Falls!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shougeki no Gekiryuu! Kyodaidaki Death Fall!</title>
<summary>As the quest for the Shining Gourami continues, Toriko grows more and more impressed with Sunny`s training. An unexpected battle with a Hippo Shark gives the rainbow-haired gourmet hunter a chance to show off his strength!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651663</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="144033" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">75</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-09-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">水晶の輝き! サンサングラミー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Glittering Crystal! Shining Gourami!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suishou no Kagayaki! Sansan Gourami!</title>
<summary>Toriko, Komatsu, and Sunny embark on a hair-raising quest to track down the Shining Gourami, an extremely rare sea creature that lives deep within Death Falls!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651661</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="144034" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">74</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-09-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ニワトラの卵! よっち爺さんと妻の記憶</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chicken Beast`s Egg! The Memories of Old Man Yocchi and His Wife!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Niwatora no Tamago! Yocchi Jii-san to Tsuma no Kioku</title>
<summary>After his recent lottery win, Komatsu wants to buy Toriko a gift. There`s just one problem. The legendary gourmet hunter has his heart set on a priceless piece of land where the Chicken Beast lays its eggs!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651659</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="144617" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">80</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-11-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ド派手演出! 食事に最高のサービスを!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Flashy Presentation! Supreme Service with a Meal!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Do Hade Enshutsu! Shokuji ni Saikou no Service o!</title>
<summary>When Melk the Second needs help finishing a very special knife, Toriko and Komatsu compete in a prestigious competition in an attempt to win the final ingredient needed to complete her project!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651671</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="144618" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">79</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-10-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">直観調理! 小松とサンサングラミー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cooking by Intuition! Komatsu and the Shining Gourami!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Choukkan Chouri! Komatsu to Sansan Gourami!</title>
<summary>Komatsu takes center stage as the little chef struggles to unlock the secret to preparing the Shining Gourami! Toriko and Sunny are exhausted and hungry, and Komatsu must listen to his ingredients if he wants to feed his friends!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651669</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="144619" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">78</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-10-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">合体30倍! 36連ツイン釘パンチ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Thirty Times Combo! Thirty-Six-Fold Twin Spiked Punch!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gattai 30-bai! 36-ren Twin Kugi Punch!</title>
<summary>Toriko and Sunny must team up for a powerful combination move that`s their only hope for surviving the journey through Death Falls! But even if they reach the other side, they`ll need help to capture their prey.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651667</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="144620" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">77</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-10-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">サニー新技! 華麗なる修業の成果!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sunny`s New Attack! The Result of Gorgeous Training!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sunny Shinwaza! Kareinaru Shugyou no Seika!</title>
<summary>The devastating power of Death Falls sends Sunny into a flashback where he reflects on the days spent battling beasts and honing his instincts on the Road of Three Hells!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651665</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="145284" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">84</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-12-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">分かれ道! 料理人のめざす先</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crossroads! A Chef`s Destination!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakare Michi! Ryourinin no Mezasu Saki!</title>
<summary>Komatsu is shocked by the lack of culinary honor exhibited by his old friend. Meanwhile, Toriko and Coco team up to open a giant treasure chest - but what they find inside leaves them baffled!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651679</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="145285" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">83</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-11-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">再会! オトギの城の竹ちゃん!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reunion! Take-chan of Fairytale Castle!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikai! Otogi no Shiro no Take-chan!</title>
<summary>A sinister force is abducting the top chefs in the world, and an old friend of Komatsu’s may be in great danger! Elsewhere, Toriko and Coco attempt to capture a rare appetizer!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651677</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="145286" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">82</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-11-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">秋山に集合! テリー・ユン・キッス・クイン!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Assemble on Autumn Mountain! Terry, Yun, Kiss, Queen!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akiyama ni Shuugou! Terry Yun Kiss Quin!</title>
<summary>Toriko, Coco, and Sunny race to see who`ll be first to capture a delicious Supear, but their adventure takes a dangerous turn when Komatsu is abducted by Mutton Boars!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651675</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="145287" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">81</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-11-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">極上の千歳飴! 小松とユンの物語</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Supreme Chitose Ame! Komatsu and Yun`s Tale!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gokujou no Chitose Ame! Komatsu to Yun no Monogatari!</title>
<summary>Toriko and Komatsu are asked to track down the ingredients for a very special batch of candy, but the most unlikely of heroes ends up saving the day!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651673</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="145764" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">87</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">メリーイタダキマス! グルメサンタの贈り物!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Merry Feastmas! Gourmet Santa`s Present!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Merry Itadakimasu! Gourmet Santa no Okurimono!</title>
<summary>Chief recruits Toriko and the whole gang to help spread tasty Christmas cheer to hungry kids across the world! Even Zebra manages a good deed by mistake, and the holiday ends with a delicious miracle!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651685</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="145765" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">86</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-12-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">四天王招集! 真冬の夜の奇跡!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gathering of the Four Kings! A Midwinter Night`s Miracle!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shitennou Shoushuu! Mafuyu no Yoru no Kiseki!</title>
<summary>Toriko, Sunny, Coco, and Komatsu brave frigid temperatures and Bison Frogs as they search for a legendary tree that`s entirely edible!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651683</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="145766" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">85</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-12-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">劇的変身! 美容室バーバーグルメ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dramatic Transformation! Hair Salon Barber Gourmet!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekiteki Henshin! Biyoushitsu Barber Gourmet!</title>
<summary>Toriko and Komatsu reunite for some much needed rest and relaxation at a gourmet barber shop. The food is superb, but their hair may never recover!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651681</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="145812" update="2013-04-07">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-01-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146131" update="2013-05-05">
<epno type="1">99</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">走れ最強軍団! トリコとルフィと悟空!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Run, Strongest Army! Toriko, Luffy, and Gokuu!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hashire Saikyou Gundan! Toriko to Luffy to Gokuu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146132" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">98</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">隠された修業食材! 一龍からの緊急指令!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hidden Training Ingredient! Emergency Instruction from Ichiryu!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakusareta Shugyou Shokuzai! Ichiryuu kara no Kinkyuu Shirei!</title>
<summary>Before beginning the search for his next training ingredient, Toriko must defeat a ferocious Devil Planet Horse and then dine with a fortune telling sushi chef!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651707</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146133" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">97</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">頂上対決! 一龍VS[たい]美食會・三虎!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Showdown at the Summit! Ichiryu vs. Midora of the Gourmet Corp.!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Choujou Taiketsu! Ichiryuu Tai Bishokukai Midora!</title>
<summary>Toriko searches for more training ingredients, Komatsu impresses his boss with dazzling new cooking techniques, and Ichiryu comes face-to-face with an old nemesis!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651705</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146134" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">96</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">うまさ宇宙級! 実食メテオガーリック!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Taste That`s out of This World! Eating the Meteor Garlic!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Umaki Uchuukyuu! Jisshoku Meteor Garlic!</title>
<summary>Komatsu gets help preparing the Meteor Garlic from a very unexpected source, and Granny Setsu is paid a visit by the IGO!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651703</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146135" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">95</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">決着の時! ココの壮絶なるシナリオ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Moment of Truth! Coco`s Daring Scenario!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kecchaku no Toki! Coco no Souzetsunaru Scenario!</title>
<summary>The true genius of Coco`s plan is finally revealed as Livebearer finds himself unable to eat the poison potato, but the memory-devouring madman won`t go down without a fight!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651701</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146136" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">94</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">クライマックス! 残された最悪の食材!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Climax! The Last, Most Terrible Ingredients!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Climax! Nokosareta Saiaku no Shokuzai!</title>
<summary>Toriko keeps his team in the game by surviving mouthfuls of Shock Lemons and Nitro Cherries, but if Livebearer can withstand a bite of poison potato - all will be lost!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651699</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146137" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">93</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">食うか食われるか! トリコVS般若パンダ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eat or Be Eaten! Toriko vs. Hanya Panda!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuu ka Kuwareru ka! Toriko VS Hannya Panda!</title>
<summary>Toriko`s slugfest with the Hanya Panda proves to be more brutal than expected, and even if he survives, the difference between victory and defeat may ultimately lie with Komatsu!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651697</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146138" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">92</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ココの策略! 勝負を決めるハズレ食材!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Coco`s Gambit! The Ingredients That Determine Victory or Defeat!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Coco no Sakuryaku! Shoubu o Kimeru Hazure Shokuzai!</title>
<summary>The deadly game unfolding between Coco and Livebearer reaches an unprecedented level of danger as Toriko must face off against a fearsome Hanya Panda to avoid the agony of defeat!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651695</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146139" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">91</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">デッドヒート! ココVS[たい]ライブベアラー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dead Heat! Coco vs. Livebearer!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dead Heat! Coco Tai Livebearer</title>
<summary>Coco and Livebearer continue their epic showdown, but Toriko does most of the heavy lifting, devouring a mountain of pudding and handful of acorns as hard as bullets!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651693</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146140" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">90</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">命がけのカードゲーム! グルメテイスティング!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Life and Death Card Game! Gourmet Tasting!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inochigake no Card Game! Gourmet Tasting!</title>
<summary>Toriko, Komatsu, and Coco go head-to-head with Livebearer in a game of Gourmet Memory that could cost the loser all their memories of ever eating food!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651691</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146141" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">89</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">登場! 地下料理界ボス, ライブベアラー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Enter: The Boss of the Underground Cooking World, Livebearer!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toujou! Chikaryourikai Boss, Livebearer!</title>
<summary>Toriko and the gang make a splash at the casino as they attempt to win enough cash and ingredients to be gain admittance to the VIP area, but what lies ahead could prove deadly!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651689</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146142" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">88</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">天国か地獄か!? 突入, グルメカジノ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heaven or Hell?! Storming Into the Gourmet Casino!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tengoku ka Jigoku ka!? Totsunyuu, Gourmet Casino!</title>
<summary>Toriko, Komatsu, and Coco venture into the Pleasure Zone on quest to track down some extremely rare Meteor Garlic, but they soon cross paths with an old friend who could use their help!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651687</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146834" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">100</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-04-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">百回記念で四天王全員大集合!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Four Kings Assemble to Mark the 100th Episode!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hyakkai Kinen de Shitennou Zen`in Daishuugou!</title>
<summary>In order to find the next training ingredient, Toriko must first get a hold of a Fortune Roll. To that end, Ichiryu gives him emergency instructions: capture the Mistress of the Pond, Madam Fish. And with the rest of the Four Kings?! Is that really a good idea?! In the end, will Toriko and the others be able to carry out their mission?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651709</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148961" update="2013-04-07">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-04-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148962" update="2013-04-07">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-04-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="149676" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">101</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-04-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">トリコ悶絶!? 世界一臭い食材を捕獲せよ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Toriko Faints in Agony?! Capture the World`s Stinkiest Ingredient!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toriko Monzetsu!? Sekaiichi Kusai Shokuzai o Hokaku Seyo!</title>
<summary>Toriko and Komatsu are on the trail of two ingredients needed for the Fortune Roll, which when completed should tell the exact location of one of the last training ingredients. Their first stop is Firewater Island, but can they stop drinking booze long enough to focus on their goal?! Later, Toriko and Komatsu go after the stinkiest ingredient in the world, a Durian Bomb!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651711</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="149677" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">106</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">感謝あるのみ! 食義の極意!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gratitude Is What Counts! The Secret to Honoring the Food!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kansha Aru nomi! Shokugi no Gokui!!</title>
<summary>Toriko and Komatsu train in earnest to master the art of Honoring the Food, but will they starve to death first?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651721</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="149678" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">105</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">トリコ完全敗北!? 繊細かつ豪快, 食義の威力!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Toriko Totally Defeated?! The Delicate and Dynamic Power of Honoring the Food!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toriko Kanzen Haiboku!? Sensai Katsu Goukai, Shokugi no Iryoku!!</title>
<summary>Both Toriko and Komatsu are forced to face off against their Honoring the Food instructor, Shu! Komatsu is worried about Shu`s welfare (and sanity) as the teacher engages in a no-holds-barred fight with Toriko. And then, Toriko has the utmost confidence in Komatsu as the chef goes head-to-head against Shu in a chop-off! Will both students be taken down a peg?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651719</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="149679" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">104</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">感謝なき者入るべからず! 恐怖の食林寺!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">People Without Gratitude Aren`t Welcome! Terrifying Chowlin Temple!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanshanaki Mono Hairubekarazu! Kyoufu no Shokurinji!!</title>
<summary>Master Chin takes Toriko and Komatsu to Chowlin Temple, but the temple itself attacks them and won`t let up, never mind let them in, unless they can manage to feel grateful to everything. The temple isn`t the only thing that`s dangerous, though, as Toriko and Komatsu learn there`s more to Chin than meets the eye.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651717</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="149680" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">103</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">合掌一礼! 美食人間国宝・珍鎮々登場!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Put Your Hands Together and Bow! Gourmet National Treasure, Chin Chin-Chin, Appears!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gasshou Ichirei! Bishoku Ningen Kokuhou Chin Chinchin Toujou!!</title>
<summary>Toriko and Komatsu follow the giant Fortune Roll, eating along the way towards the next training ingredient found somewhere in the Lost Forest... Bubble Fruit! But somehow they encounter a restaurant that vanishes at will and food that`s more difficult to eat than anything they`ve had before!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651715</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="149681" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">102</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-04-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">デカすぎ! プロレス技で巨大恵方巻き完成!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Too Huge! The Giant Fortune Roll, Completed with a Pro Wrestling Move!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dekasugi! Prowres Waza de Kyodai Ehoumaki Kansei!!</title>
<summary>Toriko and Komatsu need to obtain just one more ingredient for sushi chef/fortune teller Monchy to make the Fortune Roll! On the way, they meet old friends (and a friendly rival) before traveling to Eco City, home to Monchy`s double(?!) and lots of eco-friendly animals!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651713</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150650" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">110</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">"国宝級"一振り一億円の技! トリコVS千代婆</title>
<title xml:lang="en">National Treasure Class One Stroke 100 Million Yen Technique! Toriko vs. Granny Chiyo!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Kokuhoukyuu" Hitofuri Ichiokuen no Waza! Toriko Tai Chiyo-baa</title>
<summary>Master Chin lies mortally wounded! Toriko faces off against his opponent, the master of blades, Granny Chiyo! Komatsu is devastated by how far his old friend Otake has fallen! Making matters worse, Otake`s new partner shows up... and it`s a GT Robot?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651729</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150651" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">109</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">剛力無双! 食義を極めし者!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unrivaled Strength! The One Who Mastered Honoring the Food!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gouriki Musou! Shokugi o Kiwameshi Mono!</title>
<summary>Master Chin arrives back at the devastated Chowlin Temple and takes on the leader of the attackers, Chiyo, a famous, super-powerful chef who somehow fell in with Gourmet Corp. A rejuvenated Toriko also come back from his long hike down Bubble Way, but waiting for him is the giant-sized Golem known as a Scum Beast!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651727</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150652" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">108</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">惨劇! 食林寺の終焉... さらば, 小松!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tragedy! The End of Chowlin Temple! Farewell, Komatsu!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sangeki! Shokurinji no Shuuen... Saraba, Komatsu!!</title>
<summary>Will Toriko finally reach the end of Bubble Way and get the Bubble Fruit, or starve to death first? Meanwhile, the assault on Chowlin Temple is well underway, with monsters and led by Chiyo, who`s so good with knives that she can fillet a person without them even noticing!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651725</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150653" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">107</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">迫る脅威! いそげ, トリコ! シャボンフルーツへの道!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Approaching Threat! Hurry, Toriko! The Path to the Bubble Fruit!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Semaru Kyoui! Isoge, Toriko! Shabon Fruits e no Michi!</title>
<summary>Toriko is one step away from obtaining Bubble Fruit... or maybe that`s a million or billion steps, since Bubble Way, the path that leads to the training ingredient, seems to be never-ending. It seems the key to reaching his goal is mastering the secret technique of Food`s End!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651723</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151117" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">111</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">幻の食材"C(センター)" 一龍と最強第0ビオトープ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Legendary Ingredient, `Center`! Ichiryu and the Strongest Biotope, 0!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maboroshi no Shokuzai "Centre" Ichiryuu to Saikyou Dai 0 Biotope</title>
<summary>Master Chin`s mortal wounds are healed with a Revival Knife! He reveals to Toriko and the others what made Chiyo defect to the evil Gourmet Corp. In the Gourmet World, IGO President Ichiryu calls to order an important meeting of the members of Biotope 0. He reveals that Gourmet Corp is after a secret, powerful ingredient, so they have to get it first... except there may be a traitor in their midst!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651731</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151321" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">115</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-07-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">人類の存亡をかけた戦い! 四獣VS四天王!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Battle with the Existence of the Human Race on the Line! The Four-Beasts vs. the Four Kings!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jinrui no Sonbou o Kaketa Tatakai! Shijuu Tai Shitennou!!</title>
<summary>The military throws all of its might against the invading Four-Beasts... and if that isn`t good enough to stop them, there`s always the Four Kings: Toriko, Coco, Sunny, and Zebra!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651739</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151322" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">114</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-07-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">四天王集結! グルメ界の怪物"四獣"の目覚め!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Four Kings Assemble! The Gourmet World Monsters, the Four-Beasts, Awaken!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shitennou Shuuketsu! Gourmet-kai no Kaibutsu "Shijuu" no Mezame!</title>
<summary>The fearsome 100+ Capture Level Four-Beasts awaken and start heading for the Human World from four different directions to chow down! The IGO evacuates billions of people, but only the Four Kings can ensure their safety. Toriko and his brothers-in-arms share one last fine meal before they head out to face creatures fiercer than any they`ve encountered so far.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651737</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151323" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">113</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-07-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">本領発揮! 小松の食義 実食! 幻の麺"全麺"</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Showing His True Ability! A Taste of Komatsu`s Honoring the Food!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Honryou Hakki! Komatsu no Shokugi - Jisshoku! Maboroshi no Men "Zenmen"</title>
<summary>Toriko`s battle with the new type of GT Robot ends unexpectedly, but then it`s Komatsu`s turn to step up to a challenge as he follows Granny Setsu`s recipe for All-Noodles!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651735</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151324" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">112</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-07-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">伝説の蜂"インフィニ・ビー" トリコVS新型GTロボ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Legendary Bee, Infinibee! Toriko vs. New-Style GT Robot!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Densetsu no Hachi "Infini Bee" Toriko Tai Shingata GT Robo</title>
<summary>Humanity watches in horror as the Four-Beasts easily destroy the military`s strongest weapons, but all hope is not lost - the Heavenly Kings are about to join the fight!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651733</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151978" update="2013-07-18">
<epno type="3">C13</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-07-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152232" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">116</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-08-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">トリコ・ココ・サニー・ゼブラ 四天王, 嵐の猛攻!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Toriko, Coco, Sunny, Zebra! The Four Kings` Storming Onslaught!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toriko, Coco, Sunny, Zebra: Shitennou, Arashi no Moukou!!</title>
<summary>The Four Kings go all out against their respective Four-Beasts to save the human race from being devoured! Meanwhile, Komatsu and Rin discover a startling revelation about the Four-Beasts` very nature!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651741</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152270" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">120</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-09-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">奇跡の食運で人類を救え!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Save Humankind with Miraculous Gourmet Luck!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiseki no Shokuun de Jinrui o Sukue!!</title>
<summary>Chefs from all over the world have gathered to save the poisoned human race, but it all depends on Komatsu`s cooking skill!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651749</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152271" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">119</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-09-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">四天王最大の窮地! 小松の決意!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Four Kings` Toughest Predicament! Komatsu`s Resolve!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shitennou Saidai no Kyuuchi! Komatsu no Ketsui!</title>
<summary>The Four Kings throw everything they have against the true form of the Four-Beasts, but it still isn`t enough! Meanwhile, Komatsu and several other great chefs are about to start producing a dish that will neutralize the Green Rain`s poison, but it looks like they`ll only be able to save a fraction of the human race!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651747</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152272" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">118</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-08-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">四獣, 衝撃の合体と緑の雨(グリーンレイン)!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Four-Beasts` Shocking Combined Form and Green Rain!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shijuu, Shougeki no Gattai to Green Rain!!</title>
<summary>The Four Kings have beaten the four Beasts, but now they have to go up against the actual Four-Beasts, a battle that takes place near the refugee center, Food Park Plaza! And as if the Four-Beasts isn`t tough enough, poisonous Green Rain has fallen, giving all who got wet just one hour to live... unless Komatsu can create an antidote for hundreds of millions of people first!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651745</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152273" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">117</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-08-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">トリコ新たなる危機 忍び寄る四獣の本体!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Toriko`s New Crisis! The Creeping Main Body of the Four-Beasts!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toriko Aratanaru Kiki: Shinobiyoru Shijuu no Hontai!!</title>
<summary>Toriko and the other Four Kings finish their battles with the gigantic four Beasts, but little do they know that the Four-Beasts` main body is targeting the evacuated human race directly!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651743</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="153892" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">124</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-10-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">トリコVSグルメ界の怪物"モンプラン"</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Toriko vs. the Monster of the Gourmet World, Mon Plan!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toriko Tai Gourmet-kai no Kaibutsu "Monplan"</title>
<summary>Toriko and a few friends track down a giant plant monster from the Gourmet World! Sunny revisits Death Falls and meets an oil artisan! Coco returns to the Gourmet Casino, where he bets against Match! And Zebra goes back to the destroyed Gourmet Pyramid, but something is still alive in there!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651757</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="153893" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">123</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-09-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">来るべき祭典 うごめく"ヤバイ奴ら"</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Upcoming Festival! Dangerous Wriggling Critters!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kitarubeki Saiten: Ugomeku "Yabai Yatsura"</title>
<summary>Fortunately, Teppei has survived his encounter with the mastermind behind Four-Beasts, but the mysterious figure isn`t done with him yet! Then Komatsu gets some startling news from two visiting members of G7!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651755</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="153894" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">122</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-09-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">奥義 "王食晩餐"</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Secret Technique: Meal Fit for a King!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ougi "Oushoku Bansan"</title>
<summary>The Four Kings turn the tables on the apex predator of the Human World, Four-Beasts, by unleashing the secret technique, Meal Fit for a King. It looks like humanity has dodged a bullet this time, but the grand manipulator behind Four Beasts is lurking around...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651753</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="153895" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">121</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-09-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">炸裂! 味への好奇心! 四天王合体技!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Burst! Curiosity About the Flavor! The Four Kings` Combined Skill!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakuretsu! Aji e no Koukishin! Shitennou Gattai Waza!!</title>
<summary>With the Four Kings on the brink of death, the Four-Beasts is triumphant, but Toriko and friends have one last trick up their sleeves to save the human race!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651751</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="154890" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">128</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-11-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">伝説の料理人 天狗のブランチ, 見参!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Meet Legendary Chef Brunch the Tengu!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Densetsu no Ryourinin: Tengu no Branch, Kenzan!!</title>
<summary>The strange but popular and powerful Chef Brunch enters the fray, better late than never! After hearing the Four Kings brag about Komatsu, Brunch is mighty disappointed when he first meets the last-place chef. Can Komatsu change his mind?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651765</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="154891" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">127</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-10-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">小松ピンチ!? トライアスロンクッキング!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Komatsu Is in a Pinch?! Triathlon Cooking!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Komatsu Pinch!? Triathlon Cooking!</title>
<summary>The preliminary round of the Cooking Festival begins, and it`s a grueling Cooking Triathlon that will eliminate 50 of the 100 participating chefs! Will Komatsu make the cut or will his inability to swim sink his chances?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651763</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="154892" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">126</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-10-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大波乱必至!? クッキングフェス開幕!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inevitable Turmoil?! The Cooking Fest Begins!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daiharan Hisshi!? Cooking Fes Kaimaku!!</title>
<summary>The Cooking Festival begins! But will Komatsu be able to get overcome his nervousness at facing off against 99 of the top-ranked chefs worldwide, while being watched by a live audience of 100 million people?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651761</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="154893" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">125</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-10-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">トリコ新技"ネイルガン"!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Toriko`s New Attack, `Nail Gun`!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toriko Shinwaza "Nailgun"!!</title>
<summary>Toriko unleashes a new attack against the seemingly unstoppable Mon Plan from the Gourmet World! The other members of the Four Kings track down ingredients for the Cooking Fest too, even as sinister forces gather...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651759</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="155384" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">132</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-12-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">開戦! 美食會, 激烈の総攻撃!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Outbreak of War! Gourmet Corp.`s Fierce Full-Scale Offensive!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaisen! Bishokukai, Gekiretsu no Soukougeki!!</title>
<summary>Gourmet Corp. invades the Cooking Fest as Komatsu is groping around in the dark for his Darkness Cooking Duel with Zaus! Will the beginning of the final tournament also be its end?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>647001</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="155385" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">131</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-11-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">最強コンビはだれだ? 島を丸ごとクッキング!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Who Are the Strongest Partners? Whole Island Cooking!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikyou Combi wa Dare Da? Shima o Marugoto Cooking!!</title>
<summary>It`s the third round of the Cooking Fest and Toriko finally gets something to do as he teams up with Komatsu in an event called Whole Island Cooking! They choose an island with an abundance of delicious ingredients... only to find it`s actually an overabundance!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>646999</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="155386" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">130</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-11-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">生きるか死ぬか 天秤デスクッキング!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Live or Die? Death in the Balance Cooking!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikiru ka Shinu ka: Tenbin Death Cooking!!</title>
<summary>Komatsu`s fate is in the balance as he`s in a cook-off with Oil Artisan Wabutora that employs a giant scale and roiling flames for the chef on the losing end!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>646997</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="155387" update="2014-07-06">
<epno type="1">129</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-11-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ド卑劣! 爆走! ブランチ, ごぼう抜き!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Playing Dirty! Roaring Ahead! Brunch Overtakes Everyone in a Single Spurt!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Do Hiretsu! Bakusou! Branch, Gobounuki!!</title>
<summary>Giraffe Birds and Sand Hamsters make their presence felt, Komatsu catches a lift with Brunch, and Triathlon Cooking kicks into high gear!</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651767</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="156381" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">136</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-01-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">最悪の切り札! グルメ界の怪物"ニトロ"</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Worst Trump Card! The Gourmet World Monster, "Nitro"!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saiaku no Kirifuda! Gourmet Kai no Kaibutsu "Nitro"</title>
<summary>When the chefs and Gourmet Hunters start holding their own against the Gourmet Corp. horde, the latter puts into play its deadliest trump card, the savage, well-nigh invincible Nitro! Plus, the ultimate match-up between Toriko and Starjun continues!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>649063</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="156382" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">135</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-12-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">頂上決戦! IGO VS 美食會</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Climactic Battle! IGO versus Gourmet Corp.!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Choujou Kessen! IGO Tai Bishokukai</title>
<summary>Battles are going on all over Cooking Stadium! Toriko is in an escalating fight with Starjun, but is already almost out of energy! And Mansom has unleashed his true potential to wipe out an army of giant GT Robots, but that also means losing control of himself!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>647007</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="156383" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">134</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-12-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">野生の闘い! トリコ, 最強攻撃!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Savage Battle! Toriko`s Strongest Attack!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yasei no Tatakai! Toriko, Saikyou Kougeki!!</title>
<summary>When they first met, Starjun didn`t give Toriko a second glance. Now, in the pandemonium that has become of the Cooking Festival, Toriko shows what he`s learned to Vice-chef Starjun in a fierce battle. And if Toriko loses, Komatsu will be made the next captive chef of Gourmet Corp.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>647005</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="156384" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">133</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-12-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">小松を守れ! トリコVSスタージュン!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Protect Komatsu! Toriko vs. Starjun!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Komatsu o Mamore! Toriko Tai Starjun!!</title>
<summary>There`s pandemonium at Cooking Stadium as Gourmet Corp. and their menagerie disrupt the Cooking Fest and threaten to eat the millions of spectators! Meanwhile, the Four Kings are doing everything they can to keep Komatsu from being kidnapped by Starjun!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>647003</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157025" update="2014-01-04">
<epno type="3">C14</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-10-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157026" update="2014-01-04">
<epno type="3">C15</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2014-01-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157084" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">140</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-02-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">逆襲! ゼブラ始動!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Counterattack! Zebra Starts Up!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gyakushuu! Zebra Shidou!!</title>
<summary>Zebra takes on all of Gourmet Corp.`s Nitro at once! Plus, Setsuno versus her old rival, Chiyo! Traitors are revealed within the ranks of IGO! And Komatsu sees a startling sight!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>649687</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157085" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">139</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-01-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">決着の時! サニー, 最後の力!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The End Is Here! Sunny`s Final Power!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kecchaku no Toki! Sunny, Saigo no Chikara!!</title>
<summary>The conclusion to the epic battle between Sunny and Tommyrod! Komatsu`s old friend stumbles onto a conspiracy that overshadows both IGO and Gourmet Corp.! And Brunch pits his electric-based powers against Elg, an immortal centaur!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>649069</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157086" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">138</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-01-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">決闘! サニーVS[たい]トミーロッド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Duel! Sunny vs. Tommyrod!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kettou! Sunny Tai Tommyrod</title>
<summary>Sunny squares off against Tommyrod, master of disgusting bugs! Tommyrod`s insect arsenal has expanded since he last fought Toriko, but Sunny also has a new power... except instead of controlling it, the power may end up controlling him!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>649067</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157087" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">137</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-01-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">死闘! ココVS[たい]グリンパーチ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mortal Combat! Coco vs. Grinpatch!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shitou! Coco Tai Grinparch</title>
<summary>Only Coco stands between Komatsu and Grinpatch, but the gluttonous Vice-chef can`t get enough of Coco`s poison! Coco imparts an urgent oracular message to Komatsu, then stakes his life on one last shot, but first he needs to take Grinpatch far, far away...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>649065</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157686" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">144</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-03-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">終わりの始まり! トリコVS[たい]ジョア!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Beginning of the End! Toriko vs. Joie!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Owari no Hajimari! Toriko Tai Joa!!</title>
<summary>Joie intends to abduct Komatsu, an idea that both Toriko and Starjun are dead-set against! Meanwhile, the final battle between Ichiryu and Midora rages on! Plus, learn about the connection between these two leaders and Acacia!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>649695</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157687" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">143</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-02-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">驚愕! 黒幕"ジョア"の正体!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shock! The True Identity of the Mastermind, "Joie"!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyougaku! Kuromaku "Joa" no Shoutai!!</title>
<summary>Knocking Master Jiro comes to Setsuno`s rescue against the mysterious and utterly powerful Joie! Will Jiro be able to unmask this new interloper? Meanwhile, Ichiryu and Midora begin their final face-off in the Gourmet World!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>649693</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157688" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">142</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-02-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">史上最大の敵! "ジョア"出現!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Greatest Enemy in History! "Joie" Appears!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shijou Saidai no Teki! "Joa" Shutsugen!!</title>
<summary>The fiery battle between Toriko and Starjun ends here! Will either one of them be able to walk away? And Joie, the power and enigmatic Dark Chef, leader of NEO, appears, but for what purpose? Other than trying to kill Setsuno, that is...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>649691</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157689" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">141</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-02-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">トリコ, 反撃! アルティメットルーティーン!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Toriko Strikes Back! Ultimate Routine!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toriko, Hangeki! Ultimate Routine!!</title>
<summary>Komatsu arrives just in time to see Starjun murder Toriko... except the end of the battle proves to be just the beginning, as Toriko comes back thanks to striking a bargain with his "inner demon"! Now it`s Toriko`s turn to show what he learned from Aimaru... the Ultimate Routine!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>649689</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158253" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">147</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-03-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トリコと小松 新たな旅の出発!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Toriko and Komatsu Embark on a New Voyage!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toriko to Komatsu: Arata na Tabi no Shuppatsu!!</title>
<summary>The finale of the battle between Toriko and Joie! The Human World is devastated by a storm of mysterious meteorites! Amongst a backdrop of hope, forgiveness, and devious plans, Toriko and Komatsu embark on their greatest challenge: surviving a new world!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651367</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158254" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">146</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-03-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">届け, 小松の叫び! トリコ覚醒!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Be Heard, Komatsu`s Scream! Toriko Revives!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Todoke, Komatsu no Sakebi! Toriko Kakusei!!</title>
<summary>With the Four Kings utterly defeated, Joie is about to take Komatsu away, until Toriko tries one last, desperate gambit, which could make him lose control of himself and kill even his dearest friends! Meanwhile, the final battle between Ichiryu and Midora ends with a bang!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651365</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158255" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">145</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-03-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">起死回生の一撃! 四天王, 究極技!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Resuscitation Strike! The Four Kings` Ultimate Skill!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kishikaisei no Ichigeki! Shitennou, Kyuukyoku Waza!!</title>
<summary>The Four Kings fight together against Joie, the strongest enemy they`ve ever faced and one who can`t be eaten! Meanwhile, NEO gets ready to leave the chaos of the stadium and indeed the Human World behind them, but they also plan to take Komatsu with them, whether he`s willing or not!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651363</identifier>
<identifier>toriko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
