<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8154" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-04-12</startdate>
<enddate>2011-06-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Seikon no Qwaser II</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Seikon no Qwaser 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">seikon 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">qwaser 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">SnQ2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Qwaser2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">聖痕のクェイサーII</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The Qwaser of Stigmata II</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">圣痕炼金士 II</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6816" type="Prequel">Seikon no Qwaser</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="466811">I`ll keep it very simple.
For plot - Stop watching the season after the ending battle at the new school.
For shameless amounts of fan service - keep watching after the above mentioned.
Season two`s plot lacks a lot compared to the plot of Season 1, and it really shouldn`t require more than 6 or 7 episodes as is the new school part of Season 2.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.qwaser.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1540" type="Series Composition">Uezu Makoto</name>
<name id="3097" type="Direction">Kaneko Hiraku</name>
<name id="11225" type="Animation Work">Hoods Entertainment</name>
<name id="3672" type="Character Design">Sugimoto Isao</name>
<name id="4250" type="Original Work">Yoshino Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="10188" type="Original Work">Satou Ken`etsu</name>
<name id="3672" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sugimoto Isao</name>
<name id="10106" type="Music">Katou Tatsuya</name>
<name id="16146" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yamamoto Akihiro</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a manga series authored by http://anidb.net/cr4250 [Yoshino Hiroyuki], featuring art by http://anidb.net/cr10188 [Satou Ken`etsu], serialised in the shounen manga magazine http://anidb.net/cr32008 [Champion Red].
The High Ancient Circuit — The witnesses of its existence: Maria of Sword, Magdalena of Thunder, Noah of Gold, Moses of Silence, and David of Resurrection. These five items are the only ones in existence, and cannot be reproduced or copied. Whatever it is that gave birth to the circuit itself is also completely unknown... — from intro
The Church sends http://anidb.net/ch11297 [Sasha the Martyr] on an important mission with http://anidb.net/ch12417 [Katsuragi Hana] to retrieve the long lost Magdalena of Thunder. Apparently a girl at the Japan Seirei Private Academy, an all-girl school, is endowed with this artefact. The Adepts sect is also aware of the Magdalena of Thunder`s location, and has begun to interfere...
— written by foo2
Note: Again every TV broadcast is heavily censored.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="980">2.89</permanent>
<temporary count="999">5.75</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>64992.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12359</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10920</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>10073</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4874</identifier>
<identifier>gotzsh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.qwaser.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>The_Qwaser_of_Stigmata</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>聖痕のクェイサー</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2121</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>339114</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13437</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="301" parentid="2848" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-10">
<name>lactation</name>
<description>Capable of secreting breast milk, sometimes referred to as Mother`s milk.</description>
<picurl>176139.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1136" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-18">
<name>transfer student</name>
<description>A transfer student is a student who changes from one institution or course to another at the same level. Their arrival, when not at the beginning of the school year, tends to cause a stir.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1774" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-05">
<name>gigantic breasts</name>
<description>Gigantic breasts are unnaturally large breasts, even by anime standards; they are true gargantuan monstrosities, either because of sheer size or through the combination of size and exceedingly unnatural shape. Essentially, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are gigantic; smaller breasts are the more common http://anidb.net/t2741 [large breasts], even if they`re as big as the character`s head.</description>
<picurl>160446.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2671" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>school dormitory</name>
<description>A school dormitory or residence hall is the student living quarters at an elite academy, boarding school, or military school. The main characters may live or work at the dormitory, and it often becomes the backdrop for a reoccurring part of the story.</description>
<picurl>223167.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2823" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>paper clothes</name>
<description>Worn clothing appears paper-thin and takes little abuse to be shredded or torn from the body. This is common in ecchi anime where the main storyline involves some type of fighting but consists primarily of dialogue and fanservice (Ikkitousen and Platonic Heart). Various girls’ clothing exploding as if made of rice paper is a very enticing prospect.</description>
<picurl>150776.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2828" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-26">
<name>borderline porn</name>
<description>Breaks the bounds of "excessive fanservice".
While the physical interactions and dialogue between characters may be extremely sexual, the most sexual situations do *not* have sex itself take place.
Specifically descriptive of containing all the plentiful features of (excessive) fanservice in addition to the interactions between characters being quite sexual — at most, sexual in NATURE only. This means physical touching such as groping, molesting, or bondage will focus primarily on the revealed (i.e. nude) upper portion of the body or through/over clothing on the lower half of the body. This is all WITHOUT actual sex acts (penetration, etc.) taking place.</description>
<picurl>214855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2829" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-21">
<name>shower scene</name>
<description>The anime contains a shower scene, obligatory for ecchi anime. The person under the shower will most likely be female — providing "fanservice".</description>
<picurl>208635.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2830" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>furo scene</name>
<description>Furo (polite: Ofuro) is Japanese for bath, specifically a type of bath which originated as a short, steep-sided wooden bathtub. Baths of this type are found all over Japan in houses, apartments and traditional Japanese inns (Ryokans).
Furo are part of the Japanese ritual of bathing, not used for washing but for relaxing and warming oneself. Washing is carried out separately outside the furo, and only when completely clean does the bather enter the water. Generally Japanese bathrooms are small, so the bathroom is set up much like a walk-in shower area but containing the ofuro.
The cheapest and shortest way to show naked skin on TV, at least as much as allowed. It usually only takes up few minutes at most and as such it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales while still maintaining a "non-filler" episode.
Compare to the big brothers http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode] and http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160785.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3575" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-13">
<name>damsel in distress</name>
<description>The damsel in distress is usually a young, nubile woman placed in a dire predicament by a villain or a monster and requires a hero to dash to her rescue. Often used to unite the cast of a show for this one goal, to make them put differences aside and become a band of nakama. 
Examples: Sakoshita Yanagi from Rekka no Honoo, Yuuki Miaka from Fushigi Yuugi or Higurashi Kagome from Inuyasha.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3908" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-02">
<name>lap pillow</name>
<description>As a sign of closeness the usually male character is encouraged to rest his weary head on the female’s lap.</description>
<picurl>167007.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3909" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>talking is a free action</name>
<description>Time in comics is flexible. Each panel shows a single event, which is usually accompanied by a length of dialog, which must take some time to say. This disparity is usually accepted if it isn`t taken to extremes.
But often, characters will exposit when it`s most needed: at the story`s climax, when both the intricacies of the plot and the intensity of action hit their highest.
While the Heroes Outrun the Fireball, Mr. Exposition might explain why the Evil Overlord`s death caused the explosion. The Action Girl can deliver impressive lectures on why the monster`s Achilles` Heel will work, while still engaging in Waif-Fu. The Superhero can quip to his heart`s content and explain his abilities while dueling one insignificant mobster, or deliver a Kirk Summation during the course of a single Finishing Move. Sometimes even apparent mere mortals can give a lecture on what is happening when it would be a much better idea to simply run like hell.
Without stopping to breathe, apparently.
Source: TvTrope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4112" parentid="3842" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-14">
<name>excessive censoring</name>
<description>There are basically two cases to which this term can be applied to:
1) creative censorship
The TV station airing the anime does its best to remove most ecchi parts from the show, using various and original methods. Usually, an uncensored BD/DVD is released later. Apart from the publisher`s greed - sometimes the censorship is used intentionally to make a scene look more obscene than it actually is.
2) convenient censorship
Another case of it - more often known under the term of "convenient censoring/ship" - is a blatant substitute for mosaic/steam/etc. over nether regions. This applies both to normal shows with occasional nudity as a normal part of human life (or just occasional flash of fanservice), as well as to heavy ecchi / borderline hentai shows where /literally/ everything is a fair (and far more "obscene" no matter how to look at it) game, except that misinterpreted taboo nonsense coming from §175 of JPC.</description>
<picurl>169459.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4302" parentid="2876" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-11-24">
<name>Christianity</name>
<description>Christianity is a monotheistic religion based on the life and teachings of Jesus of Nazareth as presented in the New Testament. http://anidb.net/t524 [Christians] believe Jesus is the son of God, God having become man and the saviour of humanity. Christians, therefore, commonly refer to Jesus as Christ or Messiah.
Source: EN Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5705" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-08-18">
<name>butchered foreign languages</name>
<description>In this anime, some characters "speak" foreign languages, successfully making the audience`s ears bleed. That is especially true if the viewer is a native speaker of or otherwise proficient in the languages in question.
The foreigners in the show do not seem to take much notice of the fact that their supposed native languages are being massacred. In fact, oftentimes they also actively participate in the butchering of said languages. That happens, of course, because they, too, are voiced by Japanese people without knowledge of the language they`re supposed to speak, or to pretend to speak at any rate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5859" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-30">
<name>monster of the week</name>
<description>On a pretty much regular basis — weekly or episodic — the protagonists engage in some kind of conflict. This can be an actual showdown between mecha, or the all-out fight against an enemy, or a (car) race that needs to be won.
This can make the anime quite repetitive.</description>
<picurl>60013.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6083" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>master-servant relationship</name>
<description>To some genres, this would suggest a genuine pairing where one person exists to serve another person, such as in some action/dramas where the pair becomes united by destiny as partners — fighting or battles between different pairs/partners will usually be a dominant part of the story.
In other genres, this suggests a relationship where one person may be occupied as or even forcefully treated as a servant or slave to the other who designates themself the master — these services usually apply anywhere from tsundere/romantic-comedies to ecchi or to the more extreme in hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="11293" type="main character in" update="2010-04-26">
<rating votes="76">7.41</rating>
<name>Oribe Mafuyu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The titular female character, Mafuyu is the adopted daughter of St.Mihailov`s last dean, and the self-appointed protector of Yamanobe Tomo. Upbeat and cheerful, she is so proficient in kendo that she carries a wooden sword with her all the time. She has to endure hardship on a daily basis in form of her classmates picking harshly on her and especially Tomo. This changes when she encounters Sasha for the first time, where she starts living with him and, little by little, is pitted herself in the fights between Qwasers. Though at odds with Sasha`s coldness, Mafuyu has started to open up to him and the two have formed a stronger bond. A running gag has Mafuyu hit heavily Tomo when the latter makes mistakes.</description>
<picture>46957.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11294" type="main character in" update="2010-04-26">
<rating votes="71">6.24</rating>
<name>Yamanobe Tomo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Daughter of St. Mihailov`s last dean and currently best friend and roommate of Oribe Mafuyu, Tomo is her exact opposite, both physically and mentally: she herself is very childish and naïve, and while having the largest bust of the whole female cast so far, she is physically weak. Tomo is the spitting image of Sasha`s original protector, Olja, which explains why he took so willingly the role of Tomo`s guardian, much to Mafuyu`s chagrin. Also, sometimes an upside down Eastern Cross (with its third slab being a scar), the symbol of the Adepts, appears between her breasts. This is later revealed to be the presence of the Qwaser of Gold, which apparently inhabits Tomo`s body and, as itself stated, is slowly draining her of her life, which is why she has to replenish herself through Teresa`s Soma.</description>
<picture>46958.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11296" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-26">
<rating votes="107">6.99</rating>
<name>Katya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A little Russian girl, no more than ten years old and with the beauty of a doll, she arrives in Japan shortly after the beginning of the war of the Qwasers. While she is presented as extremely shy and child-like, befitting her age (she has a habit of addressing herself in third person in these instances), her true colours depicts her as a domineering, arrogant, prideful and almost malicious queen, all maintaining a façade of childish innocence. She is a powerful Qwaser who wields the element of copper, which usually makes her gain control and manipulate electrical wires and redirect their flow to electrocute and incinerate her foes. She does not fight herself due to her frailty as a little girl, and this is why she is always guarded by a grim, archaic gynoid dressed in regal attire named Anastasia, which Ekaterina calls mother for reason currently unknown. Currently she attends at St. Mihailov`s primary school, being the subject of admiration and love of her classmates and teachers thanks to her doll-like features, and has Hana serve as her slave and replenish her of Soma. Recently, it has been revealed that she shares heavy connections with the Imperial Family of late Tsar Nicholas II, and it is heavily hinted that she herself is the same Tsarina Alexandra that served as Nicholas` consort, though this is has not been proved, just suggested by Ekaterina herself (although this would also explain why her guardian gynoid is named Anastasia).</description>
<picture>46967.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4" picture="177060.jpg">Hirano Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11297" type="main character in" update="2010-04-26">
<rating votes="55">6.45</rating>
<name>Sasha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The titular character and male protagonist of the story, Alexander is a young Qwaser of Russian origin that controls the element of Iron, with which he can manipulate the said element on a molecular level, thus being capable not only to morph it in any form he wishes, but also create extreme heat or cold. He was held captive and trained with the other Qwasers into harnessing his powers, and survived the brutal ordeal thanks to the affection received from an older girl named Olja, and whose murder by the Qwaser of Gold he witnessed. He received a large scar on the left side of his face from the same Qwaser. The scar is shaped like an Eastern Cross, and tends to bleed heavily when he draws upon his powers. He appeared out of nowhere on the grounds of St. Mihailov, and was quickly accepted into the school as a student of class 1-A, the same that Mafuyu Oribe and Tomo Yamanobe attend. He became Tomo`s protector because of her resemblance to Olja. Silver-haired with blue eyes, Alexander, or Sasha for short (though he allows only those close to him to call him by this nickname) is usually extremely cold, harsh and serious, although his weakness for borscht, his favourite dish, can soften him. He slowly changed and warmed to those around him, especially Mafuyu, though he remains extremely fierce when fighting other Qwasers. Usually he fights wielding an enormous black scythe that is at least twice his size. Sometimes he tends to comment on things in Russian.</description>
<picture>46956.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="81" picture="41282.jpg">Sanpei Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12417" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-26">
<rating votes="70">6.21</rating>
<name>Katsuragi Hana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A student of class 1-A, she acts as an enforcer on school grounds, but also she is the main architect of the physical abuses that Mafuyu and Tomo have to endure every day, such as regularly throwing the class` garbage can on them or forcing them to fill it after "casually" tripping on it, to covering Tomo`s desk with writings and trash. Being the right hand of Miyuri, she welcomes Ekaterina Kurae when she arrives in Japan, and it`s here that her apparent fondness for lolicon is discovered, as she becomes extremely embarrassed in Ekaterina`s presence and, while the latter fakes to fade out, she kisses her out of lust. These events let her become the unwilling slave of her new mistress, subject to humiliation and erotic torment on a daily basis (which, on a side note, made her very proficient in S&amp;M, such as making extremely complex nodes with little effort). She appears to have some masochistic tendencies, as she derives pleasure from Ekaterina`s abuses.</description>
<picture>46973.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12418" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-29">
<rating votes="66">7.81</rating>
<name>Tsujidou Miyuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The daughter of the current dean at St. Mihailov Academy, who succeeded Tomo`s father. While beautiful and well-endowed, Miyuri is extremely bossy, arrogant and prideful, making nothing to conceal her disrespect for Tomo and Mafuyu and to bully them on a daily basis, supported by Hana. Greatly humiliated by Sasha, who correctly defines her as a leecher of others` powers, she "takes revenge" by welcoming and taking care of Ekaterina Kurae, the Quaser of Copper. It can be noted that Miyuri is very rich and appears to have a sheltered upbringing, based on her drowning Ekaterina with expensive gifts. However, being treated as a fool after Sasha`s arrival made her somewhat of a comic relief character. On a positive note, it can be assumed that she truly cares even for those she bullies, as she stripped naked for a group of terrorists so as to spare the same ordeal to Ekaterina, Mafuyu and the others.</description>
<picture>39436.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12419" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-22">
<rating votes="58">6.77</rating>
<name>Mitarai Fumika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The class president.</description>
<picture>39437.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13999" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-10">
<rating votes="8">6.43</rating>
<name>Yuuri Noda</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41277.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="375" picture="17221.jpg">Chiba Susumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15808" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-14">
<rating votes="35">8.52</rating>
<name>Oikawa Urara</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44606.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15809" type="appears in" update="2010-03-14">
<rating votes="31">6.72</rating>
<name>Elizabeth</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl with short blonde hair and red eyes, whose undeveloped body, brash manners and manner of dressing make similar to a boy, she is a disciple to Shin`ichiro Ootori and a Qwaser herself, whose element is titanium, that she primarily wields in a massive double-handed greatsword she calls Excalibur, after the legendary blade from the Arthurian myth, which can not only cut through practically anything, but when drawn produces a deafening wail. Deeply loyal to her master, she bitterly followed him when he feigned treachery so as to draw the Qwaser of Gold out of hiding, where she provided defence for him by challenging Sasha, who however spared her life. After Ootori`s death she accepted Teresa as her partner and joined the ranks of Athos, thus becoming an ally to Sasha and his companions.</description>
<picture>44607.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="550" picture="151677.jpg">Shimizu Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19030" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-20">
<rating votes="9">5.59</rating>
<name>Jita Phrygianos</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50050.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="142" picture="68482.jpg">Ooura Fuyuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19033" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-20">
<rating votes="3">2.71</rating>
<name>Wan Chen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50054.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="373" picture="191382.jpg">Hamada Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26398" type="appears in" update="2011-01-03">
<rating votes="15">5.52</rating>
<name>Shiizaki Lulu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61942.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1511" picture="173601.jpg">Akesaka Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28324" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-19">
<rating votes="8">5.49</rating>
<name>Amano Tsubasa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70181.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="617" picture="65451.jpg">Nanjou Yoshino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28325" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-19">
<rating votes="7">6.75</rating>
<name>Seta Miyuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70180.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1918" picture="225099.jpg">Sakurai Harumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28326" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-19">
<rating votes="9">5.48</rating>
<name>Satsuki Ayame</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70179.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="578" picture="193571.jpg">Tatsumi Yuiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31556" type="main character in" update="2011-04-26">
<rating votes="6">4.77</rating>
<name>Alexandra Hell</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70533.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="81" picture="41282.jpg">Sanpei Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36126" type="appears in" update="2011-08-31">
<rating votes="2">4.43</rating>
<name>Shiba Emi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50774.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="216" picture="171983.jpg">Takahashi Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36127" type="appears in" update="2011-08-31">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Wan Chen (Kodomo)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50775.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28272" picture="51017.jpg">Betsui Tomomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36128" type="appears in" update="2011-12-15">
<name>Edgar</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78560.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1609" picture="19579.jpg">Mizuhara Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36129" type="appears in" update="2011-12-15">
<name>Clifford C.J. Crawford</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78561.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="369" picture="223406.jpg">Aoyama Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36130" type="appears in" update="2011-12-15">
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<name>Hiiragi Yumie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78557.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36131" type="appears in" update="2011-12-15">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Okiura Nami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78558.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="89" picture="148709.jpg">Yahagi Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36173" type="appears in" update="2011-09-01">
<name>Athos</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="36174" type="appears in" update="2011-09-05">
<name>Adept</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Adept is a secret group of thirteen Qwasers who, much like Athos, desire to uncover the Theotokos, though apparently to use its powers for their own ends. They were introduced as a cult-like organisation best known for its extreme brutality and harsh ways to initiate new members, willing or not, to their cause. Sasha was part of their ranks before being wounded and banished by the Qwaser of Gold, who appears to be the sect`s leader. However, recent chapters have revealed the group to be far less sinister, showing them to be respectable - albeit still sinister - people. Subsidiary to the Adepts appears to be a secretive organisation known as Paracelsus, formed from the remnants of Japan`s Unit 731 and the Nazi eugenics program, whose members, through demented medical science, can conquer feat deemed impossible and blasphemous, such as reviving the dead and cloning at will. Their base appears to be a secluded place named Magnolia, the ruins of a fortress splendidly decorate by lush gardens, which stands in stark contrast with the grim portrait of the organisation.</description>
</character>
<character id="36175" type="appears in" update="2011-09-01">
<name>Meteora</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Meteora is a troop of executioners of Athos, known for their might and ruthlessness, according to Sasha they destroy everything that stands in their way. The Meteors have their vision of Athos and believe the current organization to not be enough to save the world, thus taking matters in their own hands.</description>
</character>
<character id="39674" type="appears in" update="2011-12-15">
<rating votes="6">8.45</rating>
<name>Madam Lily</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78559.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39675" type="appears in" update="2011-12-15">
<name>Leon Max Mueller</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78563.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20249" picture="186289.jpg">Matsuoka Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76933" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-08-20">
<rating votes="5">7.23</rating>
<name>Big Mom</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The strongest tactician of the Athos. She is a strong muscled woman who wears a nun uniform, known as Big Ma`am. Her real name is Nikuma. Nikuma is a burly woman and the best strategist of Athos according to Teresa. Referred to as "Hell`s Dairy Cow" by Teresa, she is a master tactician and trainer for the Qwasers of Athos. She also handles the occasional training of the group of Qwasers at the St. Mihailov Academy. She has a military attitude and is harsh in her methods, but despite this she has the best intentions.</description>
<picture>176542.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36" picture="228350.jpg">Saitou Kimiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="128674" update="2011-03-10">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">銀色の百合姫</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Lily Princess of Silver</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gin`iro no Yuri Hime</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129380" update="2011-04-12">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔女の生贄</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Witch`s Living Sacrifice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Majo no Ikenie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129381" update="2011-04-12">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">荊の檻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Cage of Thorns</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ibara no Ori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129382" update="2011-04-12">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">玻璃の罠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Trap of Quartz</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hari no Wana</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129383" update="2011-04-12">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">携香女(マグダラ)の在処(ありか)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Location of the Magdalene</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Magudara no Arika</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130051" update="2011-05-10">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドキ☆ドキ創立祭</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Exciting Founding Celebrations</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Doki Doki Souritsu Matsuri</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130052" update="2011-05-10">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">美しき挑戦者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Beautiful Contender</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Utsukushiki Chousensha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130053" update="2011-05-10">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">マダム・リリィのおっぱい占い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Breast Divination of Madame Lily</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Madame Lily no Oppai Uranai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130054" update="2011-05-10">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">再会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reunion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130698" update="2011-06-07">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">聖痕のくぇ☆いさー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stigmata * Qwaser</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seikon no Qwaser</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130752" update="2011-06-10">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">平穏は終わりを告げ, 運命の歯車は回りだす</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Calm Before the Storm &amp; the Wheels of Fate Begin to Turn</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Heion wa Owari o Tsuge, Unmei no Haguruma wa Mawari Dasu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130753" update="2011-06-10">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">含鉄泉(がんてつせん)の夜2 ~吸ったら驚いた~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Night at the Iron Spring 2: Suck It and Be Surprised</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gantetsusen no Yoru 2: Suttara Odoroita</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132058" update="2011-08-31">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2011-07-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">カーチャ様と遊ぼうスペシャル☆第一夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama: Play with Katya-sama Special - First Night</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Katja-sama to Asobou Special: Dai Ichi Ya</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132571" update="2011-08-31">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2011-08-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">カーチャ様と遊ぼうスペシャル☆第二夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama: Play with Katya-sama Special - Second Night</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Katja-sama to Asobou Special: Dai Ni Ya</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132756" update="2012-06-12">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-04-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132757" update="2011-11-07">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-04-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132759" update="2011-08-31">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2011-10-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">カーチャ様と遊ぼうスペシャル ☆ 第四夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama: Play with Katya-sama Special - Fourth Night</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Katja-sama to Asobou Special: Dai Shi Ya</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132760" update="2011-08-31">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2011-09-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">カーチャ様と遊ぼうスペシャル ☆ 第三夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama: Play with Katya-sama Special - Third Night</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Katja-sama to Asobou Special: Dai San Ya</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134097" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2011-09-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview of ep 8-9-10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134098" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2011-08-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview of ep 5-6-7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134571" update="2012-06-12">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-06-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134572" update="2011-11-02">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>9</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD/BD ads collection</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134573" update="2017-08-25">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV ads collection</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176448" update="2017-08-25">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-10-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview of ep 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176449" update="2016-03-28">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2011-07-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview of ep 2-4</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
