<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8159" restricted="false">
<type>Music Video</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-01-01</startdate>
<enddate>2011-01-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Naruto x UT</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Naruto Shippuuden OVA: Sage Naruto vs Sasuke</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Naruto x Uniqlo</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">NARUTO×UT</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4880" type="Parent Story">Naruto Shippuuden</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://store.uniqlo.com/jp/store/feature/ut/naruto/</url>
<description>A DVD offered in UNIQLO clothing stores. A limited number of DVDs were offered as presents to people who bought UNIQLO`s Naruto graphic T-shirts online or in Japan` stores.
The DVD contains an original Naruto anime video that summarises the bonds and rivalry between http://anidb.net/ch226 [Naruto] and http://anidb.net/ch7719 [Sasuke] on an exclusive version of http://anidb.net/s40083 [Mayonaka no Orchestra], a song by the Japanese rock band http://anidb.net/cr4021 [Aqua Timez].</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="740">4.64</permanent>
<temporary count="755">6.48</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>61118.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10075</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://store.uniqlo.com/jp/store/feature/ut/naruto/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2572" parentid="2282" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-09">
<name>ninja</name>
<description>A ninja was a covert agent or mercenary of feudal Japan specializing in unorthodox arts of war.
The functions of the ninja included espionage, sabotage, infiltration, and assassination, as well as open combat in certain situations.
The ninja, using covert methods of waging war, were contrasted with the samurai, who had strict rules about honor and combat.</description>
<picurl>244347.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="226" type="main character in" update="2013-07-05">
<rating votes="1440">6.74</rating>
<name>Uzumaki Naruto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60771.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="240" type="main character in" update="2010-07-04">
<rating votes="740">4.36</rating>
<name>Uzumaki Naruto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>36317.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7194" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="532">2.31</rating>
<name>Haruno Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haruno Sakura is a female ninja affiliated with the village of http://anidb.net/ch8864 [Konohagakure], and part of Team 7, which consists of herself, http://anidb.net/ch240 [Uzumaki Naruto], http://anidb.net/ch7196 [Uchiha Sasuke], and their sensei, http://anidb.net/ch7248 [Hatake Kakashi].
Sakura initially has an infatuation for Sasuke, praising him at every juncture, and heaping scorn upon the less skilled Naruto. Over the course of the series, she begins to shed this singularly driven persona, and grows more appreciative and accepting of Naruto.</description>
<picture>36318.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7196" type="main character in" update="2010-07-04">
<rating votes="321">3.27</rating>
<name>Uchiha Sasuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Uchiha Sasuke is a rival and foil to the series` titular character, Uzumaki Naruto. Sasuke is a member of the Uchiha clan, a highly skilled clan of ninjas allied to the village of Konohagakure. His primary motivation throughout the series is to avenge the destruction of his entire clan by killing his brother, Uchiha Itachi, a task he pursues at all costs. While he was initially cold and singularly driven by his revenge, he becomes more empathetic through his relationships with other characters, notably Uzumaki Naruto, whom he comes to consider as a rival.</description>
<picture>36315.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7248" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="1671">8.57</rating>
<name>Hatake Kakashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hatake Kakashi is the leader and teacher of Team 7, consisting of http://anidb.net/ch7196 [Uchiha Sasuke], http://anidb.net/ch7194 [Haruno Sakura], and http://anidb.net/ch240 [Uzumaki Naruto]. He is initially portrayed as a detached and apathetic figure, but as the series progresses, his loyalty to his friends and students becomes increasingly apparent. Kakashi`s past has been extensively explored in the series, resulting in a gaiden being devoted to his past experiences. Kakashi has appeared in several pieces of Naruto media, including three of the four featured films in the series, all of the original video animations, and several video games.</description>
<picture>54614.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7698" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-09-25">
<rating votes="784">2.77</rating>
<name>Haruno Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haruno Sakura is the sole female member of Team 7. Kishimoto created her as the heroine of the series, although he has admitted that he has little perception of what an ideal heroine should be. As a child, Sakura was taunted by other children because of her large forehead, a feature Kishimoto has tried to emphasize in Sakura`s appearances. She was comforted by Ino Yamanaka. As the two continued to grow, however, they became increasingly distant due to their shared affection for Sasuke Uchiha. During most of Part I, Sakura is infatuated with Sasuke, and spurns the advances of Naruto Uzumaki. After Sasuke leaves the village, she resolves to become stronger by training with Tsunade. In Part II, she displays highly developed skills from her training, and a more open disposition towards Naruto.</description>
<picture>2928.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="234" picture="244740.jpg">Nakamura Chie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7719" type="main character in" update="2010-07-04">
<rating votes="504">3.28</rating>
<name>Uchiha Sasuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26580.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7720" type="appears in" update="2009-09-27">
<rating votes="103">6.66</rating>
<name>Gaara</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>36316.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7854" type="appears in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="396">8.68</rating>
<name>Uchiha Itachi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>For much of the series, the only information given about Itachi`s background is what his younger brother, Sasuke Uchiha, knows or remembers, as is chronicled in volume twenty-five of the Naruto manga. He grew up as the child prodigy of the Uchiha clan, establishing milestones for Sasuke and future Uchiha to live up to. Over time, however, Itachi began to distance himself from the clan, acting hostile towards its members and prompting his father to discourage Sasuke from following in Itachi`s footsteps.Itachi soon afterwards killed every member of the clan with the explanation that he was testing his potential. He spared only Sasuke, who he claimed was too weak to be worth killing, and challenged him to live a life of hate so that he would get strong enough to someday pose a challenge to Itachi. Itachi vanished into the night, leaving Sasuke with the motive for revenge that drives his actions for most of the series.</description>
<picture>54612.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8600" type="appears in" update="2012-09-09">
<rating votes="117">7.50</rating>
<name>Tobi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tobi, whose real name is Obito Uchiha, is the leader of Akatsuki who initially acts as a regular member of the group. He first appears as a carefree and a goofy person whose actions often result on him being attacked by his partner, Deidara. After Deidara dies in a suicidal bid to kill Sasuke Uchiha, Tobi starts taking a special interest in Sasuke`s development up to Itachi Uchiha`s death while leading the Akatsuki. He falsely claims to be Madara Uchiha, the leader of the Uchiha clan, and shows a more serious personality.</description>
<picture>54596.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8603" type="appears in" update="2015-01-26">
<rating votes="284">7.59</rating>
<name>Orochimaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Orochimaru is a major antagonist of Naruto series. He is a missing ninja from http://anidb.net/ch8864 [Konohagakure], who is recognised as one of the most powerful ninjas and known as one of the "Legendary Sannin" (Legendary Three Ninja), which was a title that was given to him and his former team mates, http://anidb.net/ch7213 [Jiraiya] and http://anidb.net/ch8606 [Tsunade], by Hanzou during the Second Shinobi World War. His main goals are to capture http://anidb.net/ch7196 [Uchiha Sasuke] as his new body to gain possession of the Sharingan and to destroy Konoha.</description>
<picture>37851.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8607" type="appears in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="92">3.92</rating>
<name>Yakushi Kabuto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54628.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8609" type="appears in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="171">7.58</rating>
<name>Hyuuga Neji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54696.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8623" type="appears in" update="2019-01-13">
<rating votes="88">8.15</rating>
<name>Uchiha Madara</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Madara`s fame and powerful Sharingan eye chakra was even known to the Kyuubi. Kyuubi regarded this chakra from the cursed bloodline as even more ominous than his own. He would bear witness to this chakra again in the form of Uchiha Sasuke. Madara himself was said to have the ability to control the Bijuu. This ability was apparently similar to the one possessed by Shodai Hokage.
When he was young, Madara and his younger brother competed against each other. Both possessed the Sharingan and attained Mangekyou through their rivalry. With their newfound power, they increased their clan`s power and standing. Unfortunately, usage of Mangekyou leads one to blindness and Madara was the first to fall to this side effect. With his eyesight gone, Madara took his brother`s eyes in desperation. These new eyes allowed him to see once again and granted him "Eternal" Mangekyou. With these powerful eyes he met representatives of a nearby clan and helped found Konoha. This clan was lead by the man who would become Shodai Hokage. At some point the men had a falling out, and the two did battle at the Valley of the End. It is said the destruction was so great it tore the earth asunder, creating the very valley. Two gigantic statues were later erected on the spot in their honor.
Madara apparently fled, still alive. He would later use his bijuu abilities to secretly direct the Kyuubi to attack Konoha. Kyuubi was stopped and Madara remained underground. The group Akatsuki sought to capture the Bijuu for their own ends. It was revealed that their leader Pain, actually reported to Tobi, one of the new members of the group. There was apparently more to Tobi than meets the eye, as he revealed in an ominous voice that Uchiha`s Sasuke`s Sharingan was growing powerful. This was something he could recognize with his own Sharingan power, as Uchiha Madara. The exact nature of Tobi and Madara is still unknown.
Take form http://www.leafninja.com</description>
<picture>229001.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="10971" type="appears in" update="2010-05-27">
<rating votes="26">5.86</rating>
<name>Ichibi no Shukaku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The One-Tailed Shukaku (一尾の守鶴, Ichibi no Shukaku) is a monster tanuki sealed within Gaara of Sunagakure.</description>
<picture>32754.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="11993" type="appears in" update="2013-11-05">
<rating votes="192">8.54</rating>
<name>Pain (Tendou)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pain (Deva Path) is the first of the Six Paths of Pain to be shown, was the body of http://anidb.net/ch20618 [Yahiko]. It was the most often seen and used of the six paths, and acted as Nagato`s representative during Akatsuki meetings. Its main abilities revolved around manipulating gravity, allowing it to repel or attract objects. The Deva Path was permanently incapacitated after its chakra receivers were removed from its body following its defeat by Naruto Uzumaki`s Rasengan. Konan took this body, along with Nagato`s body, after he died, and returned them to Amegakure.
As the Deva Path was the body of Yahiko, it had retained all of his physical features from when he was alive, most notably his medium length spiky orange hair. As the Deva Path, the body possessed Nagato`s Rinnegan, bore six piercings, a metal bar through each ear, three studs through the side of its upper nose, and one spike stud on each end of the bottom lip. It also had three piercings on each wrist, at least one on its upper wrist and some just under his neck. He also wore a beaded necklace, which is quite similar to the one worn by the Sage of the Six Paths. Underneath his Akatsuki robes, the Deva Path bears a faint scar at his stomach, most likely when Yahiko jumped onto the kunai to commit suicide under Hanzou`s order.
The Deva Path was the only path to be seen interacting with other Akatsuki members besides Konan. When all six paths were in active use, Nagato tended to speak only through the Deva Path, and showed the tendency to sacrifice other paths to keep it safe, suggesting that Nagato had some partiality to the path or that it was merely the most valuable.
The Deva Path was regarded as Pain`s most powerful and cherished of the six Paths. Its main abilities revolved around gravity manipulation, allowing it to repel or attract objects or people. However, it could not perform these techniques in rapid succession, leaving it vulnerable for a short period of time after each use. This period of time between usages varied from five seconds to several minutes, depending upon the force of the repulsion or attraction that the Deva Path had used. When performing a large-scale attack, Nagato had to first sever his connections with the other paths and then employ his chakra only to the Deva Path for the attack. However this is considerably risky as the other Pains were healing considerably sluggishly when the Naraka Path administered his jutsu. The Deva Path`s Chibaku Tensei allowed it to release a black orb of energy that could attract all surrounding matter to form a huge makeshift terrestrial body. The Deva Path`s most infamous and one of his greatest feats was singlehandly wiping out Konohagakure with one powerful Shinra Tensei.
In addition to gravity manipulation, Nagato was able to use a number of other miscellaneous jutsu through the Deva Path, something none of the other bodies had been shown doing. He was able to use the Shapeshifting Technique through the Deva path to make body doubles of others with human sacrifices. Other techniques used included astral projection, barriers to protect hideouts, and control rain, a possible throwback to Yahiko (who wanted to be able to stop the rain in Amegakure), which even allowed him to sense the chakra of everyone in Amegakure, making stealthy entrances by enemies impossible. In addition, like most of the other paths, it possessed considerable strength and speed, as seen with its fight with Jiraiya and Kakashi.
As Pain`s main body, the Deva Path was the primary body used for performing the Sealing Technique: Illusionary Dragon Nine Consuming Seals, which Akatsuki used to seal the tailed beasts. The members would convene to forcibly extract the beast from its host`s body over a three day period, depending on the number of people assisting with the sealing, and would then store it in a giant statue. He was not the only one who could use this technique, however. Madara Uchiha and the remaining Akatsuki members have been shown to initiate the extraction without using the Deva Path while it was occupied with invading Konoha.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>54552.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="11994" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="118">7.60</rating>
<name>Konan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Konan is the only female ninja in http://anidb.net/ch8599 [Akatsuki]. As such, Kishimoto originally wanted her to have an obscene appearance showing more of her bust. Being a partner of http://anidb.net/ch12003 [Nagato], Konan was also a pupil under http://anidb.net/ch7213 [Jiraiya] after she was orphaned as a child by one of Amegakure`s many wars and forced to fend for herself. Because she serves under http://anidb.net/ch11993 [Pain], she is referred to by villagers of http://anidb.net/ch12202 [Amegakure] as "God`s angel". Though she worries for Nagato as he was straining himself from having his Pains battle http://anidb.net/ch226 [Naruto], she respects his wishes to stand aside so that he and Naruto might meet face to face. While under Jiraiya, Konan learned to take advantage of her natural talent with origami, using it as a key component in her battle style. Konan can divide her body into countless sheets of paper, which she controls and reshapes remotely to scout out an area, form weapons for attack, or create wings that mirror her title. However, Konan`s abilities are restricted when the paper is wet; since paper will cling to itself and lose its stiffness. After Nagato`s death, Konan withdraws her position in Akatsuki and leaves the organization, pledging the support of Amegakure to Naruto and http://anidb.net/ch8864 [Konoha].</description>
<picture>54551.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12000" type="appears in" update="2019-07-25">
<rating votes="34">7.29</rating>
<name>Gamabunta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54600.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12223" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-10-11">
<rating votes="28">6.80</rating>
<name>Tayuya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>37085.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12225" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-10-11">
<rating votes="7">4.63</rating>
<name>Kidoumaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>37088.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12226" type="cameo appearance in" update="2019-07-25">
<rating votes="9">2.25</rating>
<name>Jiroubou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>37091.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="17693" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-05-16">
<rating votes="18">8.22</rating>
<name>Pain (Chikushoudou)</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pain (Animal Path) was the second of Nagato`s Six Paths of Pain to be shown. It is the only path shown to have existed as two different bodies. The first Animal Path was captured by Jiraiya and sent to Konoha for study. It was replaced with a female body and the original was later recovered and destroyed by the Preta Path during the invasion of Pain. The second Animal Path was later incapacitated by Naruto`s Sage Technique: Rasenrengan.</description>
<picture>4423.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="18184" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="14">7.23</rating>
<name>Pain (Gakidou)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pain (Preta Path) was the third of Nagato`s Six Paths of Pain to be shown. It was incapacitated during the invasion of Pain after it absorbed too much of Naruto Uzumaki`s senjutsu chakra and turned into a toad statue.
When it was alive, the Preta Path belonged to a large, bulky man from Kusagakure. The anime showed that he was both a ninja and a farmer who`d failed to cultivate the land for his family due to his participation in the Third Great Shinobi World War. The Preta Path, like all of the six paths, possessed Nagato`s Rinnegan. It had orange hair tied in a short ponytail. It had small spike piercings covering its entire bottom lip, two vertical spike studs on the front of his nose, two spike studs (one on each cheek), a metal bar going through each ear, and a stud on his shoulder, one on each side, close to his neck.
This path`s "Energy Absorption" ability was primarily defensive, since it was capable of absorbing any ninjutsu-related technique, thereby nullifying its effect. This technique could also take the form of a barrier around its body, allowing it to absorb attacks from all directions. In addition to its defensive properties, this body`s ability had also shown offensive capabilities, as it could absorb all the chakra out of any person that it touched or grabbed.</description>
<picture>48736.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="18185" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="12">6.84</rating>
<name>Pain (Ningendou)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pain (Human Path) was the fourth of Nagato`s Six Paths of Pain to be shown. It was destroyed during the Invasion of Pain after it was struck by Naruto Uzumaki`s Wind Release: Rasenshuriken.
When it was alive, the Human Path belonged to a tall, slender man from Takigakure. In the anime, he was shown to have been a level-headed ninja who believed that all he could do to try and achieve peace and to teach the next generation to survive the battles with other ninja until it came. The Human Path, like all of the six paths, possessed Nagato`s Rinnegan. It had long, loose orange hair, which was a light gray-blue colour while it was alive. It had multiple piercings, including a diagonal bar though its nose, two circular studs in a vertical row on each of its cheeks, two studs placed horizontally on its chin, and a stud on each of its shoulders near its neck. The diagonal nose piercing makes it the only Pain with asymmetrical facial piercings.
During Pain`s battle with Jiraiya, the Human Path`s eyes were damaged and it was left unable to see. For this reason, it used only taijutsu during the battle. The Human Path was later shown to have the capability of mind reading simply by placing its hand over the target`s head, and could extort any information or secret being hidden by the victim against his/her will. The most powerful and lethal ability possessed by the Human Path was its power to remove its target`s soul by ripping it out of his/her body, thus killing the victim.
Despite its lethal ability, Nagato deemed the Human Path less important than Animal Path, as he sacrificed it to get the Animal Path out of Naruto`s Wind Release: Rasenshuriken`s radius, having the path ripped to bits.</description>
<picture>48737.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="18186" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="13">5.36</rating>
<name>Pain (Shuradou)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pain (Asura Path) was the fifth of Nagato`s Six Paths of Pain to be shown. It was destroyed twice during the invasion of Pain, first by Kakashi`s Lightning Cutter and then for a second time by Naruto`s Rasengan.
When it was alive, the Asura Path belonged to a tall, bald man with an unusual body shape, possessing a very thick neck, no ears and a large jaw. In the anime, the Asura Path was shown to be a wandering puppeteer with insight to the world. He also had part of his face obscured by a rice hat in the anime, possibly hiding a headband that had not been shown in the manga, as Jiraiya quickly discovered that he was a ninja. The Asura Path`s unnamed puppet was made to look like a baby, and was capable of emitting infantile cries.
The Asura Path, like all of the six paths, possessed Nagato`s Rinnegan. It was the only body to not have orange hair, simply because it had no hair at all. It had a vertical ring piercing on its nose, six spike studs all around its head, three studs on the top and bottom of each of its six arms, an enormous cylindrical stud on its chin, and two vertical studs on each of its upper cheeks. The body had three faces, each with a different expression, and two of which appeared from the sides of its head only when it removed its cloak in a fight: happy (its normal face), angry, and neutral.
This body was very different from all other paths, being more like an android, as it had a number of body alterations. It was shown to have robotic inner workings, possessing six arms and a folded, serrated blade-like tail. It could fire one of its left forearms off as a long-range projectile, and could pull out his arms to reveal and fire a cluster of segmented missiles at its targets. It could quickly propel itself forward with a burst of chakra from its boots, and could protract multiple blades and a drill from one of its arms in battle. Also, it could open up the crown of its head to release a titanic shockwave that was capable of destroying numerous buildings at once. Its physical raw power was enough to rip Jiraiya`s arm off, and then crush his throat with basic Taijutsu moves, as well as to throw Animal Path all the way into Konohagakure from the forests in its outskirts. All of these abilities befitted the "warring demon" name that the Asura Path held, whilst giving it a considerably higher degree of versatility than the other paths had (aside from the Deva Path).
Despite being used frequently and providing heavy firepower, the Asura Path was readily sacrificed to protect the even more powerful Deva Path, acting as a human shield against Kakashi`s Lightning Cutter.</description>
<picture>48738.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="18187" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-05-29">
<rating votes="12">7.73</rating>
<name>Pain (Jigokudou)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pain (Naraka Path) was the sixth of Nagato`s Six Paths of Pain to be shown. It was incapacitated during the invasion of Pain by Naruto Uzumaki`s Sage Technique: Rasenrengan.
When it was alive, the Naraka Path belonged to a tall, stocky, muscular man. The anime showed him to be somewhat of a holy man in a small village, strongly emphasizing the power of prayer among his religious disciples. The Naraka Path, like all of the six paths, possessed Nagato`s Rinnegan. It had a spiky mop of orange hair, which had been a gray-brown color while he was alive. It had multiple body piercings, such as a circular stud on the bridge of its nose, a diagonal row of studs on each of its cheeks, three spike piercings in each of its ears, and a stud on each of its shoulders near its neck.
Although it was physically strong enough to lift a man with one hand, the only ability exhibited by the Naraka Path lay in the use of summoning the Outer Path. The Outer Path is a large head which sprouts out of the ground surrounded by purple flames and possesses the Rinnegan. The Outer Path could fulfill two purposes: interrogation and restoration.
To interrogate, the Naraka Path need only catch hold of a person, causing the Outer Path to appear before them. With the victim seemingly paralyzed, the Naraka Path begins questioning them. After answers are given, the King of Hell will unzip its mouth to release tendril-like arms and would draw out the victim`s tongue. The Outer Path then proceeds to pass its judgment. If the person was lying or refused to answer the questions, the Outer Path would remove their tongue and consume it, apparently killing them. However, if they told the truth, they would be spared, although left extremely exhausted.
The second ability the Naraka Path possessed is the ability to repair any damage. To do so the Naraka Path has the Outer Path ingest the damaged body with its tendril-like arms into its mouth. Then, after some time, the destroyed body will emerge from its mouth, completely healed and rejuvenated.
In all situations where Pain`s bodies were shown in a combat formation, the Naraka Path always took a rear position with the others protecting it, behind even the Deva Path. This indicates that the Naraka Path`s healing ability made it one of Pain`s most important bodies.</description>
<picture>48739.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="126290" update="2011-01-07">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2011-01-01</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
