<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="816" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2001-07-07</startdate>
<enddate>2001-09-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Cosmo Warrior Zero</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ヤングハーロックを追え! コスモウォーリアー零</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="synonym">Cosmo Warrior Zero</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="synonym">Cosmowarrior Zero</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Cosmowarrior Zero Gaiden</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Cosmo Warrior Rei</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Cosmo Warrior Zero Gaiden</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Космічний вояка Зеро</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">CWZ</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">コスモウォーリアー零</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Cosmo Warrior Zero</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Cosmowarrior Zero</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Cosmo Warrior Zero - La jeunesse d`Albator</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Cosmowarrior Zero</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Zero, El Guerrero Cósmico</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="725" type="Parent Story">Uchuu Kaizoku Captain Harlock</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.leiji-matsumoto.ne.jp/zero/</url>
<creators>
<name id="773" type="Animation Work">Vega Entertainment</name>
<name id="1107" type="Original Work">Matsumoto Reiji</name>
<name id="7671" type="Character Design">Masunaga Keisuke</name>
<name id="4879" type="Direction">Yokota Kazuyoshi</name>
<name id="56883" type="Series Composition">Doctor Serial Nishioka</name>
</creators>
<description>The time of oppression and lawlessness in deep space has begun. In order to preserve itself, humanity has reluctantly accepted peace with the invading force of mechanical people. Warrius Zero, a mercenary armada captain, has lost his immediate family during the war for Earth. Reduced to serving the mechanized victors, Zero carries out his orders without the will to resist. Now he has received a mission unlike any other. Zero has been commanded to travel to the farthest reaches of the universe to hunt down a single wanted man known to all as Space Pirate Harlock.
Source: HKFlix.com</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="224">5.43</permanent>
<temporary count="226">6.70</temporary>
<review count="2">7.58</review>
</ratings>
<picture>10475.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>469</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>1283</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1677</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>1676</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>419</identifier>
<identifier>yeiurf</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.leiji-matsumoto.ne.jp/zero/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Cosmo_Warrior_Zero</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>コスモウォーリアー零</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>239183</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>236065</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>cosmo-warrior-zero</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7562</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>18849</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="201" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-01">
<name>bounty hunter</name>
<description>A bounty hunter is one who hunts and captures targets (be it people, animals, etc.) for monetary gain, preferably without killing/destroying their target. Despite being illegal in most of the world today, it is a legal profession in the United States and Philippines (a former commonwealth of the US), who are known as "bail enforcement agents".
If they are only and constantly hired to kill, they are likely an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2868" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-20">
<name>racism</name>
<description>Racism is prejudice, discrimination, or antagonism directed against someone of an ethnically different background based on the pseudo-scientific belief that biological differences between peoples form so-called "races" and that one`s own "race" is superior to another, possibly also holding that members of different "races" should be treated differently. Some definitions include only consciously malignant forms of discrimination, and some views include discriminatory behaviors and beliefs based on cultural, national, ethnic, caste, or religious stereotypes. In works of fiction, this may also include similar actions against other sentient species.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2871" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>anti-war</name>
<description>The anime portrays the insanity of war.</description>
<picurl>70855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3269" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-11">
<name>genocide</name>
<description>The systematic killing of substantial numbers of people on the basis of ethnicity, religion, political opinion, social status, or other particularity.
Acts committed with intent to destroy, in whole or in part, a national, ethnic, racial or religious group.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3309" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-12">
<name>space pirates</name>
<description>Depending how you view the future, lawlessness will always be present in society. There`s always going to be a shadier, nastier way of doing business, and that will almost certainly follow humanity to the stars. Thus, sci-fi authors will include Expies of modern and historic (un)organized crime—be they space mafia, gangs, or—in our case—pirates.
It`s not as anachronistic as it might seem. After all, pirates themselves have made a Real Life comeback in Somalia, and it`s a lucrative enough "business" that it`s taken a multinational military response to fight back. Surely an established society in outer space with significant trade and commerce would suffer similar problems!
... Well, maybe. The major problem with space pirates preying on space commerce is that space is vast. The challenge of catching commercial shipping in open space is orders of magnitudes more difficult than catching them on the open seas. Sometimes, this is cleverly worked around and justified. Most of the time, however, it isn`t.
There are two kinds of Space Pirates in science fiction. The normal version are violent criminals with a spaceship, who attack other spaceships, just like present-day pirates. Once you have shipping between different solar systems/planets, pirates preying on said shipping are bound to show. Simple as that. Done this way, piracy actually makes sense, provided there`s an enabling factor. That could be anything from the technology of the setting creating trade lanes (via a Portal Network, predictable Faster Than Light Travel routes thanks to Negative Space Wedgies, or timed space flights between planets to reduce time spent between planets, as in Real Life), to using a variant of the method employed by modern pirates (say, smaller ships striking at commercial shipping in the orbit of a planet).
The other version does a Recycled In SPACE on every eighteenth century pirate cliche ever. Reasons for including this version will typically be along the lines of "Because Space Is An Ocean, it has to have Pirates" rather than making any meaningful attempt at justifying their existence. They have Cornish accents, beards, say "Arr!" a lot, have parrots (probably robot) and false limbs (probably cybernetic) and wear tricorn hats and eyepatches (or have cybernetic eyes). They may even have ships shaped like boats.
One of the best known space pirates is http://anidb.net/ch2087 [Captain Harlock] from the same named popular http://anidb.net/a725 [TV anime series].
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>41919.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3464" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-08-07">
<name>space western</name>
<description>Space Western is a subgenre of science fiction that transposes themes of American Western books and film to a backdrop of futuristic space frontiers; it is the complement of the science fiction Western, which transposes science fiction themes onto an American Western setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3611" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-12-06">
<name>evil empire</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3909" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>talking is a free action</name>
<description>Time in comics is flexible. Each panel shows a single event, which is usually accompanied by a length of dialog, which must take some time to say. This disparity is usually accepted if it isn`t taken to extremes.
But often, characters will exposit when it`s most needed: at the story`s climax, when both the intricacies of the plot and the intensity of action hit their highest.
While the Heroes Outrun the Fireball, Mr. Exposition might explain why the Evil Overlord`s death caused the explosion. The Action Girl can deliver impressive lectures on why the monster`s Achilles` Heel will work, while still engaging in Waif-Fu. The Superhero can quip to his heart`s content and explain his abilities while dueling one insignificant mobster, or deliver a Kirk Summation during the course of a single Finishing Move. Sometimes even apparent mere mortals can give a lecture on what is happening when it would be a much better idea to simply run like hell.
Without stopping to breathe, apparently.
Source: TvTrope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4446" parentid="2639" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-12">
<name>faster-than-light travel</name>
<description>Faster-than-light travel is taken for grated in this anime. This is achieved by travelling via hyperspace, nullspace, or wormholes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4459" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-12-22">
<name>undefeatable spaceship</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5816" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-10-03">
<name>massacre</name>
<description>Mass murder.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5929" parentid="2846" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>space opera</name>
<description>Space opera is a sub-genre of fiction that emphasizes romantic adventures in space. Space opera generally involves large-scale conflicts between opponents with powerful abilities and technology. The genre will often be melodramatic, sometimes playing music that can be nothing short of awesome. Warfare and a battle of wits are usually less emphasized, preferring romance (with exceptions, e.g. Ginga Eiyuu Densetsu). Some space operas tend to be formulaic and sometimes even prosaic, often employing very simple devices and somewhat obvious strategies. An example of this would be the infamous laws of physics in the Macross universe, in which the main male lead will hardly ever get hit in battle.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2087" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-11-03">
<rating votes="318">9.03</rating>
<name>Captain Harlock</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Harlock is the archetypical romantic hero, a space pirate with an individualist philosophy of life. He is as noble as he is taciturn, rebellious, stoically fighting against totalitarian regimes, whether they be earthborn or alien. In his own words, he "fight(s) for no one`s sake... only for something deep in (his) heart".
(Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>2364.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="2378" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-01-14">
<rating votes="46">6.93</rating>
<name>Ooyama Tochirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Harlock`s old friend and chief builder of the Arcadia.</description>
<picture>17631.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="296" picture="17124.jpg">Nishimura Tomohiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2493" type="appears in" update="2014-12-13">
<rating votes="434">8.57</rating>
<name>Maetel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The daughter of Queen Prometheum, ruler of a mechanised empire.</description>
<picture>38136.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19182" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12670" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-02-28">
<rating votes="149">8.45</rating>
<name>Emeraldas</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Emeraldas has been compared many times to Captain Harlock, and the two have some similarities. They also know each other from the days of the Voice of Free Arcadia, when she fought side by side with him and Tochirou, the man who is their common bond. After the Ilumidus resistance, Emeraldas became much like Harlock, sailing the sea of stars and delivering justice in her own unique way.
Emeraldas is one of the few people who know the route of Count Mecha`s Time Castle, and when her ship, the Queen Emereldas, appears next to the Galaxy Express, Tetsuro doesn`t hesitate to get her attention. Emeraldas would`ve killed Tetsuro if it weren`t for two things. First, Maetel (whom she also knows) is with him. Second, Tetsuro has Tochirou`s hat and laser. She listens and then tells Tetsuro where the Time Castle will next appear: Trader`s Fork, on the planet of Heavy Melder.
Some time after she leaves, she realizes something is happening on Heavy Melder, something that had to do with Tochirou. She arrives too late. Harlock tells her he`s already dead. She leaves but later receives a message. It`s from Tochirou, whose soul had been successfully integrated into the Arcadia. Learning that it was Tetsuro who had helped him, she realizes that she owes him a favor, and she proceeds to Andromeda, to repay the favor. She and Tetsuro will cross path a few more times.
Emeraldas is a very lonely soul, especially after the death of Tochirou. Her closest companion, like herself, is a wanderer. You see, the reason she and Maetel know each other...is because they`re sisters. Emeraldas also has a daughter, Mayu, but she rarely sees her.
Source: Absolute Anime</description>
<picture>38143.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="69850" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-04">
<rating votes="1">8.28</rating>
<name>Marina Oki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160449.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69851" type="main character in" update="2014-09-04">
<name>Warrius Zero</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160450.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69852" type="appears in" update="2014-09-04">
<name>Battlizer</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160451.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8994" picture="234982.jpg">Matsumoto Yoshiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69853" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-04">
<rating votes="1">8.28</rating>
<name>Silviana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160452.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="667" picture="32842.jpg">Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="8428" update="2019-05-16">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">終わりなき闘い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Endless Fight</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une bataille sans fin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Owarinaki Tatakai</title>
<summary>Captain Zero fears for his team and is hesitant about firing the St.Emlo`s Beam; the crew refuses to leave after Zero orders the crew to leave the ship.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>785366</identifier>
<identifier>cosmo-warrior-zero</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="8429" update="2019-05-16">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-06</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大いなる旅発ち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Start of Great Voyage</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le grand départ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ooinaru Tabidachi</title>
<summary>The end of the 30th century; a treaty has been signed, between flesh and blood humans, and mechanized men.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>785344</identifier>
<identifier>cosmo-warrior-zero</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="8430" update="2019-05-16">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">火龍の炎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Flame of Karyu</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le feu de Saint-Elme</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Karyuu no Honoo</title>
<summary>Karyu receives a call for help from a space station; the ship encounters rebel leader, General Hunter.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>785346</identifier>
<identifier>cosmo-warrior-zero</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="8431" update="2019-05-16">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マリーナ永遠の想い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Marina Eternal Love</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Marina pensées éternelles</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Marina Eien no Omoi</title>
<summary>After an explosion at the hospital, Zero finds out that Marina isn`t human; Helmatear escapes from the ship but is followed by Marina and Captain Zero.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>785359</identifier>
<identifier>cosmo-warrior-zero</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="8432" update="2019-05-16">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大テクノロジア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Great Technologia</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Technologia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai Technologia</title>
<summary>Captain Zero and his team arrive safely at Technologia; Zeth Water and Helmetear plan to destroy the planet.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>785364</identifier>
<identifier>cosmo-warrior-zero</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="8433" update="2019-05-16">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">誓い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Vow</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le serment</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikai</title>
<summary>A tenacious attack by the rebel fleet fails to do any notable damage to Helcastle; Harlock talks Zero into using St Elmo`s Fire.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>785367</identifier>
<identifier>cosmo-warrior-zero</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="8434" update="2019-05-16">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トチロー・不滅のサムライ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Immortal Samurai, Tochiro</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le samouraï immortel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tochirou Fumetsu no Samurai</title>
<summary>Karyu visits Gunfrontier on the planet Heavy Metal; Captain Zero seeks information from the bounty hunter Sylviana.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>785352</identifier>
<identifier>cosmo-warrior-zero</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="8435" update="2019-05-16">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">銀河の涯</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The End of the Galaxy</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Au fin fond de la galaxie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ginga no Hate</title>
<summary>The human and machine crew join forces to travel across the Iron Bridge galaxy; magnetic storms and unstable gravity threaten the trip to Technologia.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>785362</identifier>
<identifier>cosmo-warrior-zero</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="8436" update="2019-05-16">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">我が友ハーロック</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Friend Harlock</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Harlock mon ami</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wagatomo Harlock</title>
<summary>Harlock tries to rescue Tochiro; after being gone longer than expected, Zero goes to town in search of his crew.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>785354</identifier>
<identifier>cosmo-warrior-zero</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="8437" update="2019-05-16">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-31</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悲しみの星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sad Planet</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La planète du désespoir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanashimi no Hoshi</title>
<summary>Zero uncovers a planet decorated with the discarded flesh of humans who have become mechanized.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>785360</identifier>
<identifier>cosmo-warrior-zero</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="8438" update="2019-05-16">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マリーナの波紋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Marina`s Influence</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`emprise de Marina</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Marina no Hamon</title>
<summary>Chaos erupts among Captain Zero`s crew when it discovers that some of Kayru`s crew are robots.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>785345</identifier>
<identifier>cosmo-warrior-zero</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="8439" update="2019-05-16">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦士グレネーダーの魂</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Soldier Grenadier`s Soul</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`âme du grenadier</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senshi Grenadier no Tamashii</title>
<summary>Zero`s ship arrives on the planet El Alamain, which used to be the human battlefront in the war; a mercenary, named Heavy Grenadier, lives on El Alamain.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>785350</identifier>
<identifier>cosmo-warrior-zero</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="8440" update="2019-05-16">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">信ずるべき道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Credible Way</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La voie de la justice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinzurubeki Michi</title>
<summary>Zero and team discover a planet under attack and plan to help; Marina senses a presence on the ship and finds a machine woman named Helmatear.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>785356</identifier>
<identifier>cosmo-warrior-zero</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="11129" update="2019-10-17">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-07-05</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヤングハーロックを追え! コスモウォーリアー零 外伝 1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 1</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Harlock VS Zero</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Young Harlock o Oe! Cosmo Warrior Zero Gaiden 1</title>
<summary>Captain Zero is captured by a space pirate named Hunter who intends to trade him for Karyu.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>785370</identifier>
<identifier>cosmo-warrior-zero</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="11130" update="2019-10-17">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-07-05</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヤングハーロックを追え! コスモウォーリアー零 外伝 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`étendard la liberté</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Young Harlock o Oe! Cosmo Warrior Zero Gaiden 2</title>
<summary>Captain Zero, Harlock and Emeraldas need to defend Sarumatake from attack at all cost; the Death Shadow is recovered.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>785371</identifier>
<identifier>cosmo-warrior-zero</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="90242" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>20</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Marina Special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176072" update="2016-03-17">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176073" update="2016-03-17">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
