<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8167" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-04-12</startdate>
<enddate>2011-06-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kami nomi zo Shiru Sekai II</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">神のみぞ知るセカイII</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The World God Only Knows 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="synonym">Que sa volonté soit faite II</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Одному лишь Богу ведомый мир II</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Светът, който само Бог познава 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="synonym">دنیایی که فقط خدا می شناسد II</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">twgok 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">kaminomi 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">神のみぞ知るセカイ The World God Only Knows II</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The World God Only Knows II</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="official">کامی نومی زو شیرو سکای II</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8490" type="Sequel">Kami nomi zo Shiru Sekai: 4-nin to Idol</anime>
<anime id="7568" type="Prequel">Kami nomi zo Shiru Sekai</anime>
<anime id="9825" type="Side Story">Kami nomi zo Shiru Sekai: Magical Star Kanon 100%</anime>
<anime id="8632" type="Other">Nonstop!! Hunters</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="11">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="497799">I`d Say, the first one`s alright &amp; this one (S2) was a little better...defintly want to continue to see what S3 will be like...hopefully better than the first 2</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="490197">I loved it. But it`s not as good as it was for me for the average watcher. There are a lot of insiders you won`t notice unless you know a lot about japanese culture, anime history, visual novels, galge etc.
It`s still worth watching for everyone though.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="324464">DANGEROUS anime 

Watch with CAUTION

This anime seriously make u fell in love with Bishōjos</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="491462">strongly recommend to those who like romance comedy and a must see for those galge gamers</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="556152">a nice follow up on the first season, and it wont let you down one bit, it keeps gettting interesting, even if it`s about the same thing, but even so they keep up getting some interesting new things, into the Anime. a must see for those who liked the first season.
( this Anime is identical to the Manga storyline for those who are wondering)
also i`d like to point out, that they have announced a 3rd season, and it is being made right now.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="452346">Once again captivating. Immediately after the 1st season u want to see more and after this u want much more. Almost never boring and overall amazing. More!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="115911">If you enjoyed the first one, you`ll probably enjoy the sequel. It still has everything that made the first season such a huge success. and I`m Expect another season. ;)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="287128">The Evolution of Bishojo Games Combine with Reality.... Very funny indepth character. Better then Season 1.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://kaminomi.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="18553" type="Original Work">Wakaki Tamiki</name>
<name id="986" type="Animation Work">Manglobe</name>
<name id="1557" type="Series Composition">Kurata Hideyuki</name>
<name id="7012" type="Direction">Takayanagi Shigehito</name>
<name id="2529" type="Music">Matsuo Hayato</name>
<name id="3529" type="Character Design">Watanabe Akio</name>
<name id="13967" type="Chief Animation Direction">Samura Yoshikazu</name>
<name id="3328" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kawamura Toshie</name>
<name id="20084" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sugimoto Sachiko</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a manga series written and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr18553 [Wakaki Tamiki], serialised in http://anidb.net/cr23232 [Weekly Shounen Sunday].
Recap: http://anidb.net/ch18463 [Katsuragi Keima], a second-year high school student, is an avid dating sim gamer. He is known on the internet as The Capturing God for his legendary skills to be able to capture any 2D girl in games. One day Keima receives an e-mail offering him a contract to capture girls. He accepts what is thought to be a challenge, and http://anidb.net/ch18462 [Elysia de Lute Ima], a demon from Hell, appears. She asks for his help her in catching runaway spirits. And so Keima manages to capture the hearts of four girls and thus the spirits which hid in their hearts.
But the way to escape the real world is still long and his quest has only just begun. Suddenly a beautiful girl chasing a spirit appears before him. She is http://anidb.net/ch25896 [Haqua d`rot Herminium], Elysia`s friend and an outstanding student back in Hell, who was promoted to the rank of a district chief. However, it seems that she is hiding something. And once again Keima has to become a god, and the capture target this time is none other than a demon.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="3827">7.43</permanent>
<temporary count="3847">7.78</temporary>
<review count="3">8.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>70149.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12375</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10080</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4894</identifier>
<identifier>ikkgtz</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/kaminomi2/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://kaminomi.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Kami_nomi_zo_Shiru_Sekai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>神のみぞ知るセカイ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2139</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>339113</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13452</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1482" parentid="2751" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-08">
<name>wrestling</name>
<description>Wrestling is a fight between two people without weapons, in which each person tries to beat their opponent. Wrestlers use clinching, holding, locking, and leverage. It resembles ritual fighting as it avoids things that will likely lead to serious injury. It is similar to military hand-to-hand combat or self-defence systems.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2391" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>bishoujo</name>
<description>In Japanese, a bishoujo is any pretty female from toddlerhood to late adolescence. In the West, the word specifically refers to attractive girls generally from late childhood or early adolescence, especially those that appeal to males, and particularly to fictional characters designed in a way traditionally associated to shoujo manga. Fictional bishoujo tend to be cute, pastel-coloured teenagers; they lack the sophistication of older women, instead having detailed eye and hair design, fluttery costumes often including ribbons, and all sorts of generally sparkly fluff.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2751" parentid="2881" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-27">
<name>combat</name>
<description>Combat involves a violent conflict with the goal to establish dominance over an opponent.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3132" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-08-11">
<name>helpful couple</name>
<description>This is a very low key type of romance in which the main two characters spend a great deal of time hanging out together just helping other people solve problems. The couple`s personal interaction tends to be subtle.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3721" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-07">
<name>RPG elements</name>
<description>The anime shows elements of a `R`ole `P`laying `G`ame, either as part of a parody or because the anime is actually based on an RPG.
Typical elements: When collecting items, beating opponents, or levelling up a distinct (often childishly sounding) sound cue is played. A HUD (`H`eads `U`p `D`isplay) may also be presenting in combat, showing vital player and "enemy" statistics.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4301" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-22">
<name>play or die</name>
<description>The protagonist(s) are forced into a situation where they have to partake in some form of event, often a game of death, unless they want to bid farewell to their life.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4388" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-16">
<name>deconstruction</name>
<description>In the context of fiction, a deconstruction is the act of taking storytelling devices and exploring their real-life consequences, commonly in dark and cynical ways. Deconstructions often reveal the dark and terrifying aspects of some of the themes and elements that appear recurrently in fictional works.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5984" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-09-10">
<name>girly tears</name>
<description>Usually girly tears are the ones not shed by men (duh). 
Like when a (stereotypical) girl watches something and cries her makeup out, a (stereotypical) dude just says, proclaiming his masculinity: "Meh, yet another soap opera bulls..t, I`ll be in my garage fixing my ride while playing heavy metal on a burning guitar ...with my teeth! And where`s my beer, woman?".
So that`s how it goes: girly tears are for girls and sissies! Chuck Norris forbid a guy would weep watching something that has this tag! Now 20 push-ups!
P.S. The opposite of "manly tears". Or is it? Let`s face it - it`s all subjective (and relative, and context-dependent).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6078" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-23">
<name>gotta catch them all</name>
<description>A typical plot or sub-plot for many shows. Either the cast or somebody else, that being often the main antagonist, embarks on a quest to collect things, shiny things. Things that are said to grant simple wishes or even do miracles like bringing people back to life, destroying the whole world, galaxy, universe and in rare cases turning the hero into the greatest Pokemon Master. Those things can be weapons, lost technology, magical artefacts, pieces of a giant magical artefact and in some cases even people or little critters.
The point is, there`s stuff to collect!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="18462" type="main character in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="342">7.50</rating>
<name>Elysia de Lute Ima</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Elucia or Elsie as she is commonly known, is a demon who was assigned to capture evil spirits that have escaped from hell. Her feather cloth (the floating scarf she is always seen with) can change the appearance of an object, create disguises to aid the mission or it can hide people in plain sight. She is left-handed and is rarely seen without her broom, as it was from her original role as a cleaner for hell. To stay close to Keima, she tells Mari, Keima`s mother, that she is an illegitimate child of Keima`s father, and ends up living in the Katsuragi household as well as attending the same class in school. Elsie is often made fun of by the other demons because of the poor grades she had in the demon academy. However, after partnering with Keima, they were able to capture 9 escaped spirits within half a year`s time, which earned her the Section Chief`s Award.
Elsie is also a member of Chihiro`s band in which she plays a left handed bass. She has also developed an interest in fire trucks. She literally idolises Keima, often referring to him as "Kami-sama" or "Kami-nii-sama" in her role as his sister.</description>
<picture>55510.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18463" type="main character in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="620">8.23</rating>
<name>Katsuragi Keima</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Katsuragi Keima is the primary protagonist of the story, a 17-year-old high school student attending Maijima High School Academy. He is known as "The Capturing God (落とし神, Otoshi-gami)" in the gaming world for his legendary skills in "capturing" any girls in dating sims. But ironically, he is called otamegane (a derogatory portmanteau of the two words otaku and megane-"glasses"). At the start of the series, Keima becomes a collaborator for catching runaway spirits when he replies to an e-mail requesting his help to "capture" girls without knowing it was a contract from Hell, to which Elsee appeared and asked for his aid to "capture" girls in real-life. For each individual of the "Capture Targets"—a girl with the runaway spirit in her—Keima utilizes his analytical skills and experiences from dating sims to capture them. Whenever he isn`t capturing runaway spirits, he is almost always seen playing video games on his PFP (a parody of Sony`s PSP). Also, despite the fact he even plays video games in class, he is still at the top of class in every subject. As the story progresses, his perspective of the "real world" girls becomes different.</description>
<picture>55509.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20154" type="appears in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="176">7.42</rating>
<name>Takahara Ayumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takahara Ayumi is an athletic, cheery girl in Keima`s homeroom at school; Ayumi is a member of the school`s track-and-field team. She is an exceptional runner and was chosen as the representative for the upcoming tournament. As a result however she was pressured by jealous third-year runners, causing her to fake an injury in order to back out of the tournament. Keima, who was able to see through the deception, consoled and encouraged her not to give up which lead to capturing the escaped spirit. Ayumi and Keima are often paired up for cleaning duty together. In an omake from Chapter 14, and much more obviously in the whole of Chapter 30, she has become more eager to be around him. She is also a member of Chihiro`s band. Responsible for the guitar (SG).
Her name comes from Takanohara Station (高の原駅, Takanohara-eki).</description>
<picture>55511.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20155" type="appears in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="71">5.54</rating>
<name>Aoyama Mio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aoyama Mio is an elitist daughter of Aoyama Central Industry`s president. She is imperious and disdainful, being from a wealthy family; however, not known to the public, she is no longer rich—a secret which Keima discovers after stalking her to a shabby apartment. Despite her financial situation Mio continues to think of herself as a rich woman and is unable to let go of her late father`s memory. In order to get closer to her Keima took on the role of her chauffeur and driving her to school in various rickshaws. He then confronts her at an evening party, convincing her to accept the past and move on. Keima encounter Mio several chapters later, while occupying Yui`s body and learns that instead of him meeting her at the party, she remembers her old chauffeur Morita.
The prototype version of Mio appeared in Tamiki Wakaki`s one-shot Koishite!? Kami-sama!!, with her surname being Tsumagawa.
Her name comes from Aoyamacho Station (青山町駅, Aoyamacho-eki).</description>
<picture>55512.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="21505" type="appears in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="220">7.02</rating>
<name>Nakagawa Kanon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nakagawa Kanon is currently the most popular "traditional idol" for her quaint style, beauty and singing talents. She is also in Keima`s homeroom but had not been attending frequently because of her idol occupation. Kanon hopes that her song would "resound in everyone`s hearts." She is constantly anxious and dependent about the acknowledgment of her existence by others. When she feels ignored the spirit possessing her causes her body to appear transparent to others. Her lack of confidence is so great that when Keima first met her and didn`t recognize her she buzzed him with a pair of stun guns that she carries. On the night of her premiere performance as an idol she was overcome with stage fright, (becoming nearly invisible) until Keima encouraged her to believe in herself, filling the gap in her heart. During the performance afterwards Kanon began to glow so brightly that it was hard to see her. Keima commented on this, saying that she was no longer and `idol` but a `star`. In Kanon`s 4-box comic strips, it shows that there are leftover feelings for Keima; it`s shown that she trips when saying `kiss`, and when she sees something or someone related to Keima`s name (Exa: the wig is called a katsura in japanese).
She debuted as side member of a trio unit "Citron", became center after took off her glasses and started solo after she cut her hair. She does not use the glasses when she performs as an idol, but wears it in school and private. Raises a turtle named Kintarou as a pet.
The cause of Kanon`s crevice in the heart was her doubt of her existance as an idol.
Her name comes from Ise-Nakagawa Station (伊勢中川駅, Ise-Nakagawa-eki).</description>
<picture>73489.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="21506" type="appears in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="181">8.16</rating>
<name>Shiomiya Shiori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shiomiya Shiori is a reticent girl who loves to read books. She is a member of the Library Committee, which acts as the governing body and librarian for the school library. Her official position is a secretary. She has always wanted to talk to others but finds that she cannot articulate as fast as her thought process, as a result by the time she has formulated a response to something, the conversation has already moved on. From the beginning, Keima immediately catches her attention and anger by saying that physical books are no longer necessary in a digital era. As Keima continues to vandalize the books in the library, she becomes more conversational each time. Near the end of her story arc, she learns that three thousand books are to be disposed of to accommodate an audio-visual booth. Protesting, she locks down the building and barricades herself in the library. After Keima literally descends into the library and gives her "courage", she finally overcomes her silence.
She starts to write a story based on her faint memories during Keima`s capture, though the parts including Keima are erased.
The cause of Shiori`s crevice in the heart was her will to speak out her mind, when she had doubts of a good reply.
Her name comes from Shionomiya Station (汐ノ宮駅, Shionomiya-eki).</description>
<picture>73490.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="21742" type="appears in" update="2012-12-30">
<rating votes="18">6.54</rating>
<name>Dokurou Skull</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dokurou Skull is hell`s branch chief of "counter measures". She assigned Elsee to capture spirits in the human world and sent Katsuragi Keima the contract letter. She may be the only person from hell who doesn`t make fun of Elsea.</description>
<picture>58954.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3368" picture="132584.jpg">Kujira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23171" type="appears in" update="2020-04-13">
<rating votes="54">8.31</rating>
<name>Nikaidou Yuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nikaidou is Keima`s homeroom and national language teacher. She has been ignoring Keima ever since he told her that there are 5012 games that are more fun than her lessons. She is a sadist.
She is in reality a high ranked devil from hell but is not part of the runaway squad.</description>
<picture>246184.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="222" picture="19786.jpg">Tanaka Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23172" type="appears in" update="2020-04-13">
<rating votes="21">3.46</rating>
<name>Terada Miyako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Terada Miyako is asecond-year Maijima High School Academy student enrolled in Class 2-B. Miyako is a close friend of Ayumi and Chihiro. She has a long hair and freckles on her cheeks. Track-and-field club member. Her speciality are the 400m.
After the Chihiro Arc, she became a member of Chihiro`s band. Responsible for the keyboard (KORG X50).
Her name is derived from Terada Station (寺田駅, Terada-eki).</description>
<picture>246185.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22168" picture="186262.jpg">Chikamura Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23174" type="appears in" update="2010-11-09">
<rating votes="18">5.80</rating>
<name>Hatori Yuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Keima`s 10,000th target captured in galge.</description>
<picture>58950.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23231" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="194">6.74</rating>
<name>Kosaka Chihiro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kosaka Chihiro is a classmate and close friend of Takahara Ayumi. Chihiro is an average girl who has no redeeming features whatsoever: she`s not pretty, her grades are so-so, and she doesn`t have an after-school activity—except for going home. She is described as a "reality girl among reality" by Keima`s visual novel argot, meaning she is void of defining characteristics. Keima therefore refuses at the greatest that he does not want to `capture` her. She has a habit of confessing to handsome, attractive boys without any serious consideration, which yields no success; all because she feels "luminous" as those she is in pursuit of, for that moment. When Keima is tricked into cleaning duty with Chihiro, she demands him to help her latest confession to succeed. Keima reliezes then that a gap does not need to be filled by his love but can be filled by another person` love. He agrees to help Chihiro in her confession. During this period however her feelings begin to shift towards Keima due to their similarities (they both share a sense of disappointment in the real world). After an argument between the two Chihiro ran off and Keima realized that Chihiro did have one defining parameter and vowed to capture the spirit himself, which he does by convincing Chihiro that as long as she truly wants it, nothing can stop her from no longer being generic. Aftrwards, like Ayumi, Chihiro`s attitude towards Keima improves somewhat, becoming one of his `friends`.
Chihiro is the founder of "2B Pencils", an all-female band composed of girls from Class B of Mai-High; its members besides herself are Ayumi Takahara, Elsie, Miyako Terada and Yui Goidou. Responsible for the guitar and vocals (Mustang).
The cause of Chihiro`s crevice in the heart was her disbelief of having a straight-forward path in life that will spark her interests.
Her name is derived from Kawachi-Kosaka Station (河内小阪駅, Kawachi-Kosaka-eki).</description>
<picture>73486.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23425" type="appears in" update="2020-04-13">
<rating votes="56">8.23</rating>
<name>Katsuragi Mari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Keima`s mother resembles a typical shoujo manga-style mother; optimistic, ditsy, and loving. However, when she is angry, Mari removes her glasses and lets her hair down and changes her personality completely. Keima claims that she used to be a part of a biker gang, and has shown violent tendencies that reflect this.</description>
<picture>246186.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25896" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="196">8.57</rating>
<name>Haqua d`rot Herminium</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haqua is a fellow demon and friend of Elsie. She graduated as an outstanding honour student and was promoted to the position of District Chief of District 32 in Nagumo city. However, until meeting Keima, she had never captured an escaped spirit. After hearing of Elsie`s successes in this regard, the gap within Haqua`s heart widened. This allowed a powerful spirit to take control of her. After Elsie calmed Haqua down, they joined forces and defeated the spirit. Even though her human partner is http://anidb.net/ch26096 [Marui Yukie], Keima has occasionally assisted Haqua in her quest to find and capture escaped spirits. She seems to have taken a liking to him.
Haqua`s first name is derived from "Cretaceous (白亜, Hakua)".</description>
<picture>73485.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26044" type="appears in" update="2011-10-18">
<rating votes="38">1.91</rating>
<name>Kodama-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70364.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3149" picture="132209.jpg">Nakao Ryuusei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26062" type="appears in" update="2010-12-27">
<rating votes="4">3.91</rating>
<name>2 nen B-gumi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The class Keima is in.</description>
</character>
<character id="29407" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="52">8.66</rating>
<name>Kasuga Kusunoki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kasuga Kusunoki is an 18 year old tomboy, third-year Majima Academy student and head and only member of the Girl`s Karate Club. A practitioner of Kenpo, Kusunoki is the heir to her father`s dojo and their family`s martial arts called Koshikibujutsu Kasugaryuu Rashinkassatsujutsu (古式武術 春日流 羅新活殺術, Ancient Martial Arts, Kasuga-Style, Life And Death Technique). Keima and Elsie meet Kusunoki when she saved them from delinquents but also looks down on Keima`s weakness. Upon learning that she is his next target and investigating by becoming her disciple in the Karate club, Keima`s learns that Kusunoki is trying to be masculine in order to become her father`s successor by suppressing her feminine side. However, Kusunoki secretly likes cute things but tries to despise them and stay away from them as she sees her femininity as a weakness. As her personality continues to polarize, the spirit inside of her causes Kusunoki feminine side to manifest itself. In order to draw out her feminine personality, Keima convinces Kusunoki to do do a very girlish activity; go on a date with him. After drawing it out where both the masculine Kusunoki and her feminine side fight it out over which personality should be the dominant one, Keima manages to convince both personalities to accept each other which her feminine side agrees to merge with Kusunoki as long as the latter accepts her femininity. Before completely merging, Kusunoki`s feminine side takes over Kusunoki to kiss Keima to remember their date, which forces the spirit out.
Since then, Kusunoki has opened up to her femininity which includes liking cute things and adopting a pet cat. When Keima joins her family dojo in order to get to his next target, her older sister Hinoki, he learns she still remembers Keima during his time as her disciple but not during their date which she believes he ran away. He also learns that Kusunoki`s femininity problems before stems from her sister Hinoki, who she admired the most, left for America after having a disagreement with their father over inheriting the dojo, and in order to fill the void Hinoki left, she focuses herself in martial arts to become what she was when Keima first meet her. Yet, Kusunoki becomes a valuable help later when a powerful Weiss takes over her sister`s body where both she and Keima goes into Hinoki`s heart to fight a possessed Hinoki. As the sisters battle, the possessed Hinoki reveals her hatred for Kusunoki for forcing her to maintain the image of the perfect older sister and denying her right to be who she really wanted to be. Kusunoki at first is reluctant to hurt Hinoki but after some encouragement from Keima, Kusunoki is able to defeat the spirit possessing her sister and tells Hinoki she apologize for what she had go through as she never wanted a perfect sister, she just wanted the older sister she loved and would still admire Hinoki no matter what path she choose which finally calms Hinoki`s heart and forces the Weiss out. After Hinoki`s Weiss was captured, the supernatural events that both she and Hinoki experienced were erased from their memories, yet the relationship between the Kasuga sisters are repaired.
The cause of Kusunoki`s negative emotions was her conflicted feelings to become masculine or feminine.
Her given name is derived from Kusu Station (楠駅, Kusu-eki).</description>
<picture>73487.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29408" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="61">8.23</rating>
<name>Nagase Jun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nagase Jun is a 21 year old university student from Narusawa Kyoiku University and a Maijima Academy graduate and Nikaido`s junior. Returning to Maijima Academy as a student teacher for Keima`s class, she is very passionate to help her students. Innocent and naive, she is a fan of the pro wrestler Jumbo Tsuruma. Concerned that Keima`s is a troubled child, she tries to help him to open up and give-up on video games. But Keima, learning she has a spirit inside of her and in an attempt to get rid of it, does his best to try and get her angry, such as playing more games in class but his plans backfire which only causes her to be more concerned about him instead, which infuriates him. Eventually, Keima does cares about her when he unintentionally upsets her, causing her to try to help the other students in his class. After Keima asks Nikaido about her past, she reveals that both she and Jun were on the high school basketball team with Jun as the Team Captain but Jun passionate desire to aim for the championship caused the rest of the team to quit because they felt she was just forcing her ideals onto them. After her over-zealousness leads to a disagreement with the students in class, Keima confronts her and reveals that the problem wasn`t because she was trying too hard but she was just giving up too eaisly and tells her to continue to follow her beliefs and not give up. Right afterwords, the whole class (thanks to Keima`s manipulations) reconciles with Jun. Before returning to Narusawa University after her time as a student teacher is over, she tells Keima that she will become a better teacher, make him give up video games and kisses him which expels the spirit.
During Keima and Haqua`s search for the Jupiter Sisters, they encounter Jun at her university who still remembers him. When he claims he has become a better student and Haqua is his girlfriend, Jun congratulates him without showing any signs of jealousy which Keima sees as proof that she doesn`t have a goddess inside her as her memories of falling in love with him are gone.
The cause of Jun`s negative emotions was her doubt of having her ideals coming true.
Her surname is derived from Nagase Station (長瀬駅, Nagase-eki).</description>
<picture>73488.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31092" type="appears in" update="2011-04-11">
<rating votes="6">5.35</rating>
<name>Neko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69630.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="31102" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-04-12">
<rating votes="4">3.37</rating>
<name>Yuri Sakazaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuri Sakazaki is a video game character from SNK Playmore`s (formerly known as SNK) Art of Fighting series. She first appears in the original Art of Fighting being kidnapped by Mr. Big, a criminal from the fictional city of Southtown. The players, Yuri`s brother Ryo and his friend Robert Garcia spend the game searching for her. In the second Art of Fighting, Yuri appears for the first time as a playable character, having been trained by her father Takuma in the art of the Kyokugenryu Karate. She has also appeared in most games from The King of Fighters series, with the notable exception of the non-canon The King of Fighters XII, participating in the annual tournaments from each title. She initially starts in the Women Fighters Team (composed exclusively by women), but she later moves to the Art of Fighting Team along with her family. She was also featured in the SNK vs. Capcom crossover series as well as in SNK Gals` Fighters.
Yuri has also starred in the anime adaptation from Art of Fighting, in which she reprises her role from the first game. Her character has been well-received by gamers, having ranking high in several popularity polls developed by journals. Video games publications have commented on Yuri`s character; Yuri`s addition to Art of Fighting 2 as a playable character has been praised by several reviewers, and some have also complained on her absence in the following title.</description>
<picture>69644.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="31105" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-04-12">
<rating votes="5">4.58</rating>
<name>Kasugano Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kasugano Sakura first appeared in Street Fighter Alpha 2, where she had begun to participate in street fighting after watching Ryu win the first World Warrior tournament. She was searching for him and wished for him to train her to be a better fighter. She met up with many interesting people along the way, and eventually came across Ryu, who was still stressed over the Satsui no Hadou that had corrupted him. Ryu told her he could not train her as he still had much to learn himself. He sparred with her for a bit and as he began to leave, she took a picture of him to remember him by.
In Street Fighter Alpha 3 Sakura decided to travel the world to find Ryu. She started off in her native Japan and fought the sumo wrestler E. Honda, who mentioned that Ryu went to India and Thailand. She also fought a rematch with her rival Karin Kanzuki, and though Karin won the fight, she admitted that Sakura was better and she had learned that winning was not everything. Thereafter traveling with her self-proclaimed sensei, Dan, she met his friend Blanka along the way and was promised a match with him. She continued to search the world for Ryu, eventually ditching Dan and finding Ryu`s friend and rival Ken. She tells him how she loves to fight to better herself, and finding inspiration in those words himself, Ken joins her. Sakura eventually finds Ryu in Thailand, where he is actually being brainwashed by M. Bison. Sagat is also present and he fights Ryu while both Ken and Sakura take on Bison. Sakura is injured by Bison and this combined with Sagat`s attempts to reach Ryu finally release him of his mind control. Ryu then attacks Bison who is now forced to retreat. Ryu tells Sakura that he is not ready to train her and fight a rematch with her yet, and walks off, with Sakura watching as he leaves.
Sakura is playable in Street Fighter EX3, where she is one of the characters to have two level-3 super combos. Also, upon fulfilling certain conditions, Sakura becomes the game`s announcer.
In Street Fighter IV, years have passed since Sakura last saw Ryu, so she decides to find Ryu again for a match. She ends up joining the new World Tournament sponsored by S.I.N., an organization collecting street fighter data from around the world. In her ending after completing arcade mode, Sakura sees Ryu trying to stop the explosion of the machine holding all of the fighter`s data and attempts to help him. Instead, she gets in the way, and Ryu must stop the machine with a Shoryuken since he is worried about Sakura causing the machine to explode and release energy all around. Sakura is engulfed by a red energy and faints, and Ryu carries her to safety.
Sakura has a brother named Tsukushi and she has a friend named Chitose Kei who attends the same high school and sometimes joins Sakura on her street fight tour as a cheerleader.
Rival Schools saw Sakura involved in the adventure between her school and various others in Aohura City. After helping her childhood friend Hinata and the others out from within the ordeal, she realizes how much it means to her to protect something she cares about.</description>
<picture>69645.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="31342" type="appears in" update="2011-04-18">
<rating votes="5">3.51</rating>
<name>Kikki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70147.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2505" picture="141583.jpg">Makiguchi Mayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31343" type="appears in" update="2011-04-18">
<rating votes="4">2.66</rating>
<name>Sammy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70146.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="32023" type="appears in" update="2011-10-18">
<rating votes="3">2.98</rating>
<name>Pitcher</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70360.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32024" type="appears in" update="2011-11-03">
<rating votes="4">4.53</rating>
<name>Megumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76674.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22168" picture="186262.jpg">Chikamura Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32025" type="appears in" update="2011-11-03">
<rating votes="3">2.98</rating>
<name>Kouchou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Principal at Demon school.</description>
<picture>76676.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2228" picture="21776.jpg">Gibu Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32026" type="appears in" update="2011-11-03">
<rating votes="3">2.98</rating>
<name>Kake Tamashii</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Loose Soul.</description>
<picture>76675.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="195" picture="17009.jpg">Sakamaki Mitsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32058" type="appears in" update="2011-05-09">
<rating votes="7">5.20</rating>
<name>Yoshino Asami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yoshino Asami is a 17 year old Majima Academy student and Keima`s classmate. A very quiet girl, in class she is usually seen reading a book alone and does not actively interact with the other classmates. From the start of the story, she already had an interest in Keima and was always looking at him whenever she wasn`t reading.
Different to her sister, she is not good at socialising with people. Trying to overcome that problem of hers, she joins the tea ceremony club. Even though she always participates in the activities, she still has problems when talking to people. She even feels like puking when she talks with them too much. She can talk normally with her family members though.
Her sister, Yoshino Ikumi, tries to help deepen her relationship with Keima by disquising as Asami and interacting with him. But in the end, Keima finds out, though he agrees to deepen the relationship between him and Asami.
Her name is derived from Yoshino Station (吉野駅, Yoshino-eki).
Asami is shown as a background character in the Kami nomi zo Shiru Sekai anime adaptation during Chihiro`s arc.</description>
<picture>71270.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="32358" type="appears in" update="2011-10-18">
<rating votes="3">2.40</rating>
<name>Yuuta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70361.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32703" type="appears in" update="2011-05-24">
<rating votes="4">3.78</rating>
<name>Tenkiyohoushi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72162.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2505" picture="141583.jpg">Makiguchi Mayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32944" type="appears in" update="2011-05-31">
<rating votes="15">6.48</rating>
<name>Sugimoto Yotsuba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sugimoto Yotsuba, also known as Yokkyun, is Keima`s most favourite game girl. She is drawn in a parody style of the famed visual novel Kanon.</description>
<picture>72601.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="483" picture="27541.jpg">Tange Sakura</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34014" type="appears in" update="2013-07-12">
<rating votes="25">5.36</rating>
<name>Kujou Tsukiyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kujou Tsukiyo is a short, blond 17 year old Majima Academy student and the only member of the Astronomy Club. The daughter of designer Yoko Kujou, she rarely attends class and is frequently on the school rooftop in her private observatory to watch the moon with her doll Luna which she holds dearly. Her cold personality comes from watching her parents fighting and later divorcing when she was younger, which made Tsukiyo hate the real world and wish she could live on the moon, her ideal world with Luna, a metaphor for her desire to escape reality. Keima encounters her and finding out she has a spirit after they both get into an argument over what is "true beauty". Later that night while watching the moon, she wishes she was beautiful just like Luna which the spirit inside of her shrinks her to Luna`s size. Keima discovers her problem and with the help of Elsie, assists Tsukiyo with her situation. However, Tsukiyo begins to grow comfortable with her new life which Keima fears it will only widen the gap in her heart so he and Elsie make her new environment more bigger in order to frighten Tsukiyo by making her think she has become smaller but she later discovers the ruse and escapes to the roof. Keima confronts her there where he convince her despite what she believes, there is beauty within the real world. However, she accidentally falls but Keima jumps down to catch her and the two kiss and saved by Elsie`s magical raiment. In the aftermath, Tsukiyo still goes to her observatory with Luna but without the carpet that acted as a border between her ideal world and the real world and watches Keima through her telescope, blushing.
The cause of Tsukiyo`s negative emotions was her hatred of humanity and reality`s flaws.
Her surname is derived from Kujou Station (九条駅, Kujou-eki).</description>
<picture>139959.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="34015" type="appears in" update="2011-11-08">
<rating votes="8">4.53</rating>
<name>Ikoma Minami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ikoma Minami is a 15 year old Majima Academy Middle School student who is a member of the Swim Club. A naive girl who loves swimming, she has messy hair that won`t straighten due to chlorine from swim practice which her younger brother makes fun of by calling her "Bird Nest". Her story is unique as it is mostly told by her own point of view. When she is first introduced, she learns that she has been selected as a third substitute for the school team despite wishing to be on the main team instead. As Minami laments on whether she should give up swimming just like her friends, Elsie detects a spirit inside of her and informs Keima. Then on one late night swimming practice, Minami meets Keima swimming at the school pool where she is captivated by his handsome looks and perfect swimming (thanks to Elsie help). At first, she believes Keima is a great senior within the Swim team, only to learn from her friends that Keima has an infamous reputation for being weird which leaves her very confused. Unknown to her, Keima is actually doing this to make Minami figure out the connection between the school`s impression that he is a weirdo and her impression that he is an amazing athlete. As she starts stalking Keima and rides on the bus with him, Minami starts to fall in love with him which Keima decides to ask her out at the Tanabata Festival. After having a good time at the festival, Minami wishes to stay with him forever as the festival ends but Keima comforts her, teaching her that moving on and accepting the past is a part of growing up and kisses her, which forces the spirit out. After the festival, Minami becomes mature thanks to Keima`s words (even though she has forgotten) and decides to stay and continue in the Swim Club. During Keima`s search for the goddesses, Keima meets Minami again and finds out she does not remember who he is which he confrims she doesn`t have a goddess. Before leaving, Keima asks Minami if she is still practicing swimming and wishes her luck.
The cause of Minami`s negative emotions was being unable to achieve her dreams.
Her name is derived from Minami-Ikoma Station (南生駒駅, Minami-Ikoma-eki).</description>
<picture>76855.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="34016" type="appears in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Hinaga Rieko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hinaga Rieko is an elderly woman living in the countryside where Keima`s grandparents also live. While visiting his grandparents to celebrate the Obon festival with the rest of the Katsuragi family, Keima and Elsie meets Rieko and her granddaughter Airi, a little girl who speaks very scary things. At first, Keima and Elsie believes Airi has a spirit inside of her after seeing a ghost-like apparition of her appearing at the village cemetery at night but upon further investigating, Keima learns the apparition is actually Rieko due to the fact she looks similarly to her granddaughter when she was younger. As he meets Rieko at the cemetery, Elsie talks to the spirit possessing Rieko`s body and convinces it to leave and surrender as Rieko is too old to bear children. At the cemetery, Rieko`s apparition, now in a form when she was a teenager, explains to Keima the gap in heart was because she feels lonely and misses her family and friends who are either old, have left or passed away. However both she and Keima agrees that she was able to live a long and happy life before her apparition departs. In aftermath, Keima explains while she is no longer possessed by a spirit, the gap in Rieko`s heart remains but she has accepted it and moved on with her life just like his grandparents.
The cause of Rieko`s negative emotions was her loneliness being without her loved ones and a wish of a return to the time of her youth.
Her surname is derived from Hinaga Station (日永駅, Hinaga-eki).</description>
<picture>139763.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="34017" type="appears in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="2">4.32</rating>
<name>Airi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Airi is Rieko`s granddaughter. She has the same appearance like her grandmother when she was a child.</description>
<picture>139764.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="34018" type="appears in" update="2011-11-08">
<rating votes="8">4.92</rating>
<name>Uemoto Sumire</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Uemoto Sumire is a 17 year old girl from Narusawa 3rd Public High School. Her a father is a chef and owner of a small Chinese restaurant called "Uemoto-ya" while her mother used to work there before she ran away which the only memento Sumire has of her mother is a cheongsam which she also wears while working at Uemoto-ya. Keima and Elsie first met Sumire during the last weeks of summer vacation while she goes out tasting every Ramen store`s ramen in the city. As they follow her to Uemoto-ya, they watch how both Sumire and her father have a thorny relationship which the latter doesn`t want her to work here. In order to figure out what is the cause of the gap in Sumire`s heart and the Uemoto`s family situation, Keima decides to work at Uemoto-ya much to Sumire`s suspicions. After gaining her trust, Sumire reveals she wants her father`s acceptance of her helping his ailing restaurant by researching the other Ramen stores and creating her own unique recipe of Ramen called "Sweet Ramen" with Keima as her food taster much to his displeasure as he dislike sweet food. After several failures and their relationship going smoothly, both Sumire and Keima finally make a Sweet Ramen that is delicious and edible. However, Sumire`s father refuses to eat it and tells her to just quit which Keima realizes the problem between father and daughter. In reality, both of them wants the other to be happy which Sumire wants to help her father`s restaurant and her father wants Sumire to give up the restaurant and have a better life. Eventually, Keima manages to have her father taste a ramen made by Sumire which taste exactly like his which Sumire explains that all that she wants is to help him succeed which will make her happy. Realizing his mistake, her father finally relents and passes the restaurant to Sumire. Before Keima leaves, Sumire thanks Keima and promises to make any ramen he wants if he visits and kisses him which expels the spirit in her.
After these events, the restaurant, now renamed "Sumire-ya" and under Sumire`s management becomes popular thanks to her Sweet Ramen which is a hit with the customers. While she still continues making new Ramen recipes and trying to lose weight from her research, Sumire remembers having a "boyfriend" but doesn`t remember who he was.
The cause of Sumire`s negative emotions was her disappointment that her father refuses her help.
Her surname is derived from Osaka Uehommachi Station (大阪上本町駅, Osaka Uehonmachi-eki).
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>76853.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="34021" type="appears in" update="2012-10-12">
<rating votes="64">7.38</rating>
<name>Ayukawa Tenri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ayukawa Tenri is a shy 17 year old girl from Maijima Municipal Misato East High School. A reticent childhood friend of Keima`s, she was his neighbor before his family moved seven years ago. In the present, she and her mother visit the Katsuragi`s where Keima does not remember her well. Unknown to Keima at first, he believes Tenri has a spirit inside of her but in reality it is a Goddess name Diana. Ten years ago during a school trip, both Keima and Tenri got lost in an underground cave where they both witness the Weiss (what evil spirits where called before) escaping from Hell and were saved by Diana who agreed to take over Tenri`s body. In order to save Diana, who is being chased by Nora who believes Tenri has a spirit inside of her, Keima pretends to capture Tenri`s heart and kiss her and have Elsie release a weak spirit in order to fool Nora. After that incident, Tenri`s family soon moves next door to Keima home.
Tenri has been love with Keima since they were children as she admired his ability to remain calm and collected no matter the situation. Despite Diana suggesting that Tenri should do more to make Keima fall for her, Tenri is just fine with their current relationship of being friends. She also enjoys doing magic tricks and playing with bubble wrap.
As Diana`s host, whenever Diana takes over Tenri`s body, she is able to perform and do amazing feats that Tenri is unable to. While she usually does nothing when Diana takes over, Tenri will sometimes interfere if Diana does something she disapproves especially when it comes to Diana`s attempts to make her and Keima closer. While not taking over, Diana can communicate and see others via a reflective surface like glass or mirrors. Because of Diana`s knowledge about Heavens involvement with the New Hell regime, Keima usually meets Tenri to discuss with Diana about these topics. With recent events of Keima trying to find Diana`s other Goddesses sisters, Keima has warned Tenri to be careful as to not catch the attention of those targeting the Goddesses.
Tenri`s name is derived from Tenri Station (天理駅, Tenri-eki) and her character design is modeled after Diana Barry, from Anne of Green Gables.</description>
<picture>126782.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="34022" type="appears in" update="2013-09-03">
<rating votes="61">7.99</rating>
<name>Diana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Diana is the goddess of "the hunt and the moon", as well as the first goddess Keima encounters who resides in Tenri`s body. Keima first meets Diana when he assumes she is a Weiss, but Tenri manages to convince him otherwise after she tells Keima about how she first met Diana, who saved them both ten years ago from the Weiss. Because of her knowledge which Elsie and Haqua aren`t aware of, Keima visits her when he wants to know more about the relationship between Heaven and the Underworld. When Diana takes over Tenri`s body, she appears with slanted eyes in contrast to Tenri`s rounded eyes. Diana acts cold, selfish and thoughtless most of the time which tends to irk some people, yet she is very supportive of Tenri`s love for Keima. She wishes for Tenri and Keima to be a couple as it would restore her powers, despite being disgusted that Keima has managed to make other girls fall in love with him as well. Diana is also the one who originally requested that Keima should find her sisters, in exchange for helping him seal back the Weiss. Later on in the series, after Keima apologises to her for his indecisiveness, Diana regains more of her powers and now has the ability to use her angel wings.</description>
<picture>126783.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="34023" type="appears in" update="2011-06-28">
<rating votes="4">3.78</rating>
<name>Meruko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74406.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2505" picture="141583.jpg">Makiguchi Mayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60780" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-01-11">
<rating votes="160">8.42</rating>
<name>Takao Buchou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>(The real) President of the Game Development Club. She`s a tsundere and she`s taken a liking to Kazama. She`s had a long relationship with all the members of her (temporary) club.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>146526.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="128679" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-12</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一花[いっか]繚乱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Flower in Bloom</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fleur aux pétales d`acier</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikka Ryouran</title>
<summary>One day at school, Keima becomes the target of a group of delinquents, which is when an imposing girl by the name of Kusunoki Kasuga appears.
She dispatches of the delinquents and saves Keima, but she appears to be disgusted by the "weak" Keima and his inability to fight back...
After a harsh lecture from Kusunoki, Keima wants nothing to do with her, but once the loose soul sensor goes off, he can no longer ignore her.
He attempts to approach Kusunoki by joining the girls` karate club where she is captain...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>573612</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129282" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-19</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一拳落着</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Problem Solved by the Fist</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fleur est dans le sac</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikken Rakuchaku</title>
<summary>There are two of Kusunoki!?  In order to succeed the Kasuga School of Martial Arts, Kusunoki had forsaken her weak "feminine" side.  However, when she engages in weak activity, her lingering "girly side" appears...  Kusunoki agrees to go on a date with Keima to draw out the "feminine Kusunoki" and conquer her weakness.  Elsie watches nervously as Keima and Kusunoki go on their date.  How will their date go...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>573614</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129322" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-10</airdate>
<rating votes="14">7.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">たどりついたらいつも雨ふり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Always Rains at the End of a Hard Journey</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Il pleut toujours quand j`arrive</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tadoritsuitara Itsumo Amefuri</title>
<summary>One gloomy Monday morning, Keima`s sour mood is exacerbated by harsh words from Chihiro.
Keima doesn`t give a damn about the real world, but her words still leave him a little depressed. However, he brushes them off as the ramblings of a background character...but then they discover that she`s been possessed by a loose soul!
And Chihiro`s parameters are the worst Keima`s seen so far...
Keima is beaten down by the ordinary girl who exemplifies the real girl.
That is when a certain someone appears before him—!?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>573620</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129323" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-03</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地区長, 誇りを取り戻す.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Section Chief Regains Her Pride</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La chef de zone regagne sa fierté</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikuchou, Hokori o Torimodosu.</title>
<summary>Keima and the demon girls find the fugitive loose soul in one of the older school buildings. However, the matured loose soul is far more powerful than any of the previous loose souls!! Haqua and Elsie work together to capture the loose soul, but it escapes after taking control of students and using them as a distraction. Haqua yells at Elsie for her mistake and runs after the loose soul by herself...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>573618</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129324" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-31</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめての☆おつかい / 3人でお茶を.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Her First Errand / Tea for Three</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ma première commission / Tous les trois au café</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no Otsukai / 3 Nin de Ocha o.</title>
<summary>Keima and Elsie head to a game store in a neighboring town to buy a certain game.
However, there is a very enticing fair at a different store... Keima dispatches Elsie to obtain the game in his stead. Will she succeed... ("Her First Errand") Haqua shows up because she needs to write a report about the loose soul which was secured a while back.  It appears that she wants help writing the report... ("Tea for Three.")
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>573626</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129325" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-24</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Singing in the Rain</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Singing in the Rain</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Chanter sous la pluie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Singing in the Rain</title>
<summary>An extremely fired-up Keima and somewhat apathetic Chihiro have spent many days going through possible situations and conversations to prepare for the conquest of Yuta. Everything is going smoothly as the day of the confession finally arrives——However, Chihiro says something which leaves Keima dumbfounded...Will this be the first failure for the God of Conquest?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>573624</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129326" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-17</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">10%の雨予報</title>
<title xml:lang="en">10% Chance of Rain</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Précipitations estimées à 10%</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">10% no Ame Yohou</title>
<summary>Keima was under the impression that he had found a potential route where he would cheer up the broken-hearted Chihiro, but she`s already found a new love!?
Keima snaps at the absurdness of the real world, but he is beaten down by Chihiro`s counterattack.
That is when Keima is helped by a previous conquest, Ayumi!
Ayumi manipulates Keima and Chihiro into cleaning the classroom by themselves.
Eventually, Keima finds himself caught up in a certain event...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>573622</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129327" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-26</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地区長, 来たる.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Section Chief Cometh</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La venue du chef de zone</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikuchou, Kitaru.</title>
<summary>Elsie reunites with her classmate, the overachieving Haqua. Chief Docrow reports an evil spirit on the loose in their area.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>573616</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129843" update="2011-05-05">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-05-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129844" update="2011-05-05">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-04-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129845" update="2011-05-05">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-04-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129935" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-28</airdate>
<rating votes="12">4.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サマーウォーズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summer Wars</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Summer Wars</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Summer Wars</title>
<summary>One night, Keima is in his room when he picks up a certain game.  On the cover is a very poorly drawn heroine, Yotsuba.
Will this game change the world as Keima knows it?──
Keima Katsuragi, the god who has won the hearts of many girls.  Will he finally see his ideal ending...!?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>573634</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129936" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-21</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いつも心に太陽を</title>
<title xml:lang="en">There`s Always a Sun in Your Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ton cœur brille toujours</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itsumo Kokoro ni Taiyou o</title>
<summary>Jun begins to lose the support of the students as she continues on her impassioned crusade.  The shock drives Jun to attend a pro wrestling match to cheer herself up.
Keima uses a special ticket made by Elsie to ambush Jun and forces her to face the barrier of reality that she came up against in her past...
A touching ending to the three episode story of the young student teacher, Jun Nagase, who faces both ideal and reality.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>573632</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129937" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-14</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スクール★ウォーズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">School Wars</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">School Wars</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">School Wars</title>
<summary>Jun is doing her best to meet the expectations of the students.  She`s very popular with the students, but she`s been possessed by a loose soul.  And so, Keima begins his conquest of Jun.  However, she`s preoccupied with becoming the ideal teacher, so she only sees Keima as a student.  In order to break free of the teacher-student mold, Keima decides to approach Nikaido, who was Jun`s senior in school...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>573630</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129938" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-07</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">2年B組長瀬先生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Class 2-B Miss Nagase</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">2eme annee Classe B Professeur Nagase</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">2 Nen B Gumi Nagase-sensei</title>
<summary>It`s the season for student teachers at Mai High.  Keima`s class gets Miss Nagase, a cheerful pro wrestling fan who has great hopes and dreams about becoming a teacher.
However, her attention is immediately drawn to a problem child who plays games during class (...Keima, of course).
The other teachers have already given up on Keima`s attitude, but Jun is inspired to save him...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>573628</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="141453" update="2017-10-28">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending Episode 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="141454" update="2017-10-28">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-06-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending Episode 12</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
