<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8177" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-07-03</startdate>
<enddate>2011-12-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Nurarihyon no Mago: Sennen Makyou</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ぬらりひょんの孫 ~千年魔京~</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">滑头鬼之孙~千年魔京~</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">NuraMago2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ぬらりひょんの孫 千年魔京</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Nura: Rise of the Yokai Clan - Demon Capital</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Le seigneur des yôkai, La cité des démons</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7404" type="Prequel">Nurarihyon no Mago</anime>
<anime id="9368" type="Other">Nurarihyon no Mago (2012)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="10">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="684617">I dont give a cent about those fights and shit. I love the girls. Other stuff are worthless, the girls! the Girls!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="533419">love it!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="366933">good series, worthwhile for all who have seen the first season</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="558578">Better than the 1st season... a must watch for all shounen genre fans.... the only thing annoying about this is the 2 recap episodes that are in both the 1st and 2nd season</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="326975">I honestly hated the first season, it was a total trainwreck, and I wouldn`t have recommended it to anyone, but the second season is fantastic so far. I don`t know if it`s because of the new director or just the manga simply got better after the first part, but this is one of the best shounens I`ve seen in a while. If you somehow got through the first season, don`t miss this one, it`s worth the time.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="233389">As far, it`s a way better than the first season. Very enjoyable. Especially for a shounen fan.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="492184">very nice anime 

hope for fast season III :D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="389591">Must see! Definitely better than 1st season!
You`ll get what you expect!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.nuramago.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3918" type="Character Design">Oka Mariko</name>
<name id="6898" type="Series Composition">Koyasu Hideaki</name>
<name id="20100" type="Original Work">Shiibashi Hiroshi</name>
<name id="125" type="Direction">Fukuda Michio</name>
<name id="1393" type="Music">Tanaka Kouhei</name>
<name id="6945" type="Music">Sawaguchi Kazuhiko</name>
<name id="27275" type="Music">Inai Keiji</name>
<name id="22685" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kitahara Hiromasa</name>
<name id="5259" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sakurai Masaaki</name>
<name id="10833" type="Chief Animation Direction">Morimoto Hirofumi</name>
<name id="6586" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kudou Yuka</name>
<name id="3918" type="Chief Animation Direction">Oka Mariko</name>
</creators>
<description>At first glance, http://anidb.net/ch15458 [Nura Rikuo] seems like nothing more than a normal middle-schooler. In actual fact, he is the grandson of http://anidb.net/ch17493 [Nurarihyon], master of a youkai clan.
Having only recently resolved the hostilities between the Nura Clan and the Shikoku Yokai, Rikuo finds no rest as an ancient enemy of the Nura Clan, Haguromo-Gitsune, resurfaces. After 400 years of inactivity, Haguromo-Gitsune suddenly sweeps through Kyoto with overwhelming power.
~ translated and adapted from official site by Cranston</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1662">7.34</permanent>
<temporary count="1676">7.73</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221674.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12357</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11083</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>10049</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4909</identifier>
<identifier>ichnda</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.nuramago.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.viz.com/anime/streaming/nura-rise-of-the-yokai-clan</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Nura:_Rise_of_the_Yokai_Clan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ぬらりひょんの孫</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2215</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>340041</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13594</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2011/nuramago2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1291" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-01">
<name>aristocrat</name>
<description>An aristocrat or noble is a member of the aristocracy or nobility, an upper class in feudal societies. Nobles may or may not hold any specific nobility title. For simplicity`s sake, royalty should also be considered nobility.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2488" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>multiple personality disorder</name>
<description>Multiple personality disorder is a psychiatric diagnosis that describes a condition in which a single person displays multiple distinct identities or personalities (known as alter egos or alters), each with its own pattern of perceiving and interacting with the environment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3539" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-10-16">
<name>growing hair</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4048" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>Japanese mythology</name>
<description>Japanese mythology is a system of beliefs that embraces Shinto and Buddhist traditions as well as agriculture-based folk religion. The Shinto pantheon alone consists of an uncountable number of kami (Japanese for "gods" or "spirits").
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4182" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-01-22">
<name>hidden power</name>
<description>For some reason or another a character has powers (or potential) he or she can`t access and may not even know about. 
In some anime these hidden powers are used quite frequently to overcome an enemy or threat (e.g. Naruto, Bleach).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4564" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-06-01">
<name>spirits</name>
<description>Spirits will appear throughout this anime. These will often be depicted as small orbs of glowing light, or transparent images of the deceased.
Not to be mistaken with "I see dead people", these spirits will usually appear at the location of their departure when the characters have gotten close to the truth surrounding their death. Or as plot element, when a spirit will often stay close to a character as a sort of "Guardian Angel". Although they are never actually seen, their presence is sometimes felt.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5863" parentid="2798" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-06">
<name>Weekly Shounen Jump</name>
<description>The Weekly Shounen Jump is a Japanese manga magazine released on a weekly basis. Its main target audience consists of young males and it features several manga titles. The magazine was created by http://anidb.net/cr780 [Shueisha] in July, 1968, and was originally only called Shounen Jump, because it was not published every week at the time. A number of very famous shounen manga were or are published in it, such as http://anidb.net/a386 [Hokuto no Ken], http://anidb.net/a231 [Dragon Ball], http://anidb.net/a942 [City Hunter], http://anidb.net/a826 [Saint Seiya], http://anidb.net/a590 [Slam Dunk], http://anidb.net/a312 [Yuu Yuu Hakushou], http://anidb.net/a69 [One Piece], http://anidb.net/a239 [Naruto], http://anidb.net/a2369 [Bleach], http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], http://anidb.net/a3468 [Gintama], to name a few of the most well-known.</description>
<picurl>66685.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5882" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>secret identity</name>
<description>The (usually main) protagonist has a secret identity that he or she desperately tries to keep secret.
This can lead to all sorts of amusing misunderstandings, thus is used as comedy element in some anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6083" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>master-servant relationship</name>
<description>To some genres, this would suggest a genuine pairing where one person exists to serve another person, such as in some action/dramas where the pair becomes united by destiny as partners — fighting or battles between different pairs/partners will usually be a dominant part of the story.
In other genres, this suggests a relationship where one person may be occupied as or even forcefully treated as a servant or slave to the other who designates themself the master — these services usually apply anywhere from tsundere/romantic-comedies to ecchi or to the more extreme in hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="15458" type="main character in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="50">4.69</rating>
<name>Nura Rikuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rikuo is the title character and main protagonist of the series, an average 12-year old boy who inherited 1/4 of his grandfather`s youkai blood. In times of impending danger his youkai blood awakens and he switches into his night form to become the Master of the youkai (the master of all spirits). His youkai form is confident, strong and inspires "Fear" amongst his allies leading many to join him. Rikuo is destined to take over as the Third Master of youkai from his grandfather, though the main conflict for the first portion of the series lies in his rejection of the idea. As a child, Rikuo respected and looked up to youkai, playing pranks on members of the Nura house and often declaring he would become more youkai-like and take over as the Third. However, after a discussion at school, he came to realize the evil nature of youkai deeds and decided to set himself firmly on the path of living a strictly human life. Since then, he has attempted to become more like a normal human by doing all sorts of good deeds. Even though he appreciates all that his youkai underlings do for him, he is nevertheless desperate to prevent his school friends from learning of his connection to youkai. After being tested by Gyuuki he decides to take the position of Young Head and saves both humans and youkai.</description>
<picture>47591.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15459" type="main character in" update="2011-04-13">
<rating votes="50">4.78</rating>
<name>Ienaga Kana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kana is Rikuo`s childhood friend and neighbor. She first appears in the original Nurarihyon no Mago one-shot as Yura Usami and says she hates things relating to youkai and spirit mediums. She is hinted to have some affection for Rikuo, as she gets jealous seeing Rikuo and Tsurara together. Rikuo made a promise to help her if she is ever in need. After being kidnapped by a youkai on her 13th birthday, she was saved by "Night" Rikuo and was taken to a youkai party. The next morning Kana asked Rikuo if he was friends with his youkai form and blushed when Rikuo asked why. She has fallen for Rikuo`s Night form. However, it is hinted that she is also starting to like Rikuo as she is much concerned and distracted when Tsurara gets too close to him.</description>
<picture>47592.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4" picture="177060.jpg">Hirano Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15460" type="main character in" update="2015-02-20">
<rating votes="132">8.44</rating>
<name>Yukionna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yukionna is Rikuo`s trusted attendant and part of Rikuo`s new "Hyakki Yakou" who follows him to school disguised as Tsurara Oikawa, a normal schoolgirl. She is affectionate towards Rikuo and even gets jealous when other girls pay him attention. This is also reinforced by the fact that other characters express how bad a situation would be come if Tsurara were to see what other female characters did to Rikuo. She also admires Rikuo`s youkai form, because she finds him very reliable and magnificent. She is overprotective of Rikuo when he is his "day" or human form and expresses great concern for his well being, which is the reason why she is always around him at school (which causes misunderstandings and concern on Kana`s part). She also acts as a cook and, though her food is delicious, most of the time it is chilled or cold.
She also has a fear of Yura as she is an onmyouji and a rivalry with Kana (going so far as to nearly freeze her), however she protects as her death would sadden Rikuo. She is in Kyoto protecting the Investigation group along with Aotabou. Later, she rejoins Rikuo but is kidnapped by Tsuchigumo.</description>
<picture>47590.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17492" type="main character in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="78">7.93</rating>
<name>Nura Rikuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>His night (youkai) form is confident, strong and inspires "Fear" amongst his allies leading many to join him. He decides to leave the human side of things to his "Day" form and handle the youkai-side of things. After losing to his grandfather, he is taken to the youkai village to train and finally learns what type of demon he is and how to gain his Fear abilities. He has departed for Kyoto to face Hagoromo Gitsune to save Yura and avenge his father. He is currently undergoing a 3-day training with Gyuuki to surpass "Himself" after losing to Tsuchigumo. He seems to get stronger when his "Day" and "Night" blood mix. But now it seems as though night Rikuo and day Rikuo are one being and are not a split personality. His primary weapon is the Spirit Blade Nenekirimaru, which was designed to only harm youkai.</description>
<picture>47585.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17493" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="34">7.50</rating>
<name>Nurarihyon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nurarihyon is Rikuo`s grandfather, known as the master of all spirits or as the Supreme Commander. It is said that he plays pranks and hates humans, but he doesn`t really hate them - rather, he doesn`t believe humans should interfere in youkai affairs. He dislikes the fact that Rikuo goes to school and acts human but respects his wishes.
400 years ago, he fell in love with Youhime and fought with the Hagoromo-Gitsune in Kyoto. He won and became the master of all spirits but at the cost of shortening his life span greatly. In his prime, he and Keikan Hidemoto were considered friends. Even in his old age, he can easily best "Night" Rikuo and Muchi. Normal demons feel so much "Fear" that he is invisible to them until he strikes, that is his "Meikyou Shisui".</description>
<picture>47586.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="456" picture="17358.jpg">Ootsuka Chikao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17494" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-06">
<rating votes="64">7.76</rating>
<name>Oikawa Tsurara</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47587.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17495" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="22">6.17</rating>
<name>Zen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Poisonous bird Youkai who was a childhood friend of Rikuo, he was disappointed the Rikuo had become so soft. His species has short lifespan and as a result he has become very weak, but he specializes in making medicine. After being betrayed and nearly killed he was rescued by "Night" Rikuo, he continues to support Rikuo and is the first to exchange Sakazuki and tells him to form a new "Hyakki Yakou".He was on board of Takarabune and poured his medicine on Kubinashi and Itaku to stop their battle. Rikuo later punch him.</description>
<picture>47588.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17496" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="11">5.05</rating>
<name>Kiyojuuji Kiyotsugu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rich and influential amongst his class, he used to tease Rikuo about youkai until he was saved by "Night" Rikuo years ago. He now has an obsession with youkai, even to the point of wanting to be kidnapped. He is constantly inventing new youkai-related games and quizzes and has a very forceful personality.</description>
<picture>47589.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="181" picture="171560.jpg">Taniyama Kishou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19463" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-16">
<rating votes="39">7.20</rating>
<name>Gyuuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The kanji for his name means `bull.` According to legend, he was once a human who died searching for his mother. His resentment led him to become a youkai after his death. He is a high-ranked subordinate of the Nura group. He was in charge of a conspiracy against Rikuo using Kyuuso. It was revealed this coup was a means of a test, to see if Rikuo could handle being what he was and told Rikuo to abandon his human side as that would only get him killed. In response to Rikuo`s aim for being the third he works even harder now.He fought the Tengu of Mount Kurama 400 years ago. He appeared in Kyoto by the order of Nurarihyon to help Rikuo.</description>
<picture>54299.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19465" type="main character in" update="2011-04-16">
<rating votes="36">6.23</rating>
<name>Kubinashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A "No-neck" Youkai and one of Rikuo`s demon guardians. He fights using thread that entangle you the more you struggle, made from Kejourou`s personality and Jorougumo`s restriants. Part of Rikuo`s new "Hyakki Yakou" he is traveling to Kyoto. He used to go by the name `Joushuu No Gentsatsushi Kubinashi` (Lit. String Assassin of Hitachi Province) and is strong enough to restrain Toono youkai easily using his "Black string" technique. He seems to be a gizoku (honorable thief) before he joined the Nura clan. He goes back to his murderous way in Kyoto and is confronted by Ibaraki Douji. He was almost killed by Ibaraki Douji until he was saved by Kappa and Yura.</description>
<picture>54301.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19466" type="main character in" update="2011-09-10">
<rating votes="35">6.38</rating>
<name>Aotabou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The degenerate priest who wears the iron blue robe and the physically strongest Youkai in the Nura household. He used to be a monk who killed many warriors. He has fists that can crush rock and palms that can fit a person`s head. He was enlightened by a holy man. He wishes to protect children after being enlightened. The holy man once stated that it is up to him whether to become human again or a raging god, he almost became human but he killed the people who were torturing the children he wishes to protect while crying. He is often seen with Kurotabou and the two are known as the assault officers of the Nura House. He has a skull necklace that when removed greatly increases his strength. He is also the leader of a biker gang called the Blood Night Hyakki Yakou. Part of Rikuo`s new "Hyakki Yakou" he is in Kyoto along with Yuki Onna. He fought and managed to kill Shoukera.</description>
<picture>54302.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19467" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-22">
<rating votes="15">4.36</rating>
<name>Kurata</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch19466 [Aotabou], in his human form. He`s following http://anidb.net/ch15458 [Rikuo] along with http://anidb.net/ch17494 [Tsurara], making sure he`s safe all the time.</description>
<picture>216555.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19468" type="main character in" update="2011-04-16">
<rating votes="41">7.06</rating>
<name>Kurotabou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Assassin and Destruction Monk &amp; Master of the hidden blade, he is often seen with Aotabou and the two are known as the assault officers of the Nura House. In his human form he dresses like a businessman, and he also saved Torii from her curse as repayment for helping him. Part of Rikuo`s new "Hyakki Yakou", he is traveling to Kyoto. He is currently fighting Ibaraki Douji with Ryuuji and Mamiru.</description>
<picture>54303.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19470" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-16">
<rating votes="18">6.80</rating>
<name>Karasu Tengu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A "Crow-Tengu" Youkai he is the adviser to Nurarihyon and Messenger, he loyally follows the Nura clan. He has two sons and one daughter, the Sanbagarasu.</description>
<picture>54300.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="400" picture="171989.jpg">Majima Junji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19471" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-13">
<rating votes="25">7.94</rating>
<name>Kappa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Kappa Youkai in the Nura clan whose domain is the fear of water and one of Rikuo`s demon guardians, he loves cucumbers. He fights extremely well near water and fights in a ninja suit. As part of Rikuo`s new "Hyakki Yakou", he is traveling to Kyoto. He appears to save Kubinashi and Kejourou.</description>
<picture>54284.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="340" picture="17176.jpg">Yabe Masahito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19472" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-16">
<rating votes="40">7.85</rating>
<name>Kejourou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A demon who uses her hair to fight, she serves as one of Rikuo`s Guardians. After Rikuo got beat at the first seal in Kyoto and went to recover and train she got the Hyakki Yako to keep motivated by asking them if they want to disappoint Rikuo when he got back. She appears to be Kubinashi`s lover, of sorts, having, in the past, offered her life to save his. She is also closest to Kubinashi out of all the Youkai in the series ad is once known as Kino. Her fear is Midaregami.</description>
<picture>54286.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="223" picture="228520.jpg">Kakazu Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19473" type="main character in" update="2010-10-16">
<rating votes="39">6.92</rating>
<name>Keikain Yura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An Onmyouji of the Keikan House who specialises in shikigami, she can manage four at once impressing even Nurarihyon. She was trained by Akifusa and raised to see Youkai as evil, seeks to complete her training by defeating Nurarihyon and then inheriting the Household. After her brother reveals Rikuo as a Youkai and as Nurarihyon`s grandson, she says she can accept it if it`s him. She has returned to Kyoto to deal with the Hagoromo-Gitsune and has currently retreated to the keikan main house.</description>
<picture>54298.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1660" picture="53927.jpg">Maeda Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19474" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-16">
<rating votes="18">6.03</rating>
<name>Maki Saori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A classmate of Rikuo and close friend of Torii, she stayed with her in the hospital until she woke up.</description>
<picture>54295.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19475" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-16">
<rating votes="20">8.10</rating>
<name>Nura Wakana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rikuo`s mother. Though she herself is human, she seems to have no problem living in a home full of youkai.</description>
<picture>55507.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="613" picture="155849.jpg">Mizuno Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19476" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-16">
<rating votes="17">5.49</rating>
<name>Torii Natsumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A classmate of Rikuo, she is a member of the Investigation squad. She is cursed by Sodemogi and nearly dies until Senba is given power by Torii`s grandmother`s belief, saving her life.</description>
<picture>54297.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12352" picture="130106.jpg">Hirata Mana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19477" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-16">
<rating votes="11">3.91</rating>
<name>Shima Jirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kiyo`s underling has been supporting Kiyo since they were kids. Also a classmate and member of Kiyo`s Squad.</description>
<picture>54296.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="174" picture="41158.jpg">Kakihara Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19755" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-16">
<rating votes="9">4.52</rating>
<name>Mokugyo Daruma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leader of Nura clan`s Daruma alliance. He fought Shoukera 400 years ago.</description>
<picture>54287.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2021" picture="187129.jpg">Tsuji Shinpachi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19756" type="appears in" update="2018-04-21">
<rating votes="10">3.58</rating>
<name>Asajigahara no Kijo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Asajigahara no Kijo are the eaders of Kijo clan, made of a couple of an old hag and a little girl.</description>
<picture>216540.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5352" picture="134103.jpg">Tani Ikuko</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20086" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-16">
<rating votes="20">4.28</rating>
<name>Nattou-Kozou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the demons who lives in Nura`s house. His head is a nattou and he consequently smells like nattou.</description>
<picture>54285.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20578" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-01">
<rating votes="18">6.22</rating>
<name>Mezumaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gyuuki clan`s young head assistant. Wears a horse`s skull and his face looks like a girl. Can control human with string but don`t have any other mean to attack so he usually become a support. Now lives in Nura`s house.</description>
<picture>54291.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="381" picture="186189.jpg">Hoshi Souichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20579" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="22">5.13</rating>
<name>Gozumaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gyuuki clan`s young head. Cool and cruel, wield a katana, Tsume, he also able to control human with string but not as good Mezumaru. Now he lives in Nura`s house as candidate for next Gyuuki clan`s next leader, but actually a hostage.</description>
<picture>54290.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20580" type="appears in" update="2010-10-16">
<rating votes="7">6.77</rating>
<name>Kuroumaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The messy-haired tengu with a gem on his forehead.</description>
<picture>54292.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20581" type="appears in" update="2010-10-16">
<rating votes="8">6.18</rating>
<name>Tosakamaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The blond tengu with a mohawk.</description>
<picture>54294.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="470" picture="17419.jpg">Irino Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20582" type="appears in" update="2010-10-16">
<rating votes="11">6.93</rating>
<name>Sasami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The long-haired tengu who wears glasses and the only female of the Sanbagarasu (as revealed in an omake in volume 6). She was disgusted by Mezumaru attacking the women`s baths. She wields a pair of short whips as weapons.</description>
<picture>54293.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20583" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-16">
<rating votes="21">1.88</rating>
<name>Hitotsume Nyudou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leader of One-eyed demon clan. One of those who rejected Rikuo as the third Supreme Commander of the Nura clan. 400 years ago he was really different as he stated to Kokehime after being saved from Hagoromo-Gitsune, "Even if her tear become pearls, the one that fits her best is her smile", speaks volume of how different he was in the past.</description>
<picture>54289.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="293" picture="185431.jpg">Matsuyama Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21904" type="appears in" update="2010-10-15">
<rating votes="8">4.95</rating>
<name>Hihi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Former leader of Kantou great ape alliance (Hihi clan). Wears miko suit and a noh mask. Killed by Muchi. He has been with Ayakashi for 400 year before he was killed he told his son that he would choose for himself whether he would follow the Rikuo.</description>
<picture>55499.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="23220" type="appears in" update="2010-10-15">
<rating votes="6">5.75</rating>
<name>Shouei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The son of Hihi, his father was murdered by the Shikoku demons, he`s larger than most other demons in the group. He is strong enough to stop a charging Takarabune with the help of Reira freezing the ground.</description>
<picture>56868.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="177" picture="170981.jpg">Hoshino Takanori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23223" type="appears in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="10">3.50</rating>
<name>Yosuzume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the seven heads of the 88 kiyakou. A youkai whose black feathers make whoever they touch go temporarily blind, her "Genyakou" (Lit: Phantom Night Parade). She faces Yuki Onna but is defeated. She later takes the Maou`s Hammer from Tamazuki and returns it to Mitsume Yazura of the Nura clan, who started this incident.</description>
<picture>56871.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="24938" type="appears in" update="2018-04-21">
<rating votes="9">5.33</rating>
<name>Koke-hime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Koke-hime is one of the land gods. She wears a Heian-style kimono and usually stays in her shrine. Koke-hime was almost cursed by http://anidb.net/ch23226 [Sodemogi] but saved by http://anidb.net/ch19468 [Kurotabou].
400 years ago, Kokehime was a human, but because of her power that made her tears into pearls, she was targeted by Hagoromo Gitsune. After being saved by the http://anidb.net/ch37514 [Nura Clan], she moved to Edo. She was shown to be attached to http://anidb.net/ch20583 [Hitotsume Nyudou] after the defeat of Hagorome Gitsune 400 years ago. Afterwards she was worshiped by the people and became a land god.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>216543.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1626" picture="156857.jpg">Ookubo Aiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27182" type="appears in" update="2011-07-15">
<rating votes="9">1.45</rating>
<name>Gagoze</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Head of Gagoze alliance.
He was known as a youkai that kidnapped and ate children.
Many believed that he would be next in line to be the master of all spirits and was surprised when Rikuo was put forth as a candidate instead. After a failed plan to kill the potential third, he is killed by Night Rikuo.</description>
<picture>75519.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4688" picture="29259.jpg">Hirota Kousei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33911" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-25">
<rating votes="37">8.33</rating>
<name>Nurarihyon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74281.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33912" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-06">
<rating votes="22">7.62</rating>
<name>Setsura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Another yuki-onna who was part of Nurarihyon`s Hyakki Yakou 400 years ago. Her solution to things she didn`t like was to freeze them. She is Tsurara`s mother and had an unrequited love for Nurarihyon, which resulted in her greatly disliking his eventual wife, Youhime. At the final battle with Hagoromo-Gitsune, she had a death match with Ibaraki-douji.</description>
<picture>76563.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34216" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-04">
<rating votes="6">6.67</rating>
<name>Nura Rikuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Child version of Nura Rikuo around the time when he first awoke as a youkai.</description>
<picture>74784.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34631" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-15">
<rating votes="7">7.23</rating>
<name>Keikain Ryuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is Yura`s older brother and follows the belief that the world is black and white, with youkai being absolute black, whereas he and the rest of the Onmyouji are white, causing him to have no hesitation in striking down one. He is a trickster and a liar, he constantly teases and berates Yura and attacks Rikuo to make him turn into his "Night" form. He only left his first battle with Rikuo out of respect for the latter`s human blood, saying he doesn`t accept "grey" existences. He later returns to fight Akifusa. He`s revealed to have been a potential candidate for the leadership of the household and is injured in his fight with Akifusa and rescued by Mamiru.</description>
<picture>75520.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34632" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-15">
<rating votes="4">8.24</rating>
<name>Keikain Mamiru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is completely devoted to destroying youkai to the point where he will fight even if outnumbered. He is said to be the most talented in the house so far and managed to defeat Aotabou, albeit while the latter was in his sealed form. Yura comments that his personality was different when he was younger, indicating that since they last met he had been changed somehow. He appeared during the invasion to save Ryuuji.</description>
<picture>75521.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34634" type="appears in" update="2011-07-18">
<rating votes="16">8.33</rating>
<name>Nura Rihan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rikuo`s father and the second head of the Nura group. The son of Nurarihyon and Yohime, he is a hanyou (half youkai) and the Nura group`s power reached its peak under his leadership. Mostly because of his wife, Yamabuki Otome encouraging him. He didn`t want Rikuo to know about the yakuza aspect of the youkai world, and raised the boy in such a way as to prevent him from learning of it. He was killed by Hagoromo Gitsune when Rikuo was young.
It was later revealed that before he married his current wife, Rihan fell in love with and wedded Yamabuki Otome, a beautiful ayakashi. However, due to Hagoromo-Gitsune`s curse on Nurarihyon (that his youkai bloodline would die out), they couldn`t have children. Blaming it on herself, Yamabuki Otome eventually left Rihan a poem grieving her infertility and disappeared, presumably dead. In a scheme to get rid of Rihan to revive Hagoromo-Gitsune, Abe no Seimei and Sanmoto Gorouzaemon revived Yamabuki Otome as a child or her younger self and Hagoromo-Gitsune, who possessed her body and fabricated her memories. As her form resembled his late first wife, Rihan got close to her. It was only then when Rihan turned his back from Hagoromo-Gitsune that she recited Yamabuki Otome`s farewell poem (The `key` to his death) and slashed him from behind, killing Rihan with young Rikuo witnessing his father`s death.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>75524.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34635" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-17">
<rating votes="24">7.57</rating>
<name>Hagoromo-Gitsune</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The demon fox who was originally considered the master of spirits, she is the head of the Kyoto youkai. According to Keikan records, Hagorome-Gitsune first appeared during turbulent times, possessed the body of a notable child, and took control of the body to attain adult form. Gathering power by absorbing hatred, envy, anger, despair and large quantities of malice from the center of government, she continued to grow stronger and it is said that the stronger the malice in the world, the stronger she will become. Despite this, she can only live as long as a human lifetime, for when her host body`s life reaches its end, she must hide her "true form" somewhere safe until a suitable candidate for her reincarnation appears. If her "true form" isn`t sealed, then regardless of how many times she is defeated, she will continue to reincarnate into the next generation.
400 years ago, she posed as the legendary courtesan Yodo-dono and fought Nurarihyon at Osaka Castle, but was eventually defeated. In the course of 400 years, her reincarnation was repeatedly prevented due to Nura Rihan`s interferences, until Abe no Seimei and Sanmoto Gorouzaemon successfully plotted his murder by reviving and manipulating Rihan`s ex-wife, the ayakashi Yamabuki Otome. Yamabuki Otome` revived body (which resembled her previous appearance) later became Hagoromo Gitsune`s current host and successfully gave birth to Nue, Abe no Seimei`s reincarnation during the battle in Kyoto. Hagoromo Gitsune was eventually forced out of the host`s body by Rikuo`s Nenekirimaru and Yura`s Hangun. As soon as Nue broke out of his cocoon, he killed and sent Hagoromo Gitsune to hell.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>53015.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34661" type="appears in" update="2011-07-15">
<rating votes="4">6.24</rating>
<name>Jami</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A youkai who protects the descendant of his lord, he was a loyal samurai who was betrayed by his lord`s wife out of jealousy but as he died from a flood while being trapped in prison he was so concerned over protecting him, he became a youkai. Part of Rikuo`s new "Hyakki Yakou", he is currently fighting alongside the Nura household against Kyoto youkai. He fought Tsuchigumo</description>
<picture>75568.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="82" picture="216596.jpg">Asakawa Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35238" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-27">
<rating votes="13">7.27</rating>
<name>You-hime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A human noblewoman 400 years ago with the power to heal sickness/injuries. She became Nurarihyon`s wife (and thus is Rikuo`s grandmother). Her father took advantage of the people`s desire for healing by charging exorbitant fees that only the wealthy could afford. Youhime herself is kind but sheltered and only saw the outside world after meeting Nurarihyon, who spirited her away from her family`s home to give her a taste of the real world. She was targeted and kidnapped by Hagoromo-Gitsune, but was rescued by Nurarihyon after a gruelling battle. After their son Rihan is born, she worries constantly about her husband and prefers he not get involved in unnecessary fights.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>76564.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35239" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="4">2.26</rating>
<name>Yodo-dono</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76565.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="158" picture="38198.jpg">Neya Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35240" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-06">
<rating votes="5">3.06</rating>
<name>Kidomaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Loyal servant of Hagoromo, he tries to recruit the Toono demons, only for his proposition to be declined. Following this he attempts to kill Rikuo. He was fighting Hihi 400 years ago. He appeared and stab Kejourou while Ibaraki Douji was fighting with her and Kubinashi. He has god-like speed and his fear is to allow his sword to attack like tree branches from a tree spreading or cherry blossom petal scattering. He wears a oni mask that is created by is fear when he fights seriously. He was defeated by Rikuo and Kurotabou.</description>
<picture>76567.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="371" picture="166173.jpg">Kuroda Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35244" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-06">
<rating votes="5">5.05</rating>
<name>Ibaraki Douji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A youkai in the form of a man with half of his body that looks like a wood. He was seen fighting Setsura 400 years ago. He is quite rude. He wields a Daishou and is currently preparing to fight Kubinashi and Kejourou, and later Kurotabou. His Hatsu is "Onideko" which allows him to manipulate lightning and can shoot lightning no matter which direction Ibaraki Douji is facing. He is a youkai who likes to see blood. The reason for this is because long ago, an old couple prayed for a child and found Ibaraki Douji who have been abandoned beside a shrine. The old man was a barber and he taught his skill to Ibaraki Douji. One day, Ibaraki Douji injured one of his customers, he panicked and without realising it, he licked the blood on his hand. He remembered the taste of blood because he was an Oni. He was feared and threw out of his hometown. He killed his customer and father and soon his named was known by the whole nation. It was then Shuten Doji, the commander of oni reached out to him. Shuten Douji was the first one to accept him and made him his son. Nue became the leader of the oni after killing Shuten Douji. The wood on his face acts as a stupa for Shuten Douji who now resides in Ibaraki Douji`s left cheek.</description>
<picture>76570.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="592" picture="170729.jpg">Tsuda Kenjirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35245" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-06">
<rating votes="3">3.79</rating>
<name>Shoukera</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A youkai in the form of a man with long hair. He is seen 400 years ago with Hagoromo Gitsune and also in a church. He is now with Hagoromo Gitsune. He fought Daruma 400 years ago. He attack the Keikain along his insect youkai minion. He uses a massive attack that is in the form of a cross and he wield a cross spear. He can turn into a form where his eyes and body became those of a bee, growing a pair of giant mosquito wings, with hands similar to those of a praying mantis. According to the Keikain report, Shoukera is a yokai who reports the sins of a human to Heaven. Legend said that Shoukera come forth once every 60 days on "Koushin", the 57th day. He is an insect yokai who ascends to heaven and reports all the human`s sin while they are sleeping to heaven. Heaven then takes the lives of those who have sinned. This is why people must not sleep on the day of Koushin. To avoid this, one would spend the entire day praying to a statue of the raging god, Shoumen Kongou. He didn`t show up in the castle along with the other heads and is the first of all the heads to be killed.</description>
<picture>76571.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="180" picture="171567.jpg">Saiga Mitsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35248" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-23">
<rating votes="4">4.79</rating>
<name>Kurama Yama no Oo Tengu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is a Tengu. He is shown fighting Gyuuki 400 years ago. He fights with Rikuo alongside Gyuuki. It was revealed when Hagoromo-Gitsune became the nine-tails, he no longer had a place by her side as it was replaced by Minagoroshi Jizou who had altered Ibaraki Douji, Shoukera, Kyokotsu and Kidoumaru`s memories. He stated this is the only time he cannot accept the birth of the Nue because Minagoroshi Jizou had made a fool out of him and he will stop it without fail. He and Gyuuki seem to have agreed to a time to train Rikuo.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>76572.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="282" picture="223615.jpg">Houki Katsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35249" type="appears in" update="2011-12-08">
<rating votes="4">2.96</rating>
<name>Kyoukotsu (Chichi)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A youkai in the form of a mummy-like man. In the present, his daughter seems to have taken up his position.</description>
<picture>76573.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2062" picture="188714.jpg">Ichijou Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35250" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-07">
<rating votes="10">4.56</rating>
<name>Kyoukotsu (Musume)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53188.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35255" type="appears in" update="2011-08-06">
<rating votes="4">1.72</rating>
<name>Gairouta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A ogre youkai. He is killed by Nurarihyon 400 years ago. He uses a giant club and an attack called Raikonbou-Lightning Club And Takekaze-Tempest.</description>
<picture>76576.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6011" picture="223622.jpg">Juku Ikkyuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35257" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-06">
<rating votes="10">7.66</rating>
<name>Keikain Hidemoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The 13th head of the Keikain family, he fought alongside Nurarihyon to seal the Hagoromo-Gitsune using the shikigami, "Hagun", which summons the spirits of all the previous heads of the Keikain family. He lends the spirit blade, Nenekirimaru, to Nurarihyon during the battle, and later after he dies he becomes part of "Hagun".</description>
<picture>76577.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35258" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-06">
<rating votes="3">7.08</rating>
<name>Keikain Koremitsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76578.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="68" picture="16675.jpg">Yasumura Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36430" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-07">
<rating votes="7">3.33</rating>
<name>Akagappa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The leader of the Toono village and possibly the strongest.</description>
<picture>53022.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="623" picture="18148.jpg">Miyauchi Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36431" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-07">
<rating votes="7">2.75</rating>
<name>Amezou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Numa(Swamp)Kappa demon, he normally cleans the bathrooms. He fights using water.</description>
<picture>53050.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="326" picture="17162.jpg">Mizushima Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36433" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-05">
<rating votes="12">6.97</rating>
<name>Awashima</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An Amanojaku demon who normally chops the firewood, he fights with a sword. He is a type of demon who turns into a female at night. The female form of Awashima can dance like a heavenly nymph. She uses attack that is respectively "Hatsu: Ikusa Otome Enbu (Spirit Emission: Dance of the battle maiden)", "Hyoui of the heavenly nymph, Perfect Motherhood Izanami" and "Hyoui of the raging god, Perfect Fatherhood Izanagi". His/Her name comes from the name of the second child of Izanagi and Izanami in the Kojiki, Awashima no Kami, who was neither male nor female, for that she was discarded.</description>
<picture>53079.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36434" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-07">
<rating votes="3">5.02</rating>
<name>Dohiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Huttachi demon in charge of cleaning.</description>
<picture>53080.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2145" picture="82117.jpg">Miyashita Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36435" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-07">
<rating votes="7">7.22</rating>
<name>Itaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Kamaitachi demon instructed to watch and teach Rikuo. He fights using two or three sickles and his best skill is "Youkai Ninpou: Rera Makiri", a sickle wind blade. He, like most others dislike Kyoto demons. He turns into a Weasel in the day time and his true form is that of a weasel faced demon.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>53125.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="63" picture="186695.jpg">Kishio Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36436" type="appears in" update="2011-09-07">
<rating votes="3">5.99</rating>
<name>Namahage</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Two Namahage from Toono, red and blue colored.</description>
<picture>53126.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="231" picture="23486.jpg">Madono Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36437" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-07">
<rating votes="7">6.04</rating>
<name>Reira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Yuki-onna demon who normally prepares the baths, she was capable of temporarily freezing Kidomaru.</description>
<picture>53128.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36438" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-07">
<rating votes="5">4.95</rating>
<name>Yukari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Zashiki Warashi demon, she seems to be the only child in the Toono village.</description>
<picture>53147.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36439" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-07">
<rating votes="6">2.10</rating>
<name>Keikain Pato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The protector of the second seal and next leader of the Aika branch , he is a child who uses the original shikigami "Gomoramaru" a large black cyclops. He was defeated at the third seal and is trapped by Hagoromo but rescued by Mamiru.</description>
<picture>53157.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="359" picture="65537.jpg">Sanada Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36440" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-07">
<rating votes="6">4.61</rating>
<name>Keikain Akifusa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The protector of the first seal and next leader of the Yaso branch, he was Yura`s teacher and uses "Yousou Kioku", a blade he constructed to surpass Hidemoto`s blade. It possess him turning him into a demon to fight. He was defeated at the third seal and fought against the Keikain house at the second seal after being possessed by Minagoroshi Jizou who used the darkness in his heart to take over. He construct weapons for demons to use against barriers and is fighting Ryuuji, stating he always wanted to fight against him seeing as they both were candidates for leadership over the main family. He was purged by Yura and rescued by Ryuuji.</description>
<picture>53165.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="143" picture="23260.jpg">Morikubo Shoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36441" type="appears in" update="2011-09-07">
<rating votes="4">1.99</rating>
<name>Keikain Gora</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53168.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16129" picture="45035.jpg">Ooba Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36442" type="appears in" update="2011-09-07">
<rating votes="4">2.01</rating>
<name>Keikain Haigo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53169.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1616" picture="23191.jpg">Inada Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36443" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-07">
<rating votes="5">3.36</rating>
<name>Keikain Matsasugu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The protector of the third seal and next leader of the Fukuju branch, he specializes in barriers and seals. He was defeated at the third seal and is trapped by Hagoromo but later rescued by Mamiru.</description>
<picture>53185.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="214" picture="238138.jpg">Nojima Hirofumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36444" type="appears in" update="2011-09-07">
<rating votes="5">4.77</rating>
<name>Gashadokuro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gashadokuro is a large skeleton sealed under the fourth seal, he is a follower of Hagoromo-Gitsune. He appears at the seal to fight. He later appears at the castle and tries to devour Nurarihyon. Ibaraki Douji told him to get out of the way after he blocked Ibaraki Douji`s way to Nurarihyon.</description>
<picture>53189.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2231" picture="235895.jpg">Kusunoki Taiten</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36445" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-07">
<rating votes="4">2.99</rating>
<name>Minagoroshi Jizou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A yokai in the appearance of an old man with a large eye ball in his forehead. Yosuzume gave the Maou`s hammer to him. He has altered Ibaraki Douji, Shoukera, Kyokotsu and Kidoumaru`s memory and took up the Great Tengu Of Mount Kurama`s seat to further his own ambitions. He is actually Sanmoto Gorouzaemon, leader of the Edo Hyaku Monogatari clan which Nura Rihan destroyed. Because of Akifusa`s activation of a forbidden technique, it resulted in him being possessed by Jizou and attacking Ryuuji at the location of one seals. Later, he was killed by Rikuo.</description>
<picture>53190.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="173" picture="150067.jpg">Chafuurin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37370" type="appears in" update="2011-11-15">
<rating votes="4">6.40</rating>
<name>Tsuchigumo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsuchigumo joined Hagoromo-Gitsune to fight someone strong. He was sealed by Hidemoto Keikain 400 years ago and is described by Hidemoto as an ayakashi that must not be encountered. He is tremendously strong, able to defeat Rikuo and his Hyakki Yakou easily and without any signs of injury. Hidemoto only managed to seal him by tricking him into a deep sleep 400 years ago. When Tsuchigumo is hungry, he will devour anything, whether it is human, youkai or God. He seems to be the only one who remembers the Great Tengu of Mount Kurama. It is probable that this is due to him being sealed before Minagoroshi Jizou started to alter everyone`s memories.</description>
<picture>77183.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37514" type="appears in" update="2011-10-08">
<rating votes="8">5.51</rating>
<name>Nura-gumi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Nura Clan is the biggest youkai faction in eastern Japan, they were first formed during the Sengoku Era and currently rule over the Kantou area. They are a yakuza youkai group with Nurarihyon as their leader and use the character for fear (畏) as their symbol. There are about ten thousand youkai who are considered members of the Nura group, divided into about 70 sub-clans. The group itself has been said to be in decline since the death of the second head, Rihan Nura.
The Nura Clan main house is located in Ukiyoe Town.
Source: http://nurarihyonnomago.wikia.com</description>
<picture>1723.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="37515" type="appears in" update="2011-10-08">
<rating votes="4">3.75</rating>
<name>Oumukade</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Oumukade is a Nura Clan board member and the chairman of the Centipede Tribe.
Source: http://nurarihyonnomago.wikia.com</description>
<picture>1725.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="37517" type="appears in" update="2018-04-21">
<rating votes="4">3.17</rating>
<name>Mottainai Obake</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mottainai Obake is a http://anidb.net/ch37514 [Nura Clan] board member and the chairman of the Obake Clan.
Source: Nurarihyon no Mago Wiki</description>
<picture>216545.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="37518" type="appears in" update="2018-04-21">
<rating votes="3">4.01</rating>
<name>Mitsume Yazura</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mitsume Yazura is a member of the http://anidb.net/ch37514 [Nura Clan] and chairman of the Three-Eyed Party.
Source: Nurarihyon no Mago Wiki</description>
<picture>216544.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17632" picture="170934.jpg">Hirota Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37611" type="appears in" update="2011-10-12">
<rating votes="4">5.24</rating>
<name>Tanrou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tanrou is a Honshuu Wolf shikigami used by Yura Keikain. He has green eyes and is frequently used as a means of transportation by his owner. He is named for the star Dubhe of the constellation Ursa Major, which was called "Tanrou" in scriptures from China`s Tang Dynasty.
Source: nurarihyonnomago.wikia.com</description>
<picture>1731.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="37612" type="appears in" update="2011-10-09">
<rating votes="1">5.46</rating>
<name>Keikain-ke</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Keikain House is a premiere onmyouji house from Kyoto that exorcise youkai for a living.</description>
</character>
<character id="37620" type="appears in" update="2011-10-12">
<rating votes="5">5.01</rating>
<name>Rokuson</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rokuson is a Sika Deer shikigami used by Yura Keikain. He has extraordinary jumping power and the kanji for his name written on either cheek. He is named for the star Phecda of the constellation Ursa Major, which was called "Rokuson" in scriptures from China`s Tang Dynasty.
Source: nurarihyonnomago.wikia.com</description>
<picture>1736.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="37624" type="appears in" update="2018-04-21">
<rating votes="4">4.98</rating>
<name>Bukyoku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bukyoku is an "ochimusha" (落武者, lit. "defeated samurai") shikigami used by http://anidb.net/ch19473 [Keikain Yura]. He is the only one shown capable of speech among her shikigami.
Source: Nurarihyon no Mago Wiki</description>
<picture>216541.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="37681" type="appears in" update="2018-04-21">
<rating votes="6">5.60</rating>
<name>Sannokuchi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sannokuchi is a small youkai of the http://anidb.net/ch37514 [Nura Clan]. Because his mouth looks like the number "3," he is named as such. He is often seen in the company of http://anidb.net/ch20086 [Nattou Kozou], http://anidb.net/ch37686 [Toufu Kozou] and http://anidb.net/ch37687 [Ko-oni], and the group frequently play Go or hold miniature banquets.</description>
<picture>216512.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="37686" type="appears in" update="2011-10-11">
<rating votes="8">4.51</rating>
<name>Toufu Kozou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Toufu Kozou is a youkai of the Nura Clan who is frequently seen together with Nattou Kozou, Sannokuchi and Ko-oni. He often played with Rikuo when the latter was a child. His appearance resembles that of a one-eyed goblin.</description>
<picture>68061.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10949" picture="39324.jpg">Furukawa Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37687" type="appears in" update="2011-10-11">
<rating votes="7">5.13</rating>
<name>Ko-oni</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ko-oni is a small youkai of the Nura Clan who is often seen in the company of Nattou Kozou, Toufu Kozou and Sannokuchi. About 400 years ago, his hair was black but it has since gone gray except for the top of his head, which is bald. He likes sake and used to play tag with Rikuo when the latter was a child.</description>
<picture>68072.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="39838" type="appears in" update="2017-11-11">
<rating votes="4">1.84</rating>
<name>Abe no Seimei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Son of Hagoromo-Gitsune, and legendary onmyouji of the Heian Era.</description>
<picture>78800.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39839" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-22">
<rating votes="4">2.73</rating>
<name>Nue</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78798.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="302" picture="17134.jpg">Takeuchi Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39840" type="appears in" update="2011-12-28">
<rating votes="6">4.91</rating>
<name>Yamabuki Otome</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yamabuki married the Nura Clan`s second head Rihan, but as a result of Hagoromo Gitsune`s curse on Nurarihyon, the two were unable to have children. Yamabuki Otome disappeared, presumably dead, after leaving Rihan a note containing a haiku that described her pain of not being able to bear any children for him. She was revived in the form of a child to become http://anidb.net/ch34635 [Hagoromo Gitsune]`s host.
source: wikia.com</description>
<picture>79073.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40374" type="appears in" update="2012-01-12">
<rating votes="4">3.67</rating>
<name>Kappa inu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79848.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40667" type="appears in" update="2012-01-17">
<rating votes="4">2.54</rating>
<name>Hagoromo-Gitsune</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch34635 [Hagoromo-Gitsune] true form</description>
<picture>80110.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41251" type="appears in" update="2012-02-11">
<rating votes="3">3.37</rating>
<name>Keikain Hidemoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81401.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="420" picture="186676.jpg">Akimoto Yousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41391" type="appears in" update="2012-02-17">
<rating votes="3">6.62</rating>
<name>Hakuzouzu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is a bird-like yokai who has a sense of honor in fighting, only allowing a one-on-one between himself and the commander of the opposing force. He watches the skies of Kyoto. He wields a spear called Dakini. He is defeated by Rikuo and asks for death. Rikuo instead hits him in the head with a log. Rikuo tried to recruit him but failed. He told Rikuo to head for Fushime Inari, the location of the first spiral seal.</description>
<picture>81664.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="493" picture="65381.jpg">Itou Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41392" type="appears in" update="2012-02-17">
<rating votes="3">2.72</rating>
<name>Nijunanamen Senju Mukade</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A yokai with 27 faces, 1000 hands and 100 feet. He is an Ayakashi that takes root in the "realm of the heart" of the children he frightened. The greater the child`s fear of him, the stronger he became. He is the guardian of the forest of bewilderment and the gate. He was killed by Awashima "Hyoui of the raging god,Perfect fatherhood,Izanagi".</description>
<picture>81665.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="68" picture="16675.jpg">Yasumura Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44072" type="appears in" update="2012-04-30">
<rating votes="3">3.37</rating>
<name>Shiragiku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>86875.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3128" picture="24744.jpg">Suzuki Mariko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="130828" update="2011-06-11">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131293" update="2012-02-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-07-03</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">覚醒, 奴良組三代目</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Nura Clan`s Third Heir Awakens</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`éveil du troisième nom du clan Nura</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakusei, Nura-gumi Sandaime</title>
<summary>In Rikuo`s past, Rikuo`s father Nura Rihan is seen walking with a five-year-old Rikuo and a mysterious black-haired woman. As Rikuo runs ahead, Rihan stops to observe his surroundings; suddenly, the woman stabs him from behind, killing him, while Rikuo can only look on in shock. Three years later, Rikuo is shown playing pranks on his yokai family and learning the yokai art of "dine-and-dash" with his grandfather, the Supreme Commander Nurarihyon. In a meeting with the yokai leaders of the Nura Clan, the Supreme Commander made an official announcement, declaring that his grandson would become the next heir; however, Rikuo is against this due to an encounter with his friends, who claimed that all yokai are evil, and upon hearing the evil deeds of the clan leaders towards humans. On the way home from school, his classmates were involved in an accident on their bus, the cause being a group of yokai from the Nura clan that sends children to the depths of hell. In order to save them, Rikuo transforms into Night Rikuo for the first time and leads his own Night Parade of a Hundred Demons, claiming to all that he would become the Third Heir of the Nura Clan and declaring that he will protect humans.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="131533" update="2012-02-11">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">今へと繋ぐ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Towards Today</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Lien vers le présent</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ima e to Tsunagu</title>
<summary>Nurarihyon hurriedly went to Osaka Castle to save Youhime. He challenge Hagoromo-Gitsune and her clan, he manage to defeat her with the help of his comrades and Hidemoto (13th head of Kekain Family). After, Nurarihyon became "The Lord of Pandemonium" and his clan the most powerful of all. Youhime realized that she was in love with Nurarihyon and decided to stay by his side for her entire life.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="131534" update="2012-02-11">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぬらりひょんと珱姫[ようひめ]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nurarihyon and Princess Yo</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Nurarihyon et la princesse Yô</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nurarihyon to You-hime</title>
<summary>400 years ago, the Nura clan was starting to become the most fearful group in the land, they`re different from the others because their protecting humans as well as gaining fear from the Youkai clan`s and Ayakashi that live to eat the liver of a new born babies, priests, priestesses and noble persons. In this era, there was a beautiful princess named Youhime, she is said to be God`s gift because of her power to cure any kinds of disease. The princess` power was abused by her father; all people that wanted to get cured needed to pay high amounts of money, because of this, Youhime was unable to see the outside world. Soon enough the news spread, she became the new target of Kyouto Youkai. They wanted to offer her liver to their master Hagoromo-Gitsune. Nurarihyon heard about Youhime and became interested in her, he went to Youhime`s place and proved that rumors were true: she is beautiful and can cure wounds, at that time he asks Yohime to become his girlfriend. Every night Nurarihyon went to visit Yohime. One night Nurarihyon took Youhime outside the mansion and went to their hideout, to introduce Youhime to his comrades. To their surprise, Nurarihyon asked her to become husband and wife. Yohime does not answer, instead said not to go again in the mansion. Next night Yohime`s mansion was attacked by Youkai, and all of the Onmyoji looking after her were killed, only one survived. Nurarihyon arrived wondering what happened and he found out that Yohime had been captured by Hagoromo-Gitsune`s clan.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="131535" update="2012-02-11">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">花開院ゆらの納得</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yura`s Realization</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Yura Keikain est convaincue</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Keikain Yura no Nattoku</title>
<summary>The battle between Ryuuji and Rikuo begins. Ryuji uses his ultimate weapon, and challenges Rikuo that if he manages to survive in three minutes, there might be a chance that Rikuo might win. Rikuo manages to survive but he is severely injured. Believing that Rikuo can`t move as fast as before, Ryuji attacks him but he gets tricked by Rikuo, who slashes him. Mamiru suddenly attacks in order to protect Ryuji, but Rikuo`s trusted comrades appear to protect their master. Surprisingly, Ryuuji gets up and asks himself why he isn`t wounded. He realizes that Rikuo uses a sword that only slices a youkai. He decides to leave the battle between them and told Yura why he was there. After the battle, Yura asks Rikuo whether he is a human or not. He replies that he is a human by day and a yokai by night but still the same Nura, even if he does seem different.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="131536" update="2012-02-11">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二人の正義</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Two Justice</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Deux idées de la justice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari no Seigi</title>
<summary>Kekain Ryuuji (brother of Kekain Yura) and Kekain Mamiru went to Ukiyoe Town to find Yura. During the search, they encounter Aotabo and manage to defeat him. Meanwhile, the Kiyotsugu Parananormal Patrol is having another youkai search, but they realize that lately Yura is not attending in school. They decide to search for her instead. Rikuo finds her training herself in an abandoned place. Moments later, Kekain Ryuji appears. He realizes that Rikuo is a Youkai. At first, Yura doesn`t believe her brother and tries to protect Rikuo but she is defeated. Seeing it made Rikuo decide to transform into his "Night" self to help his friend.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="131608" update="2011-10-12">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131609" update="2011-07-07">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131709" update="2012-02-11">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-08-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">遠野・物語</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Legends of Tono</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Chapitre de Tôno</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Touno Monogatari</title>
<summary>Rikuo was desperate to go Kyouto to save Yura and revenge the death of his father, that`s why Nurarihyon leaves no choice but to sent his Grandson at Tono Village to trained him and improve his power to the next level, because he will never defeat Hagoromo-Gitsune in his current ability and worst, he might die by only going at Kyouto. In the village, he met new friends that helped him discover his own self as a powerful youkai nurarihyon.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="132029" update="2011-07-20">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132030" update="2011-07-20">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132031" update="2011-07-20">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132032" update="2011-07-20">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132033" update="2011-07-20">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132034" update="2011-07-20">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132035" update="2011-07-20">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132295" update="2011-08-07">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-09-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">破軍</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hagun</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Hagun</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hagun</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132296" update="2011-08-07">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">灰色の陰陽師</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Gray Onmyoji</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`onmyôji couleur cendre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haiiro no Inyou Shi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132297" update="2012-02-11">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">羽衣狐[はごろもぎつね]京都全滅侵攻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hagoromo-Gitsune Kyoto Invasion</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Hagoromo Gitsune fond sur Kyôto</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hagoromogitsune Kyouto Zenmetsu Shinkou</title>
<summary>The 5th seal broked, only three seals left to achieve the goal of Hagoromo-Gitsune. Yura and Mamiru was under the hard training of Ryuuji while the other onmyoji the guardian of 1, 2 &amp; 3 seals are doing their ultimate plan to kill Hagoromo-Gitsune. After hearing that skilled onmyoji are taken down one by one, Rikuo decide to go back in the Nura Clan together with his new friends they need to meet his night parade of demons and gain powerful comrades that will come him in Kyouto.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="132298" update="2012-02-11">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-08-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鏡花水月</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kyokasuigetsu</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Kyôkasuigetsu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyouka Suigetsu</title>
<summary>Rikuo`s training continues. At the same time, Kyouto Youkai`s went at Touno Village, they offered Akagappa (leader of the village) to help Hagoromo-Gitsune fulfill her goal but of course Akagappa refuse. The Kyouto Yokai`s are preparing to leave the place, accidentally, they saw Rikuo and attemt to kill him. During the fight, Rikuo realize what is the real power of youkai nurarihyon and manage to cut the fear of his enemy. The enemies retreat and leaving a message that they will see each other again and in that time they will surely defeat him together with his clan and all onmyoji. The invasion of Hagoromo-Gitsune is finally start.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="132821" update="2011-09-05">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">京上空の戦い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle Above Kyoto</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Combat dans le ciel de Kyôto</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyou Joukuu no Tatakai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132985" update="2012-02-11">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">迷宮・鳥居の森</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Torii Labyrinth</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Labyrinthe – La Forêt de Torii</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meikyuu Torii no Mori</title>
<summary>This episode opens up with Rikuo and his Night Parade going to the summit of the Forest of Torii. Once at the summit Awashima picks up a rock and unknown to anyone in the group except Kuroutabo is instantly tagged to be spirited away. After the parade walks a little further in the torii Awashima is spirited away by a boy and the Nijunanamen Senjuu Mukade. So Awashima is spirited away by Mukade and the boy. Once in the realm of Mukade Awashima leg is grabbed and pulled into a small torii. She sees an arm come out of one of the torii and try to cut her head off. It misses and immediately goes to cut off her leg. After a bit of Awashima getting sliced to ribbons with Mukade`s arms coming out of all the mini torii. She is given a glimmer of hope when Kurotabo pierces Mukade`s world but is unable to help any further. Awashima then remembers what Amezo said to him about some youkai being invinceible in their own territories, and that when that happens find the source of their power and stop it. Awashima realizing that the more the boy cries the stronger Mukade gets she goes over and conforts the boy making Mukade lose his fear. Then with a quick dance she defeats Mukade and leaves the Forest of The Lost only to realize no one knew she was gone. Then Hidemoto comes and sees Rikuo and tells the Night Parade what they have to do to defeat Hagoromo-Gitsune.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="132986" update="2018-04-22">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宿願</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Long-Standing Wish</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un vieux rêve</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shukugan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133274" recap="true" update="2018-04-22">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">総集編 因縁の千年魔京</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Destiny of the Demon Capital</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cité des démons, Cité du destin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soushuuhen Innen no Sennen Makyou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133634" update="2011-10-03">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶対に遭遇してはならない妖</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Ayakashi to Avoid</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un Yôkai qu`il ne faut pas rencontrer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zettai ni Souguushite wa Naranai Ayakashi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133900" update="2011-10-11">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-06</airdate>
<rating votes="3">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">全部あずけろ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Entrust It All to Me</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Confie-moi tout</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zenbu Azukero</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133901" update="2011-10-11">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-30</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">百鬼纏う御業</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Equipping a Hundred Demons</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`essece divine d`un cortège</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hyaku Oni Matou o Gyou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133902" update="2011-10-11">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二人の過去</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shared Past</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Leur passé</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari no Kako</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133903" update="2011-10-11">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">闇に沈む...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Descent into Darkness</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Immersion dans les ténèbres</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yami ni Shizumu...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133954" update="2011-10-12">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133955" update="2011-10-12">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134814" update="2011-11-15">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">背中越しの絆</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Bond of Trust</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Dos à dos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senaka Koshi no Kizuna</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134823" update="2011-11-14">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">輪廻の環</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Cycle of Rebirth</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le cycle des réincarnations</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rinne no Tamaki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134983" update="2011-11-27">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">誕生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Birth</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Naissance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tanjou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135084" update="2011-11-30">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">追憶の欠片</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fragments of the Past</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Débris de souvenirs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuioku no Kakera</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135226" update="2011-12-08">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暗黒の宴</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Banquet of Darkness</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Banquet dans les ténèbres</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ankoku no Utage</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135312" recap="true" update="2018-04-22">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">総集編 乾坤の千年魔京</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fate of the Demon Capital</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tout se joue à Kyoto</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soushuuhen Kenkon no Sennen Makyou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135313" update="2011-12-14">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">リクオ, 宣言す</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rikuo`s Declaration</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Déclaration solennelle de Rikuo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rikuo, Sengensu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139788" update="2012-05-26">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">promo from season one`s BD</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
