<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8179" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-07-08</startdate>
<enddate>2011-09-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Mayo Chiki!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">迷える執事とチキンな俺と</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Эй, цыпочка!</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">마요치키!</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Хей, Пиленце!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Mayoeru Shitsuji to Chikin na Ore to</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">迷茫管家与懦弱的我</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">まよチキ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Mayo Chiki!</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">ฉันนี่ล่ะพ่อบ้าน!</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="7622" approval="20" total="26">MM!</anime>
<anime id="8419" approval="6" total="19">Boku wa Tomodachi ga Sukunai</anime>
<anime id="6087" approval="4" total="10">Maria Holic</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="15">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="15390">This series starts off really well.  Very promising with the characters and animation/art.  Unfortunately, the romance portion never blooms or progresses (the guy is your typical can`t-tell-his-feelings character, frustrating).  

The ecchi is great and it is genuinely funny, the romance portion is way overly stated in the tags as it is emphasized but never developed.

Don`t watch for romance, and the last episode has nothing to do with the previous 12 eps as most reviewers have said.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="502713">it actually had some serious story and romance potential that was frankly almost ruined by the over the top moronic silliness which was not funny, it`s like the author was afraid to go all out, like a nervous laughter, i also didn`t care for any of the wrestling stuff, it`s just a cheap half-assed attempt at comedy, it also didn`t fit the mood of the romance elements. 
It probably should have ended at episode 12, it felt more of a stopping point than ep 13, not that either of them makes for a decent ending (because they are not an ending), and if i wasn`t gonna continue the story by reading the manga i would probably have been quite pissed/disappointed, but that is what half of animes made these days are, animated summaries of the first few volumes of the manga, not proper adaptations.
So if you also plan to read the manga afterwards then i guess i can recommend this, otherwise it`s just a long trailer for a movie you are never gonna see. (6/10)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="429421">Very fun series, surprisingly more character development than you would think, and a good job through the first 7eps of plot continuity.  I anticipate soon that it will turn into Ranma or Mariaholic (running in circles), but so far good work!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="443715">Good anime for ecchi fans and great for any kind of light moe (glasses, cat ears, maids, yuri, yaoi, etc) it hits most of those bases. It just never lands a home-run with any of the potentials it builds up. There are many more seasons of this they could have made but the ending was kind of rushed it looks like and ep 13 is just a "wtf" episode they could have placed anywhere in the series. It`s a good romp but nothing spectacular. Which is sad cause it could have been so much more.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="448871">Nothing revolutionary, but not anything bad either. In fact this is quite good harem comedy. So don`t think that this is a waste of time, because this can be suprisingly good if you give it a chance.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="394403">its a good show, lot of ecchi. the ending however it is pathetic i dont even qualify it as an ending.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="495511">Second season?! I want second season! :D
;) Seriously, I had great fun watching those series and I want more. Subaru is sweet, but... Kanade/Usami stole the show for me ^^.
Recommended to watch for anyone who wants great comedy and cute moments.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="220655">Surprised at how well the storyline is  along with the fact that the humor is borderline Hentai...but overall though no crazy annoying characters and an intriguing mesh of various characters.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="261826">If you`re looking for a comedy anime that involved some ecchi scenes this is a recommendable one.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="416107">Really nice anime funny exactly what i was expecting. but ending has left such sour taste in my mouth i really don`t know what to think</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="84998">It is what it is. It`s executed well within the structural framework of its particular sub-genre. It would never be a classic example of its genre by any means, but it`s slightly above-average for a harem show (which is pretty hard to achieve).</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="494541">With a nice romance. a cute character and a bit of ecchi, this show can be enjoyable ...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="473021">Cosy characters, amusing comedy and an overall nice anime. It`s the first anime in a couple of seasons that I can`t find anything to complain about.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/mayochiki/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1006" type="Animation Work">Feel</name>
<name id="9389" type="Character Design">Kawamura Kousuke</name>
<name id="1790" type="Series Composition">Yoshida Reiko</name>
<name id="6090" type="Direction">Kawaguchi Keiichirou</name>
<name id="9389" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kawamura Kousuke</name>
<name id="3073" type="Music">Hashimoto Yukari</name>
<name id="27458" type="Original Work">Asano Hajime</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a light novel series by http://anidb.net/cr27458 [Asano Hajime] and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr6633 [Kikuchi Seiji].
http://anidb.net/ch30385 [Konoe Subaru] is a beautiful boy who serves as a butler to a classmate named http://anidb.net/ch30384 [Suzutsuki Kanade]. However, another boy named http://anidb.net/ch30382 [Sakamachi Kinjirou] with gynophobia (a fear of women), accidentally discovers Subaru`s secret — Subaru is really a http://anidb.net/ch30387 [girl]. So when Kinjirou and Subaru are forced to spend time together, due to circumstances, they do their best to protect Subaru`s secret while trying to cure Kinjiro`s phobia.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="3448">5.27</permanent>
<temporary count="3470">6.99</temporary>
<review count="2">6.91</review>
</ratings>
<picture>228416.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12364</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10110</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4905</identifier>
<identifier>jhwprj</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/mayochiki/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://king-cr.jp/special/mayochiki/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Mayo_Chiki!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>まよチキ!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2198</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>339539</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13582</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2846</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2011/mayochiki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mayo_chiki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14705</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1482" parentid="2751" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-08">
<name>wrestling</name>
<description>Wrestling is a fight between two people without weapons, in which each person tries to beat their opponent. Wrestlers use clinching, holding, locking, and leverage. It resembles ritual fighting as it avoids things that will likely lead to serious injury. It is similar to military hand-to-hand combat or self-defence systems.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1637" parentid="2565" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>reverse trap</name>
<description>A reverse trap is a plot device where a female character is mistaken for a male, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the female (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the female, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the female character as a male; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through her behaviour, and/or language. A female character misinterpreted by others as male, without action from the female (explicitly masculine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a reverse trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t618 [trap].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2751" parentid="2881" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-27">
<name>combat</name>
<description>Combat involves a violent conflict with the goal to establish dominance over an opponent.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2816" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sexual fantasies</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime let their imaginations run wild thinking about another character.
Yes, they are thinking about sex, and in an ecchi anime these thoughts are often perverted, leading to a nosebleed. But it may also be romanticising simply being husband and wife, and everything that implies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2822" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>skirt flipping</name>
<description>Naughty characters — usually boys — flip the skirts of female protagonists to ascertain what panties they are wearing (also see Pantsu category).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3129" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-13">
<name>fake relationship</name>
<description>A relationship where characters just play the boyfriend and girlfriend roles.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3202" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-04">
<name>adoring fan club</name>
<description>A character, group or characters, or an organisation is considered so awesome that a adoring fan club is formed to idolise them. Not only do they have notable admirers, but their fans become organised in such a fashion to have a following that could only be guaranteed in real life by precise and long increments of paparazzi-like stalking.
If the character is sufficiently cool, an instant fan club may happen practically overnight (i.e., within a few episodes of them being introduced), although the subject of admiration typically has mixed feelings about the entire affair.</description>
<picurl>48684.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3606" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-11">
<name>family without father</name>
<description>For some reason the protagonists father is no longer among the living. The much too early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family: Possibly the grieve-stricken mother and children barely function as humans. Or adding emphasis to the overall financial predicament of the family, should the father have been the money earner.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3863" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-05">
<name>competition</name>
<description>Some sort of confrontation occurs in this show. The protagonists "duke it out" via various competitions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3993" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-28">
<name>kidnapping</name>
<description>In criminal law, kidnapping is the taking away or transportation of a person against that person`s will, usually to hold the person in false imprisonment, a confinement without legal authority. This may be done for ransom or in furtherance of another crime, or in connection with a child custody dispute.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10583.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4112" parentid="3842" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-14">
<name>excessive censoring</name>
<description>There are basically two cases to which this term can be applied to:
1) creative censorship
The TV station airing the anime does its best to remove most ecchi parts from the show, using various and original methods. Usually, an uncensored BD/DVD is released later. Apart from the publisher`s greed - sometimes the censorship is used intentionally to make a scene look more obscene than it actually is.
2) convenient censorship
Another case of it - more often known under the term of "convenient censoring/ship" - is a blatant substitute for mosaic/steam/etc. over nether regions. This applies both to normal shows with occasional nudity as a normal part of human life (or just occasional flash of fanservice), as well as to heavy ecchi / borderline hentai shows where /literally/ everything is a fair (and far more "obscene" no matter how to look at it) game, except that misinterpreted taboo nonsense coming from §175 of JPC.</description>
<picurl>169459.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4383" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-23">
<name>hostage situation</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime are taken hostage, to pressure or blackmail other involved parties.
A person given as a pledge or security for the performance of the conditions of a treaty or stipulations of any kind, on the performance of which the person is to be released.
(Source: Wiktionary)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4455" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>dysfunctional family</name>
<description>When the nuclear family (Mother, Father and child(ren)) goes boom due to conflicts between family members, sometimes resulting in the breakup of the family or even violence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5355" parentid="3863" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-13">
<name>tournament</name>
<description>A competition involving a large number of participants. Such competitions may range from friendly, moderated sporting events to anything-goes, all-out fights to the death.
All participants take part in the tournament in want or need of the final goal and possible prizes; which depending on genre, may range from a boastful record at school to great riches and/or the granting of a wish. 
Depending on the type of tournament, contestants will either act alone, be permitted a team, or construct a team of chance throughout the ongoing competition.</description>
<picurl>227699.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5790" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-30">
<name>family without mother</name>
<description>For some reason, the protagonist`s mother is no longer among the living. The much-too-early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime, and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family. For example: the grief-stricken father and children barely function as humans; the oldest daughter has an extra burden of raising the other children, additional emphasis is given to the only female child in the family, i.e. with bishounen brother and dad in a shoujo setting.
In rare cases the mother may still be alive, just not living with the rest of the family presently, i.e. on some quest or job and gone for a long time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6083" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>master-servant relationship</name>
<description>To some genres, this would suggest a genuine pairing where one person exists to serve another person, such as in some action/dramas where the pair becomes united by destiny as partners — fighting or battles between different pairs/partners will usually be a dominant part of the story.
In other genres, this suggests a relationship where one person may be occupied as or even forcefully treated as a servant or slave to the other who designates themself the master — these services usually apply anywhere from tsundere/romantic-comedies to ecchi or to the more extreme in hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="11057" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-08-10">
<rating votes="141">7.52</rating>
<name>Senou Natsuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>32939.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="11059" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-08-10">
<rating votes="94">7.95</rating>
<name>Mishima Akane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>32942.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="11062" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-08-11">
<rating votes="58">5.58</rating>
<name>Kondou Mikoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>32945.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="11063" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-12-22">
<rating votes="109">2.40</rating>
<name>Sakura Kaede</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shizuku`s childhood friend and one of the Three Beauties of Seitetsu, she has many admirers, Natsuru being one of them. She has a large collection of stuffed Zoumotsu Animal dolls and likes to present them to her friends; those who receive the dolls, however, tend to end up becoming Kämpfers. She began to develop a crush on Kämpfer Natsuru after being saved from Kämpfer Akane at the beginning of the series, later coming under the mistaken impression that the normal Natsuru is her rival for Kämpfer Natsuru`s affection and consequently becoming somewhat hostile to him. Later in the series, it is revealed that she leads the white Kämpfer, who enforce the proxy war.</description>
<picture>32946.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12349" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-10-17">
<rating votes="106">8.88</rating>
<name>Sangou Shizuku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3634.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="20530" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-03-05">
<rating votes="23">5.97</rating>
<name>Fujiwara Yumeji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fujiwara Yumeji is the main character of Yumekui Merry. Student in high school, he received 10 years ago the ability to perceive the aura of people`s dreams, which allows him to predict what kind of dreams they are going to have. He is a lazy, yet strong-willed and determined person with a heart of gold, who is always ready to help others. He is also a member of a writing club at his high school, and is a big fan of the superhero called Guricho. He meets Merry when she falls on top of him as he comes back from his errands, and together, they enter a daydream - basically, a dream that occurs in full daylight. He is firmly decided to help Merry to come back in the Dreamworld, even if she is not convinced at the beginning, but they soon end up becoming very good friends.</description>
<picture>59608.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="25129" type="cameo appearance in" update="2016-08-14">
<rating votes="28">5.62</rating>
<name>Engi Threepieces</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Engi Threepieces is a dream demon like Merry, who however needs a vessel to access the real world. She wants to avenge her older sister, who was tricked in going to the real world and ended up being killed there. Engi thus asked Yui`s help to search for the dream demon Elcres, who she believes is responsible for Patti`s death. Although she can only physically appear during daydreams, she can possess Yui`s body in order to speak with others.</description>
<picture>62410.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="25344" type="cameo appearance in" update="2015-12-09">
<rating votes="102">4.82</rating>
<name>Kanzaki H Aria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The titular character and the main female protagonist of the series is a transfer student of Butei High School. An "Assault" department elite rank S (The highest rank), she wishes to recruit Kinji after their encounter. She can wield two guns and two swords at the same time, earning the title of a "Quadra". Her weapons of choice are two Colt Government Model semi-automatic pistols, and two undersized Japanese swords known as Kodachi. The H in the middle name stands for "Holmes" as she is a descendant of Sherlock Holmes himself, and her full name is Aria Holmes Kanzaki IV. She is very short for her age and what is causing her stunted growth is a special HihiIrokane bullet embedded in her back. Irokane is a special element that can turn a normal human into a super power user. HihiIrokane is red Irokane that requires a childish nature and prideful personality to be able to use. Although Kinji learned about the special properties of the bullet and potential powers it gives from Holmes, Aria seems largely unaware of anything unusual about the bullet or herself. Just that some stranger shot her for an unknown reason and the bullet can`t be removed safely. As a side effect of the bullet lodged within her eye color and hair color, which were originally flaxen with sapphire blue eyes changed to a pinkish strawberry blonde and ruby colored eyes. Her mother is Japanese and her father is half English half Japanese. Her grandmother is a member of the British Royal Family, having received the title of a "dame". She also starts to have feelings for Kinji after they kissed on episode 5, and gets jealous when other girls approach Kinji.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>67904.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="25345" type="cameo appearance in" update="2017-07-14">
<rating votes="49">4.78</rating>
<name>Tooyama Kinji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main male protagonist of the series and a student at Butei High School. He was ranked Level E (lowest combat rank) due to missing the third term`s final examination. However, when he is sexually aroused, he enters a state known as "Hysteria Mode" in which his cognitive and physical abilities increase to around thirty times his normal state, which allows him to perform feats of near-superhuman strength and skill, such as accurately shooting up the muzzle of an enemy gun, swinging his knife at supersonic speeds, and accurately shooting enemy bullets out of the air. Hysteria Mode is a genetic trait that all members of the Tooyama family possess, and is stated to be an extremely highly evolved version of the natural male instinct to protect women. As such, when in Hysteria Mode, Kinji`s major weakness is the fact that he cannot directly harm women, though he is still able to fight and restrain them without directly hurting them. In addition to this, Hysteria Mode also causes Kinji to develop a suave and seductive attitude towards women, which makes him very attractive to them while in Hysteria Mode. He is currently enrolled in the Inquesta department, though in the past, he was a prodigy (being ranked Level S) of the Assault department, the most dangerous department in Butei High. He starts to respect and have romantic feelings for Aria. He proves his feelings for Aria by kissing her on the lips on episode 5, though this is done to calm her down. Currently, his feelings for Aria are so strong that even the slightest bit of sexual/romantic involvement with Aria will activate his Hysteria Mode.
His gun of choice is a Beretta 92F (which was illegally modified to fire a three-round burst; he refers to it as the Beretta Kinji Model). He also wields a butterfly knife.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>67905.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="25346" type="cameo appearance in" update="2017-07-14">
<rating votes="82">6.35</rating>
<name>Hotogi Shirayuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A female student of Butei High School, childhood friend of Kinji. Enrolled in Butei`s special department known as SSR. Butei rank A. She`s the current student council chairman, and president of various clubs like the gardening club, handicraft club, and girl`s volleyball club. A perfect Japanese beauty according to Kinji, except for one flaw - jealousy, which turns her into a berserker who assaults any girl approaching Kinji. When she finds out that Aria is living with Kinji she goes as far as trying to murder her. She is shown to love Kinji to the point that she will do anything for him. Kinji and Shirayuki kissed on episode 8, and since then, Shirayuki`s feelings for Kinji has increased to the point that she is willing to show her nudity to Kinji in order for him to notice her. She uses a Japanese sword named Irokane Ayame as a weapon of choice. It is revealed that her name, Shirayuki, was an alias to hide her real name, Himiko.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>67906.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="25347" type="cameo appearance in" update="2017-07-14">
<rating votes="67">6.58</rating>
<name>Mine Riko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Female student of Butei High School, friend of Kinji. She`s enrolled in the Inquesta department; although often considered the biggest idiot in Kinji`s class, this is a deliberate facade which breaks down when she is forced into dangerous circumstances. She has a talent for intelligence assessment and, at Butei High, gossip. She enjoys customizing her uniform in an Elegant Gothic Lolita style. She wields two Walther P99s and two knives. Like Aria, she earned the title of a "Quadra".
Riko is revealed as a descendant of Arsène Lupin. Her real name is Riko Mine Lupin IV. Riko also reveals that she was the Butei Killer. She appears to have an inferiority complex towards the first Lupin and wanted to overcome him. Her plan was to make Aria and Kinji become a partner so it would create the same battle situation where Sherlock has Watson as a partner before. Defeating both of them would mean she would overcome her ancestor since Sherlock Holmes and Arsene Lupin fought 100 years ago and neither side came out on top. Due to being locked in a cell at very young age after both of her parents died, and was constantly used as an experimental tool by Toru; and on top of that, due to Toru`s saying that she is worthless and does not inherit any of the past Lupins` abilities and that her only existence is that she could produce Lupin the V, she despises being referred to by her generation`s number. At that time, she was also given very little food and muddy water.
It was also revealed that there is in fact a reason for Riko`s complex of wanting to surpass the original Lupin, Riko was held captive by Vlad the Bad and was recently `let go`, under certain circumstances, these were that Riko would have to prove to surpass the original Lupin causing her to have an obsession in the defeat of Sherlock Holmes the 4th.
She has feelings for Kinji, but these feelings are considered unhealthy because she constantly attempts to seduce Kinji. Even so, she proves them by sharing a kiss with him on episode 11.
After defeating Vlad with the assist of Kinji and Aria, she helps Aria justify that Kanae Kanzaki (Aria`s mother) is not the Butei Killer, and that Vlad is the one who is truly behind all of the murders.
Riko and Aria share several traits: small height, Quadra status, twin-tailed hair and representation of the fourth generation of their ancestral family, and lastly, both are romantically interested in Kinji.</description>
<picture>67907.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="25348" type="cameo appearance in" update="2015-12-09">
<rating votes="73">7.04</rating>
<name>Reki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Snipe department`s ace, Butei rank S. No family name. She`s habitually taciturn, impassive and indifferent in fashion. Kinji later finds out that this, along with her hair color, was to due to the influence of large quantities of RiriIrokane in her birthplace. RiriIrokane is Azure Irokane and can nullify other powers in a state of calm. However, according to a Hotogi Historical Record it `hates` human hearts and the princesses of Ulus (of which Reki is part of) revere and offer their `hearts` to it. She`s always seen wearing headphones. Her signature quote is "I am a single bullet. It has no heart. Therefore, it does not think. It just flies straight towards its target", which she always say before she shoots her target. She can shoot anything without missing her target within a 2km radius. Her personal weapon is a Dragunov sniper rifle with an attachable bayonet. She apparently listens to the sound of wind from her homeland (somewhere between Northern Mongolia and Siberia) with her headphones, which are Sennheiser PMX990.
She plays a minor role in the series, usually providing covering fire to Aria and Kinji when they are fighting at close range or saving them during times of trouble.
Apparently before coming to Butei High, Reki was also doing "unrecorded" jobs in Russia and China due to her Butei license. In other words, she worked as a "Sweeper", killing her targets.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>67908.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="30381" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-04-06">
<rating votes="37">4.80</rating>
<name>Sakamachi Kureha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kureha is the younger sister of Kinjirou, who is a first year in high school and loves martial arts. She is a member of the crafts club. After watching and following Kinjirou and Subaru, believing him a male pervert cross-dresser, attacks Subaru to reclaim Kinjirou, only to be quickly defeated in turn. After this incident, still believing her a male, she has fallen in love with Subaru, much to Kinjirou`s chagrin. While tomboyish most of the time, she tends to try and act feminine when Subaru is around. Due to her father dying from an illness she gets extremely worried whenever her brother gets sick.</description>
<picture>70644.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30382" type="main character in" update="2013-10-31">
<rating votes="30">4.37</rating>
<name>Sakamachi Kinjirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The protagonist of the story. A second year high school student who discovers Subaru`s secret. Frequently just referred to as Jirou, he suffers gynophobia in which his nose bleeds whenever a girl touches him. He reveals the cause to be his mother and sister practicing their wrestling moves on him on a daily basis for 10 years as part of his training, he states his nose bleeds when a girl touches him because his body developed the reflex because he believed his mother and sister would stop beating him up once he started bleeding (as his blood would ruin the carpet). As a result, he can take pain well and is fairly competent as a fighter which is kept sharp by his sister, Kureha, who wakes him up every morning with a series of beatings. He is shown to enjoy instant noodles. When he was young, his father passed away from an illness but not before telling him that his name means "Stand by me" telling him to become a man strong enough to tell others "I will protect you so stay by my side" which sometimes causes him to wonder whether he can keep that promise. He was forced to sign a contract with Kanade to not reveal the secret of Subaru and find a way to cure his gynophobia. He hates it when people call him his full name as, due to the Japanese culture of putting the family name before their given name, it creates a pun on the english word chicken as his full name is Sakamachi Kinjirou.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>73704.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30383" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-10-31">
<rating votes="45">6.13</rating>
<name>Usami Masamune</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Usami is a member of S4 or Shooting Star Subaru-Sama, but quit afterward and is also a member of the crafts club. She is shown to have considerable leg power which she uses in the form of kicks. She is shown to be a good cook, partly because she lives on her own and has to cook her own meals. She blackmailed Kinjirou, with the picture of him and Subaru on a mock date, to be her boyfriend up until the end of their school fair. Kinjirou accepted because of the condition that she will not spread the photo with Subaru and Kinjirou going out together. However she later becomes friends with Kinjirou and the others and is implied to have fallen for Kinjirou. Her name is noted to sound similar to the Japanese word for rabbit which becomes the source of Kinjirou`s nickname for her; Usamin, her own nickname for him is "stupid chicken". She later allows Kinjirou to call her by her first name, Masamune. As a gag, Usami is shown to be able to attract ghosts if not living together with them perfectly (ghosts appear in her photos and randomly pops out in her apartment).
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>73702.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="101" picture="16709.jpg">Ise Mariya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30384" type="main character in" update="2013-10-31">
<rating votes="77">7.28</rating>
<name>Suzutsuki Kanade</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The single daughter of the high school`s principal, who, on the outside, behaves well like a rich man`s polite and elegant daughter. On the inside, she is revealed to be quite sadistic and threatens Kinjirou on his greatest fear and using his gynophobia to make him suffer. She is shown to enjoy tormenting and teasing Kinjirou by using his gynophobia against him. However, she did give thoughts about finding a way to cure his gynophobia although her methods to do so are generally overly complicated or humiliate him in some way and she does not deny that she finds them amusing. She notes that Kinjirou is the first, and only, man who is willing to talk her down and she is implied to have fallen in love with him as a result. She is also implied to be a bisexual as she has claimed that Subaru was her first love.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>73706.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30385" type="main character in" update="2014-10-05">
<rating votes="70">8.10</rating>
<name>Konoe Subaru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The female protagonist of the story, Konoe is a second year high school student who works as a butler for the Suzutsuki family and suffers from aichmophobia. When she was young she was noted to be antisocial and was not close to anyone which worried her mother. She dresses like a male due to the family circumstance of a requirement to have a male from her family serve Kanade`s family. Because of her being the only child, she has to cross-dress and Kanade`s father only allowed her to be Kanade`s butler if she could spend the entire 3 years at school with her true gender undiscovered. Due to her physical features she is believed by everyone to be a boy until one day, Kinjirou accidentally discovers her secret. She is very bad at naming things, such as fighting moves, and is aware of it but nevertheless, despite her petite figure, is shown to be a very strong fighter. Although she initially hated Kinjirou, both because he discovered her secret and for being a "pervert", she quickly warms up to and becomes friends with him - even developing romantic feelings for him as well as becoming less cold and more outgoing. Her father also noted that she started looking forward to going to school. Like Kinjirou, she enjoys instant noodles and is also a fan of the popular "Lost Sheep" series of plush dolls.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>73705.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30386" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-10-31">
<rating votes="39">6.43</rating>
<name>Narumi Nakuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The cat-eared ganguro student that is spying Kinjirou and Subaru. She is a busty first year and a member of the crafts club along with Kureha, she is also revealed to be the chairman of the "Let`s warmly protect Subaru-Sama committee" and is shown to have a fetish for glasses and boy love which is expressed through her manga drawing of Kinjirou and Subaru (much to his chagrin). She is shown to be quite perverted, using a sheep ticket to coerce Subaru into reading a graphic novel of her and Kinjirou out loud prompting an offended Subaru to throw the book out a window. She apparently becomes drunk when she drinks carbonated drinks, and, in that state, gains a an ability known as the "Stripping Drunken Fist", where she can take off a person`s undergarments almost instantaneously.</description>
<picture>73703.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30387" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-25">
<rating votes="59">8.39</rating>
<name>Konoe Subaru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61613.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33528" type="appears in" update="2011-09-24">
<rating votes="4">4.88</rating>
<name>Saotome Ichigo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59444.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="245" picture="46862.jpg">Chihara Minori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33529" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-10-31">
<rating votes="15">2.46</rating>
<name>Konoe Nagare</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Subaru`s father. Head Butler of the Suzutsuki family and Kanade`s father`s butler. He is shown to loathe Kinjirou (partly because Konoe ends up explaining that he accidentally groped her) and is suspicious of his intentions towards Subaru. He beats him up during his trip to the pool as he was acting as a kidnapper. This later created an estrangement between him and Subaru which only further increased his loathing towards Kinjirou. He is shown to be in excellent fighting condition, much like Subaru, when a punch by Kinjirou didn`t even make him flinch although he is apparently no match for his daughter. Despite Subaru`s consistent mistreatment of him, he is shown to dote on his daughter and is very protective of her.</description>
<picture>89910.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="211227.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33530" type="appears in" update="2011-09-24">
<rating votes="4">4.86</rating>
<name>Samejima Kosame</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59420.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33531" type="appears in" update="2011-09-24">
<rating votes="2">4.48</rating>
<name>Kurose Yamato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59416.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4039" picture="91415.jpg">Mogami Tsuguo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35353" type="appears in" update="2011-08-08">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Ookami</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>89508.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19" picture="50583.jpg">Imaruoka Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35354" type="appears in" update="2013-10-31">
<rating votes="3">5.44</rating>
<name>Sakamachi Jirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kinjirou`s and Kureha`s father and their mother`s coach. He tends to be abused by Akemi a lot. Before passing away from an illness, he asked Kinjirou to become a good man. Kinjirou uses his name so that no one will make a fun of his full name.</description>
<picture>89568.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2145" picture="82117.jpg">Miyashita Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35355" type="appears in" update="2011-08-08">
<rating votes="2">7.48</rating>
<name>Sakamachi Kinjirou (Youshouki)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>89465.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35356" type="appears in" update="2011-08-08">
<rating votes="4">5.28</rating>
<name>Onnanoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>89413.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29850" picture="203454.jpg">Nakamura Sakura</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35357" type="appears in" update="2011-08-08">
<rating votes="2">4.43</rating>
<name>Hahaoya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>89383.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29993">Nakamura Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35358" type="appears in" update="2011-08-08">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Otokonoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>89443.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29696">Amawatari Yurina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35359" type="appears in" update="2011-08-08">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Kuma</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>89694.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29673">Wakabayashi Tatsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35360" type="appears in" update="2011-08-08">
<rating votes="3">6.30</rating>
<name>Suzutsuki Kanade</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90154.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35361" type="appears in" update="2011-08-08">
<rating votes="6">6.21</rating>
<name>Konoe Subaru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90227.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36091" type="appears in" update="2011-08-28">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Newscaster</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50294.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29673">Wakabayashi Tatsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36092" type="appears in" update="2011-08-28">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Okami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50293.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="334" picture="228623.jpg">Nabei Makiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36093" type="appears in" update="2011-08-28">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Shikai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50295.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2488" picture="186147.jpg">Matsuda Ken`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36094" type="appears in" update="2011-08-28">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Shatekiya no Tenshu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50296.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29673">Wakabayashi Tatsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36387" type="appears in" update="2011-09-05">
<rating votes="5">4.93</rating>
<name>Choco</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52459.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16763" picture="45795.jpg">Ishihara Kaori</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="16794" picture="214757.jpg">Ogura Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36388" type="appears in" update="2011-09-05">
<rating votes="12">6.36</rating>
<name>Maria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52463.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="328" picture="17164.jpg">Kuwatani Natsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36389" type="appears in" update="2011-09-05">
<rating votes="6">5.14</rating>
<name>Milk</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52457.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16763" picture="45795.jpg">Ishihara Kaori</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="16794" picture="214757.jpg">Ogura Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36678" type="appears in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="4">5.79</rating>
<name>Sakamachi Kureha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55077.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36990" type="appears in" update="2011-09-23">
<rating votes="2">4.43</rating>
<name>Joshi Seito</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59374.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7789" picture="34523.jpg">Moriya Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37006" type="appears in" update="2011-09-24">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Tannin Kyoushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59624.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29673">Wakabayashi Tatsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37007" type="appears in" update="2011-09-24">
<rating votes="17">8.52</rating>
<name>Takanashi Punyuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59625.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53262" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-03-02">
<rating votes="7">3.75</rating>
<name>Suenaga Mirai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Suenaga Mirai is the site mascot character for Culture Japan (dannychoo.com) who http://anidb.net/cr17222 [Danny Choo] developed with illustrator Azami Yuuko (アザミユウコ). Mirai started off as a single illustration in the corner of the site back in 2007 and since then has gained much popularity worldwide.
There has been many Mirai collaboration projects with Japanese companies such as Good Smile Company, Cospa, Nitro Plus, Kadokawa, King Records and more.
The kanji of her name is 末永未来 but "Mirai" is written as Hiragana. Her name means "Eternal Future".</description>
<picture>132840.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="130624" update="2011-06-24">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-05-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130800" update="2011-06-10">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="15">5.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エンド・オブ・アース</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The End of the Earth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">End of Earth</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131132" update="2011-06-24">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131604" update="2011-07-07">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-08-05</airdate>
<rating votes="11">3.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アタシと付き合いなさい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Go Out with Me</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atashi to Tsukiai Nasai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131605" update="2011-07-07">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あんまりジロジロみるな...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Stare So Much...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anmari Jirojiro Miruna...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131606" update="2011-07-07">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">もちろん, ベッドの上で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Is Without a Doubt, in Bed</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mochiron, Bed no Ue de</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131607" update="2011-07-07">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大好きになっちゃった!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Fell in Love!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daisuki ni Nacchatta!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131654" update="2011-07-08">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131655" update="2011-07-08">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132214" update="2011-08-05">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-08-12</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦争を始めましょう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Start a War</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sensou o Hajimemashou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132215" update="2011-08-05">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-09-09</airdate>
<rating votes="11">3.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いっただっきまーす</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Eat</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ittadakkimasu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132216" update="2011-08-05">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-09-02</airdate>
<rating votes="11">4.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">しばらく旅に出ます</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Will Go Out on a Journey for a While</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shibaraku Tabi ni Demasu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132217" update="2011-08-05">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">初めてなんだ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s My First Time</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete Nanda</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132218" update="2011-08-05">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-08-19</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">駆け落ちしよう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Elope!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakeochi Shiyou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132901" update="2011-09-11">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="11">4.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">にゅ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hic!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nyu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132936" update="2011-09-13">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">迷える執事とチキンな俺と</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dismay of a Butler and I, the Chicken</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mayoeru Shitsuji to Chicken na Ore to</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133019" update="2011-09-13">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-09-30</airdate>
<rating votes="11">2.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">揉んでください!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Please Fondle It!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Monde Kudasai!</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
