<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8203" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-06-04</startdate>
<enddate>2011-06-04</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gekijouban Sengoku Basara: The Last Party</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Ерата Сенгоку: Последното парти</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">劇場版 戦国BASARA The Last Party</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Sengoku Basara: Samurai Kings - The Last Party</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7490" type="Prequel">Sengoku Basara Ni</anime>
<anime id="10406" type="Other">Sengoku Basara: Judge End</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1"/>
<url>http://www.basara-movie2011.com/main.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="8586" type="Direction">Nomura Kazuya</name>
<name id="2949" type="Character Design">Ookubo Tooru</name>
<name id="1283" type="Original Work">Capcom</name>
<name id="2949" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ookubo Tooru</name>
<name id="6722" type="Music">Sawano Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="721" type="Work">Production I.G</name>
</creators>
<description>With the fall of http://anidb.net/ch18083 [Toyotomi Hideyoshi], Japan is once again plunged into chaos as his once subordinate http://anidb.net/ch30977 [Ishida Mitsunari] seeks revenge against http://anidb.net/ch5949 [Date Masamune]. http://anidb.net/ch30976 [Tokugawa Ieyasu], however, seeks a different path despite having once been under Toyotomi`s command. Their fates soon intertwine with http://anidb.net/ch5950 [Sanada Yukimura]`s and other warriors` across the land. With a new unknown threat looming on the horizon, all warriors advance to Sekigahara for a final showdown, while a sinister plot unfolds in the background.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="492">5.76</permanent>
<temporary count="496">6.89</temporary>
<review count="2">6.41</review>
</ratings>
<picture>53748.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12387</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9745</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>18549</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5163</identifier>
<identifier>iivgcw</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.production-ig.co.jp/works/basara-the-last-party/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.basara-movie2011.com/main.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.productionig.com/contents/works_sp/84_/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2623</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>338754</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13543</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="267" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-04">
<name>headstrong</name>
<description>A headstrong person is one that is determined to do as one pleases, and not as others want.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1589" parentid="2622" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-08">
<name>samurai</name>
<picurl>244341.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2572" parentid="2282" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-09">
<name>ninja</name>
<description>A ninja was a covert agent or mercenary of feudal Japan specializing in unorthodox arts of war.
The functions of the ninja included espionage, sabotage, infiltration, and assassination, as well as open combat in certain situations.
The ninja, using covert methods of waging war, were contrasted with the samurai, who had strict rules about honor and combat.</description>
<picurl>244347.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2687" parentid="2641" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-02-05">
<name>Sengoku period</name>
<description>The Sengoku period (戦国時代, Sengoku jidai) or Warring States period in Japanese history was a time of social upheaval, political intrigue, and nearly constant military conflict that lasted roughly from the middle of the 15th century to the beginning of the 17th century. The name "Sengoku" was adopted by Japanese historians in reference to the Warring States period in Chinese history (Sengoku jidai (戦国時代) in Japanese) which preceded the unification of China. Likewise, the Sengoku period in Japan would eventually lead to the unification of political power under the Tokugawa shogunate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2802" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-14">
<name>action game</name>
<description>Any game where reflexes are the key to the gameplay, violence is optional.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3327" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-08">
<name>manly</name>
<description>Masculinity is possessing qualities or characteristics considered typical of or appropriate to a man.
Typical characteristics associated with masculinity are: courage, a strong physique, competitive, strong willed, and a sense of honor.
Very important for being considered masculine however is the ability to inspire respect from your fellow brethren and/or being perceived as a virile man by the opposite sex.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6029" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-04-08">
<name>mundane made awesome</name>
<description>Sometimes normal just doesn`t cut it. Eating: you put food in your mouth and chew. Playing sports: you throw a ball around. You need to make it awesome, no matter how mundane it is.
Let`s throw in some gripping orchestral music, lighting changes, different camera angles, something! Don`t write like a man, write like an evil overlord! Exaggerate your expressions and gestures, speak with excessive intonation, and if all else fails, throw in some close-ups, slow motion, and ominous Latin chanting! With practice, even you can turn something like eating chips into an epic battle of light and dark, blinding the viewer with sheer awesomeness.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>149443.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="5949" type="main character in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="127">8.63</rating>
<name>Date Masamune</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Date Masamune (September 5, 1567 - June 27, 1636) was a Japanese samurai of the Azuchi-Momoyama period through early Edo period. Heir to a long line of powerful daimyo in the Tohoku region, he went on to found the modern-day city of Sendai. An outstanding tactician, he was made all the more iconic for his missing eye, for which he was often called dokuganryuu (独眼竜), or the "one-eyed dragon."</description>
<picture>93620.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="259" picture="17082.jpg">Nakai Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5950" type="main character in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="82">7.56</rating>
<name>Sanada Yukimura</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sanada Saemon-no-Suke Yukimura (真田 左衛門佐 幸村 ,Sanada Yukimura?, 1567 - June 3, 1615) was a Japanese samurai, second son of the Sengoku period daimyo Sanada Masayuki (1544-1611). His proper name was Sanada Nobushige (真田信繁), named after Takeda Shingen`s younger brother Takeda Nobushige (武田信繁), who was a brave and respected warrior. Sanada Yukimura was called "A Hero who may appear once in hundred years" and "crimson demon of war", and Shimazu Tadatsune (島津忠恒, arguably the best performer in the invasion of Korea) called him the "number one warrior in Japan." ("日本一の兵", 兵 means soldier originally, but here it is read as "tsuwamono" which means samurai or warrior, so it is not appropriate to translate it as soldier.)</description>
<picture>93619.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="381" picture="186189.jpg">Hoshi Souichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5951" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="29">7.10</rating>
<name>Takeda Shingen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takeda Shingen (武田信玄) (December 1, 1521 - May 13, 1573) of Shinano and Kai Provinces, was a preeminent daimyo or feudal lord with military prestige who sought for the control of Japan in the late stage of Sengoku or "warring states" period.</description>
<picture>93616.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5952" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="31">6.46</rating>
<name>Sarutobi Sasuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sarutobi Sasuke (猿飛佐助) was a famous ninja featured in many Japanese children`s stories from 1911 to 1925. The character was immortalized in contemporary Japanese culture by the 1962 Sampei Shirato comic of the same name. Thereafter the name Sasuke became something of a default ninja moniker.</description>
<picture>93615.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5953" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="22">8.10</rating>
<name>Oda Nobunaga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93617.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2" picture="16471.jpg">Wakamoto Norio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5957" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="14">6.39</rating>
<name>Uesugi Kenshin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Uesugi Kenshin (上杉謙信, February 18, 1530-April 19, 1578) was a daimyo who ruled Echigo province in the Sengoku period of Japan.
He was one of the many powerful lords of the Sengoku period. He is famed for his prowess on the battlefield, the legendary rivalry with Takeda Shingen, his military expertise, strategy and his belief in the god of war — Bishamonten. In fact, many of his followers and others believed him to be the avatar of Bishamonten, and called Kenshin god of war.</description>
<picture>93610.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5958" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-06">
<rating votes="52">7.61</rating>
<name>Kasuga</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93612.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="328" picture="17164.jpg">Kuwatani Natsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5959" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="18">5.32</rating>
<name>Maeda Keiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Keiji Maeda, also known as Maeda Toshimasu, is Maeda Toshiie`s and Matsu`s adopted nephew, and occasionally fights with them. He has a mysterious past with Toyotomi Hideyoshi and Takenaka Hanbei. Keiji is what people call a happy-go-lucky man. He enjoys festivals, as well as pulling pranks on Toshiie and others. Despite his demeanor towards his adopted family, he loves them, though sometimes shows resentment towards them due to their objection to his lifestyle. Accompanying him is a small monkey named Yumekichi.</description>
<picture>93590.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="138" picture="23200.jpg">Morita Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5960" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="12">4.56</rating>
<name>Maeda Toshiie</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93588.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="5961" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="57">5.11</rating>
<name>Oichi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>O-Ichi (1547 - 1583) lived during the Sengoku Period of Japanese history. She was the sister-in-law of Nouhime (daughter of Saitou Dousan) and the younger sister of Oda Nobunaga. Oichi was renowned for her beauty. She was descended from the Taira clan and Fujiwara clan.</description>
<picture>93614.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5963" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="9">4.09</rating>
<name>Azai Nagamasa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Azai Nagamasa (1545 - August 28, 1573) was a Daimyo during the Sengoku period of Japan. His clan, the Azai, were located in northern Oomi Province, east of Lake Biwa. He was both the brother-in-law of Oda Nobunaga, starting in 1564, and one of Nobunaga`s enemies from 1570-1573. Nagamasa and his clan were utterly destroyed by Oda Nobunaga in August of 1573. Major battles of Azai Nagamasa include the battle of Anegawa in 1570 and the many sieges of Odani castle between 1570 and 1573.</description>
<picture>93592.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="342" picture="17179.jpg">Tsujitani Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18081" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-06">
<rating votes="21">6.12</rating>
<name>Matsu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93587.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="18083" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="2">6.57</rating>
<name>Toyotomi Hideyoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93594.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30976" type="main character in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="11">6.29</rating>
<name>Tokugawa Ieyasu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93593.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30977" type="main character in" update="2017-11-16">
<rating votes="7">7.64</rating>
<name>Ishida Mitsunari</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93596.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40265" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-06">
<rating votes="5">5.53</rating>
<name>Yumekichi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93589.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="328" picture="17164.jpg">Kuwatani Natsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40266" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-06">
<rating votes="2">1.47</rating>
<name>Ootani Yoshitsugu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93598.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32" picture="16618.jpg">Tachiki Fumihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40267" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-06">
<rating votes="3">7.72</rating>
<name>Tenkai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93601.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27" picture="26123.jpg">Hayami Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40268" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-06">
<rating votes="5">1.88</rating>
<name>Magobee</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93622.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="195" picture="17009.jpg">Sakamaki Mitsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40269" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-06">
<rating votes="5">1.21</rating>
<name>Kobayakawa Hideaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93600.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40270" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-06">
<rating votes="2">4.88</rating>
<name>Samanosuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93621.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="298" picture="216156.jpg">Tokumoto Yukitoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40271" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-06">
<rating votes="8">2.70</rating>
<name>Bunshichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93624.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4741" picture="45560.jpg">Konno Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40272" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-06">
<rating votes="1">1.13</rating>
<name>Mogami Yoshiaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93599.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2605" picture="22592.jpg">Shiratori Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40273" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="7">3.77</rating>
<name>Mouri Motonari</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93591.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2218" picture="226178.jpg">Nakahara Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40274" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="37">7.50</rating>
<name>Katakura Kojuurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93586.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40275" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-06">
<rating votes="2">4.88</rating>
<name>Yoshinao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93623.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2474" picture="228619.jpg">Endou Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40276" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="10">7.77</rating>
<name>Chousokabe Motochika</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93595.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2219" picture="23794.jpg">Ishino Ryuuzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48525" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-06">
<rating votes="9">2.79</rating>
<name>Honda Tadakatsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93602.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48533" type="appears in" update="2012-09-06">
<name>Utsunomiya Hirotsuna</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93625.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48534" type="appears in" update="2012-09-06">
<name>Amago Haruhisa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93626.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48535" type="appears in" update="2012-09-06">
<name>Anegakoji Yoritsuna</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93627.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48536" type="appears in" update="2012-09-06">
<name>Satake Yoshishige</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93628.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="129552" update="2011-12-24">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>95</length>
<airdate>2011-06-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154290" update="2013-09-20">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154291" update="2013-09-20">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154292" update="2013-09-20">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154293" update="2013-09-20">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154294" update="2013-09-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
