<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8206" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-03-26</startdate>
<enddate>2011-06-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Dog Days</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ドッグデイズ</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ドッグ・デイズ</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Собачьи деньки</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Psie Dni</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Дните на Кучетата</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="synonym">روزهای سگی</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">DOG DAYS</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">DOG DAYS</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8882" type="Sequel">Dog Days`</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4146" approval="49" total="73">Zero no Tsukaima</anime>
<anime id="9332" approval="16" total="33">Mondaiji-tachi ga Isekai kara Kurusou Desu yo?</anime>
<anime id="8869" approval="13" total="28">Oda Nobuna no Yabou</anime>
<anime id="13004" approval="10" total="14">Isekai wa Smartphone to Tomo ni.</anime>
<anime id="6304" approval="4" total="15">Isekai no Seikishi Monogatari</anime>
<anime id="1677" approval="2" total="8">Kyou kara Maou!</anime>
<anime id="13896" approval="2" total="3">Hyakuren no Haou to Seiyaku no Valkyria</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="9">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="448871">Started pretty interesting, but then downfall started. Fanservice began and it ruined the whole series. 
Only reason to watch this is for the really cute girls.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="366427">one of the most enjoyable series I ever watched. not too generic, no fanservice overkill, just nice to watch</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="405614">its a nice not borring anime...
theres noting more to say actualy oo...
its kinda enpty ... but its not borring oo
wierd one...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="433878">Time flies by watching this series.
There`s nothing remarkable about it, plot-wise, however it excels at giving you a warm feeling.
Relaxing but with just the right amount of action not to feel slow.
Good natured story, loveable characters and beautiful art.
Nice watch indeed.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="525522">When I sat down to watch this, I`m not sure what I was expecting. But after watching the first episode, I was very reluctant to continue watching the show. I knew it was going to be cute-sy, but I didn`t realize just how cute-sy it was going to be. But, I figured why not give the next one a try, its only 20 minutes right? I`m glad I did. Its not the best series out there, but its pretty good. Its got some ecchi, a acceptable plot, some good emotions, some character development. The last 4 episodes were really good. If you are looking for something a little different that`s lighter than most series, then check Dog Days out.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="242116">Definitely a really good one. It may be a little bit childish for a lot of people. But I think this anime leaves you with a good feeling and a interesting story.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="43461">A cute feel-good anime. The characters are likable and are presented in a beautiful fantasy world with some interesting reality boundaries in place. The art is great and the voice talents are amazing. The story is purposefully simple and left me wanting a Season 2, which gladly is coming up in July 2012.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.dogdays.tv/1st/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1566" type="Character Design">Sakata Osamu</name>
<name id="6261" type="Original Work">Tsuzuki Masaki</name>
<name id="1566" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sakata Osamu</name>
<name id="4112" type="Music">Iuchi Maiko</name>
<name id="1140" type="Animation Work">Seven Arcs</name>
<name id="3422" type="Direction">Kusakawa Keizou</name>
<name id="14061" type="Music">Isshiki Yui</name>
<name id="9388" type="Chief Animation Direction">Karasu Hiroaki</name>
<name id="33741" type="Music">Natsume Susumu</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch26552 [Princess Millhiore] of the Biscotti Republic decides to summon a brave warrior from an alternate world — that happens to be Earth — to defend her country from the neighbouring fiefdom of Garrett led by the powerful http://anidb.net/ch26558 [Leonmitchelli Galette des Rois].
The "brave warrior" turns out to be an athletic boy named http://anidb.net/ch26551 [Cinque], visiting the international school in Kinokawa City. On arrival in this world, Cinque, quickly takes on the role of a successful hero. There is a downside to all this though: once summoned, a return to the hero`s world of origin is no longer possible, as the disclaimer in tiny alien writing on the magic circle explains, that http://anidb.net/ch30750 [Tatsumaki] used to teleport Cinque to this world. The temporary fun-packed visit to this strange land, has become quite permanent as it seems.
Will Cinque be able to cope with all the adventures of this new reality?
Note: The first episode received a preview airing on Saturday, March 26 and Sunday, March 27, 2011 at Gamers Akihabara headquarters in Tokyo, Gamers Nagoya branch and Gamers Namba branch in Osaka. It was limited to 100 people at Nagoya and Namba and 80 people at Akihabara. Initially the preview was planned as part of an event at Animecontents Expo on Sunday, March 27, 2011 but the Expo was cancelled because of the Great Tohoku Kanto Earthquake. The regular television airing started on April 2, 2011.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2272">4.63</permanent>
<temporary count="2288">6.64</temporary>
<review count="2">5.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>69504.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12246</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10155</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4885</identifier>
<identifier>bgeqwz</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.dogdays.tv/1st/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Dog_Days_(anime)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>DOG_DAYS</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2146</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>338897</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13351</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>dog-days</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1244" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>summoning</name>
<description>Ability to call/materialize some kind of creature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2788" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-21">
<name>confession</name>
<description>Someone confesses his/her love to someone else.</description>
<picurl>160903.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2820" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>wardrobe malfunction</name>
<description>A euphemistic term for an embarrassing display of a body part when clothing droops, falls, or is torn. Wikipedia: "Super Bowl XXXVIII half-time show" for more details.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2823" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>paper clothes</name>
<description>Worn clothing appears paper-thin and takes little abuse to be shredded or torn from the body. This is common in ecchi anime where the main storyline involves some type of fighting but consists primarily of dialogue and fanservice (Ikkitousen and Platonic Heart). Various girls’ clothing exploding as if made of rice paper is a very enticing prospect.</description>
<picurl>150776.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3138" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-08">
<name>fictional language</name>
<description>Fictional languages are intended to be the languages of a fictional world and are often designed with the intent of giving more depth and an appearance of plausibility to the fictional worlds with which they are associated, and to have their characters communicate in a fashion which is both alien and dislocated.
Some of these languages, e.g. in worlds of fantasy fiction, alternative universes, Earth`s future, or alternate history, are presented as distorted versions or dialects of modern English or other natural language, while others are independently designed conlangs.
A fictional language often has the least amount of grammar and vocabulary possible, and rarely extends beyond the absolutely necessary. At the same time, some others have developed languages in detail for their own sake, such as J. R. R. Tolkien`s Quenya and Sindarin and Star Trek`s Klingon language which exist as functioning, usable languages. Here "fictional" can be a misnomer.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3314" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-10">
<name>fate</name>
<description>Fate — The predestined path of all things. The outcome is inevitable and the consequences predetermined. Whether or not the protagonist ultimately decides to follow this path shall weigh heavily on their soul.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3758" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-28">
<name>concert</name>
<description>The main characters play one or more live music performances during the show. This mostly happens for anime with the main focus on music.</description>
<picurl>169133.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3836" parentid="3314" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-28">
<name>the chosen one!</name>
<description>One of the characters in the anime is the "chosen one", the one to bring about change, the only one to "set things right" in a "good" ending, or bring about complete destruction in a "bad" ending.</description>
<picurl>66957.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4150" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-01">
<name>everybody is nice</name>
<description>All characters are nice in their own way; nobody has ill intentions to others. Even if a secondary character appears to be bad at the beginning, they will redeem themselves or become tamed/pacified/neutralized swiftly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4481" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>protection complex</name>
<description>A character has a protection complex if the character is overly protective of other characters, beyond what would be considered a "normal" or "expected" duty of care.
The magnitude of overprotection can vary. It can be as low as constantly nagging someone to "stay safe". It can be as extreme as the protector making it their mission in life to protect the other character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5585" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-29">
<name>curse</name>
<description>A "curse" in this manner depicts an adversity placed upon a person or object by a supernatural power often represented by unique designs and symbols found on the inflicted. While not all curses have negative effects, the majority are meant to remain forever hexing to the receiving victim`s soul.
A common portrayal is that which is conjured by an individual that has been caused great suffering and thereby extracts revenge against the accuser in the form of a curse. This abuser will then have their soul spirited away to hell to suffer endlessly for the rest of eternity. In some instances (such as in `Jigoku Shoujo`) the character who extracts revenge also condemns their own soul to Hell upon death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5824" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-23">
<name>god is a girl</name>
<description>In storylines where many or all gods are portrayed as goddesses (female gods), "The God of all Gods", or the Number-One-God so to speak, is also female.
In other instances, such may just refer to a girl with god-like powers.</description>
<picurl>215285.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6744" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>isekai</name>
<description>An isekai story is one in which the lead characters are transferred to and become stuck or trapped in another world, one completely different from the one they lived in up until the transfer. The new world is commonly a http://anidb.net/t2628 [fictional world], such as a http://anidb.net/t2838 [parallel world] or http://anidb.net/t2839 [virtual world] (other fictional world types can also apply). What defines the isekai genre is that the characters are sent to another world, often but not always a parallel one, and they generally cannot come back permanently without meeting a highly specific goal.
In order to adapt to their new environment, they must use the abilities and knowledge brought from their former world as well as any that may have been bestowed upon them by their brave new world. In some cases, they will seek and eventually find a way to return; in others, they will gleefully embrace their new life.
http://anidb.net/a144 [Inuyasha] is an example where isekai applies to a fictional world that is not also a parallel or virtual world. http://anidb.net/ch7246 [Higurashi Kagome] climbs down an ancient well at her grandfather`s shrine and is transported to feudal Japan (time travel). While she eventually gains the physical ability to travel back and forth between her time period and feudal Japan, her bonds and responsibilities to feudal Japan tie her there until they are ultimately resolved.
For clarity, below is an illustrative example where isekai is applied to a non-fictional, non-parallel, non-virtual world.

* The main characters are from Earth. One day, they are abducted by Nazis from Mars (alternate "world") are brought back to their Martian base. The main characters are trapped on Mars. Their only escape is to defeat the Nazis and steal their spaceship to return to Earth (specific goal required to escape); they are left to thier own devices, with no prospect of help from Earth, and no way to contact Earth.
</description>
<picurl>210952.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="26551" type="main character in" update="2011-01-08">
<rating votes="65">4.10</rating>
<name>Cinque Izumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62467.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="255" picture="40713.jpg">Miyano Mamoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26552" type="main character in" update="2011-01-08">
<rating votes="90">6.12</rating>
<name>Millhiore F Biscotti</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62468.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26553" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-17">
<rating votes="91">6.99</rating>
<name>Eclair Martinozzi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62470.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26554" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-08">
<rating votes="68">5.74</rating>
<name>Ricotta Elmall</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62471.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26555" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-08">
<rating votes="20">5.10</rating>
<name>Laurent Martinozzi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62474.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26556" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-08">
<rating votes="65">7.02</rating>
<name>Brioche d`Arquien</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62475.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26557" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-08">
<rating votes="85">8.46</rating>
<name>Yukikaze Panettone</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62476.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26558" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-08">
<rating votes="94">8.27</rating>
<name>Leonmitchelli Galette des Rois</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62477.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26559" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-08">
<rating votes="30">4.91</rating>
<name>Gaul Galette des Rois</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62478.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="174" picture="41158.jpg">Kakihara Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30352" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-23">
<rating votes="82">7.54</rating>
<name>Noir Vinocacao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68374.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30353" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-23">
<rating votes="44">5.79</rating>
<name>Jaune Crafty</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68375.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4010" picture="25938.jpg">Nagata Yoriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30354" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-23">
<rating votes="42">5.32</rating>
<name>Vert FarBreton</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68376.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1798" picture="20493.jpg">Kotobuki Minako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30355" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-23">
<rating votes="25">5.85</rating>
<name>Godwin Doryur</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68373.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2" picture="16471.jpg">Wakamoto Norio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30356" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-23">
<rating votes="16">3.86</rating>
<name>Framboise Charle</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68372.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30357" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-23">
<rating votes="29">5.46</rating>
<name>Lisl Conchiglie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68371.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12352" picture="130106.jpg">Hirata Mana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30358" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-05-21">
<rating votes="53">5.09</rating>
<name>Rebecca Anderson</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68369.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="216" picture="171983.jpg">Takahashi Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30359" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-23">
<rating votes="27">5.77</rating>
<name>Amerita Trumpe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68370.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21733" picture="152476.jpg">Seto Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30360" type="appears in" update="2012-07-11">
<rating votes="24">4.96</rating>
<name>Bernard Sabraj</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90822.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30361" type="appears in" update="2012-05-21">
<rating votes="29">7.59</rating>
<name>Violle Amaretto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88249.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="483" picture="27541.jpg">Tange Sakura</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30362" type="appears in" update="2011-04-25">
<rating votes="19">7.54</rating>
<name>Rouge</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70496.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4781" picture="68994.jpg">Teramoto Yukika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30750" type="appears in" update="2012-05-21">
<rating votes="3">6.60</rating>
<name>Tatsumaki</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88251.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="30751" type="appears in" update="2011-04-03">
<rating votes="5">6.78</rating>
<name>Halla</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68974.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="32133" type="appears in" update="2011-05-11">
<rating votes="5">6.60</rating>
<name>Remy Anderson</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71389.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28893" picture="151182.jpg">Sakura Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32562" type="appears in" update="2011-05-20">
<rating votes="9">4.61</rating>
<name>Emilio Alcide</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71968.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3155" picture="24137.jpg">Ono Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32970" type="appears in" update="2011-05-31">
<rating votes="9">5.52</rating>
<name>Elita</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72622.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="203" picture="38566.jpg">Matsuki Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37042" type="appears in" update="2011-09-25">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Mamono</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Demon beast.</description>
<picture>59836.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29682" picture="78341.jpg">Iwata Yasunobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37043" type="appears in" update="2011-09-25">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Haha Kitsune</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fox god.</description>
<picture>59838.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="588" picture="41015.jpg">Orikasa Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37044" type="appears in" update="2011-09-25">
<rating votes="3">3.08</rating>
<name>Cinque no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Father of Cinque.</description>
<picture>59841.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13954" picture="186143.jpg">Tokumoto Eiichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37045" type="appears in" update="2011-09-25">
<rating votes="11">4.15</rating>
<name>Cinque no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mother of Cinque.</description>
<picture>59842.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4958" picture="177897.jpg">Takamori Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45066" type="appears in" update="2012-05-21">
<rating votes="28">4.38</rating>
<name>Takatsuki Nanami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88246.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45069" type="appears in" update="2012-05-21">
<rating votes="9">7.04</rating>
<name>Percy Gaudi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88250.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12352" picture="130106.jpg">Hirata Mana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48928" type="appears in" update="2012-10-02">
<rating votes="4">3.26</rating>
<name>Jean Casoni</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126384.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3155" picture="24137.jpg">Ono Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="128738" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-03-26</airdate>
<rating votes="11">3.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇者誕生!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Birthday Hero!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusha Tanjou!</title>
<summary>Sink Izumi makes a promise with his best friend Rebecca to go flower viewing during the last three days of Spring Break. However, while he is alone trying out some acrobatic moves in school, a dog appears and opens a magical portal while Sink is in mid-air, resulting in him jumping through the portal with the dog. He arrives in the land of Flonyard, and is greeted by a beautiful girl, albeit with bestial features like dog ears and tail. The girl, who introduces herself as Princess Millhiore, requests for his assistance, which he agrees to and becomes the Princess` Hero, in order to drive away the forces of Galette which seeks to invade Biscotti.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>609927</identifier>
<identifier>dog-days</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129115" update="2012-06-22">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-03-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129116" update="2012-06-22">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-03-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129118" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-30</airdate>
<rating votes="7">3.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">激闘! ミオン砦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Severe Battle! Mion Fortress!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitou! Mion Toride!</title>
<summary>Sink and Gaul`s duel is interrupted by Leonmichelli who reprimands both for ruining Biscotti`s victory party. Almost running out of time for Millhiore`s concert, Sink comes with a plan to return the princess to the castle for her performance.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>609935</identifier>
<identifier>dog-days</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129119" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">突撃!姫様奪還戦!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Charge! Princess Recovery Battle!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Totsugeki! Hime-sama Dakkansen!!</title>
<summary>Gaul`s special forces, the Génoise trio, kidnaps Millhiore and he challenges Sink to a duel. Sink, Éclair and chief researcher Ricotta Elmar come with a plan to storm the fortress where she is being held to rescue her in time for her victory concert. Heavily outnumbered by the enemy, Sink and Éclair manage to turn the tides when the freelance knights Brioche Dalkian and Yukikaze Panettone come to assist them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>609933</identifier>
<identifier>dog-days</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129120" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="8">3.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">帰りたい! 帰れない? 勇者inフロニャルド!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Want to Go Home! I Can`t Go Home? Hero in Flognarde!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaeritai! Kaerenai? Yuusha in Fronyaldo!</title>
<summary>The battle ends with Biscotti`s victory, but Sink learns that Millhiore was not aware that once he was summoned to Flonyard, he cannot return home. Meanwhile, Leonmichelli`s younger brother, Gaul, learns of his sister`s defeat and is eager to face Sink in combat.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>609931</identifier>
<identifier>dog-days</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129121" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめての戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My First Battle!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no Ikusa!</title>
<summary>Biscotti`s army fights a losing battle with the forces of Galette until Cinque manages to hold off the enemy`s offensive fighting alongside Captain Éclair Martinozzi. However, the two must join forces to confront Galette`s commander and most powerful warrior, Leonmichelli Galette des Rois.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>609929</identifier>
<identifier>dog-days</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129738" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">グラナ砦攻防戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle at Grana Fortress</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Grana Toride Koubousen</title>
<summary>Bearing both sacred swords, Millhiore reaches the top of the fortress to confront Leonmtchelli, who trembles when she realizes that her actions are leading the princess to the same destiny she fought so much to avert, when a powerful and ominous creature appears before them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>609943</identifier>
<identifier>dog-days</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129739" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">開戦の日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Day of War</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaisen no Hi</title>
<summary>The day of the battle comes and it does not take long for Millhiore to confirm her suspicions about Leonmichelli`s behavior and she joins Sink and Éclair to storm the fortress where Leonmichelli is stationed to confront her. Meanwhile, Brioche and Yukikaze feel that a strange presence is approaching.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>609941</identifier>
<identifier>dog-days</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129740" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-14</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宣戦布告</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Declaration of War</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sensen Fukoku</title>
<summary>Desperate to change Millhiore and Sink`s dreadful fate, Leonmichelli challenges Biscotti for another battle with each country waging their most sacred treasures on it. Millhiore reluctantly accepts the challenge, unaware of her true intentions.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>609939</identifier>
<identifier>dog-days</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129741" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-07</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">星詠みの姫</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fortune Telling Princess</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hoshi Yomi no Hime</title>
<summary>Sink learns from Millhiore how she used her stargazing powers to learn about him and why she chose him as her hero. Meanwhile, Leonmichelli confirms by using her own stargazing powers that an ominous fate awaits them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>609937</identifier>
<identifier>dog-days</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129923" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-18</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">4つの条件</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The 4 Conditions</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">4 Tsu no Jouken</title>
<summary>At last Ricotta and her assistants come with a way for Sink to return home. However, she finds that by doing so, not only he will forget all memories and experiences of his time at Flonyard, but he will never be able to come back. Upon learning of it, Sink asks Ricotta to not tell the truth to the others, as he does not want them to send him off with a sad face.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>609949</identifier>
<identifier>dog-days</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129924" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-11</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夜空に花が舞うように</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Like Flower Petals Dancing in the Night Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yozora ni Hana ga Mau You ni</title>
<summary>Sink and Millhiore manage to subdue the monster and restore the fox cub to its former self. Yukikaze offers herself to take care of it and a huge concert featuring the princess is held to celebrate the end of the hostilities between Biscotti and Gallete.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>609947</identifier>
<identifier>dog-days</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129925" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-04</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇者と姫と希望の光</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hero, Princess and the Light of Hope</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusha to Hime to Kibou no Hikari</title>
<summary>The monster grabs Millhiore and flees the fortress on a rampage. Sink struggles to reach the princess before she is absorbed by the creature, while she learns that the monster is actually a fox deity cub whose body was pierced by a cursed sword.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>609945</identifier>
<identifier>dog-days</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="131012" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">約束</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Promise</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yakusoku</title>
<summary>Just after Millhiore confesses her love for him, Sink is sent back home and has no recollecions of his days at Flonyard. However, Ricotta learns that a way to make his memories return and be summoned back is possible, thanks to the possessions he left behind as a keepsake to his friends and the promise he made to them that he would indeed return. Upon regaining his memories, Sink renews his vow to visit Flonyard again as soon as possible.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>609951</identifier>
<identifier>dog-days</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="135101" update="2012-05-20">
<epno type="2">S14</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2011-11-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Promised Love Music Video</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139636" update="2012-05-13">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 04</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139637" update="2012-05-13">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 03</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139638" update="2012-05-13">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 02</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139639" update="2012-05-13">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 01</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139640" update="2012-05-13">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">今週のあらすじ #13</title>
<title xml:lang="en">SP 13</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Konshuu no Arasuji 13</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139641" update="2012-05-13">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">今週のあらすじ #12</title>
<title xml:lang="en">SP 12</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Konshuu no Arasuji 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139642" update="2012-05-13">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">今週のあらすじ #11</title>
<title xml:lang="en">SP 11</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Konshuu no Arasuji 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139643" update="2012-05-13">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">今週のあらすじ #10</title>
<title xml:lang="en">SP 10</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Konshuu no Arasuji 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139644" update="2012-05-13">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">今週のあらすじ #9</title>
<title xml:lang="en">SP 09</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Konshuu no Arasuji 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139645" update="2012-05-13">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">今週のあらすじ #8</title>
<title xml:lang="en">SP 08</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Konshuu no Arasuji 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139646" update="2012-05-13">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">今週のあらすじ #7</title>
<title xml:lang="en">SP 07</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Konshuu no Arasuji 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139647" update="2012-05-13">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">今週のあらすじ #6</title>
<title xml:lang="en">SP 06</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Konshuu no Arasuji 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139648" update="2012-05-13">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">今週のあらすじ #5</title>
<title xml:lang="en">SP 05</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Konshuu no Arasuji 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139649" update="2012-05-13">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">今週のあらすじ #4</title>
<title xml:lang="en">SP 04</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Konshuu no Arasuji 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139650" update="2012-05-13">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">今週のあらすじ #3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">SP 03</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Konshuu no Arasuji 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139651" update="2012-05-13">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">今週のあらすじ #2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">SP 02</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Konshuu no Arasuji 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139652" update="2016-10-03">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">今週のあらすじ #1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">SP 01</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Konshuu no Arasuji 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
