<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8225" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-07-06</startdate>
<enddate>2011-09-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Nyanpire The Animation</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Мяупырь</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">nyanpire</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">にゃんぱいあ The Animation</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="232559">I consider this the vampire version of Chii`s Sweet Home.

We see the adventures of a small, cute vampire cat trying to find some blood to drink and meeting new friends along the way.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.nyanpire.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="735" type="Animation Work">Gonzo</name>
<name id="3630" type="Character Design">Yoshimatsu Takahiro</name>
<name id="1465" type="Series Composition">Takahashi Natsuko</name>
<name id="3630" type="Direction">Yoshimatsu Takahiro</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on Yukiusa`s popular the Gothic World of Nyanpire doujinshi about a vampire cat.
Once upon a time, there was a poor abandoned black kitten. It was so weak and hungry that it could no longer stand. On the threshold of death, a vampire came across the kitten and took pity upon it. While gently holding the kitten, the vampire gave the kitten his blood, and the kitten changed. It grew fangs, a pair of wings, and developed a thirst for blood. Thus was born a nyanpire!
Since then, the nyanpire has been adopted by a human girl, and leads a fun life as a house-cat.
~ translated and adapted from official site by Cranston</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="699">3.62</permanent>
<temporary count="703">5.89</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>63319.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12414</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10197</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4938</identifier>
<identifier>wtfuht</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://web.archive.org/web/20141221093006/http://www.nyanpire.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gonzo.co.jp/works/nyanpire/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Nyanpire</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>にゃんぱいあ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2199</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>339090</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13663</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1409" parentid="1152" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-20">
<name>vampire</name>
<description>A vampire is a mythological or folkloric nocturnal undead. Vampires use long fangs to penetrate the necks of people, usually young females, to drink their blood, both as a form of nourishment and to turn the targets into slaves.
In the classic vampire stories, they are thought to have no reflection in mirrors, are able to shapeshift into bats (sometimes also wolves or some form of fog), have unlimited lifespan and superhuman strength, reflexes and senses, and may only be killed by silver bullets, silver blades, a stake through the heart, fire, or exposure to sunlight; on the other hand, they cannot tolerate garlic, holy water, or Christian crosses (sometimes expanded to religious symbols in general).
In modern anime, these limitations are usually dropped, and they become far more powerful and fearsome opponents than usual. A human bitten, or sometimes even scratched, by a vampire typically becomes a slave, eventually dying as if poisoned, and becoming a vampire, ghoul, zombie, or other form of undead after death, often staying under the command of the vampire who originally bit them.</description>
<picurl>231496.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3102" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-13">
<name>Halloween</name>
<description>"The time of year when the Great Pumpkin rises from the pumpkin patch to bring presents to all the good children." (Peanuts)
Well, something like that...</description>
<picurl>160836.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3968" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>animal protagonist</name>
<description>The anime revolves around an animal, usually only communicating with typical onomatopoeia. The animal mostly lives in a human family and has adventures on a regular base. This can be the discovery of a new room, or being lost by having taken a wrong turn in the outside world.
Typical example: http://anidb.net/a5801 [Chii`s Sweet Home].
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t4259 [animal world], where the whole world is composed of animals.</description>
<picurl>10255.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4199" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-20">
<name>live-action closing -- TO BE MOVED AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is set to be removed. For each tagged anime, please tag the corresponding ending/credits episodes with the http://anidb.net/t6679 [live-action episode] tag (adding them and their relation to the ending songs if necessary) and then remove this tag from it. Please do not apply this credit to the main episode that has the live-action ending, only to the corresponding credits episode. For example, if episode 22 has a live-action ending, and that ending is also credits episode C7, tag episode C7, not episode 22.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6137" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-09">
<name>catchphrase</name>
<description>A catchphrase is a sound, word or phrase commonly used by a person. That may be simply out of habit, or in an attempt to deliver some form of image, like that of cuteness. In fiction, characters often use catchphrases as a way to deliver specific personality traits. Examples include Otohime Mutsumi`s "ara ara" in Love Hina, Yang Wenli`s "yare yare" in Legend of the Galactic Heroes, Misuzu`s "gao" in AIR, Sakura`s "hoe" in Card Captor Sakura, Suiseiseki`s "desu" in Rozen Maiden, and Ayu`s "uguu" in Kanon (as well as several other characters in the same show).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="30373" type="main character in" update="2011-07-17">
<rating votes="5">5.89</rating>
<name>Nyanpire</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cat turned into vampire.</description>
<picture>68433.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30374" type="main character in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="4">6.88</rating>
<name>Dokuganryuu Masamunya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68434.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="221" picture="17039.jpg">Sugiyama Noriaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30375" type="main character in" update="2011-08-05">
<rating votes="3">6.40</rating>
<name>Nyatenshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68435.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30376" type="main character in" update="2011-08-05">
<rating votes="2">5.69</rating>
<name>Chachamaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68436.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30377" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-25">
<rating votes="2">4.29</rating>
<name>Mouri-kun</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68437.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27349" picture="74959.jpg">Maeda Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30378" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-25">
<rating votes="2">4.29</rating>
<name>Komori-kun</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68438.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27349" picture="74959.jpg">Maeda Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33022" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-09">
<rating votes="2">5.06</rating>
<name>Vampire</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75039.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1680" picture="132752.jpg">Tachibana Shinnosuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33023" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-09">
<rating votes="2">5.69</rating>
<name>Misaki-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75040.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6037" picture="30750.jpg">Hirota Shion</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34854" type="appears in" update="2011-07-21">
<name>Katsuo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Katsuo is a fearful neighbourhood cat.</description>
<picture>75859.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6037" picture="30750.jpg">Hirota Shion</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35025" type="appears in" update="2011-07-30">
<name>Tenshinyanko (Mesu)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tenshinyanko (Mesu) was Nyatenshi`s putative lady-love in heaven. Voiced by Nyatenshi and played by Dokuganryuu Masamunya.</description>
<picture>76203.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35026" type="appears in" update="2011-07-30">
<rating votes="1">2.14</rating>
<name>Kako Nyatenshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nyatenshi in heaven before his fall, voiced by himself and played by Nyanpire.</description>
<picture>76202.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="130774" update="2011-07-06">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2011-07-06</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">血ぃくれにゃ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gimme Some Blood!</title>
<title xml:lang="sk">Daj mi krv!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chii Kure Nya</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131596" update="2011-07-06">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2011-07-20</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">にゃてんしさん登場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Enter Meowcifer, the Fallen Angel</title>
<title xml:lang="sk">Poď ďalej, Mňaucifer, padlý anjel!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nyatenshisan Toujou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131597" update="2011-07-06">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2011-07-13</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">独眼流まさむにゃ登場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Enter, Dokuganryuu Masamunya</title>
<title xml:lang="sk">Poď ďalej, jednooký drak, Mňausamuraj!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dokuganryuu Masamunya Toujou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131706" update="2011-07-08">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2011-08-03</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめまして</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Meow There Friend</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimemashite</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131707" update="2011-07-08">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2011-07-27</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">にゃてんしさん物語</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Meowcifer`s Story</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nyatenshisan Monogatari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131920" update="2011-07-16">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2011-08-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">毛利くんと小森くん登場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mori and Komori Appear</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mouri-kun to Komori-kun Toujou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131921" update="2011-07-16">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2011-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="4">1.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">うちに来ないか</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Want to Come to My House?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchi ni Konai ka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132097" update="2011-07-30">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2011-08-31</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめてのおつかい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Errand</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no Otsukai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132098" update="2011-07-30">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2011-08-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏祭り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summer Festival</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu Matsuri</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132382" update="2011-08-11">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2011-09-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">武士まさむにゃの献身</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Devotion of Meowsamune, the Warrior</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bushi Masamunya no Kenshin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132707" update="2011-08-26">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2011-09-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヴァンパイア再び</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Vampire Again</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Vampire Futatabi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132708" update="2011-08-26">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2011-09-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハロウィン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Halloween</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Halloween</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133165" update="2011-09-25">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-07-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133763" update="2011-10-08">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189294" update="2017-07-22">
<epno type="6">O2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Intro 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189295" update="2017-07-22">
<epno type="6">O1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Intro 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
