<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8229" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-07-09</startdate>
<enddate>2011-09-24</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Itsuka Tenma no Kuro Usagi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Itsuten</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">いつか天魔の黒ウサギ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">A Dark Rabbit has Seven Lives</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Dark Rabbit</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8481" type="Sequel">Itsuka Tenma no Kuro Usagi: Kokoro Utsuri no Toukoubi - School Attendance Day</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="6751" approval="19" total="27">11 Eyes</anime>
<anime id="7674" approval="1" total="4">Kore wa Zombie Desuka?</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="622725">Nice to fill some hour, but truly nothing special</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="419931">The plot deeply changes from the begining to the end of the series.

The quality of the draws is just amazing</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.itsu-ten.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="7944" type="Character Design">Isono Satoru</name>
<name id="7037" type="Series Composition">Morita Shigeru</name>
<name id="7132" type="Direction">Yamamoto Takashi</name>
<name id="17906" type="Original Work">Kagami Takaya</name>
<name id="2422" type="Music">Komori Shigeo</name>
<name id="1869" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kondou Yuuji</name>
<name id="13979" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yahiro Yuuko</name>
<name id="7944" type="Chief Animation Direction">Isono Satoru</name>
<name id="5259" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sakurai Masaaki</name>
<name id="788" type="Animation Work">Zexcs</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on light novel series by http://anidb.net/cr17906 [Kagami Takaya].
The first-year high school student http://anidb.net/ch30172 [Kurogane Taito] is a disillusioned youth, and no longer believes that hard work and effort will be compensated. Now, he simply exists as the days pass him by.
However, there is something that he has forgotten. A stolen memory of a girl, a pact, and a curse: nine years ago, the young Taito met http://anidb.net/ch30166 [Saito Himea], an elder vampire, and made a pact with her.
Now, as Taito`s memories slowly return, after an accident he should not have been able to survive, he will remember the girl who had been kidnapped and kept imprisoned for the past nine years, waiting for him to free her.
~ translated and adapted from the official site by Cranston</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1343">3.20</permanent>
<temporary count="1358">5.95</temporary>
<review count="2">2.49</review>
</ratings>
<picture>70090.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12422</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12579</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>9750</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>13137</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4903</identifier>
<identifier>pppzkk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.itsu-ten.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://kadokawa-anime.jp/itsu-ten/top.php</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Itsuka_Tenma_no_Kuro_Usagi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>いつか天魔の黒ウサギ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2210</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>339622</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13554</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>a-dark-rabbit-has-seven-lives</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1409" parentid="1152" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-20">
<name>vampire</name>
<description>A vampire is a mythological or folkloric nocturnal undead. Vampires use long fangs to penetrate the necks of people, usually young females, to drink their blood, both as a form of nourishment and to turn the targets into slaves.
In the classic vampire stories, they are thought to have no reflection in mirrors, are able to shapeshift into bats (sometimes also wolves or some form of fog), have unlimited lifespan and superhuman strength, reflexes and senses, and may only be killed by silver bullets, silver blades, a stake through the heart, fire, or exposure to sunlight; on the other hand, they cannot tolerate garlic, holy water, or Christian crosses (sometimes expanded to religious symbols in general).
In modern anime, these limitations are usually dropped, and they become far more powerful and fearsome opponents than usual. A human bitten, or sometimes even scratched, by a vampire typically becomes a slave, eventually dying as if poisoned, and becoming a vampire, ghoul, zombie, or other form of undead after death, often staying under the command of the vampire who originally bit them.</description>
<picurl>231496.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1632" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-13">
<name>twin -- TO BE DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is meant to be purged in the short term. Please DO NOT assign it to any further characters; add the appropriate char-char relations to them instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1773" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-12">
<name>tentacle</name>
<description>A tentacle or bothrium (plural: bothria) is one of usually two or more elongated flexible organs present in animals, especially invertebrates. Usually, Tentacles are used for feeding, feeling and grasping.</description>
<picurl>236087.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2830" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>furo scene</name>
<description>Furo (polite: Ofuro) is Japanese for bath, specifically a type of bath which originated as a short, steep-sided wooden bathtub. Baths of this type are found all over Japan in houses, apartments and traditional Japanese inns (Ryokans).
Furo are part of the Japanese ritual of bathing, not used for washing but for relaxing and warming oneself. Washing is carried out separately outside the furo, and only when completely clean does the bather enter the water. Generally Japanese bathrooms are small, so the bathroom is set up much like a walk-in shower area but containing the ofuro.
The cheapest and shortest way to show naked skin on TV, at least as much as allowed. It usually only takes up few minutes at most and as such it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales while still maintaining a "non-filler" episode.
Compare to the big brothers http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode] and http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160785.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3265" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-09">
<name>death is cheap</name>
<description>Important characters will have a terrible tendency to die dramatically, but will not, under any circumstances, stay dead. This tends to cheapen the dramatic death of a character to the point of being little more than a flesh wound if overused. If you ever hear passing mention of any form of afterlife in a series, be warned that the value of "dead" has become a whole lot less all of a sudden. Similarly, if the entire supporting cast is being killed off left and right, expect a resurrection by the end of the current arc. This trope became so common in some series that most people are more likely to be shocked if a character does not come back from the dead than when it does.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4327" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-18">
<name>be careful what you wish for</name>
<description>Be careful what you wish for... your wish may actually come true. This is an age-old philosophical problem of what human beings think they want and what is actually good for them. The power to wish for anything can be very dangerous and usually — as a moral lesson — yields unexpected / unwanted results.
A contract with the devil is a specific case of this; receiving great power, especially from a devil, is usually a double edged sword.</description>
<picurl>230309.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4394" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-21">
<name>defeat means friendship</name>
<description>In a series based around an endless series of one-on-one fights, defeating a Worthy Opponent or The Rival will sometimes convert them to the hero`s side, if not always to his cause. 
Furthermore, no matter how many people the Worthy Opponent has killed, how much grief he has caused, even if he slaughtered helpless children or the hero`s own family, as soon as he shows a bit of remorse or goes out of his way to help the hero even once, he will be welcomed into the hero`s circle of True Companions with open arms.
(Source: TVTropes)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4499" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-07-28">
<name>some weird shit goin` on</name>
<description>Scenes of this show point to insanely strange events which seem to be taking place; throughout its episodes, the show may or may not explain what is going on. Either way, many viewers will find that a succinct and accurate way to describe the show is "WTF?", and the show`s explanations (or lack thereof) to the events will often be subject of heated debate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5850" parentid="2869" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-13">
<name>absurdly powerful student council</name>
<description>A student council is a student-managed body inside a school which engages in administrative affairs, usually usually working in a partnership with management, staff and parents, for the benefit of the whole school environment. In real life, a student council holds no actual power; however, in many anime/manga, they have an insane amount of power, which usually allows them to overrule nearly everyone else (the school board, the mayor, the prime minster, you name it). In those cases, that device is explored as a major source of slapstick comedy.</description>
<picurl>70561.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="30166" type="main character in" update="2013-07-24">
<rating votes="28">5.44</rating>
<name>Saito Himea</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Excluding the sealed up Bahlskra, Saitohimea is the last of the Vampires. In the story, `Vampire` is used as the furigana reading of `Most Ancient Sorcerer` (最古の 魔術師). Saitohimea is described to have mischievous crimson eyes, pink lips, and lavender colored hair which ends in a spectrum of colors. Since she was born, everyone around her has sought and hunted her for her powers, except for Taito, whom she fell in love with and subsequently formed a contract with. In order to revive the dead Taito, she exchanged most of her powers in order to revive him, but still retains a large amount compared to humans. She later joins Miyasaka High as a student, and together with Taito, becomes part of Gekkou`s student council and takes on the name of Himea Saito.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>70085.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1445" picture="33610.jpg">Takamoto Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30167" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-06">
<rating votes="21">4.14</rating>
<name>Andou Mirai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Andou Mirai is a student of Miyasaka High, despite her age. She is a lightning demon that takes on the form of a cute 14-year old girl. Initially tasked to kill http://anidb.net/ch30171 [Gekkou], she later went on to form a contract with him as she became unable to release her powers without his consent. While she is considered to be an upper-class demon of noble blood, most of her powers are usually sealed away by Gekkou and can only be reactivated with his permission, upon which her hair will turn golden and her body will be wrapped in a vortex of lightning. She is described to be excessively boisterous and annoying to Gekkou, though she is also often irritated by his apparent indifference to her existence. Her favorite pastimes are reading manga and drawing, and her favourite drink is Mr Pepper.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>70087.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5886" picture="30429.jpg">Nomizu Iori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30168" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-24">
<rating votes="16">3.62</rating>
<name>Shigure Haruka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl with medium length hair, Haruka is the classmate and childhood friend of Taito. She carries romantic feelings for Taito. Her role is revealed to be of an observer later in the story, though she only knows this when her other personality is in control. Her other personality lacks emotion compared to her counterpart and is aware of the events around her.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>70089.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5889" picture="30436.jpg">Mina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30169" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-24">
<rating votes="17">4.35</rating>
<name>Aomi Izumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A delinquent of Miyasaka High. Due to the fact that her memory of a demon attack in school was not erased, she decided to become the secretary of Gekkou`s student council, much to his discontent. She has a friendly rivalry with Gekkou.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>74282.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1611" picture="70006.jpg">Horikawa Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30170" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-06">
<rating votes="8">2.93</rating>
<name>Kurenai Hinata</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kurenai Hinata is the younger identical twin brother of http://anidb.net/ch30171 [Gekkou]. Described as cold and emotionless, he sees all other humans, including his own brother, as inferior to himself. He wields several powers, including the ability to summon different contracted demons and dimensional beings to do his bidding.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>72005.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30171" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-06">
<rating votes="14">4.45</rating>
<name>Kurenai Gekkou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kurenai Gekkou is a freshman in and the student council president of Miyasaka High. Due to a deed committed by his younger twin brother, http://anidb.net/ch30170 [Hinata], he began to constantly seek out power. He is demonstrated to be quick-witted and highly intelligent, wields an ancient fencing-like sword known as Spell Error, and is trained in several traditional arts of exorcism. As the student council president, Gekkou has made a contract with the lightning demon http://anidb.net/ch30167 [Mirai] and is tasked to be the guardian of the Holy Ground, a location with special properties over which Miyasaka High was built. He claims Mirai as his property and is very possessive over her. He proclaims himself to be a genius and considers himself to be stronger than his brother.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>70086.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30172" type="main character in" update="2013-07-24">
<rating votes="14">3.29</rating>
<name>Kurogane Taito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A light-blue hair 16-year old freshman of Miyasaka High, the protagonist of the story, Kurogane Taito used to excel in karate when he was young, but later had to give it up due to a leg injury. Since then, he had believed himself to be an ordinary, regular guy. However, his memories of an event nine years ago were sealed up, during which he had made a contract with the beautiful Saitohimea and acquired an extraordinary ability which grants him a conditional form of immortality. At the start of the story, he manages to regain those memories after a certain incident and goes on to reunite with Saitohimea. He later acquires further powers and swears to protect Saitohimea from the Tenma. One of the powers he acquires is a familiar in the form of a cat, this familiar, called Nyankichi, required a certain amount of blood to be summoned which was impossible for a normal human to give without dying. The familiar enabled him to cast spells which allowed him to see in the dark as well as a magic which curses other magic, therefore sealing them. While Tenma is normally translated as evil spirit or demon, in the story, it is a special existence different from the conventional evil spirit. He gradually remembers the feelings he had for Saitohimea and realizes he is falling in love with her as she is with him.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>70084.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1680" picture="132752.jpg">Tachibana Shinnosuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32586" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-21">
<rating votes="5">4.43</rating>
<name>Suuga Saeko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72007.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9865" picture="37436.jpg">Gouda Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34992" type="appears in" update="2011-07-27">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Taito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Taito as a child.</description>
<picture>76106.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3198" picture="160468.jpg">Shimamura Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34993" type="appears in" update="2011-07-27">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Hinata</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hinata as a child.</description>
<picture>76107.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="142" picture="68482.jpg">Ooura Fuyuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34997" type="appears in" update="2011-07-28">
<rating votes="2">2.22</rating>
<name>Gekkou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gekkou as a child.</description>
<picture>76154.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3712" picture="240126.jpg">Tamura Mutsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34998" type="appears in" update="2011-07-28">
<name>Tenshi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76155.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10380" picture="38227.jpg">Yamamoto Kazutomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36136" type="appears in" update="2011-09-01">
<name>Tenma</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A monster from beyond the Moon.</description>
<picture>50845.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="2193" picture="21749.jpg">Kawamura Maria</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36137" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-05">
<rating votes="7">2.65</rating>
<name>Kurosu Firiel Yuuichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>New english teacher at school.</description>
<picture>52342.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36138" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="3">3.83</rating>
<name>Kurogane Yuika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Taito`s little sister.</description>
<picture>74298.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23312" picture="205591.jpg">Takamori Natsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36139" type="appears in" update="2011-09-01">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Sakai Satomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of Haruka`s friend.</description>
<picture>50867.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10860" picture="39000.jpg">Takahashi Yumeha</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36702" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<name>Nyankichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A monster who has made contract with Taito.</description>
<picture>74333.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23589" picture="127456.jpg">Tsukimiya Midori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36703" type="appears in" update="2011-09-13">
<name>Edelka</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A monster to which Taito came for power.</description>
<picture>55332.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9512" picture="35180.jpg">Togashi Misuzu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36708" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-24">
<rating votes="5">2.09</rating>
<name>Serge Entorio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A powerful half-elf spell breaker from the world of elves. His power is oriented towards seals and barrier construction. Serge has golden hair and deep blue eyes and possesses a friendly disposition. The desire to save their mother from the wounds and damages incurred from the Church`s experiments prompted him and Hasga to join Gekkou`s student council in the human world, after they have helped rescue their mother, Ela of the East. He was influenced by Taito, causing him to seal his mother rather than destroy her, against his original intentions and her pleas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>74215.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27987" picture="76491.jpg">Togashi Kazumi</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36709" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-24">
<rating votes="5">2.09</rating>
<name>Hasuga Entorio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A powerful half-elf spell breaker from the world of elves. His power is oriented towards destruction which also includes seals and barriers and magic. The younger brother of Serge, Hasga has deep blue hair and golden eyes and possesses a temperament disposition. The desire to save their mother from the wounds and damages incurred from the Church`s experiments prompted him and Serge to join Gekkou`s student council in the human world, after they have helped rescue their mother, Ela of the East.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>74265.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="191" picture="17006.jpg">Suzumura Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="12352" picture="130106.jpg">Hirata Mana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37425" type="appears in" update="2011-10-06">
<name>Haruka no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haruka`s mother.</description>
<picture>65145.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27987" picture="76491.jpg">Togashi Kazumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37426" type="appears in" update="2011-10-06">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Ramiel Lilith</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The witch inside Himea.</description>
<picture>65223.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="130728" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">900秒の放課後&amp;lt;前編&amp;gt;</title>
<title xml:lang="en">900 Sec After School (Part One)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Après les cours, 900 secondes (Partie 1)</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">900 Segundos Após A Aula (Parte Um)!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">900 Byou no Houkago (Zenpen)</title>
<summary>Kurogane Taito is an ordinary high school student who keeps having a dream about a mysterious girl who says that she loves him. On this particular day, he`s on his way home from school when he sees a truck barreling down on Andou Mirai, a fellow student at Miyasaka High School. Taito quickly moves to save her...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>580756</identifier>
<identifier>a-dark-rabbit-has-seven-lives</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="130843" update="2012-07-18">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131599" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">900秒の放課後&amp;lt;後篇&amp;gt;</title>
<title xml:lang="en">900 Sec After School (Part Two)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Après les cours, 900 secondes (Partie 2)</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">900 Segundos Após A Aula (Final)!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">900 Byou no Houkago (Kouhen)</title>
<summary>Taito has remembered his promise to the ancient magician (vampire) Saitohimea. After Gekkou injures Himea, Taito and Gekkou get into a fierce fight. That is when Gekkou`s twin brother, Kurenai Hinata, appears. Taito confronts Kurenai Hinata, who was the one reason Taito was separated from Himea nine years ago. Meanwhile, Gekkou appears intent on illing his brother. A fateful battle is about to begin.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>580758</identifier>
<identifier>a-dark-rabbit-has-seven-lives</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="131600" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そして天魔が, 歌われる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">And the Seraphim Is Sung</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">E O Serafim É Reconhecido!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soshite Tenma ga, Utawareru</title>
<summary>Gekkou passes through the dimensional rift to come face to face with the Seraphim. The Seraphim offer Gekkou the power to kill Saitohimea. Meanwhile, Taito attempts to save Himea from a new persona inside her. Taito refuses to give up on the stricken Himea, and eventually— Finally, a dark figure approaches Haruka. What is the prophecy that the Seraphim speak of? And who is Ramiel Lilith...?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>581046</identifier>
<identifier>a-dark-rabbit-has-seven-lives</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="131601" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いまだ天魔は歌われない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Seraphim Yet Unsung</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">O Demônio Ainda Não Reconhecido!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Imada Tenma wa Utawarenai</title>
<summary>Taito and Himea run inside the school building to escape the red rain that is lethal to the touch. Once inside, Himea`s body is possessed by some other being. Taito faces off against the invisible enemy to keep his promise to Himea. As Himea`s love for Taito and Taito`s desire to protect Himea come together, the wheels of fate begin to turn.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>581044</identifier>
<identifier>a-dark-rabbit-has-seven-lives</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="131602" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">《月》が揺れるプールサイド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">"Month" of the Poolside Swing</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">A (Lua) Oscila À Beira Da Piscina!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Tsuki" ga Yureru Poolside</title>
<summary>Miyasaka High School`s student council president, Kurenai Gekkou, has named Taito and Himea as student council members. Soon after, Taito learns about how Gekkou and Mirai first met, as well as the military which is secretly behind Miyasaka High School. Meanwhile, Gekkou reminiscences about his younger twin brother, Hinata. The student council members believed that the battle was finally over, but then a sinister red rain began to fall.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>581042</identifier>
<identifier>a-dark-rabbit-has-seven-lives</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="131809" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-09-24</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほのかに白い終業式</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Faint White Closing Ceremony</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Graduação Branca!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Honoka ni Shiroi Shuugyoushiki</title>
<summary>After saving Hime and Haruka, Taito is granted a brief respite. The Miyasaka High School student council members gather together at a certain location for a break from their brutal experience. A location where girls can chat freely without any boys around.  Meanwhile, the boys are engaged in a battle of pride...?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>581060</identifier>
<identifier>a-dark-rabbit-has-seven-lives</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="131810" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏休みカタストロフィ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summer Vacation Catastrophe</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Catástrofe Nas Férias De Verão!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsuyasumi Catastrophe</title>
<summary>The Spell Breakers have sealed Taito`s powers of immortality. As Hasga relentlessly attacks, Taito must choose between Himea and Haruka. Back in the student council room, Gekkou is forced to kneel before Kurosu`s overwhelming power. That is when someone unexpected appears... How strong is their desire to protect those who are dear?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>581058</identifier>
<identifier>a-dark-rabbit-has-seven-lives</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="131811" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神隠しの同級生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Spirited Classmates</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Colega De Classe Raptada!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kamigakushi no Doukyuusei</title>
<summary>On the day after the student council training camp ended, Shigure Haruka disappeared. The military`s indifferent reaction and Taito`s disgust with how powerless he is leave Himea feeling miserable, which is when the half-breed Serge appears before her. Serge proposes a deal which will return Haruka to Taito. What are the Spell Breakers Serge and Hasga trying to accomplish...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>581056</identifier>
<identifier>a-dark-rabbit-has-seven-lives</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="131812" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">波打ちぎわの黒ウサギ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dark Rabbit at the Beach</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">O Coelho Negro Na Praia!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Namiuchigiwa no Kuro Usagi</title>
<summary>Haruka arrives at the student council training camp to provide cooking. As Taito and Haruka get cozy together, Himea distances herself from Taito. Once Izumi sees what`s happening, she comes up with a plan to help Himea... Kurosu was quietly watching them. The summer beach is fraught with innocent love and not so innocent schemes.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>581054</identifier>
<identifier>a-dark-rabbit-has-seven-lives</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="131813" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">全員補習の生徒会室</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Student Council of Remedial Students</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">O Conselho Estudantil Dos Alunos Em Recuperação!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zen`in Hoshuu no Seito-kai-shitsu</title>
<summary>Kurosu has sent Himea, Taito, Gekkou, Mirai, and Izumi, the newest member of the Miyasaka High School student council, to a sunny beach with a barrier to keep away trespassers. Kurosu plans to train the members on their combat abilities. And then the exhausted members are dealt one last blow when faced with Izumi`s cooking.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>581052</identifier>
<identifier>a-dark-rabbit-has-seven-lives</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="131814" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">抜き打ちテストの新任教師</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The New Pop Quiz Teacher</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">O Novo Professor Das Perguntas Repentinas!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nukiuchi Tesuto no Shinnin Kyoushi</title>
<summary>Taito has promised to become stronger so he can protect Himea, so he knocks on the door of the student council office. Gekkou opens a dimensional rift for Taito, who finds Edelka inside. Will Taito receive the power to protect Himea, in return for a price? At the same time, Gekkou finds a suspicious-looking man in a suit who claims to be a new teacher waiting in the student council office.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>581050</identifier>
<identifier>a-dark-rabbit-has-seven-lives</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="131815" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">すれ違いの《課外》授業</title>
<title xml:lang="en">"Extracurricular" Lessons Passing Each Other</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Atividades (Extracurriculares) Ao Passar Uns Pelos Outros!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Surechigai no "Kagai" Jugyou</title>
<summary>Himea asks Taito out on a date, but Taito doesn`t believe that he is capable of protecting Himea. His hesitation ends up hurting Himea. Taito wishes to protect Himea, who has been alone for too long. Himea wishes to never be separated from Taito. A moment of misunderstanding is driving them apart...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>581048</identifier>
<identifier>a-dark-rabbit-has-seven-lives</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="132015" update="2012-05-17">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132016" update="2012-05-17">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132017" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 1</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>580796</identifier>
<identifier>a-dark-rabbit-has-seven-lives</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="132041" update="2011-07-27">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-07-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132042" update="2011-07-27">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-07-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132084" update="2012-05-17">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-07-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132309" update="2011-08-09">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-08-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132542" update="2011-08-16">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-08-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132858" update="2012-05-17">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-09-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136827" update="2012-05-17">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2012-02-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136828" update="2012-05-17">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2012-01-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136829" update="2012-02-04">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2011-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136830" update="2012-02-04">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2011-11-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136831" update="2012-02-04">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2011-10-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136832" update="2012-02-04">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2011-09-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139714" update="2015-04-15">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139715" update="2015-04-15">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139716" update="2012-05-19">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139717" update="2012-05-17">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139718" update="2012-05-17">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-02-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒い翼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">AMV "Kuroi Tsubasa"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139719" update="2012-05-17">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-01-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">片割れ星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">AMV "Katawareboshi"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139720" update="2018-08-11">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-02-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Next Ep Animation Compilation</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
