<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8230" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-10-02</startdate>
<enddate>2011-12-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Maji de Watashi ni Koi Shinasai!!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh" type="synonym">請認真的和我戀愛!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Fall in Love with Me for Real!!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">まじこい</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">真剣恋</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Majikoi</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">真剣で私に恋しなさい!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Majikoi: Oh! Samurai Girls!</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5235" type="Same Setting">Kimi ga Aruji de Shitsuji ga Ore de: They Are My Noble Masters</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="5786" approval="5" total="12">Sekirei</anime>
<anime id="6747" approval="4" total="11">Baka to Test to Shoukanjuu</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="268930">some say they can`t find the correlation between this and "they are my noble masters". the problem is you need to see a few episodes to understand that part. as for plot, barely in the second half you actually get to see one forming and even that is lacking at best. it`s a good waste of time and it does give some decent fan service so watch it if you have nothing better to do.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="206025">if you are a fan of ecchi/comedy/harem anime like me then this a great show.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="490197">Only fanservice here. For all who didn`t read the vn, it`s just some random ecchi anime without plot or sense</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="507028">I don`t know what comes first, the anime or the hentai game, but this anime lacks of something. It have 1 or 2 funny moments, the action scenes (there`s none "action scenes") are ok (just that). The "joke" of the censorship (exhibition poster style), again, is just that. The voices are good enough for personality of each character. The story seems so compress, not FLAC compressed but WMA, like alot is lost in the conversion. I think they totally failed trying to make an ecchi anime with a hentai game story.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.anime-majikoi.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="4511" type="Character Design">Watanabe Mayumi</name>
<name id="4511" type="Chief Animation Direction">Watanabe Mayumi</name>
<name id="8580" type="Original Work">Minato Soft</name>
<name id="27220" type="Animation Work">Lerche</name>
<name id="2836" type="Series Composition">Takayama Katsuhiko</name>
<name id="1539" type="Direction">Motonaga Keitarou</name>
<name id="9448" type="Music">Nakanishi Ryousuke</name>
</creators>
<description>Second-year student http://anidb.net/ch27357 [Naoe Yamato] and his precious comrades are present here at Kawakami Academy. This group of four boys and three girls have been together through thick and thin since their earliest years.
Now their ranks are about to swell with the addition of two new members, and things are going to become livelier than before. This is especially the case since all the girls are superb fighters for whom blood and violence is a daily occurrence!
~ translated and adapted from official site by Cranston</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1862">3.53</permanent>
<temporary count="1879">6.15</temporary>
<review count="2">4.41</review>
</ratings>
<picture>231324.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12425</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10213</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4915</identifier>
<identifier>cqizgm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.anime-majikoi.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Maji_de_Watashi_ni_Koi_Shinasai!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>真剣で私に恋しなさい!!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2276</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>339784</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13529</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/3201</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1143</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2011/majikoi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>majikoi-oh-samurai-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14767</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="34">
<externalentity>
<url>https://ch.nicovideo.jp/majikoi</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="204" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-06-19">
<name>violent</name>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="760" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>robot helper</name>
<description>In a http://anidb.net/t2846 [science fiction] setting, the robot helper is, in a comedic sense, pretty much equivalent to what the "cute comic relief http://anidb.net/t1835 [animal sidekick]" is in a fantasy setting. The usually small machine has artificial intelligence, enabling it to support their owner / master with advice or help with menial tasks.
http://anidb.net/t1278 [Androids] should not be considered robot helpers since these are far more complex; use the android tag instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2180" parentid="2636" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-24">
<name>cyborg</name>
<description>A cyborg is a cybernetic organism (i.e. an organism that has both artificial and natural systems). The term was coined in 1960 when Manfred Clynes and Nathan Kline used it in an article about the advantages of self-regulating human-machine systems in outer space. D. S. Halacy`s Cyborg: Evolution of the Superman in 1965 featured an introduction which spoke of a "new frontier" that was "not merely space, but more profoundly the relationship between `inner space` to `outer space` -a bridge...between mind and matter." The cyborg is often seen today merely as an organism that has enhanced abilities due to technology, but this perhaps oversimplifies the category of feedback.
Fictional cyborgs are portrayed as a synthesis of organic and synthetic parts, and frequently pose the question of difference between human and machine as one concerned with morality, free will, and empathy. Fictional cyborgs may be represented as visibly mechanical (e.g. the Cybermen in the Doctor Who franchise or The Borg from Star Trek); or as almost indistinguishable from humans (e.g. the "Human" Cylons from the re-imagining of Battlestar Galactica). The 1970s television series The Six Million Dollar Man featured one of the most famous fictional cyborgs. Cyborgs in fiction often play up a human contempt for over-dependence on technology, particularly when used for war, and when used in ways that seem to threaten free will. Cyborgs are also often portrayed with physical or mental abilities far exceeding a human counterpart (military forms may have inbuilt weapons, among other things).
Real (as opposed to fictional) cyborgs are more frequently people who use cybernetic technology to repair or overcome the physical and mental constraints of their bodies. While cyborgs are commonly thought of as mammals, they can be any kind of organism.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42022.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2578" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-12">
<name>vulgar</name>
<description>Talking (and acting) in a way that is considered uncultivated, bawdy, common, coarse or unrefined, or "taboo" according to existing cultural standards. Includes boorish manners and obtrusive display of carnal "assets".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2621" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>bullet time</name>
<description>Bullet time refers to a simulation of variable speed (i.e. slow motion, time-lapse, …) and is characterized both by its extreme transformation of time and space to show normally imperceptible and un-filmable events, such as flying bullets.
Most infamous scene using this technique, Neo dodging bullets in The Matrix film.</description>
<picurl>211279.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2780" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>indirect kiss</name>
<description>Comedy element: Especially in a school setting the character who has fallen for a fellow student, but has not yet confessed his/her love, will be desperate for any sign of "closeness".
The indirect kiss: Anything the adored person touches with his/her lips — e.g. a used glass of lemonade, some half-eaten food, a half-emptied can of soda — the love struck will want to touch with her/his own lips.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2823" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>paper clothes</name>
<description>Worn clothing appears paper-thin and takes little abuse to be shredded or torn from the body. This is common in ecchi anime where the main storyline involves some type of fighting but consists primarily of dialogue and fanservice (Ikkitousen and Platonic Heart). Various girls’ clothing exploding as if made of rice paper is a very enticing prospect.</description>
<picurl>150776.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2825" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-28">
<name>pseudo blowjob</name>
<description>A character is sucking or licking a banana, ice pop, sausage, or similar item in an erotic way.</description>
<picurl>160588.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2830" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>furo scene</name>
<description>Furo (polite: Ofuro) is Japanese for bath, specifically a type of bath which originated as a short, steep-sided wooden bathtub. Baths of this type are found all over Japan in houses, apartments and traditional Japanese inns (Ryokans).
Furo are part of the Japanese ritual of bathing, not used for washing but for relaxing and warming oneself. Washing is carried out separately outside the furo, and only when completely clean does the bather enter the water. Generally Japanese bathrooms are small, so the bathroom is set up much like a walk-in shower area but containing the ofuro.
The cheapest and shortest way to show naked skin on TV, at least as much as allowed. It usually only takes up few minutes at most and as such it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales while still maintaining a "non-filler" episode.
Compare to the big brothers http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode] and http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160785.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2861" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>cyberpunk</name>
<description>Cyberpunk focuses on computers or information technology, usually coupled with some degree of breakdown in social order. The plot often centres on a conflict among hackers, artificial intelligences, and mega corporations, tending to be set within a near-future dystopian Earth.</description>
<picurl>211264.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4170" parentid="5626" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-08-08">
<name>police are useless</name>
<description>The civilian law enforcement representatives do not seem to be of much use, when trying to take on the usually vastly superior foes.
The "helpless" and often clumsy antics of the police can be used as a comedy element.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5626" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>adults are useless</name>
<description>For when adults can`t do anything right.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5793" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-13">
<name>Asimov`s Three Laws of Robotics</name>
<description>The SF author Isaac Asimov developed (1942) a set of laws he used to govern the behaviour of robots:
1. A robot may not injure a human being or, through inaction, allow a human being to come to harm.
2. A robot must obey any orders given to it by human beings, except where such orders would conflict with the First Law.
3. A robot must protect its own existence as long as such protection does not conflict with the First or Second Law.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5874" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>guns are useless</name>
<description>Guns are about as effective as throwing tissue while only manly things like swords, spears, and bare fists are any use at all.
If the weapon shoots a projectile faster than human eyes can track, it is useless. Most guns only serve as a filler for the protagonist to dodge all their shots so they can kill them with a "real" weapon.
The sniper rifle is an occasional exception to this rule. This is because it can be used to quickly and efficiently reduce the amount of character development the animators have to worry about.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2304" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-13">
<rating votes="50">7.97</rating>
<name>Kuki Ageha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A rich girl who is Yume`s classmate. She has a butler of her own named Kojurou whom she often hits regardless of whether he has failed a task or done a good deed. She comes to have feelings for Ren after seeing his honest, hardworking personality.</description>
<picture>17520.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="291" picture="17122.jpg">Matsui Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27347" type="main character in" update="2011-07-21">
<rating votes="31">6.76</rating>
<name>Christiane Friedrich</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75894.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27348" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-12-18">
<rating votes="19">7.45</rating>
<name>Fushikawa Kokoro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fushikawa Kokoro is a student of class 2-S in Kawakami Academy and the heiress of the Fushikawa clan, one of the three noble families of Japan. She likes to brag about her noble lineage and is quite good in martial arts but never tries to fight stronger opponents. She considers herself superior to the rest of her school mates, viewing common people as "peasants" or "monkeys".</description>
<picture>88825.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="591" picture="226209.jpg">Mizuhashi Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27349" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-11">
<rating votes="3">4.95</rating>
<name>Inoue Jun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64243.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27350" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-11">
<rating votes="5">3.42</rating>
<name>Oowada Iyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67488.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="647" picture="53824.jpg">Chiaki Mahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27351" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-21">
<rating votes="2">5.25</rating>
<name>Shimazu Gakuto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75898.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="198" picture="202893.jpg">Kusao Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27352" type="main character in" update="2011-07-21">
<rating votes="34">6.59</rating>
<name>Kawakami Kazuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75889.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2011" picture="233461.jpg">Tomonaga Akane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27353" type="main character in" update="2011-07-21">
<rating votes="42">5.87</rating>
<name>Kawakami Momoyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75888.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="82" picture="216596.jpg">Asakawa Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27354" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-21">
<rating votes="2">5.25</rating>
<name>Morooka Takuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75899.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="191" picture="17006.jpg">Suzumura Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27355" type="main character in" update="2011-07-21">
<rating votes="33">7.47</rating>
<name>Shiina Miyako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75891.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="650" picture="233419.jpg">Hyousei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27356" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-11">
<rating votes="12">6.02</rating>
<name>Sakakibara Koyuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64223.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="461" picture="188441.jpg">Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27357" type="main character in" update="2011-07-21">
<rating votes="23">4.81</rating>
<name>Naoe Yamato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75896.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27358" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-11">
<rating votes="4">6.03</rating>
<name>Fukumoto Ikurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48571.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27359" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-11">
<rating votes="5">1.65</rating>
<name>Ayanokouji Maro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48585.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27360" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-11">
<rating votes="5">2.18</rating>
<name>Aoi Touma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64242.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27361" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-21">
<rating votes="3">6.36</rating>
<name>Kazama Shouichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75897.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27362" type="main character in" update="2011-07-21">
<rating votes="36">7.22</rating>
<name>Mayuzumi Yukie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75892.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35901" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-11">
<rating votes="8">5.77</rating>
<name>Ogasawara Chika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48565.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5284" picture="37793.jpg">Serizono Miya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35902" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-11">
<rating votes="12">3.43</rating>
<name>Amakasu Mayo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48567.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3182" picture="55949.jpg">Sakata Kayo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35903" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-11">
<rating votes="5">2.13</rating>
<name>Haguro Kuroko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48576.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="408" picture="17255.jpg">Fujita Yoshinori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35904" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-02">
<rating votes="8">4.31</rating>
<name>Cookie</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48586.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="187" picture="17002.jpg">Ogata Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36565" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-11">
<rating votes="13">5.95</rating>
<name>Margit Eberbach</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64222.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13796" picture="172018.jpg">Mizusawa Kei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36566" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-11">
<rating votes="7">5.73</rating>
<name>Kuki Hideo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64250.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36567" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-11">
<rating votes="2">5.25</rating>
<name>Oogushi Suguru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64246.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36568" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-11">
<rating votes="5">5.35</rating>
<name>Kawakami Tesshin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76803.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6942" picture="41078.jpg">Takaoka Binbin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36569" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-11">
<rating votes="9">5.84</rating>
<name>Oshitari Azumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53839.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2007" picture="76719.jpg">Ashiro Megu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36570" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-11">
<rating votes="3">6.68</rating>
<name>Minamoto Tadakatsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64248.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37364" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-11">
<rating votes="12">5.34</rating>
<name>Matsunaga Tsubame</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64261.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22625" picture="59506.jpg">Nagatsuma Juri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37365" type="appears in" update="2012-01-02">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Cookie 2</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64129.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37366" type="appears in" update="2011-10-04">
<rating votes="5">7.52</rating>
<name>Matsukaze</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64180.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37634" type="appears in" update="2011-12-11">
<rating votes="3">3.02</rating>
<name>Musashi Kosugi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67499.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="329" picture="55683.jpg">Rikimaru Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37815" type="appears in" update="2011-12-11">
<rating votes="2">3.43</rating>
<name>Shimazu Reiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69593.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="648" picture="53823.jpg">Tauchi Natsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37967" type="appears in" update="2011-10-23">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Memu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72032.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13954" picture="186143.jpg">Tokumoto Eiichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37968" type="appears in" update="2011-12-11">
<rating votes="3">3.75</rating>
<name>Kojima Umeko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72041.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1813" picture="172159.jpg">Katsuki Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38449" type="appears in" update="2011-11-06">
<rating votes="5">5.43</rating>
<name>Souri</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76804.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2" picture="16471.jpg">Wakamoto Norio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38658" type="appears in" update="2011-12-11">
<rating votes="8">5.62</rating>
<name>Itagaki Ami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77082.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1918" picture="225099.jpg">Sakurai Harumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38659" type="appears in" update="2011-12-11">
<rating votes="2">2.52</rating>
<name>Itagaki Ryuuhei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77085.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1616" picture="23191.jpg">Inada Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38660" type="appears in" update="2011-12-11">
<rating votes="11">7.06</rating>
<name>Itagaki Tatsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77083.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="640" picture="18167.jpg">Yanase Natsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38661" type="appears in" update="2011-12-11">
<rating votes="9">5.33</rating>
<name>Itagaki Angel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77084.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2009" picture="45037.jpg">Kajita Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38662" type="appears in" update="2011-12-06">
<rating votes="10">6.63</rating>
<name>Tachibana Takae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78096.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1528" picture="223648.jpg">Kawaragi Shiho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38682" type="appears in" update="2011-12-11">
<rating votes="3">4.50</rating>
<name>Shakadou Gyoubu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77081.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38920" type="appears in" update="2011-12-06">
<rating votes="8">5.85</rating>
<name>Mimori Saki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78095.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10410" picture="223211.jpg">Izawa Shiori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39138" type="appears in" update="2011-11-29">
<name>Shitennou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Four strongest female martial artists in the MajiKoi world</description>
</character>
<character id="91528" type="appears in" update="2017-09-24">
<name>Kazama Family</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Kazama Family is a group of friends led by its namesake, http://anidb.net/ch27361 [Kazama Shouichi]. Feared for the fighting prowess of its ranks, which boast several of the strongest Kawakami City residents and most notably world-class fighter and womanizer extraordinaire http://anidb.net/ch27353 [Kawakami Momoyo], the group is also renowned for the tactics of its brain, http://anidb.net/ch27357 [Naoe Yamato].</description>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="133017" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="11">3.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真剣で私にかかってきなさい!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Come at Me, Seriously!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maji de Watashi ni Kakatte Kinasai!!</title>
<summary>A fierce battle takes place in the mountains of Kanagawa between
students of Kawakami Academy, a school that resolves internal disputes
with martial arts!  Behind the scenes, we see a love story unfold
between a brilliant tactician and the strongest of the Big Four, a
girl with the nickname "the God of Martial Arts." But it seems there
are others after the young tactician`s heart.  Watch to find out just
what class wins the battle and what happens when the other three
members of the Big Four show up...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>585406</identifier>
<identifier>majikoi-oh-samurai-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="133181" update="2011-09-25">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133693" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-30</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真剣で私に怒りなさい!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Get Mad at Me, Seriously!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maji de Watashi ni Okori Nasai!!</title>
<summary>amato finds himself the target of Kokoro`s rage after the humiliation she faced during the Kawakami Conflict. Yamato uploaded an embarrassing video to the Internet that`s still the talk of the school. Kokoro vows to take revenge on Yamato only to find out she`s getting involved in a little more than she bargained for.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>585780</identifier>
<identifier>majikoi-oh-samurai-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="133694" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="7">3.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真剣で私と語りなさい!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Talk to Me, Seriously!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maji de Watashi to Katari Nasai!!</title>
<summary>amato gets assaulted by Miyako, as usual, but this time Yamato also runs into someone unexpected in the bath. Yamato engages in fast talking to try to escape safely. Later, he has a heart-to-heart with Doggy.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>585778</identifier>
<identifier>majikoi-oh-samurai-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="133695" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真剣で私に萌えなさい!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Go Crazy for Me, Seriously!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maji de Watashi ni Moe Nasai!!</title>
<summary>Miyako can`t get enough of Yamato and attempts to make him hers, but he`s having none of it.  Why does he keep walking away from Miyako when she obviously cares about him so much? Mayucchi also realizes her feelings towards Yamato and discusses them with Matsukaze...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>585776</identifier>
<identifier>majikoi-oh-samurai-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="133696" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="10">2.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真剣で任務を完了しなさい!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete the Mission, Seriously!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maji de Ninmu o Kanryou Shinasai!!</title>
<summary>I`ve got a secret job from the Kawakami Academy`s hidden organization! Let`s go, Mayuchi!  It`s time for the Kazuma Family to roll out! I`ll bring down the hammer of justice on those who`d peek in on girls changing, or having fun in the bath!  We can`t let them get away with this!  I`ll bring them to justice!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>585408</identifier>
<identifier>majikoi-oh-samurai-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="133776" update="2012-01-17">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-10-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133777" update="2012-05-17">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-10-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133929" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-06</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真剣で私とかつぎなさい!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Carry It with Me, Seriously!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maji de Watashi to Katsugi Nasai!!</title>
<summary>It seems the people of Kanagawa have a rather peculiar festival they celebrate every year and this year everyone in the Kazama family is coming along for the ride. But amidst the festivities, Yamato runs into a stranger that seems to know his father and has a strange aura about him...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>585782</identifier>
<identifier>majikoi-oh-samurai-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="133997" update="2012-05-17">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-10-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134190" update="2012-05-17">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-10-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134445" update="2012-05-17">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-10-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134679" update="2012-05-17">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-11-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134723" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真剣で事情を説明しなさい!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Explain What`s Going On, Seriously!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maji de Jijou o Setsumei Shinasai!!</title>
<summary>A big fight ensues, as Tachibana Takae and Kawakami Momoyo really start to go at it. Meanwhile, the plot finally start to unfold and we get a glimpse into what has been going on. But even with the Yamato and the girls helping Momoyo during the fight, Takae doesn`t seem to be going down...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>585786</identifier>
<identifier>majikoi-oh-samurai-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="134724" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-13</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真剣で私につきあいなさい!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Come with Me, Seriously!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maji de Watashi ni Tsukiai Nasai!!</title>
<summary>Momoyo is in distress. She has nothing to do, no one to fight. Her life has slowed to a halt. As Momoyo wanders around the city, trouble starts to brew in the shadows as a massive plot unfolds.  Things start to come to light when Yamato runs into the conspirators.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>585784</identifier>
<identifier>majikoi-oh-samurai-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="134725" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真剣で私にカミングアウトしなさい!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Come Out to Me, Seriously!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maji de Watashi ni Coming Out Shinasai!!</title>
<summary>Momoyo continues to search for Tachibana Takae while Yamato is severely injured in the hospital. The girls surround him and tell them their feelings for him. It`s a touching scene. But it isn`t too long before the girls realize they`re all rivals for Yamato`s affection...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>585788</identifier>
<identifier>majikoi-oh-samurai-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="134726" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真剣で私に恋しなさい!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love Me, Seriously!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maji de Watashi ni Koi Shinasai!!</title>
<summary>The final show down comes to a head as everyone gathers on the battlefield in the middle of Tokyo. With the odds stacked against our heroes, they push through using their will and determination to try to save the day, but they`re not alone...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>585794</identifier>
<identifier>majikoi-oh-samurai-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="134727" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真剣で私と出撃しなさい!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sortie with Me, Seriously!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maji de Watashi to Shutsugeki Shinasai!!</title>
<summary>The heated battle over Yamato continues, with none of the girls willing to back down. Each of them is willing to go further and further, before inevitably it breaks into open warfare. Yamato, meanwhile, considers exactly what he`s fighting for, but it isn`t too long before Tachibana Takae announces her intent to the public...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>585792</identifier>
<identifier>majikoi-oh-samurai-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="134728" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真剣で私とぶつかりなさい!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Go at It with Me, Seriously!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maji de Watashi to Butsukari Nasai!!</title>
<summary>A battle rages over Shinjuku while Momoyo and Takae fight for supremacy. Unfortunately for Momoyo, Saki lurks in the background, giving Momoyo the upper hand. Luckily Yamato jumps in to help even the odds. But things don`t go quite as planned...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>585790</identifier>
<identifier>majikoi-oh-samurai-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="134785" update="2012-05-17">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-11-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134902" update="2012-05-17">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-11-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135210" update="2012-05-17">
<epno type="3">C13</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-12-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135211" update="2012-05-17">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-11-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135511" update="2012-05-17">
<epno type="3">C15</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-12-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135512" update="2012-05-17">
<epno type="3">C14</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-12-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137139" update="2012-02-12">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-10-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137517" update="2012-03-04">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-11-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139411" update="2012-05-17">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139412" update="2012-05-05">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2012-04-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">今週の金曜集会 #12</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This week`s Friday Meetup #12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139413" update="2012-05-05">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2012-04-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">今週の金曜集会 #11</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This week`s Friday Meetup #11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139414" update="2012-05-05">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2012-03-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">今週の金曜集会 #10</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This week`s Friday Meetup #10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139415" update="2012-05-05">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2012-03-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">今週の金曜集会 #9</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This week`s Friday Meetup #9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139416" update="2012-05-05">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2012-02-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">今週の金曜集会 #8</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This week`s Friday Meetup #8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139417" update="2012-05-05">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2012-02-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">今週の金曜集会 #7</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This week`s Friday Meetup #7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139418" update="2012-05-05">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2012-01-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">今週の金曜集会 #6</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This week`s Friday Meetup #6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139419" update="2012-05-05">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2012-01-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">今週の金曜集会 #5</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This week`s Friday Meetup #5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139420" update="2012-05-05">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2011-12-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">今週の金曜集会 #4</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This week`s Friday Meetup #4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139421" update="2012-05-05">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2011-12-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">今週の金曜集会 #3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This week`s Friday Meetup #3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139422" update="2012-05-05">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2011-11-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">今週の金曜集会 #2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This week`s Friday Meetup #2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139423" update="2012-05-05">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2011-11-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">今週の金曜集会 #1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This week`s Friday Meetup #1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139697" update="2012-05-16">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139702" update="2012-05-17">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">BD &amp; DVD CM Compilation</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
