<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8243" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-03-30</startdate>
<enddate>2011-03-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shukufuku no Campanella (2011)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">祝福のカンパネラ -la campanella della benedizione- (2011)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Blessing of the Campanella (2011)</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7280" type="Parent Story">Shukufuku no Campanella</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.marv.jp/special/campanella/</url>
<creators>
<name id="6028" type="Character Design">Fujita Mariko</name>
<name id="10737" type="Original Work">Windmill</name>
<name id="3894" type="Music">Elements Garden</name>
<name id="732" type="Work">AIC</name>
<name id="11255" type="Direction">Ushiro Shinji</name>
<name id="3644" type="Chief Animation Direction">Koga Makoto</name>
</creators>
<description>The story takes place in a trading city Eta`Aria. http://anidb.net/ch16158 [Leicester Maycraft] is an item engineer belonging to an adventurer guild "Oasis". One night, he is at a party with his friends to see a meteor stream on the rooftop of a chapel.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="322">3.20</permanent>
<temporary count="326">5.79</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>231818.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12200</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9924</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4989</identifier>
<identifier>nxfwyb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.marv.jp/special/campanella/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Shukufuku_no_Campanella</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>祝福のカンパネラ#OVA</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2191</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>338517</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13604</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/5152</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15225</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3955" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>DESCRIPTION MISSING</name>
<description>The description for this entry is missing. e.g plot, biography...
Please help by adding it, and remove this tag afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6093" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-08">
<name>short story collection</name>
<description>An anthology is a collection of literary works chosen by the compiler. It may be a collection of poems, short stories, plays, songs, or excerpts by different authors.
An omnibus format release is not just one continuous story, but several short stories. They may feature a different cast between each story, and the authors may differ.
In genre fiction, anthology is used to categorize collections of shorter works such as short stories and short novels, by different authors, each featuring unrelated casts of characters and settings, and usually collected into a single volume for publication. The complete collections of works are often called complete works or Opera Omnia (Latin language equivalent).
Source: EN Wiki</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="16086" type="main character in" update="2010-08-03">
<rating votes="14">6.87</rating>
<name>Agnes Boulange</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Agnes is an puppeteer, and holds traveling Circus act, involving many automata puppets.
Agnes also has a huge appetite and she loves desserts.</description>
<picture>45302.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="591" picture="226209.jpg">Mizuhashi Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16087" type="main character in" update="2010-08-03">
<rating votes="19">7.86</rating>
<name>Carina Verritti</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Carina is Leicester`s childhood friend, and her parents are grand duke in the city.
She is also a mage herself using a paddle like object to fly around town.
She lives in a mansion near the sea.</description>
<picture>45300.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="546" picture="17760.jpg">Koyama Kimiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16088" type="main character in" update="2010-03-27">
<rating votes="14">7.52</rating>
<name>Salsa Tortilla</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45303.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18413" picture="48519.jpg">Yunohara Ari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16089" type="main character in" update="2010-08-03">
<rating votes="24">7.26</rating>
<name>Chelsea Arcot</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chelsea is one of the Holy Knights.
She has a horrible sense of direction.</description>
<picture>45301.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4715" picture="223209.jpg">Imai Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16090" type="main character in" update="2010-03-26">
<rating votes="15">5.32</rating>
<name>Nina Lindberg</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45215.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="243" picture="17061.jpg">Yuimoto Michiru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16091" type="main character in" update="2010-08-09">
<rating votes="14">6.35</rating>
<name>Minette</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She was awoken by a meteor, and immediately considered Leicester to be her papa, due to him being the first man she saw.
She is a automata puppet made by Mise Altoise.</description>
<picture>45299.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15655" picture="44791.jpg">Kadowaki Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16092" type="main character in" update="2010-08-03">
<rating votes="23">8.75</rating>
<name>Ritos Tortilla</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ritos acts clueless a lot. She always leaves her sister Salsa, to take the blame, fall for traps, or an attack from an enemy, while Ritos escape just in time.
She also ignores her sister, and often leaves her out of any plan she has, and withholds important information from her sister, until the last second.</description>
<picture>45304.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1671" picture="19766.jpg">Gotou Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16158" type="main character in" update="2010-03-27">
<rating votes="15">7.29</rating>
<name>Leicester Maycraft</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45298.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18064" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-20">
<rating votes="7">5.68</rating>
<name>Aberdeen Roland</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53637.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="221" picture="17039.jpg">Sugiyama Noriaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18065" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-18">
<rating votes="14">5.79</rating>
<name>Avril</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52533.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18066" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-03">
<rating votes="14">5.64</rating>
<name>Erin Garnet</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is a dragons avatar, who helps Leicester when her powers are split into two, making a shadow dragon.</description>
<picture>51935.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4713" picture="186249.jpg">Hasegawa Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18067" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-31">
<rating votes="2">7.45</rating>
<name>Golem</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>52252.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18068" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-03">
<rating votes="12">7.86</rating>
<name>Shelley Maycraft</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mother of Leicester Maycraft and act affectionately toward him.</description>
<picture>51668.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="488" picture="138714.jpg">Takano Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18069" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-07">
<rating votes="2">6.94</rating>
<name>Tango</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52366.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="556" picture="17848.jpg">Koorogi Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18070" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-03">
<rating votes="3">5.33</rating>
<name>Nagan Maycraft</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is Leicester`s father.</description>
<picture>52253.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18071" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-31">
<rating votes="6">4.79</rating>
<name>Nick La`juck</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51934.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18073" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-31">
<rating votes="5">4.34</rating>
<name>Fabious Verritti</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52251.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2729" picture="186723.jpg">Ishimaru Hiroya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18074" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-01">
<rating votes="13">5.81</rating>
<name>Fiore Verritti</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52365.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="556" picture="17848.jpg">Koorogi Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18075" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-20">
<rating votes="10">5.13</rating>
<name>Mise Altoise</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53636.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3006" picture="226210.jpg">Hirata Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18076" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-09">
<rating votes="10">4.85</rating>
<name>Miriam</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is Minette`s new friend in episode 5 and she is polite and shy.</description>
<picture>53062.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2204" picture="23065.jpg">Ichimura Oma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18077" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-01">
<rating votes="1">7.75</rating>
<name>Montecchia</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>52367.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3006" picture="226210.jpg">Hirata Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20341" type="appears in" update="2010-08-08">
<rating votes="1">7.75</rating>
<name>Clan Avventuriero Oasis</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>53024.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="21426" type="appears in" update="2019-03-30">
<rating votes="2">6.09</rating>
<name>Tortilla Company</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Tortilla Company is a rival clan of Oasis from Ert`Aria, consisting of the Tortilla sisters and their automaton Golem.</description>
<picture>231814.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="127749" update="2011-03-19">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-03-30</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129560" update="2015-11-01">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2011-03-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Issho ni Bath Time: Promotional Video</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
