<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8254" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-04-05</startdate>
<enddate>2011-06-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sengoku Otome: Momoiro Paradox</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">戦国乙女~桃色パラドックス~</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Battle Girls: Time Paradox</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8869" approval="53" total="62">Oda Nobuna no Yabou</anime>
<anime id="5922" approval="30" total="32">Koihime Musou</anime>
<anime id="8571" approval="13" total="18">Brave 10</anime>
<anime id="6284" approval="2" total="8">Sengoku Basara</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="526460">Nice enough anime, ok animation, audio, VA...

Full of ecchi, bouncing boobies, scantily clad ladies; and did I mention not a single man in sight?!

Also hints of shoujo-ai here and there, but nothing too over-the-top.

The story, however, left lots to be desired. by the final few episodes, I was just wishing for the thing that I knew was going to happen to happen already... (and it did)... its very predictable..

All in all, it`s alright, good if you like boobs and such but if you`re looking for a decent story and characters then don`t waste your time here...

Though you can`t expect much from something based off a pachinko machine...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="510875">Recommended for peeps who want a history lesson while watching some nice boobies...</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/sengoku_otome/</url>
<creators>
<name id="8360" type="Animation Character Design">Yamakawa Kouji</name>
<name id="917" type="Animation Work">TMS Entertainment</name>
<name id="677" type="Series Composition">Machida Touko</name>
<name id="23593" type="Original Work">Heiwa</name>
<name id="7569" type="Direction">Okamoto Hideki</name>
<name id="24129" type="Music">Segawa Eishi</name>
<name id="13264" type="Chief Animation Direction">Fujisaki Kenji</name>
<name id="6585" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yoda Masahiko</name>
<name id="1417" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kobayashi Toshimitsu</name>
<name id="8360" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yamakawa Kouji</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr23593 [Heiwa]`s Sengoku Otome pachinko game.
One day the normal modern-day middle school girl http://anidb.net/ch28245 [Hideyoshi] is transported to a world very similar to feudal Japan, with the exception that there are no men! There, she meets http://anidb.net/ch28244 [Oda Nobunaga] whose ambition it is to unite all the land under her rule and collect the Legendary Crimson Armour.
~ translated and adapted from official site by Cranston</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="882">3.61</permanent>
<temporary count="884">6.07</temporary>
<review count="2">5.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>65056.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12506</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10308</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4876</identifier>
<identifier>ipxzsz</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/sengoku_otome/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://sengokuotome.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Sengoku_Otome:_Momoiro_Paradox</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>戦国乙女～桃色パラドックス～</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2138</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>339064</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13404</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>battle-girls-time-paradox</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="382" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-11">
<name>warrior</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1262" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-11-07">
<name>naive</name>
<description>A naive (also spelled naïve, keeping its French diacritic) person lacks worldly knowledge, experience, wisdom, understanding, or judgement.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1589" parentid="2622" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-08">
<name>samurai</name>
<picurl>244341.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2500" parentid="6191" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-29">
<name>karuta</name>
<description>Karuta (かるた, loaned from the Portuguese word meaning "card", carta) is a Japanese card game.
The basic idea of any karuta game is to be able to quickly determine which card out of an array of cards is required and then to grab the card before it is grabbed by an opponent. There are various types of cards which can be used to play karuta. It is also possible to play this game using two standard decks of playing cards.
There are two kinds of cards used in karuta. One kind is yomifuda (読札) or "reading cards", and the other is torifuda (取り札) or "grabbing cards". As they were denoted, the words in the yomifuda are read and players will have to find its associated torifuda before anybody else does.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2687" parentid="2641" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-02-05">
<name>Sengoku period</name>
<description>The Sengoku period (戦国時代, Sengoku jidai) or Warring States period in Japanese history was a time of social upheaval, political intrigue, and nearly constant military conflict that lasted roughly from the middle of the 15th century to the beginning of the 17th century. The name "Sengoku" was adopted by Japanese historians in reference to the Warring States period in Chinese history (Sengoku jidai (戦国時代) in Japanese) which preceded the unification of China. Likewise, the Sengoku period in Japan would eventually lead to the unification of political power under the Tokugawa shogunate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2823" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>paper clothes</name>
<description>Worn clothing appears paper-thin and takes little abuse to be shredded or torn from the body. This is common in ecchi anime where the main storyline involves some type of fighting but consists primarily of dialogue and fanservice (Ikkitousen and Platonic Heart). Various girls’ clothing exploding as if made of rice paper is a very enticing prospect.</description>
<picurl>150776.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3568" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-02-07">
<name>gambling</name>
<description>Gambling is the wagering of money or something of value (referred to as "the stakes") on an event with an uncertain outcome with the primary intent of winning additional money and/or material goods. Gambling thus requires three elements be present: consideration, chance and prize. The outcome of the wager is often immediate, such as a single roll of dice or a spin of a roulette wheel, but longer time frames are also common, allowing wagers on the outcome of a future sports contest or even an entire sports season.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3953" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-06">
<name>in medias res</name>
<description>In medias res, also medias in res (Latin for "into the midst of affairs (lit. into mid-affairs)"), refers to a literary and artistic technique where the narrative starts in the middle of the story instead of from its beginning. It is generally a plot-driven concept rather than a character-driven one; though characters are commonly used to provide the backstory. The characters, setting, and conflict are often introduced through a series of flashbacks or through characters relating past events to each other.
Probably originating from an oral tradition, the technique is a convention of epic poetry, one of the earliest and most prominent examples in Western literature being Homer`s Odyssey and Iliad. Virgil`s Aeneid began the tradition in literature of imitating Homer, continued in Torquato Tasso`s Jerusalem Delivered, John Milton`s Paradise Lost and "Inferno" from Dante`s Divine Comedy. George Lucas`s Star Wars saga was told using in medias res.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4287" parentid="3568" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-11">
<name>pachinko</name>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4517" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-13">
<name>inter-dimensional schoolgirl</name>
<description>One, or more, schoolgirls cross through time, space or some dimension using a space-warp-magic-portal-wormhole-singularity-thing to save one, or more, worlds, or planets.
A major twist could be that the schoolgirl might originate from that very magic-futuristic world, bearing one great secret legendary power to defeat one big bad legendary foe. The return back home is the leitmotiv of the whole series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6078" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-23">
<name>gotta catch them all</name>
<description>A typical plot or sub-plot for many shows. Either the cast or somebody else, that being often the main antagonist, embarks on a quest to collect things, shiny things. Things that are said to grant simple wishes or even do miracles like bringing people back to life, destroying the whole world, galaxy, universe and in rare cases turning the hero into the greatest Pokemon Master. Those things can be weapons, lost technology, magical artefacts, pieces of a giant magical artefact and in some cases even people or little critters.
The point is, there`s stuff to collect!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6191" parentid="2881" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-05">
<name>card games</name>
<description>A card game is any game using playing cards as the primary device with which the game is played, be they traditional or game-specific. Countless card games exist, including families of related games (such as poker). A small number of card games played with traditional decks have formally standardized rules, but most are folk games whose rules vary by region, culture, and person.
Many games that are not generally placed in the family of card games do in fact use cards for some aspect of their gameplay. Similarly, some games that are placed in the card game genre involve a board. The distinction is that the gameplay of a card game primarily depends on the use of the cards by players (the board is simply a guide for scorekeeping or for card placement), while board games (the principal non-card game genre to use cards) generally focus on the players` positions on the board, and use the cards for some secondary purpose.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="28238" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="8">4.96</rating>
<name>Uesugi Kenshin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65099.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="101" picture="16709.jpg">Ise Mariya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28239" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-16">
<rating votes="5">6.37</rating>
<name>Imagawa Yoshimoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65096.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23608" picture="65179.jpg">Mochizuki Rei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28240" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="10">4.48</rating>
<name>Date Masamune</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65095.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3424" picture="24518.jpg">Hirata Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28241" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="7">4.83</rating>
<name>Tokugawa Ieyasu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65097.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1511" picture="173601.jpg">Akesaka Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28242" type="main character in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="10">4.42</rating>
<name>Akechi Mitsuhide</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65094.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28243" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="5">5.97</rating>
<name>Takeda Shingen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65098.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9365" picture="34581.jpg">Kokuryuu Sachi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28244" type="main character in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="13">6.77</rating>
<name>Oda Nobunaga</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65093.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28245" type="main character in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="13">4.75</rating>
<name>Toyotomi Hideyoshi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65092.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="430" picture="246278.jpg">Hidaka Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30880" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-21">
<rating votes="2">3.35</rating>
<name>Shiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A male dog which wears a feudal helmet and has the ability to talk, though he only talks around Hideyoshi. He is knowledgable about the world and time, and the fact Hideyoshi is not from it.</description>
<picture>71981.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="270" picture="25681.jpg">Sasaki Nozomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30881" type="appears in" update="2011-04-07">
<name>Tokunyan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tokunyan is Hideyoshi`s school friend from the Heisei period.</description>
<picture>69296.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1511" picture="173601.jpg">Akesaka Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30882" type="appears in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="1">5.81</rating>
<name>Date-sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Date-sensei is the teacher in charge of Hideyoshi`s class.</description>
<picture>69298.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3424" picture="24518.jpg">Hirata Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30883" type="appears in" update="2011-04-07">
<name>Akerin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akerin is Hideyoshi`s school friend from the Heisei period.</description>
<picture>69294.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30884" type="appears in" update="2011-04-07">
<name>Otoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69299.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18360" picture="48491.jpg">Yamazaki Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32579" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="3">4.77</rating>
<name>Hattori Hanzou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71983.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33024" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="7">4.62</rating>
<name>Ootomo Sourin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72683.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="347" picture="41555.jpg">Nonaka Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33026" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="6">6.39</rating>
<name>Mouri Motonari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72680.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="203" picture="38566.jpg">Matsuki Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33027" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="4">3.13</rating>
<name>Chousokabe Motochika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72679.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2798" picture="22836.jpg">Oki Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34066" type="appears in" update="2011-06-30">
<name>Juushoku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74496.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="256" picture="188450.jpg">Satou Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34067" type="appears in" update="2011-06-30">
<name>Musume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74497.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34068" type="appears in" update="2011-06-30">
<name>Oda Nobusada</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74499.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3368" picture="132584.jpg">Kujira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34069" type="appears in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Oda Nobuhide</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74498.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="295" picture="25758.jpg">Shinohara Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34070" type="appears in" update="2011-06-30">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Gyouji</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74500.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="619" picture="18141.jpg">Sakata Ito</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="128673" update="2011-08-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-05</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">転送乙女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Maiden Teleported</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tensou Otome</title>
<summary>The Present Day. There`s a middle school girl named Hideyoshino who loves fashion and cell phones. Her nickname at school is "Hideyoshi". Just before her exams, she realizes that her only hope is divine intervention, and goes to a shrine. There she is whisked away by a mysterious light...The next thing she knows, she is surrounded by female bandits who proceed to attack her! She is saved by a general with a gigantic sword. The general calls herself Oda Nobunaga...</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>573554</identifier>
<identifier>battle-girls-time-paradox</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="128983" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">困惑乙女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Confused Maiden</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Konwaku Otome</title>
<summary>It`s been decided that Hideyoshi will help look for the legendary Crimson Armor.  Also, this world looks like the Warring States era, but it looks like there`s only girls...  Hideyoshi stays with Nobunaga and Mitsuhide, but she`s worried about whether or not she`ll be able to go home.  And then a weird dog appears.  For some reason, the dog starts talking to her?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>574206</identifier>
<identifier>battle-girls-time-paradox</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="128984" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-19</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天空乙女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sky Maiden</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenkuu Otome</title>
<summary>Nobunaga learns that Imagawa Yoshimoto has the left leg of the Crimson Armor.  But Yoshimoto, while uninterested in the armor, has no intention of just giving it over.  She brings a large army and attacks Nobunaga!  Nobunaga returns to her castle, where Hideyoshi gives her a plan.  And Nobunaga sends a challenging letter to Yoshimoto...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>574386</identifier>
<identifier>battle-girls-time-paradox</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="128985" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">対決乙女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Confrontation Maiden</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiketsu Otome</title>
<summary>Uesugi Kenshin and Takeda Shingen are rivals.  The two of them are battling again today like always, and seem to be enjoying themselves. Both have pieces of the armor, but neither will simply hand it over. Mitsuhide suggests a plan to trick them both and get the armor, but Nobunaga refuses, not wanting to ruin their fight.  Meanwhile, Hideyoshi is depressed that her cell phone is broken...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>574388</identifier>
<identifier>battle-girls-time-paradox</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129387" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">想出乙女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Memory Maiden</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omoide Otome</title>
<summary>The long rain has everybody feeling a bit melancholy, and each character remembers somehing from their past.  Mitsuhide thinks back to the rainy day when she first met Nobunaga.  Nobunaga shows Hideyoshi a pipe she always carries with her, and talks about the memories it holds.  And Date Masamune thinks about something that happened only a short while ago...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>574392</identifier>
<identifier>battle-girls-time-paradox</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129388" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-03</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">怪談乙女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ghost Story Maiden</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaidan Otome</title>
<summary>At Tokugawa Ieyasu`s suggestion, everyone goes hawk hunting.  Hideyoshi is looking forward to her first meat in ages.  A bit after they begin, the hawk flies off into the forest after its prey... Everyone follows the hawk, but instead they find a grave and ghosts!  If they can`t tell scary stories to satisfy the ghosts, they won`t be able to leave...!?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>574390</identifier>
<identifier>battle-girls-time-paradox</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129828" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">陽光乙女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sunlight Maiden</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youkou Otome</title>
<summary>Everyone eats a meal while cleaning up the ruins of the castle.  And then someone slips away!?  Date-sensei leaves to find the armor, still buried in the rubble.  She hasn`t given up on getting it yet.  And just as she finds it, Hideyoshi appears... What will be the fate of the battle girls?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>574406</identifier>
<identifier>battle-girls-time-paradox</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129829" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦国乙女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle Maiden</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sengoku Otome</title>
<summary>At last the Crimson Armor has activated!  The Armor absorbs Ieyasu`s dark heart and goes out of control.  Nobunaga and Mitsuhide are powerless against Ieyasu`s overwhelming might.  Imagawa Yoshimoto, Takeda Shingen, and Uesugi Kenshin come to help!  Nobunaga begs for the others to help her save the innocent people.  And the Battle Maidens at last join together...!!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>574404</identifier>
<identifier>battle-girls-time-paradox</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129830" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">強奪乙女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Thief Maiden</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Goudatsu Otome</title>
<summary>Masamune took advantage of the confusion at Honnouji to steal the armor!  Nobunaga follows her to Azuchi castle, but finds Masamune lying on the ground midway.  The armor had been stolen by Ieyasu.  Nobunaga and Mitsuhide hurry to the castle to stop Ieyasu from getting all the armor.  Masamune tells Hideyoshi the truth behind everything that`s happened...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>574402</identifier>
<identifier>battle-girls-time-paradox</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129831" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">心中乙女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Double Suicide Maiden</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinchuu Otome</title>
<summary>At last Nobunaga has all the armor!  They head back to Azuchi Castle, where they`ve left the remaining pieces.  On the way back, they stop at Honnouji Temple.  Even a dummy like Hideyoshi remembers that name!  Her textbook says that this is where Akechi Mitsuhide killed Oda Nobunaga... no way!  Meanwhile, Mitsuhide is at her breaking point.  With some advice from Masamune, she takes action.  Everything she does is for love..
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>574400</identifier>
<identifier>battle-girls-time-paradox</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129832" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-31</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">西国乙女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Saigoku Maiden</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigoku Otome</title>
<summary>The group is confronted by a very... unique trio: Mouri Motonari, Chousokabe Motochika, and Ootomo Sourin.  Nobunaga captures them and makes them give up the location of the armor.  But the box with the armor in it is trapped, and Hideyoshi is taken prisoner.  Nobunaga heads to the mountain where she`s being held, her features twisted with a terrible rage...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>574398</identifier>
<identifier>battle-girls-time-paradox</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129833" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">微熱乙女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fever Maiden</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Binetsu Otome</title>
<summary>Nobunaga sets off to recover the last three pieces of armor in Saigoku.  Of course, there`s no cars or trains, and Hideyoshi is quickly exhausted.  They decide to rest at a ton, but for some reason the town is overflowing with rumros that Nobunaga is a demon who eats children and babies!  And they say that Mitsuhide is the one who spread the rumors!  Meanwhile, Hideyoshi gets more and more tired, and finally falls ill...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>574396</identifier>
<identifier>battle-girls-time-paradox</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129834" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">演劇乙女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Drama Maiden</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Engeki Otome</title>
<summary>Everyone decides to put on a play at Hideyoshi`s suggestion.  Nobody knows what a "play" is supposed to be, so Hideyoshi has to teach them everything.  She starts making the set and working on the script!  But she has no idea what to write, and so asks Yoshimoto, who loves everything literary.  Yoshimoto`s idea is a world of passion with lots of girls in love!  And just once things start to get in shape, everybody starts trying to win themselves a bigger part...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>574394</identifier>
<identifier>battle-girls-time-paradox</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="130911" update="2011-06-30">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-06-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130912" update="2011-06-30">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-04-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130913" update="2011-06-30">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-04-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132443" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-04-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>572840</identifier>
<identifier>battle-girls-time-paradox</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="132444" update="2011-08-11">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-05-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Character PV - Date Masamune</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132445" update="2011-08-11">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-04-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Character PV - Uesugi Kenshin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132446" update="2011-08-11">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-04-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Character PV - Takeda Shingen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132447" update="2011-08-11">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-04-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Character PV - Tokugawa Ieyasu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132448" update="2011-08-11">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-04-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Character PV - Imagawa Yoshimoto</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132449" update="2011-08-11">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Character PV - Akechi Mitsuhide</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132450" update="2011-08-11">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-03-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Character PV - Oda Nobunaga</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132451" update="2011-08-11">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-03-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Character PV - Toyotomi Hideyoshi</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
