<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8263" restricted="true">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-03-11</startdate>
<enddate>2012-12-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kyuuketsuki</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Anal Vampire</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">吸尻鬼</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="6554" approval="1" total="3">Makai Kishi Ingrid</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1"/>
<url>http://www.ordin-soft.com/ap-kyuketsuki1.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="1209" type="Work">IMG</name>
<name id="18087" type="Original Work">Valkyria</name>
<name id="22714" type="Direction">Yazaki Shigeru</name>
<name id="14856" type="Character Design">Tani Keiji</name>
<name id="49645" type="Character Design">Fudou Junko</name>
<name id="49645" type="Direction">Fudou Junko</name>
</creators>
<description>Vampire. A legendary creature which lives in shadow, and preys on humanity.
http://anidb.net/ch28410 [Onohara Mikage] is an unfortunate girl that sold herself to a clan of Vampires to pay off her parents debt. What has the clan head, http://anidb.net/ch29803 [Claude], prepared for her? Will she be able to pay herself off and obtain her freedom by serving him?
Note: The word "Vampire" (Kyuuketsuki) in this anime is written with kanji for "Ass Sucking Demon" instead of usual "Blood Sucking Demon".</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="272">3.35</permanent>
<temporary count="280">5.46</temporary>
<review count="1">7.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>65857.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12546</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10325</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5222</identifier>
<identifier>uyyuyj</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.ordin-soft.com/ap-kyuketsuki2.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.ordin-soft.com/ap-kyuketsuki1.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15624</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4077</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="893" parentid="2729" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-12">
<name>dominatrix</name>
<description>A dominatrix is a woman, typically a paid professional, who takes the dominant role in BDSM activities. A dominatrix may be of any sexual orientation, which does not necessarily limit the genders of her submissive partners. The role of a dominatrix may not even involve physical pain toward the submissive; her domination can be verbal, involving humiliating tasks, or servitude. The umbrella term for BDSM activities involving a dominatrix is female dominance, female domination, or simply femdom.
Source: Wikipedia.</description>
<picurl>230370.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1409" parentid="1152" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-20">
<name>vampire</name>
<description>A vampire is a mythological or folkloric nocturnal undead. Vampires use long fangs to penetrate the necks of people, usually young females, to drink their blood, both as a form of nourishment and to turn the targets into slaves.
In the classic vampire stories, they are thought to have no reflection in mirrors, are able to shapeshift into bats (sometimes also wolves or some form of fog), have unlimited lifespan and superhuman strength, reflexes and senses, and may only be killed by silver bullets, silver blades, a stake through the heart, fire, or exposure to sunlight; on the other hand, they cannot tolerate garlic, holy water, or Christian crosses (sometimes expanded to religious symbols in general).
In modern anime, these limitations are usually dropped, and they become far more powerful and fearsome opponents than usual. A human bitten, or sometimes even scratched, by a vampire typically becomes a slave, eventually dying as if poisoned, and becoming a vampire, ghoul, zombie, or other form of undead after death, often staying under the command of the vampire who originally bit them.</description>
<picurl>231496.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2578" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-12">
<name>vulgar</name>
<description>Talking (and acting) in a way that is considered uncultivated, bawdy, common, coarse or unrefined, or "taboo" according to existing cultural standards. Includes boorish manners and obtrusive display of carnal "assets".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2615" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-25">
<name>18 restricted</name>
<description>This isn`t really an "audience".
While some anime might feature sexual content they still might not be considered pornography. This category is meant only for when the content is clearly *not* intended for minors. The distinction is made by whether the content is sold only to adults.</description>
<picurl>67867.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2649" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>dark fantasy</name>
<description>Focus set on darker themes in a fantasy setting, sometimes leaning towards horror elements. Bleak and pessimistic tones often dominate. Dark supernatural beings like vampires may play a significant role.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2695" parentid="2848" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>yuri</name>
<description>Yuri refers to anime that portray lesbian (female/female) sex. Do not confuse this with the http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai] category under Romance, which only portrays girl/girl relationships, but generally not anything pornographic. This is real female/female porn.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>150944.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2696" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-13">
<name>threesome</name>
<description>Tag for any scene where sexual acts take place with three people of any gender. Should not be used if more than three.</description>
<picurl>150774.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2697" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-05">
<name>voyeurism</name>
<description>Voyeurism is the sexual interest in or practice of spying on people engaged in intimate behaviors, such as undressing, sexual activity, or other actions usually considered to be of a private nature. The principal characteristic of voyeurism is that the voyeur does not normally interact directly with the subject of his/her interest, who is often unaware of being observed. The essence of voyeurism is the observing but may also involve the making of a secret photograph or video of the subject during an intimate activity. When the interest in a particular subject is obsessive, the behavior may be described as stalking.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162189.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2701" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-10">
<name>pussy sandwich</name>
<description>A pussy sandwich is a sex act during which a man`s penis is pressed against ("sandwiched") by two (or potentially more) vulvas. In the classic pussy sandwich, two women lie atop each other, face to face, and the man either "penetrates" the space between their vulvas or alternates penetrating their vaginas.</description>
<picurl>237174.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2702" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-16">
<name>mammary intercourse</name>
<description>Mammary intercourse is a sex act, performed as foreplay or as non-penetrative sex, that involves the stimulation of the male penis by the female breasts. Commonly, this sex act involves the man placing his penis in the woman`s cleavage and thrusting between her breasts, while the breasts are squeezed around the penis for additional stimulation, and fellatio may also be performed in combination. Mammary intercourse is also commonly known as titty-fucking or titfuck in the United States, as well as tit wank or French fuck in the United Kingdom. The Japanese term, paizuri (from oppai, breasts, and the verb suru, used in this context to describe the sexual act), is commonly used in the anime fandom. A variant term is "naizuri" (a pun on nai, the negative of the verb aru, indicating existence/presence), which describes an attempt to do a paizuri, but with insufficient cleavage.</description>
<picurl>174692.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2705" parentid="2848" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-20">
<name>creampie</name>
<description>The act of a man ejaculating inside a girl`s vagina, leaving the semen oozing out of her.</description>
<picurl>160720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2707" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-20">
<name>internal shots</name>
<description>Internal shots are pictures that display the interior of the body of a living being, either through the skin, kind of as an "x-ray" of sorts, or from the inside, as if the camera was also inside. This is generally used during sex scenes to display the inside of any area being penetrated. Those shots may happen either by making an area of the body transparent or by displaying the same area again, but from the inside; the latter method is shown in the picture.</description>
<picurl>213307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2710" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-18">
<name>squirting</name>
<description>Squirt, a small, quick stream, a jet when girl gets orgasm.</description>
<picurl>227795.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2711" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-25">
<name>urination</name>
<description>Urination, also known as micturition, voiding, peeing, weeing, pissing, and more rarely, emiction, is the ejection of urine from the urinary bladder through the urethra to the outside of the body. In healthy humans the process of urination is under voluntary control. In infants, some elderly individuals, and those with neurological injury or extreme psychological problems, urination may occur as an involuntary reflex. In other animals, in addition to expelling waste material, urination can mark territory or express submissiveness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2712" parentid="2848" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>sex toys</name>
<description>A sex toy is an object or device that is primarily used to facilitate human sexual pleasure, such as a dildo or vibrator.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2713" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>oral</name>
<description>Oral sex is sexual activity involving the stimulation of the genitalia of a sex partner by the use of the mouth, tongue, teeth or throat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2717" parentid="2848" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>anal</name>
<description>Sodomy, buggery, buttsex, cornholing, or the poop-chute polka. Call it whatever you like, but somebody is getting something stuck where the sun does not shine.</description>
<picurl>173755.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2719" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-19">
<name>gang bang</name>
<description>A situation in which one person has sexual intercourse and performs other sex acts with a number of people, either in turn or at the same time.</description>
<picurl>181529.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2721" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-13">
<name>public sex</name>
<description>Public sex refers to sexual acts that take place in public or semi-public places.</description>
<picurl>175406.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2724" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-15">
<name>double penetration</name>
<description>Double penetration is a situation during which someone is simultaneously penetrated by two penises or strap-ons.</description>
<picurl>172771.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2725" parentid="2848" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-20">
<name>ahegao</name>
<description>A term for the weird face occasionally seen in adult games/anime/manga. Canonically, ahegao has eyes rolled up, mouth open and tongue sticking out. Sometimes also referred to as "fucked silly".</description>
<picurl>175637.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2726" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>prostitution</name>
<description>Prostitution is the practice or occupation of engaging in sexual activity with someone for payment.</description>
<picurl>222173.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2727" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>stomach stretch</name>
<description>Visible abdominal distortion from objects or anatomy pressing out from within the vaginal or anal cavity. Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t2935 [stomach bulge] or http://anidb.net/t775 [pregnancy].</description>
<picurl>178246.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2728" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>fisting</name>
<description>To insert a fist into a sexual area of the human body.</description>
<picurl>172774.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2735" parentid="2729" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>enema</name>
<description>An enema is the procedure of introducing liquids into the rectum and colon via the anus for the purpose of cleaning the insides or for BDSM play.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2866" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>slavery</name>
<description>Someone is owned by somebody else. In anime this usually affects body (slaves in a fantasy setting) or mind (the evil villain brainwashes a sidekick, creates an obedient minion or places a spell on some poor bloke). Slavery is also a common element of hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2896" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-23">
<name>deflowering</name>
<description>Deflowering is the act of breaking the hymen of a female who hadn`t yet had vaginal intercourse. This tag can be applied only to pornographic anime in which a female is seen being deflowered; most often, one knows she had been a virgin because blood is seen coming out of her vagina during sex or after it, but her word on the matter is also considered valid.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2899" parentid="2712" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-04-21">
<name>strapon</name>
<description>Employs the use of an artificial phallus so that the female can engage in the penetrating role during intercourse. Not to be confused with a http://anidb.net/t6455 [double-sided dildo].</description>
<picurl>185955.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2900" parentid="2712" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-20">
<name>dildos - vibrators</name>
<description>These are toys that are used for sexual pleasure.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2901" parentid="2729" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-09">
<name>bondage</name>
<description>Bondage is the use of restraints for the sexual pleasure of the parties involved. It may be used in its own right, as in the case of rope bondage and breast bondage, or as part of sexual activity or BDSM activity. When a person is sexually aroused by bondage, it may be considered a paraphilia, known as vincilagnia (from Latin vincio, to bind or fetter with chains, and lagneia, lust).
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42021.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2905" parentid="2729" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-14">
<name>erotic torture</name>
<description>Erotic torture involves deliberately using (almost) any form of physical or excessive psychological abuse to inflict physical and/or mental pain, with the goal of inducing sexual pleasure. Examples include, among others, hot wax on skin, nipple clamps, electricity, extreme verbal and derogatory abuse, forced public exhibition, etc.
This is distinct from the common, non-erotic http://anidb.net/t6730 [torture], which is generally for the purpose of inflicting pain, to either fulfill a desire of the torturer, or to apply coercion to compel action from the victim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2921" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-12">
<name>throat fucking</name>
<description>The act of actively thrusting one`s penis into a persons mouth and throat.</description>
<picurl>236088.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3244" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-04-08">
<name>sexually dominant</name>
<description>Sexually dominant is a designation applied to those able to assertively assume and maintain control over the actions of their partner(s) during sexual activity, actively steering it towards their own intents and preferences and possibly to the detriment of those of their partner(s).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3443" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-05">
<name>orgy</name>
<description>A wild gathering marked by promiscuous sexual activity.</description>
<picurl>190911.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4049" parentid="2721" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-13">
<name>outdoor sex</name>
<description>Popular place for sex in visual novels and manga.</description>
<picurl>175405.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4741" parentid="2711" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-09">
<name>anal pissing</name>
<description>An act where a person urinates inside the ass of another person.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5205" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-09-18">
<name>dungeon</name>
<description>A dungeon is a closed environment in RPG terminology. Dungeons are usually full of enemies and loot, which corresponds to items and money that may be either lying around or dropped by enemies killed by the player. Caves and ruins are among the most common forms of dungeons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5406" parentid="2729" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-02">
<name>submission</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5445" parentid="2901" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>strappado bondage</name>
<description>Strappado bondage is a term describing a position and technique used in BDSM. A person`s arms are bound behind their back, then by use of some method of attachment such as a rope or chain that runs from their wrists to a securing point above, their arms are lifted up behind them until the person is forced to bend forward or in other genital-revealing positions. It typically also involves the usage of clamps and gags.
The main objectives of Strappado are: 
-To reduce/inhibit the one`s ability to move by placing the body in an awkward position such that any struggling on their part could result in them losing balance. As a result, it is the bound subject who chooses not to move for fear of falling over
-To create a sense of vulnerability by exposing their genital area.</description>
<picurl>228987.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5527" parentid="2729" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-07-17">
<name>spanking</name>
<description>Spanking someone`s butt as torture or for sexual pleasure.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6083" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>master-servant relationship</name>
<description>To some genres, this would suggest a genuine pairing where one person exists to serve another person, such as in some action/dramas where the pair becomes united by destiny as partners — fighting or battles between different pairs/partners will usually be a dominant part of the story.
In other genres, this suggests a relationship where one person may be occupied as or even forcefully treated as a servant or slave to the other who designates themself the master — these services usually apply anywhere from tsundere/romantic-comedies to ecchi or to the more extreme in hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6268" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>fellatio</name>
<description>Fellatio is oral sex performed upon the penis. It may be performed to induce male orgasm and ejaculation of semen, or it may be used as foreplay prior to sexual intercourse.</description>
<picurl>165408.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6455" parentid="2900" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>double-sided dildo</name>
<description>A regular dildo is inserted by hand. A double-sided dildo is inserted into the penetrating girl`s vagina and held in place there, so that she can penetrate the receiving girl the same way a male would. Not to be confused with a http://anidb.net/t2899 [strapon].</description>
<picurl>175704.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7221" parentid="7220" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>psychological sexual abuse</name>
<description>Psychological sexual abuse is the exercise of sexual coercion through non-physical means, such as verbal sexual behaviour, stalking, and emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="28410" type="main character in" update="2011-03-11">
<rating votes="10">7.25</rating>
<name>Onohara Mikage</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67505.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24052" picture="37361.jpg">Oohana Don</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29802" type="main character in" update="2014-07-25">
<rating votes="9">7.73</rating>
<name>Himeno</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158523.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23635" picture="63532.jpg">Fukai Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29803" type="main character in" update="2014-07-25">
<rating votes="2">6.63</rating>
<name>Claude</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158524.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24053" picture="18171.jpg">Small Satou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="128008" update="2011-02-08">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2011-03-11</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">淫肛を渇望する一族[ダークストーカーズ]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Anal Craving Dark Stalkers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inkou o Katsubou Suru Dark Stalkers</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145365" update="2012-11-10">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2012-12-21</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">肛悦に堕ちゆく吸穴姫[アナルドランカー]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Butt Pleasure Fallen Anal Drunker</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kouetsu ni Ochiyuku Anal Drunker</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
