<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8265" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-10-05</startdate>
<enddate>2011-12-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Maken-ki!</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">마켄키!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">マケン姫っ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Maken-ki! Battling Venus</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8566" type="Sequel">Maken-ki!: Natsu Da! Mizugi Da! Gasshuku Da!</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="5786" approval="40" total="49">Sekirei</anime>
<anime id="7900" approval="9" total="16">Freezing</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="434490">This is fanservice with a hint of a story that doesn´t really go anywhere. Reminds me a lot of C3 in that aspect. I was equally disappointed with both of ém in the end. Don´t watch this if you want a good story, unless they make a second season, that actually goes anywhere with the story. If you like ecchi series, then I guess you could watch it. But there´s better one´s around.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="506415">I`d recommend this series only for ecchi fans who don`t have anything better to watch. The useless main character is really frustrating to watch</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="85705">Only fanservice</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>https://web.archive.org/web/20130530030256/http://maken-ki.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="2217" type="Character Design">Yuuki Nobuteru</name>
<name id="1572" type="Series Composition">Kuroda Yousuke</name>
<name id="1391" type="Direction">Oohata Kouichi</name>
<name id="12885" type="Chief Animation Direction">Koshiishi Satoru</name>
<name id="2217" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yuuki Nobuteru</name>
<name id="1309" type="Animation Work">AIC Spirits</name>
<name id="23640" type="Original Work">Takeda Hiromitsu</name>
<name id="3721" type="Music">Watanabe Cheru</name>
<name id="3434" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sunagawa Masakazu</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a manga by http://anidb.net/cr23640 [Takeda Hiromitsu] formerly serialised in Dragon Age Pure, but moved to http://anidb.net/cr12273 [Gekkan Dragon Age] when the magazine was cancelled.
http://anidb.net/ch36167 [Ooyama Takeru], a mostly normal yet perverted guy, enrols into Tenbi Gakuen — once an all-girls school now turned into a co-ed school. Unbeknownst to him, the only students admitted are those who are able to control a source of energy found in all living things called Element, and thus can use magical artefacts called Maken, giving the users specific and varied abilities.
On the first day, after three years he meets again: http://anidb.net/ch36168 [Amaya Haruko], his childhood friend, http://anidb.net/ch36171 [Kushiya Inaho], a weird busty girl who declares she is his fiancée, and http://anidb.net/ch36169 [Himegami Kodama], a blonde oujo who wants to kill him. On a whim, the school principle http://anidb.net/ch36166 [Rokujou Minori] decides that he and the three girls are to live in the same room. Furthermore, after being persuaded by Haruko, Takeru decides to join the Maken-ki, a special force unit under the school student council, whose responsibility is to mediate duels between students in the school. However, he later finds out that no Maken is compatible with him.
How will his life continue in this school, where the students get into duels that showcase their magic and combat powers, which he apparently does not have?</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1835">2.80</permanent>
<temporary count="1858">5.80</temporary>
<review count="1">5.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>238109.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12925</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12449</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>9936</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4929</identifier>
<identifier>gthjle</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://web.archive.org/web/20130530030256/http://maken-ki.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Maken-ki!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>マケン姫っ!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2269</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>340592</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13763</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1774" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-05">
<name>gigantic breasts</name>
<description>Gigantic breasts are unnaturally large breasts, even by anime standards; they are true gargantuan monstrosities, either because of sheer size or through the combination of size and exceedingly unnatural shape. Essentially, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are gigantic; smaller breasts are the more common http://anidb.net/t2741 [large breasts], even if they`re as big as the character`s head.</description>
<picurl>160446.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2784" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>sudden girlfriend appearance</name>
<description>Sudden Girlfriend Appearance anime involve a sudden change in the main character`s life where (s)he suddenly gets confronted with an individual (s)he`s sexually attracted to, the two of them inevitably becoming a couple.</description>
<picurl>210066.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2816" parentid="2856" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sexual fantasies</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime let their imaginations run wild thinking about another character.
Yes, they are thinking about sex, and in an ecchi anime these thoughts are often perverted, leading to a nosebleed. But it may also be romanticising simply being husband and wife, and everything that implies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2820" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>wardrobe malfunction</name>
<description>A euphemistic term for an embarrassing display of a body part when clothing droops, falls, or is torn. Wikipedia: "Super Bowl XXXVIII half-time show" for more details.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2823" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>paper clothes</name>
<description>Worn clothing appears paper-thin and takes little abuse to be shredded or torn from the body. This is common in ecchi anime where the main storyline involves some type of fighting but consists primarily of dialogue and fanservice (Ikkitousen and Platonic Heart). Various girls’ clothing exploding as if made of rice paper is a very enticing prospect.</description>
<picurl>150776.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2828" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-26">
<name>borderline porn</name>
<description>Breaks the bounds of "excessive fanservice".
While the physical interactions and dialogue between characters may be extremely sexual, the most sexual situations do *not* have sex itself take place.
Specifically descriptive of containing all the plentiful features of (excessive) fanservice in addition to the interactions between characters being quite sexual — at most, sexual in NATURE only. This means physical touching such as groping, molesting, or bondage will focus primarily on the revealed (i.e. nude) upper portion of the body or through/over clothing on the lower half of the body. This is all WITHOUT actual sex acts (penetration, etc.) taking place.</description>
<picurl>214855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3159" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-11-27">
<name>emotions awaken superpowers</name>
<description>During an extreme emotional state — rage, love, hate, angst, sadness, compassion — something inside the character will "click" that will increase greatly his/her power or a new superpower awakes, that surpasses anything achieved by him/her until then.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3863" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-05">
<name>competition</name>
<description>Some sort of confrontation occurs in this show. The protagonists "duke it out" via various competitions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3872" parentid="2869" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>formerly one-gender school</name>
<description>This anime takes place at a school that was formerly one-gender, but has recently begun to admit the opposite sex. This can be a set-up for harem situations stemming from a still-skewed gender ratio.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4182" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-01-22">
<name>hidden power</name>
<description>For some reason or another a character has powers (or potential) he or she can`t access and may not even know about. 
In some anime these hidden powers are used quite frequently to overcome an enemy or threat (e.g. Naruto, Bleach).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4323" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-04">
<name>spacing out</name>
<description>A comedy element: The character starts to daydream or fantasize about some topic. The typical complete lack of reality makes the spacing out funny. Especially when the protagonist mumbles to himself / herself and friends hear this. Promptly teasing the possibly lovestruck and very embarrassed protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4564" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-06-01">
<name>spirits</name>
<description>Spirits will appear throughout this anime. These will often be depicted as small orbs of glowing light, or transparent images of the deceased.
Not to be mistaken with "I see dead people", these spirits will usually appear at the location of their departure when the characters have gotten close to the truth surrounding their death. Or as plot element, when a spirit will often stay close to a character as a sort of "Guardian Angel". Although they are never actually seen, their presence is sometimes felt.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5850" parentid="2869" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-13">
<name>absurdly powerful student council</name>
<description>A student council is a student-managed body inside a school which engages in administrative affairs, usually usually working in a partnership with management, staff and parents, for the benefit of the whole school environment. In real life, a student council holds no actual power; however, in many anime/manga, they have an insane amount of power, which usually allows them to overrule nearly everyone else (the school board, the mayor, the prime minster, you name it). In those cases, that device is explored as a major source of slapstick comedy.</description>
<picurl>70561.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="36165" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-12-04">
<rating votes="78">8.11</rating>
<name>Nijou Aki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She`s the school nurse and also the staff-advisor of Maken-ki, She was in the Maken-ki before it became an all-girls academy.
Like many other females, she has a gorgeous body, but also has absurdly huge breasts, which attracts the attention of all male students and the envy of girls around her.</description>
<picture>227408.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5878" picture="45926.jpg">Harada Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36166" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-06">
<rating votes="49">6.07</rating>
<name>Rokujou Minori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Minori is the Principal and P.E teacher of the Tenbi Academy. She`s the one that allowed Inaho, Kodama, and Haruno to all live under the same roof with Takeru.
She brandishes incredible power and control over Element, and she can break through amazingly powerful barriers with her bare hands thanks to nothing more than, in her own words, her "fighting spirit". She was in the Maken-ki of the school before it became an all-girls academy.
She refers to herself as "Minori-chan" most of the time. Her Maken is a pair of gauntlets called "Dragon Ace".</description>
<picture>53685.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5889" picture="30436.jpg">Mina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36167" type="main character in" update="2011-09-08">
<rating votes="64">2.18</rating>
<name>Ooyama Takeru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A perverted high school student. He hates his father believing him to be the reason his mother died. He wields a power known as "blood pointer" which allows him to drain "element" from the people around him through his mouth. He has periodically used this ability throughout the series without knowing it. After the battle with the Venus unit he has begun to undergo training to understand this power and use it. He is the childhood friend of Ayama Haruko.
His maken is known as "Overblow", which lets him cause his opponent`s maken to gain incredible power and overflow with element causing it to go out of control and force the user to not be able to use it. However, when his opponent is able to contain the overflow of element or has perfect control over his maken, it would only provide his opponent greater power or even make the maken evolve into something greater.</description>
<picture>53669.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="612" picture="79531.jpg">Maeno Tomoaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36168" type="main character in" update="2011-09-10">
<rating votes="85">6.13</rating>
<name>Amaya Haruko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Called the strongest maiden in Tenbi by Himegami Kodama and the Vice-President of the student council. She is the childhood friend of Ooyama Takeru and has romantic feelings for him often not caring when her body is revealed in front of him. She shares a room with Ooyama Takeru, Himegami Kodama and Kushiya Inaho.
She wields one of the eight legendary maken, "Murakumo" meaning "Gathering Clouds". Her maken allows her to turn her element into photons around the blade. Murakumo`s seal cannot be broken unless it reacts to opponents on par with its power. However, Haruko was able to unleash a little of the maken`s power through her anger.</description>
<picture>53670.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="232" picture="148706.jpg">Shitaya Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36169" type="main character in" update="2011-09-08">
<rating votes="102">7.22</rating>
<name>Himegami Kodama</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wields shikigami that follow her around and call her ojou-sama. She needs element to survive, it has not fully been stated what exactly she is. But she has said to herself that she can`t leave the tenbi area because the element doesn`t flow as fully elsewhere. Which is why she went out to get a stone full of element so she could travel to the training grounds for the summer vacation. She stated that Ooyama Takeru is her mortal enemy after she saw the mark on his chest. Although its has yet to be confirmed if she still feels that way as she has kissed him on a few occasions leaving the cast a bit bewildered and annoyed. She can give her shikigami life and bring them into the real world so everyone can see them, giving them a human body in which they can fight with. It is hinted that she has a weakness for cute things, specifically rare and inexpensive stuff animal toys when she forgave the Finians when they tricked her because if she forgave them, she can have the rare king penguin stuffed toy. She is also deathly afraid of ghosts and other supernatural beings. Even becoming scared of a scary story that the story-teller openly admit that he made up the half rest of the story.</description>
<picture>53673.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="89" picture="148709.jpg">Yahagi Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36170" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-06">
<rating votes="49">5.40</rating>
<name>Shinatsu Azuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She`s a strong fighter that Takeru has had problems with like visiting the shop she works at which was a maid cafe named Macaroon. She has threatened him with death if he ever tells someone else about it.
Her Maken is "Hawk" which looks like a mechanical boot when activated. Her Maken`s ability boosts her already superior agility and speed, as well as her physical power.</description>
<picture>53684.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9512" picture="35180.jpg">Togashi Misuzu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36171" type="main character in" update="2011-09-08">
<rating votes="73">5.49</rating>
<name>Kushiya Inaho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Self proclaimed fiancée of Ooyama Takeru. She feels strongly for Takeru, and although he doesn`t remember her much she has decided to wait until he fully does.
Her maken, "Kamudo", takes the shape of a gauntlet that when brandished, greatly increases her strength and speed as demonstrated in chapter 7 when she used it to protect Takeru and the cat (later named Monji) he had saved by breaking a huge rock falling on them and then rushing in front of them to deflect the broken fragments. However, overusing it puts enough stress on her to knock her unconscious.</description>
<picture>53672.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5886" picture="30429.jpg">Nomizu Iori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36172" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-06">
<rating votes="28">2.78</rating>
<name>Usui Kengo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He has open feelings for Himegami Kodama and is supposedly in her fan club. He often, like Takeru, peeks on girls when they are in the shower, changing, etc. Much like Takeru, Kengo has a strong sense of justice.
His Maken lets him exchange himself or other people with an item in their place.</description>
<picture>70330.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3141" picture="65575.jpg">Tsuruoka Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37859" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-18">
<rating votes="10">2.37</rating>
<name>Kinua Garetto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70310.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3198" picture="160468.jpg">Shimamura Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37860" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-09-13">
<rating votes="53">4.12</rating>
<name>Takaki Furan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The President of the student council. Furan is very strict when it comes to Maken-ki`s duties that need to be carried out. She often scolds Haruko for coming late (mostly because of Takeru), providing a bad role-model for the other students as Vice-President of the student council.
Despite her shyness around boys she`s very attracted to Akaya from Venus, whom she falls for at their first meeting because unlike the peeping squads around he appears like a gentleman.</description>
<picture>70312.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9865" picture="37436.jpg">Gouda Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37861" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-18">
<rating votes="15">5.14</rating>
<name>Amato Tomika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70314.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="392" picture="17237.jpg">Matsuoka Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37862" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-18">
<rating votes="7">3.56</rating>
<name>Tagayashi Gen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70333.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19" picture="50583.jpg">Imaruoka Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38224" type="appears in" update="2011-10-29">
<name>Tenbi Gakuen</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="38505" type="appears in" update="2017-09-13">
<rating votes="2">4.52</rating>
<name>Kagutsuchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207035.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3141" picture="65575.jpg">Tsuruoka Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38506" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-06">
<rating votes="61">6.02</rating>
<name>Akaza Chacha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A 2nd year student at Tenbi Academy. Her Maken is "Maken Scale Compressor" the ability to change the shape and density of objects.</description>
<picture>127081.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10391" picture="38277.jpg">Zougou Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38507" type="appears in" update="2017-09-13">
<rating votes="30">4.58</rating>
<name>Satou Kimi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148721.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27341" picture="74876.jpg">Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38508" type="appears in" update="2012-06-26">
<rating votes="30">2.45</rating>
<name>Minaya Uruchi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90153.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24092" picture="148715.jpg">Furuya Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38509" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-06">
<rating votes="43">6.35</rating>
<name>Amato Yuuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuuka is a close friend of Furan (who she likes to tease), and the Bookkeeper of the student council. She`s also the younger sister of Takeru`s homeroom teacher Amato Tomika.
Yuuka appears to be carefree most of the time. However, she is very cunning mostly encouraging activities of the Maken-ki that involve some kind of other work that needs to be done.</description>
<picture>130399.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23312" picture="205591.jpg">Takamori Natsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38510" type="appears in" update="2017-09-13">
<name>Kuragasa Kai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207036.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2888" picture="200816.jpg">Inoue Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38839" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-28">
<rating votes="10">2.13</rating>
<name>Airiru Finian</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77320.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="430" picture="246278.jpg">Hidaka Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38840" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-06">
<rating votes="40">5.33</rating>
<name>Syria Ootsuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is an American idol superstar and is shown as someone with amazing strength and is well-known through her singing/dancing career as well as a professional wrestler.
Her Jingu is an internal type named "Inverse". Its ability is to "reverse" situations at his/her will and her ability is not limited to reversing forces but could even reverse the will of her opponents.
Originally a male character who can use his/her Jingu`s "Inverse" ability is to change gender and physical appearance .</description>
<picture>77316.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="101" picture="16709.jpg">Ise Mariya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38841" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-06">
<rating votes="11">4.31</rating>
<name>Midia Demitra</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Her Jingu takes the form of a trident and can create and control water and even manipulate any liquid within its range.
She`s a very strong character pointed out by Yan Min who said that Demitra`s fighting capabilities are beyond her own. Yan Min also mentions that she only smiles at those whose power she acknowledges.</description>
<picture>77318.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38842" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-06">
<rating votes="11">3.39</rating>
<name>Minerva Martha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Her Jingu "Aegis" is a Maken that allows her to open gates to other dimensions at will this allows her to teleport various articles, such as clothing a person is wearing to even parts of their body, to another dimensions at will making the person visibly naked or rendering a fighter unable to use attacks by making their limbs disappear from the current dimension.
Her eyes, when open, emit an inexhaustible stream of Element, which allows her to engulf huge areas around her with her own Element, creating a "territory" in which she can use her inter-dimensional powers. This is also the real reason why she always has her eyes closed, except when in action.</description>
<picture>77315.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38843" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-06">
<rating votes="9">3.01</rating>
<name>Yan Min</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Her Jingu is "Kinben" which utilizes the power of lightning and takes the form of a whip split into two. Yan Min fuses the equipment into her body, which enables her to use "Reirii" in turn increasing her speed, She can also increase the speed of the transmission of her neural signals reducing her reaction time.
Another ability of hers is "Reichin" or "Thunder Fist", which turns her fists into pure lightning, increasing her power.</description>
<picture>77321.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1511" picture="173601.jpg">Akesaka Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38844" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-28">
<rating votes="6">2.42</rating>
<name>Riru Finian</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77317.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="430" picture="246278.jpg">Hidaka Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38845" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-06">
<rating votes="8">1.24</rating>
<name>Kodai Akaya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Commander of the Kamigari mercenary unit "Venus" and a former member of Maken-ki, before it became an all-girls academy. He`s the weakest member of Venus in terms of Element level.
Akaya is a flirt around most of the female cast and he appears to be carefree as he finishes the rumor about someone trying to revive Yamata no Orochwith the words "or so they say" and a dumb smile on his face. It turns out that in reality he is really serious about his work.</description>
<picture>77319.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="68" picture="16675.jpg">Yasumura Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38846" type="appears in" update="2011-11-18">
<name>Venus</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="38847" type="appears in" update="2011-11-18">
<name>Tousei-kai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="38848" type="appears in" update="2011-11-18">
<name>Kenkei-bu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="38876" type="appears in" update="2011-11-19">
<name>Kobayashi Ei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77370.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2888" picture="200816.jpg">Inoue Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38877" type="appears in" update="2011-11-19">
<rating votes="1">1.01</rating>
<name>Yamada Shisuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77369.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12659" picture="42771.jpg">Higuchi Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38878" type="appears in" update="2011-11-19">
<name>Tanaka Biyou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77371.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="434" picture="41082.jpg">Shiraishi Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38879" type="appears in" update="2017-09-13">
<rating votes="2">2.95</rating>
<name>Fujioka Gorou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207033.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="378" picture="46436.jpg">Oota Tetsuharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38880" type="appears in" update="2011-11-19">
<name>Wrestling-bu Shushou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77368.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17632" picture="170934.jpg">Hirota Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38881" type="appears in" update="2011-11-19">
<name>Manga Kenkyuu-bu Buchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77367.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="38882" type="appears in" update="2011-11-19">
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<name>Inaho Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77366.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10393" picture="38280.jpg">Maruyama Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38883" type="appears in" update="2011-11-19">
<rating votes="2">3.79</rating>
<name>Osanai Takeru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77365.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32197" picture="4765.png">Shida Arisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39484" type="appears in" update="2011-12-09">
<rating votes="1">4.52</rating>
<name>Ikazuchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78234.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="39485" type="appears in" update="2019-12-15">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Hannin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242159.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12413" picture="41795.jpg">Etou Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39486" type="appears in" update="2011-12-09">
<name>Keikan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2888" picture="200816.jpg">Inoue Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39870" type="appears in" update="2011-12-24">
<rating votes="10">3.29</rating>
<name>Yamato Otohime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78850.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="617" picture="65451.jpg">Nanjou Yoshino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39871" type="appears in" update="2011-12-24">
<rating votes="1">1.71</rating>
<name>Yamato Tsuyotake</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78851.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11275" picture="65394.jpg">Suzuki Yuuto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39872" type="appears in" update="2017-09-13">
<name>Tatsunami Masaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207037.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="185" picture="228625.jpg">Ishigami Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39873" type="appears in" update="2011-12-24">
<rating votes="3">4.61</rating>
<name>Yamato Kikyou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78852.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39874" type="appears in" update="2011-12-24">
<rating votes="3">2.32</rating>
<name>Nozuchi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78849.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="39880" type="appears in" update="2011-12-24">
<rating votes="3">5.75</rating>
<name>Amaya Haruko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78853.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="232" picture="148706.jpg">Shitaya Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="132948" update="2017-05-26">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-26</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">敵は天日にあり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Enemy Is at Tenbi</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`Ennemi au sein de Tenbi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Teki wa Tenbi ni Ari</title>
<summary>Himegami asks Takeru to go on a shopping date?! Of course, she has an ulterior motive: to inspect the mysterious mark on Takeru’s chest. Sounds easy enough, but her plans are interrupted by her roommates, her fan club, and an unknown stalker.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="132949" update="2017-05-26">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-19</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マケンキへようこそ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to Maken-ki</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bienvenue au Maken-ki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maken-ki e Youkoso</title>
<summary>Takeru decides to join the Security Committee! To welcome its new members, the Committee takes a trip to the hot springs. Things are going well until a bear shows up, giving the girls the Tenbi Academy a chance to show off their special powers.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="132950" update="2017-05-26">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-12</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">女の子はすごいんです</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girls Are Amazing</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les filles, c`est génial !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onnanoko wa Sugoindesu</title>
<summary>The beginning of the school year could only mean one thing: time for physical exams! But after getting caught peeking in on the girls from his class, Takeru finds out that he’s an anomaly at Tenbi, and that no Maken can be matched to him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="132951" update="2017-05-26">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-05</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天を契んだ日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Day We Swore to Heaven</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le jour où le ciel s`est déchiré</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ten o Kizanda Hi</title>
<summary>Takeru’s first day at the Tenbi Academy is full of fights and panties. After accidentally kissing a second-year girl, she challenges him to a duel in front of the entire student body. Without a Maken or Element, how is he supposed to protect himself?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="133182" update="2011-09-25">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133926" update="2017-05-26">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-09</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天日に雨の降るごとく</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Like Rain on a Sunny Day</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Seule sous la pluie à Tenbi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenbi ni Ame no Furu Gotoku</title>
<summary>Since Takeru`s first day at Tenbi, Inaho has called him her fiancé. On a rainy night, the story of their past together is revealed, and Takeru`s Elemental powers surface in order to protect his friend (and an adorable new addition to the household).
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="133927" update="2017-05-26">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-02</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天日最強の女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Strongest Girl in Tenbi</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fille la plus forte de Tenbi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenbi Saikyou no Onna</title>
<summary>It’s time for the clubs at Tenbi to negotiate their annual budgets! Takeru and Uru try to work together to help the Security Committee, but their work is interrupted by an assailant who claims to be responsible for the random acts of violence on campus.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="134035" update="2012-06-09">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-10-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134036" update="2012-01-17">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-10-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134600" update="2012-06-09">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-10-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134601" update="2012-06-09">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-10-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134602" update="2012-06-09">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-10-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134765" update="2017-05-26">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-07</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">光と影の乙女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Girls of Light and Shadow</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La Jeune Fille d`ombre et de lumière</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hikari to Kage no Otome</title>
<summary>If Takeru fails his Element practical again, he`ll be kicked out of Makenki! Meanwhile, there`s something not quite right about Minerva, the newest member of Venus to transfer to Tenbi. Why is she confronting Himegami in the woods?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="134766" update="2017-05-26">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-30</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">嵐を呼ぶ水上騎馬戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stormy Games</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une joute aquatique chaotique</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arashi o Yobu Suijou Kibasen</title>
<summary>The boys of Tenbi Academy petition the faculty for co-ed swim classes (for the sake of gender equality, of course). Naturally, the girls protest. There`s only one way to solve this dilemma: a boys-versus-girls water fight full of swimsuits and nosebleeds!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="134767" update="2017-05-26">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-23</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シリアの全てをあげちゃいマス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Syria Will Give You Everything</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cilia est prête à tout !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Syria no Subete o Agechaimasu</title>
<summary>Syria is Tenbi`s newest transfer student, and she`s taken quite an interest in Takeru! What does she plan to do with him in the disused shack on the outskirts of campus?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="134768" update="2017-05-26">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-16</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天日に降りた女神たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Goddesses Who Came Down to Tenbi</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une pluie de femmes sur Tenbi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenbi ni Orita Megami-tachi</title>
<summary>A group of beautiful, powerful transfer students arrive at Tenbi in order to root out a mysterious secret society. But before they can get to work, they’ll have to prove their strength against the girls of Makenki in an epic volleyball showdown.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="134770" update="2012-06-09">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-11-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134771" update="2012-06-09">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-11-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134865" update="2012-06-09">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-11-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134973" update="2012-06-09">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-11-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135120" update="2012-06-09">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-11-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135234" update="2012-06-09">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-12-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135235" update="2017-05-26">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-21</airdate>
<rating votes="6">1.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">楽園を守るもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Protectors of Paradise</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les Gardiennes du paradis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rakuen o Mamoru Mono</title>
<summary>Kamigari kidnaps Haruko as part of an incomprehensible evil scheme concerning Takeru`s untapped powers. When things backfire and Takeru goes out of control, only one person can stop him from destroying Tenbi Academy.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="135236" update="2017-05-26">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-14</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">まかろん限定サービスデー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Macaron Limited-Time Only Service Day</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une journée d`animation spéciale au café Macaron</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Makaron Gentei Service Day</title>
<summary>Takeru gets a Maken! The secret history of Makenki! A dangerous new threat! But most important, the girls of the Security Committee don their skimpiest outfits and get jobs at the local maid café in order to pay for their bikini-filled summer camp.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="135392" update="2012-06-09">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-12-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135904" update="2012-02-02">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2011-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドキドキッ! マケン姫っ! 秘密の訓練 壱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dokidoki! Makenki! Himitsu no Kunren Ichi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136743" update="2012-07-11">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2012-01-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドキドキッ! マケン姫っ! 秘密の訓練 弐</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dokidoki! Makenki! Himitsu no Kunren Ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137468" update="2012-03-02">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2012-02-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドキドキッ! マケン姫っ! 秘密の訓練 参</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dokidoki! Makenki! Himitsu no Kunren San</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138822" update="2012-07-11">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2012-03-30</airdate>
<rating votes="4">1.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドキドキッ! マケン姫っ! 秘密の訓練 肆</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dokidoki! Makenki! Himitsu no Kunren Yon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139347" update="2012-07-11">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2012-04-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドキドキッ! マケン姫っ! 秘密の訓練 伍</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dokidoki! Makenki! Himitsu no Kunren Go</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139971" update="2012-06-09">
<epno type="3">C13</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-12-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139972" update="2012-07-11">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2012-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドキドキッ! マケン姫っ! 秘密の訓練 陸</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dokidoki! Makenki! Himitsu no Kunren Roku</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
