<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8269" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-07-16</startdate>
<enddate>2011-07-16</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gekijouban Pocket Monsters: Best Wishes! - Victini to Shiroki Eiyuu Reshiram</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Victini and the White Hero: Reshiram</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pokemon: Movie 14W</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">劇場版 ポケットモンスター ベストウイッシュ ビクティニと白き英雄 レシラム</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Pokemon The Movie: Black - Victini and Reshiram</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Pokémon - Der Film: Schwarz - Victini und Reshiram</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Pokémon, Le Film: Noir - Victini et Reshiram</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Pokémon o Filme: Preto - Victini e Reshiram</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8012" type="Alternative Setting">Gekijouban Pocket Monsters: Best Wishes! - Victini to Kuroki Eiyuu Zekrom</anime>
<anime id="7891" type="Parent Story">Pocket Monsters: Best Wishes!</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.pokemon-movie.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="4235" type="Direction">Yuyama Kunihiko</name>
<name id="727" type="Animation Work">OLM</name>
<name id="721" type="Animation Work">Production I.G</name>
<name id="719" type="Animation Work">Xebec</name>
<name id="5573" type="Character Design">Matsubara Norihiro</name>
<name id="7914" type="Character Design">Yamada Shun`ya</name>
<name id="5935" type="Character Design">Satou Kazumi</name>
<name id="4464" type="Character Design">Ichiishi Sayuri</name>
<name id="5705" type="Character Design">Mouri Kazuaki</name>
<name id="27525" type="Character Design">Matsumiya Toshinobu</name>
<name id="27526" type="Character Design">Matsushima Kenji</name>
<name id="2841" type="Work">Shogakukan-Shueisha Productions</name>
<name id="5780" type="Original Plan">Tajiri Satoshi</name>
<name id="10185" type="Original Plan">Masuda Jun`ichi</name>
<name id="10181" type="Original Plan">Sugimori Ken</name>
<name id="4464" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ichiishi Sayuri</name>
<name id="5935" type="Chief Animation Direction">Satou Kazumi</name>
<name id="5660" type="Music">Miyazaki Shinji</name>
</creators>
<description>The stories of the two movies will be the same until Satoshi and Pikachu meet Victini but the legendary Pokemon will be either Zekrom or Reshiram.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="243">4.11</permanent>
<temporary count="249">6.15</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221893.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12525</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10740</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.pokemon-movie.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Pokémon_the_Movie:_Black—Victini_and_Reshiram_and_White—Victini_and_Zekrom</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>劇場版ポケットモンスター_ベストウイッシュ_ビクティニと黒き英雄_ゼクロム・白き英雄_レシラム</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2628</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>339181</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13548</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14886</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B01ASCNN4Y</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2801" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>RPG</name>
<description>Any anime that is based on a role-playing game aka RPG. A role-playing video game is a video game which includes elements of non-electronic role-playing games. The player assumes control of one or several fictional characters (a party) who have joined forces in order to perform quests and overcome a great number of challenges and enemies, usually monsters inspired by fantasy, and, to a lesser extent, science fiction and classic mythology. During the course of the game the characters, or avatars, which are generally defined by quantized characteristics, evolve and improve in that their various attributes increase, as well as by gaining more powerful artefacts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2863" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>proxy battles</name>
<description>In our terms, a proxy battle is a battle where humans use creatures/robots to do the fighting for them, either by commanding those creatures/robots or by simply evolving them/changing them into battle mode. Often the training aspect is also involved, or in some cases the proxies are nothing more than holographic representatives of some other variation of competition (like for example a card game). While many popular shounen anime fit under this category, it`s not limited to shounen anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3955" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>DESCRIPTION MISSING</name>
<description>The description for this entry is missing. e.g plot, biography...
Please help by adding it, and remove this tag afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1937" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-03">
<rating votes="479">5.97</rating>
<name>Musashi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jessie is one half of of the Team Rocket duo that follows around Ash Ketchum and friends in the Pokemon anime, usually trying to steal Ash`s Pikachu, but always failing.
Jessie`s mother, Miyamoto, was a high-ranking Team Rocket agent. When Jessie was around the age of three, Miyamoto left on a mission to the Andes Mountains to record the voice of the elusive Pokemon Mew. However, Miyamoto disappeared, and Jessie was put into a foster home which had very little money. There were times when she had no choice but to eat snow because of a lack of more nourishing food.
When she was old enough, she left home to become a Pokemon nurse in Jouto. However, the school she was enrolled in was literally for Pokemon nurses (i.e. Chansey), so she failed to graduate and left, leaving behind a Chansey she had befriended there. It is assumed that she then traveled back to Kanto, where she enrolled in Pokemon Tech, a trainer`s school, met James, and subsequently failed and dropped out. After this, Jessie and James joined a bicycle gang in Sunny Town, where Jessie was known for swinging a chain above her head as she rode her bike (nicknamed "Chainer Jess").
Due to conflicts in canon between Kanto and Johto episodes and the special episode "Training Daze", what happened between Jessie and James after the bike gang is unknown. What is known, as shown in the special episode, is that they joined Team Rocket separately and were on initially unfriendly terms after being grouped with Meowth. However, they quickly made up and the rest is history.
Sometime before joining Team Rocket, and it is not known when, Jessie obtained a Contest Pass in the Hoenn region. Also during the years before Team Rocket, she had several boyfriends, all of whom left her and/or treated her badly. In "Xatu the Future", she revealed that she had once worked at a T.V. station as the Weathergirl. In "From Cradle to Save" is also revealed that she once was a ninja.
She has a long-standing bitter rivalry with Cassidy, another member of Team Rocket. Another member, Wendy, held a grudge against Jessie for failing to pay for a drink (making Wendy pay), but got her revenge when she added the charge to Jessie`s overall Team Rocket bill.
In the episode "Ignorance is Blissey", Jessie was reunited with her friend Chansey from the Pokemon nurse school; Chansey had since evolved into a Blissey.
Starting in Hoenn, Jessie has become a Pokemon Coordinator, entering every contest that she could. She frequently makes it to the battle round, but usually loses there. However, in "Borrowing on Bad Faith", she finally succeeded in winning an (unofficial) contest by using Ash`s Aipom, which she had saved earlier in the episode. And, in "Team Shocker!", she finally wins an official contest with her Dustox in at Solaceon City. Later she also won a ribbon with help of her Yanmega. She has Contest Passes to compete in the Hoenn, Kanto, and Sinnoh regions.
While Jessie`s role in the Pokemon anime has not yet ended, in Toshihiro Ono`s manga, "The Electric Tale of Pikachu", she ended up married to James and with child.
Jessie seems to have a special preference for snake-like Pokemon, owning both an Arbok and a Seviper. In "The Ninja Poke Showdown", she expressed a preference for Poison-type Pokemon in general.
For unknown reasons, she, James and Meowth mostly use hot air balloons instead of faster ways of transportation.
In the Kanto contests, Jessie disguises herself as Jessebella (which is similar to James former fiancee Jessiebelle) wearing a red dress and glasses. Eventually, Ash, Brock, Max and May finds out her true identity at the last contest.
During the Kanto Grand Festival, Jessie dresses up as Jessadia (Japanese: キャンディ・ムサリーナ Candy Musalina). and wears glasses, long white socks, a yellow and orange dress, and has her hair in pigtails. She works there as an announcer and Lilian Meridian`s assistant; Lilian herself says she may not really like "Jessadia"`s style, but recognizes her talent. In the Latin American dub, she enters Super Contests under the name Jessiebella (referencing Jessiebelle again). Jessie currently still continues to use the Jessalina disguise while participating in Super Contests.
In "Pruning a Passel of Pals!" and "Strategy With a Smile!" she once again used her Jessadia disguise to report on the Wallace Cup.
Although Jessie had entered mostly every contest in Hoenn &amp; Kanto, she lost in every single one, whether it was the first match of the Battle Rounds or the finals. But in the Sinnoh Region, she has so far won 2 ribbons using her Dustox and Yanmega.</description>
<picture>2338.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="1938" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-13">
<rating votes="420">5.46</rating>
<name>Nyarth (Rocket-dan)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Meowth is a very unique Pokémon as it has many of the characteristics of a human. It walks on two feet, talks and is as smart as any human. Meowth is currently a member of Team Rocket and he travels around with Jessie and James trying to capture Pikachu and other rare Pokémon for Giovanni.
Meowth generally finishes his sentences with "Nyaa (ニャー)" which is the equivalent of "meow" in English. This helps people remember that despite his ability to talk like a human, he still has cat character traits.
Meowth is also known for coming up with his many schemes to try to capture Pikachu. While Jessie and James always agree with Meowth and think his plans are brilliant, they are generally foiled by Ash and his friends.
Long Con to Access Raimon City Pokémon Center
Meowth schemed with Jessie, James and Doctor Zager to figure out a way for them to infiltrate the Raimon City Pokémon Center where high-leveled Pokémon are stored in a vault that is protected by a security machine scan system that would only open if Nurse Joy (Isshu) or Nurse Joy`s Audino were scanned. Meowth pretended to be no longer part of Team Rocket making up a story that his made an error while executing a certain operation and when headquarters hear of his mistake, they told him he was fired.
Ash, Iris and Cilan believed him and allowed Meowth to travel with him. Pikachu though didn`t trust Meowth even though Meowth proved on numerous occasion that it should be trusted. Meowth`s plan was put into action when they arrived at the Raimon City Pokémon Center and as soon as Nurse Joy`s Audino was scanned to open the door, Meowth turned on Pikachu and the other and captured all the Pokémon in the vault. The long con had been a success and Meowth met up with Jessie and James below the Pokémon Center. Unfortunately, they weren`t able to get away as Ash and his friends realized that Meowth had just been conning them and they were able to stop Team Rocket.</description>
<picture>56344.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2611" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="370">7.66</rating>
<name>Kojirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>James is one part of of the Team Rocket trio that follows around Ash Ketchum and friends in the Pokémon anime, usually trying to steal Ash`s Pikachu, but always failing.
James is mostly a comedic parody of bishounen characters; the English dub in particular tends to give him a melodramatic and even campy tone. He is somewhat famous for carrying a rose, though in more recent episodes he does not display it often. Mostly, his rose is displayed in the Team Rocket motto.
The only child of millionaires, James was forced to endure formal society. At a young age, he was forcefully engaged to a girl of whom he was terrified, Jessiebelle, all because his parents wanted to have a wealthy daughter-in-law. Thus, he ran away from home, leaving behind his beloved pet Growlie. He attempted to enroll in Pokémon Tech, a trainer`s school, but, along with his new friend Jessie, flunked out. Then, with Jessie, he joined the Sunny Town bicycle gang, where he was popular for being the only gang member to have to use training wheels (nicknamed "Trainer Jim"). Eventually James, Jessie, and the bike gang went their separate ways.
Due to conflicts in canon between Kanto and Johto episodes and the special episode "Training Daze", what happened between James and Jessie after the bike gang is unknown. What is known, as shown in the special episode, is that they joined Team Rocket separately and were on initially unfriendly terms after being grouped with Meowth. However, they quickly made up and the rest is history.
Since he is proficient in several activities, including Pokémon haiku and PokéRinger, it is possible that he developed his skills during his temporary separation from Jessie, but this is not known for sure.
In the episode "Holy Matrimony!", James returned to his home as a result of a trap by his parents, who pretended to be dead. He was reunited with his old pet Growlie and managed to avoid marrying Jessiebelle. Growlie stayed behind when James returned to Jessie and Meowth.
James has a tendency to be swindled by a Magikarp Salesman, who has on many occasions tricked him into buying a Magikarp or other useless Pokémon and items for large sums of money.
James also has a tendency to cross-dress, but has not done it since "Pros and Con Artists". He does, however, dress up like famous celebrities as well, such as Professor Oak, Juan, and Norman.
James loves rare bottle caps and has an impressive collection of them. In the episode "All That Glitters!" it is revealed that he has "drunk enough soda pop to float an aircraft carrier".
For unknown reasons, he, Jessie and Meowth mostly use hot air balloons instead of faster ways of transportation. However in newer episodes the balloon is shown with `jets` attached to explain how they get from one place to another faster than walking.</description>
<picture>2423.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="6693" type="main character in" update="2013-02-13">
<rating votes="911">2.49</rating>
<name>Satoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Beginning
Ash is the main character of the Pokémon anime. Raised in Pallet Town, he started his journey to become a Pokémon Master at the age of 10. On the day that he started his journey, Ash carelessly woke up late despite being told by his mother, Delia Ketchum to get to bed. He rushed to Professor Samual Oak`s laboratory only to find out that the beginner Pokémon - Bulbasaur, Squirtle, and Charmander - had already been given out to trainers who arrived on time. However, Professor Samual Oak mentioned that there was one more Pokémon available - Pikachu. Despite constantly hitting Ash with Electric-type attacks and refusing to return to its PokéBall, Ash decided to take Pikachu along with him on his journey to become a Pokémon Master. Pikachu is cold towards Ash at first and laughs at his failures; however, when Ash saves Pikachu from a flock of wild Spearow, he begins to warm up to his new trainer and the two finally become friends. After the battle with the flock of Spearow, a Ho-Oh is seen flying towards a rainbow in the sky. The PokéDex reveals that the Ho-Oh is an unidentified Pokémon. Thus, the journey of Ash and Pikachu begins.
Captures in Viridian Forest
While making his way towards Pewter City and his first Kanto League Gym Battle, Ash came upon a wild Caterpie deep within Viridian Forest. Instead of using Pikachu to battle against the wild Pokémon, Ash took his chances and threw a PokéBall without weakining the Caterpie first. Luckily, he was able to catch the Pokémon without any trouble. The capture of Ash`s Caterpie marked Ash`s first capture as a Pokémon Trainer, making Ash`s Caterpie the second Pokémon to join his team.
The next day, while continuing the trek through the Viridian Forest, Ash came up on a wild Pidgeotto. He tried to just throw a PokéBall like he did with Ash`s Caterpie, but Pidgeotto swatted the PokéBall away. Misty informed that he must weaken the Pokémon first before attempting to capture it. He called out Ash`s Caterpie to battle against, but Misty quickly informed him that Bug-type Pokémon are weak against Flying-type Pokémon like Pidgeotto. After Pidgeotto dealt significant damage to Ash`s Caterpie, Ash recalled it and sent out Pikachu. Pikachu was able to use its Thundershock to weaken Pidgeotto and allow Ash to capture it with a PokéBall. Thus, this capture marked Ash`s second capture as a Pokémon Trainer, making Ash`s Pidgeotto the third Pokémon to join his team.
Later on, while still in the Viridian Forest, Ash was approached by Team Rocket, who attempted to steal his Pokémon. After defeating Meowth, James`s Koffing, and Jessie`s Ekans, Ash`s Caterpie evolved into Ash`s Metapod.
Some of Ash`s greatest accomplishments have been at the various Pokémon Leagues. He was the victor at the Orange League and the Battle Frontier. He also competed in the Indigo League and the Johto Silver Conference where he placed admirably in both those competitions as well.
Pokémon World Tournament Junior Cup
Ash participated in the Pokémon World Tournament Junior Cup at the Kagome Town stadium. In the first round he was in the fifth match and faced off against Marris. The match was quickly showcased and Ash won the battle and advanced to the second round while Marris was eliminated from the tournament.
The Isshu League
Ash participated in the Isshu League in the preliminary match where he was matched up against Trip. Trip`s Serperior was sent out to battle Pikachu and Cilan noted that Trip`s Serperior`s speed and its attack power had leveled up quite a bit too since the last time they saw it. The match was pretty one sided for a long time as Pikachu wasn`t able to counter Trip`s Serperior speed and ended up getting wrapped up. After using Iron Tail on the ground to get loose, Pikachu used a combination attack of Iron Tail and Electro Ball to one hit KO Trip`s Serperior. As a result, Trip was eliminated from the Isshu League and Ash advanced to the next round. The two met in the Pokémon Center after the battle, and Trip vowed that the next time they met that he would win. The two shook hands and parted ways.
In the first main round, Ash`s opponent was shown on the match up electronic board but not much else is known about the battle. Ash`s Scraggy participated in the second main round of the Isshu League tournament where it faced off against a Darumakka. It was able to defeat it so that moved on to the next round.
In the third round, Stephan was matched up against Ash. Cilan noted that the two of them have a very direct taste and that it would be a good battle. It was only a 3 on 3 battle but the both of them gave it their all. The first two battles of the third round setup the final match up of Stephan`s Sawk vs Ash`s Krookodile, both of which were very injured from the previous battles. Both of them did their best to muster up their reserve strength but in the end a surprise move of Aerial Ace by Ash`s Krookodile was super effective against Stephan`s Sawk and it knocked it out to give Ash the victory while eliminating Stephan from the tournament. Stephan realized after the battle that the reason that Ash withdrew Waruvial after the first battle was because Ash knew that Stephan would definitely send out Dageki, so he didn`t reveal that it knew Aerial Ace and saved until the end.</description>
<picture>6210.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="8091" type="main character in" update="2017-10-30">
<rating votes="989">3.91</rating>
<name>Pikachu (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Beginning
On the morning that Ash was to start his Pokémon journey, he woke up late and by the time he reached Professor Samual Oak`s laboratory, all of the beginner Pokémon were already taken. However, Professor Samual Oak did have one Pokémon left, a wild Pikachu. At first, Pikachu did not like Ash and would refuse to enter his PokéBall. He would often laugh at Ash`s failures and refused to listen to him. However, after Ash proved his loyalty to Pikachu by protecting him from a flock of Spearow, and thus began to earn Pikachu`s trust and respect. The two have since become best friends and Pikachu never leaves Ash`s side.
Since the day Team Rocket first encountered Pikachu, it has been their sole goal to capture it. Day after day, their plan to capture Pikachu has been thwarted mainly due to Pikachu`s amazingly powerful Thunderbolt that keeps on blasting them off.
On numerous occasions, Pikachu has made it evident that he is happy being a Pikachu and has no desire to evolve into a more powerful Raichu. It has proven time and time again that it is a powerful and worthy opponent to any Pokémon that dares to battle it.
Gym Battle against Burgh`s Leavanny
Pikachu was then sent out to battle Burgh`s Leavanny. Burgh`s Leavanny managed to tie up Pikachu with String Shot but unlike Ash`s Swadloon who was able to break free, Pikachu ended up getting hit with a couple of Leaf Storm attacks and a Hyper Beam before it rolled into another of Burgh`s Leavanny`s Leaf Storm attacks to break the string off its body so it could attack. Freed from the String Shot, Burgh`s Leavanny tried to tie it up again but Pikachu managed to avoid it with its speed and then knocked Burgh`s Leavanny out with a combination of Iron Tail and Electro Ball.
Gym Battle against Elesa
Elesa`s Emolga knocked out Ash`s Snivy and was then matched up with Pikachu. Pikachu made quick work of Elesa`s Emolga and knocked it out with one attack, its Iron Tail.
Elesa`s Tynamo was the last Pokémon that she used in her gym battle against Ash. It was matched up against Pikachu who had just defeated her Emonga. Pikachu had a hard time defending against the fast Tackle attack that Elesa`s Tynamo kept hitting it with but Pikachu used its Thunderbolt to create a large dust cloud leaving only a small corridor for Pikachu to focus on it and so Elesa`s Tynamo couldn`t maneuver out of the way. Pikachu one hit K.O`d Elesa`s Tynamo with a Iron Tail. The loss gave Ash the overall victory.
Battle against Alder`s Bouffalant
Ash challenged Alder to a battle and he accepted though he had been walking all night and was actually quite tired. Alder sent out his Buffron to battle Pikachu but just as the battle started, Alder fell asleep standing up and didn`t give any orders to his Buffron. Alder`s Bouffalant stood still as Pikachu began hitting it with attack after attack until it Alder`s Bouffalant finally got mad at Alder and charged at him and set him flying into a tree. After that, Alder`s Bouffalant no longer wished to battle and Alder conceded the battle.
Gym Battle against Skyla
In Skyla air battle simulation, Ash`s Tranquill was matched up against Skyla`s Unfezant and since her Pokémon was the highest evolved form, she determined that her Pokémon would be the winner in that match-up. In the actual gym battle, Ash`s Tranquill was up against Skyla`s Unfezant which was the match-up just after Ash`s Tranquill had defeated Skyla`s Swoobat. Skyla`s Unfezant proved to be stronger and faster than Ash`s Tranquill, so Ash recalled it and set out Pikachu. Pikachu had a definite advantage over Skyla`s Unfezant with its electric attacks and it quickly knocked it out with its Electro Ball attack.
Ash Just after Pikachu ended up knocking out Skyla`s Unfezant, Skyla`s Swanna was sent out to battle against it. Skyla had been watching her grandpa`s battle videos and noticed that he used the move Aqua Ring to defend against Electric attacks. She used that same defense against Pikachu which nullified its Electric attacks. It`s Iron Tail also couldn`t hit it so high in the air. Ash then noticed the rings in the air and Pikachu jumped up on them and managed to hit Skyla`s Swanna but not directly. Pikachu was now up in the air though and Skyla`s Swanna had the advantage there and it quickly knocked Pikachu out with a powerful Brave Bird attack.
Battle Against Trip`s Serperior at the Isshu League
Pikachu participated in the Isshu League in the preliminary match where it is was matched up against Trip`s Serperior. Cilan noted that Trip`s Serperior speed and its attack power had leveled up quite a bit too since the last time they saw it. The match was pretty one sided for a long time as Pikachu wasn`t able to counter its speed and ended up getting wrapped up. After using Iron Tail on the ground to get loose, Pikachu used a combination attack of Iron Tail and Electro Ball to one hit KO Trip`s Serperior. As a result, Trip was eliminated from the Isshu League and Ash advanced to the next round.</description>
<picture>88041.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7" picture="186500.jpg">Ootani Ikue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18040" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-07">
<name>Proof</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Proof is a fan of the Pokémon Backer team Tengan Fighters who was playing in the Pokémon Backer World Cup at Crown City. She was in Crown City to see a match when what she thought was Suicune left a waterfall of water behind her and she had to climb up a light post to avoid what she thought would be drowning. Zoroark was actually the Suicune she saw using its Illusion ability.</description>
<picture>48498.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="21697" type="main character in" update="2013-02-14">
<rating votes="8">1.21</rating>
<name>Iris</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>While traveling in the Isshu region just outside of Kanako Town, Ash mistakenly thought Iris was a Pokémon and threw a monster ball at her. Ash thought she was a Axew as the Zukan displayed the data for it. Her Axew appeared out of her large hair moments later though. After learning that Cilan was going to be traveling with Ash through the Isshu region, Iris decided that she would travel with them as well but she said that her goal on this journey was a secret.
In the games, Iris is one of the gym leaders of Souryuu City`s Gym but it is currently unknown if she holds the same title in the anime.
Displeasure of Ice Pokémon
Just before Ash and Trip`s three-on-three battle, Iris encountered Trip`s Vanillite. She instantly tried to avoid it and started to shiver. She explained that since Dragon types have a disadvantage against Ice types, she dislike the cold that Ice Pokémon create. Trip tried to confront her about her dislike of Ice Pokémon by telling her that Dragon Pokémon are also strong against Dragon Pokémon but she only reluctantly apologized to Trip`s Vanillite and her mind wasn`t truly changed.
Making up with Excadrill
Excadrill didn`t always want to obey Iris when its asked to do something. For awhile, it was stubborn but Iris`s Excadrill was able to overcome the feelings of resentment and lost of trust it felt from the battle against Drayden`s Haxorus. After relating her experience to Ash and Cilan, it became more clear to Iris that she was not fully understanding her Excadrill`s feelings. Iris apologized to her Excadrill as she finally realized that her Excadrill knew after the first hit during the battle against Drayden`s Haxorus that they couldn`t win against it. The two of them then practiced all through the night until Excadrill was finally able to successfully launch the Focus Blast.
Rival Langley
While on route to Raimon City, Iris encountered Georgia, a Dragon Buster who once had a battle in the Dragon Village and her Pokémon was beaten up and now has it out for anyone from the village. Georgia managed to coax Iris into a battle but Iris`s Axew was no match for Georgia`s Beartic and Georgia ended up intimidating and angering Iris by saying the victory was easy and boring. Iris though was determined to defeat her new rival and during the rematch battle she managed to end it in a draw.
Don Battles
Iris entered the Don Battles, a battle tournament to be held in Raimon Town, with her friends and rivals. Jimmy Ray was easily defeated in the first round by Iris.
Stephan`s Sawk battled against Iris`s Emolga in the second round of the Don George Battle Tournament in Raimon Town but Emonga`s Static ability proved to be the deciding factor in the match. The Static ability ended up paralyzing Stephan`s Sawk and it was then a sitting target for Iris`s Emolga`s Volt Switch which knocked it out. Iris`s Emolga`s win eliminated Stephan from the tournament.
Iris`s Axew and Luke`s Golett were matched up in the semi-final round of the Don Battles in Raimon Town. Luke`s Golett dominated most of the battle and just as Iris`s Axew was about to be defeated, it learned the move Outrage. Outrage was able to do significant damage to Luke`s Golett and it knocked it out which eliminated Luke from the tournament.
In the finals, Iris battled against Ash and though it was a close battle, Iris`s Excadrill had the type advantage against Pikachu and she won the tournament. For winning, Iris received the beautiful seven-feather "Top-Class Driftveil Wing Set," containing Health, Muscle, Resist, Genius, Clever, Swift, and Pretty Wings which she sent to Dragon Village via Pidove Shipping Service.
Day Care Monozu
In BW58, befriended a shy and lonely Monozu that was awaiting its Trainer to return. As Monozu`s are a Dragon Type Pokémon, Iris was instantly excited to spend time with it. It took her awhile to gain its trust though. Iris recalled an event to Monozu that she witnessed in the Dragon Village where she saw Elder befriend a Crimgan that got lost and somehow found its way into the Village. The Crimgan absolutely refused to get along with other Dragon types and the people of the Village. For days and days, the Crimgan wouldn`t come out from deep within the cave. The Elder waited for Crimgan at the entrance of the cave the whole time and she tried to make the Crimgan open its heart to her, by talking to it like the way Iris was talking to Monozu to gain its trust and friendship. After several days had passed, Crimgan came out of the cave. All the Elder had done was talk to it and still, she managed to free it from its insecurities.
Iris uses the same technique that Elder used and the shy Monozu became more open with Iris and the two of them became friends. Iris spent a few days with the Monozu as they awaited the Trainer to return. At one point, Iris suggested to the Monozu if its Trainer didn`t return that it could come with her. The Trainer did return though and Monozu left with it but not before it gave Iris its biggest smile.
Fukiyose Tower Bell of Wishes Festival
Stephan met up with Iris and her friends and informed them of the Fukiyose Tower Bell of Wishes Festival that he was going to participate in. After hearing from him that it was an awesome event held once a year at the Fukiyose Tower, Iris and her friends decided to enter the tournament with Stephan.
Iris and Iris`s Axew paired up for the tournament. In the scavenger hunt, Iris asked Cilan to lent her his fishing rod so she could advance to the next round. In the tub race, Iris`s Axew used Dragon Rage on the surface of the water to propel them to the next round. During the imitation competition, iris was forced to dress-up as Professor Juniper and Miles thought she did quite well and he advanced her to the next round. In the forest of trials, Iris thought she had won but Chandela`s Confuse Ray affected her and she was in the middle of the forest for the entire race and was therefore eliminated from the tournament.
Rematch Battle against Drayden at the Soryu Gym
Having accepted the challenge to battle at the Dragon Village, Iris met up with Drayden to have a rematch battle. He heard about Iris getting into trouble again by climbing the Soryu Tower but told here to eat something and have a rest while he had a school meeting and then they would have their battle.
During the battle, Drayden was evaluating how much Iris had grown and he noticed that Iris`s Excadrill power certainly seemed to have improved. The matchup between Iris`s Excadrill and Drayden`s Haxorus ended up in a draw as the two of them knocked each other out. In the matchup between, Drayden`s Druddigon and Iris` Dragonite, Drayden noted that Iris` Dragonite had had an interesting life during its past. Iris` Dragonite wanted to fight under the same conditions as Drayden`s Druddigon, who cannot fly. Everyone thought that Iris was doing well in the battle but Drayden`s Druddigon proved to be more powerful than they had anticipated. Drayden`s Druddigon knocked out Iris` Dragonite with a powerful Dragon Tail attack to give Drayden the victory in the rematch battle. Cilan thought Iris had cornered him, but Drayden was still a few steps ahead. Drayden was trying to get a clear picture of Iris by drawing out their power.
Drayden complemented Iris on making good friends and he realized that sending her off on a journey was the right thing to do. He could tell that she had grown up but standing still wasn`t good for her. He told her to strengthen herself even further, become stronger and grow and then visit him again.</description>
<picture>3561.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21700" type="main character in" update="2015-02-24">
<rating votes="9">1.69</rating>
<name>Dent</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cilan is a gym leader of Sanyo City Gym where he shares the responsibility with Chili and Cress. He is also a Pokémon Sommelier who, with his abundance of knowledge and experience, determines the compatibility of Trainers and Pokémon and gives them advice on how to befriend each other. Cilan specializes in Grass type Pokémon and his main Pokémon and partner is Yanappu. Cilan revealed during BW19 that he had passed the required exams of the Pokémon Sommelier association to become a certified A-class Sommelier who is able to make compatibility diagnoses.
Cilan has many female fans who flock to his presence though he puts off their advances almost immediately. Brock has been quoted saying that, "Cilan is gay." and Shigeru`s fanclub has extended an invitation to all female Cilan fans to join the Gary Oak`s fanclub instead! The Polish drug scene has seen an increase in the usage of the ACE inhibitor Cilan (Cilazapril) as a result of Cilan flamboyant escapades at night. In the English closed captions for BW12, the transcribers listed Cilan as `Cilas`. A quick google search for `Cilas` and the first result is Cialis, an erectile dysfunction disorder drug.
It`s Dent Time! - Dent`s Catch Phrases
Dent in the Japanese original has various phrases that are based off his original "It`s Tasting Time!" catch phrase. It`s generally modified in the episode to match what`s going on in that particular instance. Below is a list of these catch phrases.
It`s Cilan Time! - Cilan`s Catch Phrases
Cilan in the English Dub has various phrases that are based off Dent`s original "It`s Tasting Time!" catch phrase. Some of them are exclusive to the English dub.
Rival Cabernet
Burgundy is Pokémon Sommelière and a Pokémon Trainer who upon passing the C-class Sommelier test, decided to challenge Cilan at the Sanyo Gym for the Tri Badge. Cilan defeated her but when Burgundy returned to challenge Cilan at the gym, Chili and Cress had to explain that Cilan was on a journey and was no longer at the gym. Angry that Cilan was not the gym leader when she visited, she battled at the gym anyhow and won the Tri Badge.
Cilan encountered her at a Friendly Shop while on his way to Hiun City and she was now out for revenge. Burgundy challenged Cilan to a revenge battle where she ended up losing to him yet again. More angry than ever, she vowed to defeat Cilan the next time they met while working to become an S-class Sommelière and she took off.
Fishing Sommelier
In BW26, Cilan stated that he was a Fishing Sommelier. He was able to help Bianca learn how to fish better by showing her how to select a good fishing rod and then the two basic forms of casting techniques: the overhead cast and the side hand cast. Cilan also showed her the proper lure techniques by spinning the reel slowly and not rushing to attempt to catch the Water Pokémon. He has his own fishing rod that is collapsible and easy to carry. Cilan proved his Fishing Sommelier were quite good by catching a large Bassrao at the Fishing Tournament.Cilan`s Stunfisk was also captured by using his fishing skills.
Science Sommelier
In BW33, Cilan explained that he is not only a Pokémon Sommelier but also a Science Sommelier. A Science Sommelier is someone who tries to solve any kind of supernatural phenomenon by finding out the cause scientifically by collecting evidence and proving their theory. Cilan has always tried to solve mysterious problems scientifically like the poltergeist that he and his friends encountered at the Shippo Museum in BW14 which turned out to be a Deathmas.
Movie Sommelier
In BW40, Cilan announced that he as a Movie Sommelier, someone that is able to review, critique and analyze the different elements of a movie and its characters. Cilan specifically showed his knowledge as a Movie Sommelier when he was helping out with Luke`s movie "Legend of the Pokémon Knight" by making suggestions and improvising on the go. He also helped out Ash who was a bit nervous being in front of the camera and he talked about the famous movie, "The Mask of Deathmas", where the heroine is portrayed as putting her life on the line for the sake of acting. He told Ash that in order to move the viewers with his performance, he`d need to become the role he was assigned.
Metro Sommelier
While heading down to the underground railway in Raimon City, Cilan professed that he was also a Metro Sommelier. Metro Sommeliers are divided into a "car group", which is particular about the cars or into a "line group", which is particular about the lines. Cilan said he belonged to the car group. being a metro sommelier is basically joining a fan club for people that metro transit. Cilan met Subway Boss Ingo and Subway Boss Emmet at the previous years subway convention. Cilan`s knowledge came in quite handy when he had to drive the rail carriage to catch up to Team Rocket.
In BW53, Cilan used his skills as a Metro Sommelier to help him complete the subway station stamp rally so he could battle against Subway Boss Ingo and Subway Boss Emmet. Cilan had been dreaming of doing the rally for many years so he could battle them as its considered a great honor for Metro Sommelier`s. Cilan was also able to use his knowledge and skills as a Metro Sommelier to reunite Erina with her Kibago.
Trial Sommelier
While in Astilbe Town, Ash`s Tepig original owner Shamus was put on trial by Cilan after he revealed that he was a Trial Sommelier. He presented himself as an impartial courtroom judge in the Karakusa Town Pokabu Abandonment case where Prosecutor Ash told about the cruel abandonment of Ash`s Tepig where it had a rope tied up around its mouth. The defendant Shamus told a different story though as he said that forcing a talentless Pokémon into futile battles is crueler. Unable to make a decision in the case, Don George suggested that the verdict be decided with a battle and Cilan agreed. After Ash`s Pignite defeated Shamus, Cilan said the battle had a superb taste and that there`s no need to hand down a verdict as it`s obvious that Ash and Ash`s Tepig were right.
Gym Battle against Skyla
After watching Skyla perform `air battles` which were her determining how a battle would go against her gym challengers by simulating the battle in her head, Cilan got very upset that she was not actually doing the battles and he challenged her to a battle. Cilan agreed to do an `air battle` with her and she determined that he would loose the battle against her with the Pokémon he had chosen to battle her with. Cilan though wanted to have a real battle with her a he explained to her that with Pokémon battle, like any meal, must be tasted first before people can be certain to know anything. Skyla agreed and Cilan thought that he would be able to show her up by defeating her in a real battle and showing how her `air battles` are flawed. Unfortunately Cilan ended up loosing to Skyla but Ash challenged her to a battle right after.
Fukiyose Tower Bell of Wishes Festival
Stephan met up with Cilan and his friends and informed them of the Fukiyose Tower Bell of Wishes Festival that he was going to participate in. After hearing from him that it was an awesome event held once a year at the Fukiyose Tower, Cilan and his friends decided to enter the tournament with Stephan.
During the quiz, Cilan didn`t know how they`d be able to answer the question about who Miles liked better as it was a very subjectional question. Miles was going to pick Nurse Joy (Isshu) as the girl he preferred the most but Cilan seemed to notice Ricky`s Elgyem use its abilities to affect Miles but didn`t say anything as they were able to successfully get the question right and move on to the next round.
In the scavenger hunt, Cilan successfully managed to find a Miracle Shooter while he lent his fishing rod to Iris. In the tub race, Cilan`s Pansage on instruction from Cilan, paddled in the water the same way it used Dig to advance them to the next round. During the imitation competition, Cilan was forced to dress as Elesa and Cilan`s Pansage was forced to dress-up as Elesa`s Emolga. Everyone thought Cilan did an amazing job but Miles informed Cilan that he was a very big Elesa fan and he had to be very strict with imitations of her. Cilan was then eliminated from the tournament.
Pokémon World Tournament Junior Cup
Cilan participated in the Pokémon World Tournament Junior Cup at the Kagome Town stadium. In the first round he was in the third match and faced off against Shepherd. The match was quickly showcased and Cilan won the battle and advanced to the second round while Shepherd was eliminated from the tournament.</description>
<picture>169247.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="255" picture="40713.jpg">Miyano Mamoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27172" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Victini</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Victini lives in the Eindoak Town area. It has lived for many years in the area but it was bound there due to a barrier setup by the descendents of the People of the Vale. It desperately wanted to see the ocean but could never reach it due to the barrier holding it back. Ash vowed to get Victini there.</description>
<picture>243426.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27183" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Minezumi</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Patrat, known as the Lookout Pokémon, is a rodent-like Pokémon that resembles a chipmunk. It continues keeping watch for several days, saving up food in its cheek pouches. It signals to its companions with its tail. They are extremely wary and keep watch outside their burrows in turns. They become anxious if no one keeps watch.
Patrat first appeared in the first few episodes of the Pokémon: Black and White anime. Multiple Patrat made a brief cameo in Black and White episode 3 with multiple Pidove and Deerling where they needed help from Ash and his friends. In the Pokémon Master Black &amp; White manga, Monta captures a Patrat in the first chapter.
Patrat and its evolution Watchog were called "fairly unremarkable aside from their intense facial expressions" by GamesRadar`s Carolyn Gudmundson. Gudmundson later noted it as a "Bidoof analog", in spite of the fact that it can only learn one Hidden Machine, whereas Bidoof can learn many. She adds that it is very easy to become bored of it. Official Nintendo Magazine`s Chris Schilling commented that Patrat was the "new Bidoof".</description>
<picture>243436.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27184" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Mamepato</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pidove is also known as the Tiny Pigeon Pokémon. Though it listens to its Trainer`s instructions, its nature means it doesn`t always understand them. A Pokémon that lives in urban areas. It loves company so many of them gather in parks and plazas.
In Black and White episode 2 "Enter Iris And Axew!", after Ash was attacked by a flock of Pidove that later flew away, one was left behind. He battled and eventually caught it. It eventually evolves into Tranquill in episode 22 "A Venipede Stampede!". In the Pokémon Adventures manga, a Pidove is one of the Pokémon employed by White in her BW Agency.
Official Nintendo Magazine`s Chris Schilling commented that Pidove was the new Pidgey.</description>
<picture>243451.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27193" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Chillarmy</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Minccino, known as the Chinchilla Pokémon, brush each other with their tails as a greeting. They never fail to groom their tails clean.
Game Informer`s Jeff Marchiafava praised it, calling it cute, and stating its move "Tail Slap" is the "most adorable way you can get beat up".</description>
<picture>243497.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27194" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Swanna</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Swanna, known as the White Bird Pokémon, is a swan-like Pokémon. With a long yellow bill, it administers sharp, powerful pecks. It whips its long neck to deliver forceful repeated strikes. Swanna start dancing at night, and dance around the leader of the flock.
In the games, Swanna can be found flying around Marvelous Bridge. In the anime, a flock of Swanna appeared in In The Shadow of Zekrom!. A Swanna later appeared under the ownership of Officer Jenny. In the Pokémon Master Black &amp; White manga, a Pokémon Ranger used one with his Zebstrika in a double battle against Monta.</description>
<picture>243506.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27195" type="appears in" update="2020-01-07">
<name>Shikijika</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Deerling is known as the Seasonal Pokémon. Depending on the temperature, moisture, and season its color will change.It is pink in the spring, green in the summer, orange in autumn, and brown in winter.
Game Informer`s Jeff Marchiafava stated that while Deerling wouldn`t be a good fighter, they still want one, because it is so adorable.</description>
<picture>64392.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="27196" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Mamanbou</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Alomomola, known as the Caring Pokémon, is a heart-shaped pink fish Pokémon with large dorsal and ventral fins. As it floats around in the ocean, it carries wounded Pokémon to shore. With their special membrane, they heal the Pokémon`s wounds.
Alomomola first makes an appearance in the anime "In The Shadow of Zekrom!", as a wild Pokémon. It was the first Pokémon in the Unova region that Ash saw.
Game Informer`s Jeff Marchiafava criticized its "nearly-unpronounceable name", and stated that it being a "Caring Pokémon" makes it a pacifist.</description>
<picture>243515.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27197" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Reshiram</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Reshiram is the Vast White Pokémon (White Yang Pokémon in Japan), and is the mascot for Pokémon Black. It resembles a white wyvern, with wing-shaped arms and claws. Its tail resembles a rocket engine or afterburner. The fire that burns from Reshiram`s tail is capable of incinerating everything.
It (as well as its English name) was revealed on May 28, 2010, on both the official Japanese and English Pokémon websites, alongside its counterpart Zekrom. Both Reshiram and Zekrom appeared as floats in the 2010 Macy`s Thanksgiving Day Parade.
At the climax of Pokémon Black, the player must capture Reshiram and use it to defeat N`s Zekrom, while in Pokémon White the roles of the two dragons are reversed.
Reshiram debuted in the anime as one of the featured Pokémon in the film Pokémon the Movie: Black - Victini and Reshiram. In Pokemon Black and White Version, its wings, tail, and head glows red.
In the Reshiram movie, Reshiram befriends Ash. In the Zekrom movie, Reshiram befriends Damon.</description>
<picture>243561.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27198" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Zekrom</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Zekrom is the Deep Black Pokémon (Black Yin Pokémon in Japan), and is the mascot for Pokémon White. It resembles a black dragon, with wing-like formations on its forearms. Its tail resembles an electric generator. It has the ability to travel through thunderclouds and cause storms.
It (as well as its English name) was revealed on May 28, 2010, on both the official Japanese and English Pokémon websites, alongside its counterpart Reshiram. Both Reshiram and Zekrom appeared as floats in the 2010 Macy`s Thanksgiving Day Parade.
At the climax of Pokémon White, the player must capture Zekrom and use it to defeat N`s Reshiram, while in Pokémon Black the roles of the two dragons are reversed.
Zekrom appears in the first two episodes of the Best Wishes! season of the Pokémon anime and the film Pokémon the Movie: White—Victini and Zekrom. In Pokémon Black and White Version, its arms legs and tail glow blue.
In the Reshiram movie, Zekrom befriends Damon. In the Zekrom movie, Zekrom befriends Ash.
GamesRadar`s Carolyn Gudmundson stated that Zekrom`s appearance is "strikingly intimidating".</description>
<picture>243562.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27199" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-13">
<name>Kibago (Iris)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Iris`s Axew was first seen appearing out of Iris`s large hairdo, much to the surprise of Ash and Pikachu. Ash helped rescue Axew from Team Rocket when they captured it just after Iris met Ash.
Axew is Iris`s main Pokémon and it doesn`t seem to like to travel in its monster ball. It seems to prefer traveling on Iris`s shoulders and in her hair.
Mastering Dragon Rage
Iris had been practicing Dragon Rage with her Kibago for quite a while and every time the attack was used it was unsuccessful and created a crater in the ground where the attack was used and injured everyone in the area. After being captured by Team Rocket along with Crimgan, Iris`s Axew managed to master Dragon Rage which was powerful enough to crash their flying transport mecha. In the battle encounter with Team Rocket that occurred after the crash, Iris`s Axew showed everyone that it had finally mastered the move by launching a successful attack at Team Rocket but they managed to escape before it hit them.
Don Battles Against Luke`s Golett
Iris`s Axew and Luke`s Golett were matched up in the semi-final round of the Don Battles in Raimon Town. Luke`s Golett dominated most of the battle and just as Iris`s Axew was about to be defeated, it learned the move Outrage. Outrage was able to do significant damage to Luke`s Golett and it knocked it out which eliminated Luke from the tournament.
Battle against Cynthia`s Garchomp / Learning Giga Impact
Iris asked to battle Cynthia`s Garchomp with her Kibago as she was working on becoming a Dragon Master. Even before it the started, the battled seemed like Cynthia`s Garchomp would win. Iris`s Axew could not do any damage to Cynthia`s Garchomp until it finally concentrated for a few moments and learned Giga Impact. While Giga Impact was able to do some damage to Cynthia`s Garchomp, it quickly overpowered Iris`s Axew until Cynthia decided to end the match before a finishing blow.</description>
<picture>63840.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27203" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-13">
<name>Mijumaru (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ash first encountered Mijumaru at Professor Juniper laboratory as it was one of the Pokémon that Trip was to choose from. Ash called it cute when he first saw it which caused Mijumaru to blush a bit. After being shocked that it wasn`t chosen by Trip, it followed Ash and Pikachu as they started their journey in the Isshu region.
It rescued Pikachu and Iris`s Axew from Rocket Gang. Ash thanked it but quickly left it behind in the forest so that he could treat Pikachu. It continued following Ash until one day it met up again and tried to explain that it wanted to join Ash on his journey. Ash tried to capture it with one of his Poké balls but then realized it already had a Poké ball and that this Mijumaru must have been the same one that he met at Professor Juniper lab. He contacted Professor Juniper and she agreed to let him have the Mijumaru and transferred its Poké ball to him. By the time it had been transferred over, it had disappeared again.
Ash met up with Mijumaru once again when they were resting in the sands at Dan`s hotel. After protecting Ash from being scalded from a hot water geyser, Ash quickly recalled it into the Poké ball before it got scalded itself. Since then Ash`s Oshawott has had the tendency to come out of its Poké ball whenever it feels like despite what the current situation is.
Gym Battles against Lenora`s Watchog
During the first gym battle against Ash`s Oshawott, Lenora`s Watchog used Mean Look so Ash`s Oshawott couldn`t be switched out. Since Ash`s Oshawott wasn`t expecting to battle Lenora`s Watchog at that time, it was at a disadvantage and it was in a bad mood. After Ash`s Oshawott lost its shell during the battle, Lenora`s Watchog was able to use its Thunderbolt effectively to knock Ash`s Oshawott out of the match.
During the rematch battle against Lenora`s Watchog, Ash`s Oshawott had learned Aqua Jet during the time between the two battle and but its accuracy make it easy for Lenora`s Watchog to avoid it. Though through sheer luck, Ash`s Oshawott Aqua Jet managed to hit Lenora`s Watchog and both ended up getting knocked out at the same time as Lenora`s Watchog used Thunderbolt just before it got hit.
Three-on-Three Battle Against Trip`s Timburr
Ash`s Oshawott was paired up against Trip`s Timburr but the beginning of the battle didn`t go to well for Ash as Ash`s Oshawott had its eyes closed during Aqua Jet and completely missed hitting Trip`s Timburr. After a short break in the battle, the two finished up with their final attacks. Ash`s Oshawott`s Razor Shell proved to be stronger than Trip`s Timburr`s DynamicPunch and Ash`s Oshawott defeated Trip`s Timburr despite its initial problems with Aqua Jet`s accuracy.
Mastering Aqua Jet
While training in Don George`s pool for the battle against Lenora, Ash`s Oshawott learned Aqua Jet. It`s aim proved to be quite off but through sheer luck it was able to use Aqua Jet to knock out both Lenora`s Watchog and Stephan`s Blitzle. It wasn`t until Trip noticed by taking some pictures during his three-on-three battle with Ash that Ash`s Oshawott had its eyes closed during Aqua Jet. Ash vowed to help his Oshawott practice to keep its eyes open underwater so that its Aqua Jet`s targeting would be accurate.
While enroute to Raimon City, Ash, Iris and Cilan`s Pokémon all got poisoned and the only thing that could cure them was a waterweed plant found in a nearby lake. Ash`s Oshawott was training with Ash at the time and didn`t get poisoned and since it was a Water Pokémon, it was best suited for the job. Unfortunately Ash`s Oshawott still didn`t like to open its eyes underwater until it was forced to defend itself against a school of Tympole who were protecting their lake from trespassers. Ash`s Oshawott opened its eyes underwater to defend itself and it started to get comfortable doing so. Ash`s Oshawott was later forced to battle Palpitoad because it came out of the water to protect its lake. During the battle, Ash`s Oshawott managed to master its Aqua Jet as it was able to remember the battle against the Tympole school and how having its eyes opened underwater was quite effective and that proved to be the decisive factor in the battle as Palpitoad was knocked out and Ash caught it.
Battle against Bel`s Father`s Hihidaruma
Ash challenged Bianca`s Father to a Pokémon battle to allow Bianca to continue to travel. He agreed but changed the challenge to force Ash to return home to Pallet Town if he lost the battle. Ash`s Oshawott came out of its ball as it wanted to battle against Bianca`s Father`s Darmanitan and Ash thought that it would be okay because it had a type advantage being a water Pokémon. Even though Bianca`s Father`s Darmanitan only used Fire type moves throughout the battle, it proved to be too strong for Ash`s Oshawott. Ash`s Oshawott did manage to land an Aqua Jet. Bianca`s Father commented though that his Red Flash Hihidaruma gets more fired up the more resistance it faces and shortly after it knocked Ash`s Oshawott out. Despite loosing the battle, Bianca`s Father changed his mind because the battle with Ash and his Mijumaru made him remember the joy of traveling.
Battle Against Pod`s Baoppu
Initially, Ash was going to battle Chili`s Pansear with his Pikachu, but Ash`s Oshawott popped out and wanted to battle it instead. Ash agreed and despite the type disadvantage in this battle, Chili just got more fired up. Chili`s Pansear managed to cover its weakness with power and momentum and taking Cilan`s advice into account, it used Flame Charge to increase its speed to become useful when dodging Ash`s Oshawott moves. Chili`s Pansear managed to endure Ash`s Oshawott super effective moves just long enough for it to use its newly learned SolarBeam attack which Ash`s Oshawott was unable to dodge and it was knocked out. Chili`s Pansear won the battle despite the type disadvantage.
Battle Against Clay`s Krokorok
Clay`s Krokorok was the first Pokémon Clay used to battle against Ash during his gym battle. Clay`s Krokorok was paired up against Ash`s Oshawott as Pikachu initially wanted to battle it but Ash realized that an Electric type against a Ground type would be a bad idea.
At the beginning of the battle, Clay`s Krokorok had the upper hand as its Sandstorm managed to get sand in Ash`s Oshawott`s eyes and it also made it harder for Ash`s Oshawott to accurately attack. Clay`s Krokorok managed to hit Ash`s Oshawott with a Bite and a Stone Edge attack but it wasn`t enough to knock it out. Ash`s Oshawott used Water Gun to clear up the Sandstorm and then it began its counterattack. Clay`s Krokorok was repetitively hit with multiple attacks from Ash`s Oshawott including a super effective Aqua Jet and Razor Shell combo that ended up being too much for it and it was knocked out.
Battle Against Clay`s Palpitoad
Ash decided to keep his Oshawott out to battle against Clay`s Palpitoad and right away it became evident that Clay`s Palpitoad was the stronger Pokémon as its Hydro Pump ended up being more powerful than Ash`s Oshawott Water Gun. Clay`s Palpitoad followed up with a Sludge Bomb that knocked Ash`s Oshawott`s scallsword out of its hand and just as it was retrieving it, it got hit by Clay`s Palpitoad Rock Smash`s and was knocked out.
Ash`s Oshawott and Dawn`s Piplup Rivalry
Ash`s Oshawott and Dawn`s Piplup both fell in love with Meloetta and the two of them began a rivalry to win the affection of Meloetta. Ash`s Oshawott would often come out of its PokéBall when it could tell that Dawn`s Piplup was trying to take advantage of a situation. Even though the two of them often argued, they found a common ground and became friends after Meloetta left.</description>
<picture>63844.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27206" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-10-27">
<name>Pokabu (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ash`s Pokabu was first seen by Don George at his Battle Club when it original trainer came to battle. Pokabu lost to a Shikijika during the battle and its trainer tied it to a pole and left it. The Pokabu ended up getting the string tied around its snout making it impossible for it to eat.
Ash saw Pokabu on the security camera video and thought it was an Umbreon because it was all dirty. When Ash finally spotted Pokabu, he cornered it in an alley and tried to be friendly with it. Ash noticed the rope tied around its snout and loosened it. Pokabu then helped rescue Pikachu from Team Rocket.
Iris wanted to get Pokabu but it wanted to be caught by Ash instead. Realizing that Pokabu wanted to travel with him, Ash captured Pokabu just outside the Battle Club in Karakusa Town.</description>
<picture>63847.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27209" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-13">
<name>Yanappu (Dent)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cilan`s Pansage was first revealed in the Sanyo Gym when Ash was shown the three gym leaders Pokémon and he looked it up in his PokéDex. Yanappu is Cilan`s main Pokémon and is relied on quite often to help Cilan out with his various tasks.
Yanappu battled against Ash`s Oshawott during his gym battle. Cilan`s Pansage showed its speed by being able to dodge most of Mijumaru Water Gun attacks.
Battle Against Pod`s Baoppu
Chili wanted to see the results of Cilan`s studying and he challenged him to a battle. Chili thought that it would be an easy battle as they had the super effective type advantage but as the battle progressed Chili didn`t like the fact that Cilan`s Pansage kept avoiding all of Chili`s Pansear fire attacks and Chili told Cilan that running away all the time doesn`t make a battle. Cilan though told him that running away is a perfectly fine way to battle. Chili got more angry during the battle and after loosing he blamed his Baoppu for the loss as it missed its Fire Blast at the most crucial moment. Chili`s Pansear ran away in anger as it was mad it was getting blamed for the loss and Cilan then blamed Chili for the loss in the battle which only fueled Chili`s anger and he ran off as well.
Battle against Skyla
Skyla`s Unfezant was matched up against Cilan`s Pansage in Skyla`s air battle and she believed that her Unfezant would be victorious. In the actual gym battle, Skyla`s Swoobat was matched up against Cilan`s Pansage. It proved to be very fast in the air and easily dodged all of Cilan`s Pansage`s attacks. It only used two attacks against Cilan`s Pansage: a Air Cutter and a Gust attack before it knocked it out and gave Skyla the victory in the first round.
Tag Battle against Soran`s Warrgle and Riiku`s Mogurew
Cilan`s Pansage had a tag battle with Ash`s Unfezant against Soran`s Warrgle and Riiku`s Mogurew while Ash and his friends were on their way to Higaki City where the Isshu League was to be held. Soran`s Warrgle and Riiku`s Mogurew used special move combinations which proved to be effective in the tag battle against Ash and Cilan until they also decided to use their own combination of moves which ended up overpowering Soran`s Warrgle and Riiku`s Mogurew and they lost the tag battle.</description>
<picture>63851.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27216" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-13">
<name>Tsutarja (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>While on route to Shippo City, Ash encountered a resilient Tsutarja. Tsutarja started eating the cakes Dent made. Realizing that it was a strong and powerful Pokémon, he decided to try to capture it right away but it didn`t get captured in the monster ball. Ash then instructed Pikachu to attack Tsutarja but Ash ended up having to protect Pikachu from Tsutarja`s powerful vine whips as it was exposed to Attract which made it dizzy.
Ash`s Oshawott and Ash`s Tepig were both sent out to battle Tsutarja as well but it used Attract against them which proved quite effective due to the gender differences. Ash finally instructed his Mamepato to battle as it wasn`t affected by Attract. After a fierce battle between Tsutarja and Mamepato, Tsutarja was weakened enough and Ash captured it successfully.
Don George Tournament
Georgia faced Ash in the second round of the Don George tournament in Raimon Town. Georgia`s Pawniard faced Ash`s Snivy and at the beginning of the battle it looked like it was going to easily win but Ash`s Snivy was able to avoid getting hit by Guillotine. From that point on, Ash`s Snivy took control of the match and was able to defeat Georgia`s Pawniard which advanced Ash on to the next round in the tournament.
Gym Battle Against Elesa`s Emolga
After Elesa`s Emolga defeated Ash`s Palpitoad, Ash`s Snivy was sent out to battle against Elesa`s Emolga but Ash didn`t really have a battle strategy anymore since his Palpitoad had been defeated and he forgot that Emolga was also a Flying type. Elesa`s Emolga combination of Acrobatics and Aerial Ace was just too hard for Ash`s Snivy to defend against as the type advantage hampered it. Elesa`s Emolga knocked out Ash`s Snivy fairly easily.
Battle against Katharine`s Gothita
Katharine`s Gothita convinced Ash`s Scraggy to come with it outside to get something to eat. They ended up getting in trouble with a Garbodor and Katharine`s Deerling to use its Aromatherapy to calm down the raging Garbodor after Ash`s Snivy had followed them to see what they were up to. Katharine`s Gothita did not like the fact that Ash`s Snivy had been looking up on them and it decided it wanted to battle it.
Katharine`s Gothita was quite mad at Ash`s Snivy but it didn`t stand a chance against it in battle. Ash`s Snivy barely broke a sweat as it was able to counter and avoid all of Katharine`s Gothita`s attacks before it knocked it out with its Leaf Storm. Still upset, Katharine`s Gothita ran off into the distance.
Battle against Clay`s Palpitoad
After knocking out Ash`s Oshawott, Ash`s Snivy was sent out to replace it as Ash picked it because it was strong against both Ground and Water. Ash`s Snivy used Attract right at the beginning of their battle which prove to be an unexpected yet effective technique as Clay`s Palpitoad was unable to attack after the effects of Attract took hold of it. Ash`s Snivy pummeled Clay`s Palpitoad with effective Grass type attacks until it was knocked out.
Battle against Clay`s Excadrill
Ash kept his Snivy out to battle against Clay`s Excadrill but that matchup didn`t last long as Clay`s Excadrill was able to defend against all of Ash`s Snivy`s attacks. Ash`s Snivy was quickly knocked out with a strong Horn Drill.</description>
<picture>63859.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27217" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-13">
<name>Doryuzu (Iris)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Iris`s Excadrill was revealed when she was required to rescue her Axew from a raging Pendra. She called out Excadrill to help rescue Axew from between Pendra`s horns but it stayed in its curled up drill state until after Axew was rescued. Pendra though was still raging and it kicked Excadrill and got it angry. It then drilled underneath Pendra and then set it flying.
Excadrill didn`t always want to obey Iris when its asked to do something. For awhile, it was stubborn but Iris`s Excadrill was able to overcome the feelings of resentment and lost of trust it felt from the battle against Drayden`s Haxorus. After relating her experience to Ash and Cilan, it became more clear to Iris that she was not fully understanding her Excadrill`s feelings. Iris apologized to her Excadrill as she finally realized that her Excadrill knew after the first hit during the battle against Drayden`s Haxorus that they couldn`t win against it.
Battle against Drayden`s Haxorus at Dragon Village Battle Tournament
Having watched Iris`s Excadrill battle and defeat the Trainer`s Crimgan at the battle tournament in the Dragon Village, Drayden came out of the tent to meet Iris and her Excadrill. Iris challenged Drayden to a battle and if they won the battle, it would be their 100th victory together. Drayden accepted and sent out his Haxorus. Iris`s Excadrill was no match for Drayden`s Haxorus and it was defeated with a powerful Rock Smash attack. After the battle it began to distrust Iris and hid itself in its drilling position.
Mastering Focus Blast
Iris eventually realized that her Excadrill didn`t know any moves that it could use to fight with from a distance. She also realized that if it had known one at an earlier time, they would`ve had more options on how to construct our battles and would have been better prepared against Drayden`s Haxorus which had strong counter defenses against close range attacks. The night Iris apologized to her Excadrill, it decided to go out into the forest to practice working on Focus Blast. Iris showed up and the two of them practiced all through the night until it was finally able to successfully launch the attack.
Battles against Langley`s Beartic
After Iris`s Axew was defeated by Georgia`s Beartic, Iris was confident that her Excadrill was easily strong enough to defeat Georgia`s Beartic. She called her Excadrill out to battle but it appeared in its drilling position to which Iris told Georgia that it was in that position because it needed motivation. Georgia`s Beartic quickly attacked it with a Slash attack which was more than enough motivation for it to battle. Unfortunately, it wouldn`t listen to Iris`s commands and it ended up loosing the match when Georgia`s Beartic used Rock Smash, the same move that caused it to loose its first Pokémon battle and began secluding itself.
During the rematch battle, Iris`s Excadrill listened to Iris`s commands and they were able to have a more effective battle. Georgia`s Beartic still proved to be a powerful opponent but this time the battle ended in a draw.
Donamite Tournament
Burgundy`s Dewott entered the Donamite tournament and faced Iris`s Excadrill in the first round. Iris`s Excadrill was able to defend Burgundy`s Dewott new move Ice Beam with its claws but when Iris`s Excadrill dug a hole, Burgundy`s Dewott used Water Pulse in the hole to deal some significant damage and get it back above ground. Iris`s Excadrill fought back with another violent Metal Claw attack which struck its mark and looked like it had defeated Burgundy`s Dewott. Burgundy`s Dewott had another new move up its sleeve and it got up off the ground and used Revenge. Iris`s Excadrill managed to withstand Revenge and counterattack with Dig while Burgundy`s Dewott was still recovering. Iris`s Excadrill won the match and eliminated Burgundy from the tournament.
Rematch Battle against Drayden`s Haxorus at the Soryu Gym
During the battle, Drayden was evaluating how much Iris had grown and he noticed that Iris`s Excadrill power certainly seemed to have improved. The matchup between Iris`s Excadrill and Drayden`s Haxorus ended up in a draw as the two of them knocked each other out.</description>
<picture>63860.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27223" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-27">
<name>Ishizumai (Dent)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>While on route to Shippo City, Cilan and his traveling companions Ash and Iris found a group of Ishizumai that were picking on a weaker Ishizumai. The stronger Ishizumai stole the weaker Ishizumai home, a gray rock that it had been working on. Cilan became friends with the Ishizumai and helped it defeat the gang of Ishizumai to recover its home. As Cilan was departing, the Ishizumai didn`t want to part and Cilan realized this, he too had become attached to the Ishizumi and he capture it.</description>
<picture>63868.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27257" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Hatoboh</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tranquill, known as the Wild Pigeon Pokémon, is the evolved form of Pidove. It is believed that, deep within the forest where Tranquill live, there is a peaceful country without strife. Ash`s Pidove evolves into a Tranquill in Best Wishes! episode 22 "A Venipede Stampede!" after seeing Trip`s Tranquill in action. In episode 44, a flock of wild Tranquill appears, enraged at a Purrloin for stealing their berries.</description>
<picture>243452.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27258" type="appears in" update="2020-01-07">
<name>Kenhallow</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Unfezant, known as the Proud Pokémon, evolves from Tranquill, and is the final form of Pidove. Unfezant are one of the few Pokémon to have very noticeable gender differences. The males have large, pink, ribbon-like wattles, and green underbellies. The females have a small crest, and brown underbellies. Males swing their head plumage to threaten opponents, and will never let themselves feel close to anyone other than their trainers. The females have flying abilities that surpass those of the males.</description>
<picture>64532.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="27259" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Kokoromori</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Swoobat, known as the Courting Pokémon, evolves from Woobat by leveling it up when its happiness is high. Happiness can be raised by fighting through many Pokémon battles, having the Pokémon in your party or feeding it vitamins. Swoobat is a blue bat-like Pokémon with a white mane of fur, a heart shaped nose, and a vaguely heart shape at the end of its tail. The sound waves it emits from its nose are of a frequency powerful enough to destroy rocks. The ultrasonic waves emitted by a courting male causes people to have a positive mood.</description>
<picture>243459.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27263" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Waruvial</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Krookodile, known as the Menace Pokémon, is a large brick-colored crocodile. It has black stripes with pointed ends. It has large teeth and claws. Around its eyes, there is a black area resembling a bandit`s mask, or a stylized pair of sunglasses. Its belly has gray scales. With powerful jaws that can bite the body off an automobile, it doesn`t let any prey escape. With eyes like binoculars, they can see things magnified at a distance.
The Escapist listed Krookodile as one of the new Pokémon with "really cool designs", describing it as a "sunglasses-wearing crocodile".</description>
<picture>243482.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27264" type="appears in" update="2020-01-07">
<name>Hihidaruma</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Darmanitan is known as the Blazing Pokémon. Its ability, Zen Mode (Daruma Mode in Japan), changes its appearance to a stone statue with whitened out eyes, adds the type Psychic, its special attack and attack are swapped, and defenses are doubled.
Game Informer`s Jeff Marchiafava stated "Despite the flaming eyebrows, Darmanitan doesn`t look all that tough".</description>
<picture>68347.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="27268" type="appears in" update="2020-01-07">
<name>Mebukijika</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sawsbuck, known as the Seasonal Pokémon. The evolved form of Deerling. Its horns carry flowers which change with the season. The leader of the herd has the most splendid horns.
The Escapist listed Sawsbuck as one of the new Pokémon with "really cool designs", describing it as "the incredibly manly evolution of the incredibly cute deer".</description>
<picture>64393.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="27269" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Koaruhie</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ducklett is known as the Water Bird Pokémon. They are light blue, gosling-like Pokémon. They have two feathery tufts on their heads connected at the bottom, forming a `v` shape. It has a darker blue, feathery underside which makes it appear as if it were mi-moult. It had yellow, webbet feet and a beak and a small tail.
A trio of Ducklett appear in the Black &amp; White episode "Dancing With the Ducklett Trio" where they attack Ash and his friends, stealing some of their belongings, including Ash`s hat and the wild Sandile`s sunglasses.</description>
<picture>243505.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27270" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Chillaccino</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cinccino is the evolution of Minccino, known as the Scarf Pokémon. It evolves with the use of a Shiny Stone. Cinccino never goes near dust or static electricity due to their oiled fur. This oil helps deflect attacks.</description>
<picture>243498.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27278" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Mogurew</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Drilbur, known as the Mole Pokémon, burrows underground at more than 50 km/h. Its running speed above ground rivals automobiles. It evolves in Excadrill. By crossing both its claws it makes itself rotate at high speeds and progresses underground at a great speed.
Game Informer`s Jeff Marchiafava criticized its design, stating "I just don`t feel very intimidated when I look at Drilbur."</description>
<picture>243460.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27280" type="appears in" update="2020-01-07">
<name>Pururill</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Frillish is known as the Floating Pokémon. Frillish can constrict its foes using its veil-like tentacles and numb them with poison. It is said to live in dens some five miles below sea level. Pokémon Black Version:With its thin, veil-like arms wrapped around the body of its opponent, it sinks to the ocean floor. Pokémon White Version: They paralyze prey with poison, then drag them down to their lairs, five miles below the surface.
A male Frillish owned by Trip appears in the Best Wishes! anime series in the episode "A Rival Battle for Club Champ". Trip uses Frillish to defeat Ash`s Pidove with a Water Pulse attack. He also uses it in battle against Ash`s Snivy due to the opposite genders of the two Pokémon, where Frillish is able to defeat Snivy with a combination of Water Pulse and Hex.</description>
<picture>64528.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="27281" type="appears in" update="2020-01-07">
<name>Burungel</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jellicent, known as the Floating Pokémon, is the evolved form of Frillish. It`s male form is blue and resembles a king, while it`s female form is pink and resembles a queen.</description>
<picture>64529.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="27282" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Yorterry</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lillipup is known as the Puppy Pokémon. The long hairs covering its face are excellent radars. It delicately senses the state of its surroundings.
In the anime, Lillipup appeared under the ownership of Lenora, where it won in a battle against Ash`s Tepig. Later, when it evolved into a Herdier, it lost against Ash`s Tepig during the Rematch in "Rematch At The Nacrene City Gym."
GamesRadar`s Carolyn Gudmundson noted it as being initially weak, but becomes quite powerful in its final evolution. Official Nintendo Magazine`s Chris Schilling called Lillipup the new Rattata.</description>
<picture>243438.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27284" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Mooland</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Stoutland, known as the Big-Hearted Pokémon, is a dog-like Pokémon that is the final evolution of Lillipup. It looks very similar to Herdier, its pre-evolved form, with a brown base coat, black-gray thicker fur, and white-cream thick fur on its face like a long mustache. Stoutland are very talented at saving people, especially people stranded in the mountains or at sea. Its thick fur protects it from freezing cold temperatures.</description>
<picture>243440.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27365" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Choroneko</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Purrloin, known as the Devious Pokémon, is a purple feline Pokémon. It plays with and steals people`s belongings. Even the people it steals from unconsciously forgive it due to its charming behavior. Its adorable behavior causes people to let down their guard, and it takes that opportunity to steal their belongings. If it gets mad it will fight back with its claws.
GamesRadar`s Carolyn Gudmundson noted it and its evolution as a decent Dark-type pair, though the stats are somewhat low.</description>
<picture>243441.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27366" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Lepardas</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Liepard, known as the Cruel Pokémon, is the evolved form of Purrloin. They vanish and appear unexpectedly. They also stealthily sneak up to its target, striking from behind before the victim has any time to react. They resemble purple Leopards. They are one of the most commonly used Pokémon in Team Plasma.</description>
<picture>243442.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27367" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Shimama</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Blitzle, known as the Electrified Pokémon, is a zebra-like Pokémon. Its mane shines when it discharges electricity. It communicates with its comrades by the light of its mane. It appears when the sky is obscured by thunderclouds. It uses its mane to catch lightning and store the electricity.
Game Informer`s Jeff Marchiafava stated, "Something about Blitzle seems like it`s trying too hard."</description>
<picture>243453.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27368" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Zebraika</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Zebstrika, known as the Thunderbolt Pokémon, is the evolved form of Blitzle. It is known for its ill tempered nature, and when its angry, the lightning that shoots from its mane goes in all directions.</description>
<picture>243454.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27375" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Otamaro</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tympole, known as the Tadpole Pokémon, is a tadpole-like Pokémon with a cream-colored face, a blue tail, and blue bumps on the side of its head. They vibrate their cheeks to make a high-pitched sound that warns others of danger. While these sound waves are unable to be heard by humans, Tympole use them to talk with each other.</description>
<picture>243465.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27376" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Gamagaru</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Palpitoad, known as the Vibration Pokémon, is the evolved form of Tympole. Palpitoad have vibraters on their bodies that look like lumps. When they vibrate these lumps they can cause earthquakes. It possesses a sticky long tongue in which it uses to catch prey.
In the Best Wishes episode "Facing Fear With Eyes Wide Open!", a Palpitoad is encountered and it leads a school of Tympole to attack Ash`s Oshawott and prevent it from getting herbs to cure the company`s poisoned Pokémon. After the Tympole swim away, it calls on its friend, a Stunfisk, to get rid of Oshawott. Cilan makes short work of Stunfisk with his fishing rod, so Palpitoad comes to battle Oshawott personally. After a long battle, Oshawott learns to keep its eyes open underwater, leading to the perfection of its new Aqua Jet attack, which helps Ash to catch the Palpitoad and Cilan to catch the Stunfisk.</description>
<picture>243466.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27377" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Gamageroge</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Seismitoad, known as the Vibration Pokémon, is the final evolution of Tympole. According to the Pokédex, they shoot paralyzing liquid from their head bumps. They use vibration to hurt their opponents. Their vibration also increases the power of their punches. With a single punch, a boulder can be turned into a pile of rubble.
It is the only Water-type Pokémon with a double weakness to Grass to learn no damage dealing Ice-type moves. Instead of Ice-type moves though, Seismitoad can be taught Poison-type moves such as Sludge Wave to fend off Grass-types.</description>
<picture>243467.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27378" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Nageki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Throh, known as the Judo Pokémon, is a red, fat human-like Pokémon wearing a white and black martial arts outfit. When it tightens its belt, it becomes stronger. Wild Throh use vines to weave their own belts. Always traveling in packs of five, they throw foes that are bigger than them.</description>
<picture>243468.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27379" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Dageki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sawk, known as the Karate Pokémon, is a blue, thin human-like Pokémon wearing a white and black martial arts outfit. The sound of Sawk punching boulders and trees can be heard all the way from the mountains where they train. Tying their belts gets them pumped and makes their punches more destructive. Disturbing their training angers them.</description>
<picture>243469.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27383" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Monmen</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cottonee, known as the Cotton Puff Pokémon. Cottonee is a small, white Pokémon with cotton-like puffs on the top and bottom of its head. It has two leafy figures on its sides. When attacked, it escapes by shooting cotton from its body, which distracts the attacker. Going wherever the wind takes them, they take shelter beneath big trees on rainy days. It evolves into Whimsicott when exposed to a Sun Stone.
A version exclusive Pokémon in Black version, it must be obtained from a trade with an NPC known as Dye in White version (nicknamed Fluffee) or from another player with Pokémon Black.</description>
<picture>243476.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27384" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Elphoon</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Whimsicott, known as the Windveiled Pokémon, evolves from Cottonee when exposed to a Sun Stone. It resembles a plant-like creature with a large puff of cotton on its head. It not only drifts with the wind, but can also slip through cracks like the breeze can. It can therefore enter homes and pull pranks on the inhabitants.
Whimsicott can be found rarely in the wild in Black version. Whimsicott made its debut anime appearance in Pokémon the Movie: Black - Victini and Reshiram and White - Victini and Zekrom. In the Pokémon Adventures manga, Whimsicott is seen being released by its Trainer after Ghetsis`s speech in Accumula Town and holding the leg of its Trainer, wanting to stay.</description>
<picture>243477.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27385" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Churine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Petilil, known as the Bulb Pokémon, is a light green plant-like Pokémon with three leaves on top of its head. The leaves on its head are very bitter, but are known to refresh a tired body. Petilil prefer to live in places with moist, nutrient-rich soil, which is good for growing plants.
A common Pokémon in White version, in Black version it can only be obtained from a trade with an NPC known as Dye or from another player. The Petilil`s nickname is Lillil.</description>
<picture>243478.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27386" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Dredear</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lilligant, known as the Flowering Pokémon, evolves from Petilil when exposed to a Sun Stone. It has pollen on its head, and resembles a flowering plant. A Lilligant will wither when it is not treated well. Lilligant is a female-only species.
Lilligant can be found rarely in White version.</description>
<picture>243479.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27387" type="appears in" update="2020-01-07">
<name>Basslao</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Basculin, known as the Hostile Pokémon, is a green and black colored fish. It has two forms which main difference is a colored stripe and the player encounters one form more commonly depending on the game version; red-striped Basculin are more common in Black, while the blue-striped variety is more common in White.
Game Informer`s Jeff Marchiafava praised its categorization as the "Hostile Pokémon", stating "Now here`s a category I can get behind". They criticized its abilities for contradicting each other.</description>
<picture>64390.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="27391" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Symboler</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sigilyph, known as the Avianoid Pokémon, is a spherical Pokémon that is green and black with blue eyes, and yellow wings and tail that are tipped with red and blue. It has black fork-like figures coming out of its side, and a black figure with an eye coming out of the top of its body. It bears a resemblance to The Hummingbird of the Nazca lines. Sigilyph used to guard an ancient city, and still fly in the same route as they once did. They use their psychic power to attack enemies that invade their territory.</description>
<picture>243488.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27392" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Protoga</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tirtouga, known as the Prototurtle Pokémon, resembles a baby sea turtle. These Pokémon swam in oceans about 100 million years ago. They went on land to attack prey. Restored from a fossil, this Pokémon can dive over half a mile.</description>
<picture>243490.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27393" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Abagoura</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Carracosta, known as the Prototurtle Pokémon, resembles a bipedal, blue-colored sea turtle. They can live both in the ocean and on land. They are so powerful, they can open a hole in the bottom of a tanker in one slap. They are able to chew up steel beams and rocks along with their prey, by using their incredible jaw strength.</description>
<picture>243491.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27396" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Gothimu</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gothita, known as the Fixation Pokémon, is a human-like baby Pokémon with purple skin, and black and white clothes. It has three bows, and a small tuft of hair. Their bows increase their psychic abilities. Gothita closely observe both Trainers and Pokémon, looking at something that only they can see.
They are a version exclusive Pokémon and are only obtainable in Pokémon Black version.</description>
<picture>243499.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27397" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Gothimiru</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gothorita, known as the Manipulate Pokémon, is a human-like, little girlish Pokémon, with purple skin, black hair, and black and white clothing. Gothorita often use hypnosis to control Pokémon and people alike, leading them astray. While charging up their power by starlight, they mark the star`s positions with floating stones.</description>
<picture>243500.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27399" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Unilan</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Solosis, known as the Cell Pokémon, is a small green Pokémon surrounded in a green gel, with a red mouth, and a yellow spring-like figure coming out of its head. They can survive in any environment because of their body`s special liquid envelope. They can use telepathy to talk with others, and drive away attackers by unleashing psychic power.
They are a version exclusive Pokémon and are only obtainable in Pokémon White version.</description>
<picture>243502.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27400" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Doublan</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Duosion is known as the Mitosis Pokémon. It is a small,green, circle Pokémon surrounded in green gel. It has a floating portion on top of its main `body`. That is its second brain. When their brains, now divided in two, are thinking the same thoughts, these Pokémon exhibit their maximum power, and since they have two divided brains, at times they suddenly try to take two different actions at once.</description>
<picture>243503.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27401" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Lanculus</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Reuniclus, known as the Multilplying Pokémon, has a pale-colored inner body that is encapsulated within a blob of a translucent, green gel-like substance. Reuniclus can increase their psychic powers by linking their brains with others in a network. They join this network by shaking hands with others. With high intelligence, it fights by manipulating its arms with a grip that can crush rocks.
IGN compared it to "experiments from the Lilo and Stitch TV series", and also noting "It`s like a cute baby version of the X-Men villain, Holocaust". Game Informer`s Jeff Marchiafava called it "amazing", stating "Nintendo can even make a friggin` nucleus look cute!".</description>
<picture>243504.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27426" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Shibishirasu</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tynamo, known as the Electric Eel Pokémon. It is based on young electric eels and lampreys. A single Tynamo`s electrical power is tiny, but when a group comes together, that power is "as mighty as thunder". These Pokémon move in schools. They have an electricity-generating organ, so they discharge electricity if in danger.</description>
<picture>243523.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27427" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Shibibeel</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Eelektrik, known as the Electric Fish Pokémon, is the evolution of Tynamo. It is also based on electric eels and lampreys. They coil around foes and shock them with electricity-generating organs that seem simply to be circular patterns. These Pokémon have a big appetite. When they spot their prey, they attack it and paralyze it with electricity.</description>
<picture>243524.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27435" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Tunbear</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Beartic, known as the Freeze Pokémon, is an Ice-type Pokémon and the evolution of Cubchoo. It resembles a polar bear, standing on two legs, with large black nails, thick white fur, and has fangs made of ice. Their habitat is in the cold lands of the north, usually near the water, where they can prey upon aquatic creatures. It can be aggressive while protecting its Cubchoo offspring and can use its breath to freeze objects.</description>
<picture>243535.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27439" type="appears in" update="2020-01-07">
<name>Muggyo</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Stunfisk is a dual-type Ground/Electric Pokémon introduced in Generation V.
It is not known to evolve into or from any other Pokémon.
In Galar, Stunfisk has a Ground/Steel-type regional form.
Stunfisk is a flat, fish-like Pokémon with a broad, mud-brown body. At the base of its yellow tail is a yellow marking shaped like an exclamation mark when seen from behind. It has small, horizontal, oval-shaped eyes, white with a tiny black pupil and no irises. Almost exactly between these two eyes lies the two thick gray lips that form its mouth. It has two small, flimsy fins at the sides of its body; each with two lobes. It has been seen to leap into the air and flap its fins as if they`re wings to remain airborne.
Stunfisk`s very tough skin keeps them unharmed if stepped on, even by sumo wrestlers. To exploit this, it buries itself in mud of the seashore and waits for prey to pass by. Whenever unsuspecting prey touch a Stunfisk`s body, it is zapped. Stunfisk smiles when electrocuting its foes. If it cannot paralyze its foe, it contorts itself with unexpected speed and flops away.
Galarian Stunfisk is grayish-brown, with three green markings similar to footprints on its body. It cannot generate electricity, but the high iron content of the mud it lives in has strengthened its fins, which have been adapted into an apparatus akin to a bear trap. Galarian Stunfisk leaves its red and white lips visible to lure in prey, and then slams its fins shut on them so they cannot escape. It is the only known Pokémon capable of using the move Snap Trap.</description>
<picture>68390.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="27447" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Buffron</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bouffalant, known as the Headbutt Bull Pokémon, is a large, brown buffalo Pokémon. It features a large, magnificent afro on its head with two equally large horns popping out of it. Each horn has two golden rings on it. It has light brown hair ending at its knees. Even if it is dealt with a violent headbutt, its tufty fur absorbs the damage. It charges and headbutts anything indiscriminately. The destructive power will derail a running train.
The Escapist listed Bouffalant as one of the new Pokémon with "really cool designs", describing it as "the afro-sporting bison".</description>
<picture>243546.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27448" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Washibon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rufflet, known as the Eaglet Pokémon, is the pre-evolution of Braviary. As the name of its species suggests, Rufflet is a male-only avian Pokémon that resembles an eaglet. Most of his body color, including his wings, is dark blue, but his head is covered with a thick, fuzzy white down. There is a red &amp; white colored feather on his head. He has large yellow feet tipped with black talons, and his beak is also yellow. He will valiantly fight any Pokémon that attacks and not give up until it wins. He will use his talons to crush Berries, and he is capable of using many aerial and wind-based attacks. He is exclusively found in Pokémon White. Rufflet live in rugged, mountainous habitat and around gorges. Its name means "a rough eaglet".</description>
<picture>243547.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27449" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Warrgle</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Braviary, known as the Valor Pokémon, is an eagle-like Pokémon, sporting red, blue, and yellow coloration. The top part of his body and wings are red, while the underside is blue. Braviary`s tail is red, with yellow and blue stripes at the end. His talons and beak are yellow, and his feathery mane is white. Braviary is a male-only species, with his female counterpart being the vulture-like Pokémon, Mandibuzz. Braviary will fight for his comrades without a second thought for danger. He can dance through the skies while grasping an automobile. A soldier of the skies with dauntless courage, it will get more respect from its comrades the more wounds it has. Braviary are exclusively male.
In the video games, Braviary can only be found in the Pokémon White. In the Pokémon Adventures manga, Black owns a Braviary named War. War is strong and can lift Black into the sky with ease, making him useful for flying purposes.
Game Informer`s Jeff Marchiafava praised Braviary`s name, stating "Finally, a pun that doesn`t suck!", and said "Everything about this 90 pound, ass-kicking bird makes me happy." In a poll by Official Nintendo Magazine, Braviary was voted as one of the best Pokémon from Black and White. Editor Thomas East stated that "Braviary is one of the best looking birds of any Generation".</description>
<picture>243548.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27451" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Vulgina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mandibuzz, known as the Bone Vulture Pokémon, are a female only species that resembles turkey vultures. They decorate themselves with bones; one sits in their hair, while another hangs around their waist. While soaring in the sky, Mandibuzz strike weakened Pokémon, and grab weakened prey with their talons. They haul them to their nest made of bones.
They are version exclusive, and only appear in Pokémon Black version.</description>
<picture>243550.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27452" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Kuitaran</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Heatmor is a Fire-Type Pokémon that resembles an anteater. It is notorious for its appetite of Durant, and it can burn Durant`s shells to eat them with its high-temperature tongue. It has a beige face while the rest of its fur is red with yellow stripes sharing appearance of molten lava. On its lower abdomen, back, and underside are raised, beige colored bands which resemble pipes, leading to its tail. Its claws, on both its feet and hands, are a dull yellow and on its wrists are raised, dented bands; both the wrists and feet are beige-colored. Its tail is dented upward and has a hole in it, similar in appearance to a muffler.</description>
<picture>243551.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27458" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Ulgamoth</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Volcarona is a large moth-like Pokémon, that is heavily inspired in appearance by Hathor and an Atlas Moth. In the Pokédex entry, a mythological account tells of a volcano`s ash darkening the sun, and Volcarona`s flames providing a replacement of light. Other facts such as its title as "Sun Pokémon", and the fact it dwells in-game within an abandoned sun temple in a desert, imply it is a solar deity akin to the Egyptian sun god Ra.
One can be found sealed off at the end of a deep maze in the Relic Castle after defeating Team Plasma and talking to one of the Seven Sages who was planning to capture it for his lord, Ghetsis. A Volcarona is used by Pokémon League Champion, Alder. The Pokémon BW: Rival Destinies episode "Guarding the Guardian of the Mountain!" prominently features Volcarona as the protector of a sacred mountain.</description>
<picture>243557.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27462" type="appears in" update="2020-01-07">
<name>Tornelos</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tornadus is known as the Cyclone Pokémon. He is based on Fuujin, the god of wind.[citation needed] He is the first pure Flying-type Pokémon. Tornadus can only be encountered in Pokémon Black, after being seen causing massive storms all throughout the Unova region. Once seen at least once, it roams flying throughout the rest of the Unova region, waiting for its capture or defeat. The lower half of its body is covered in a cloud of energy. It zooms through the sky at 200 mph.
It was said to have been banished by Landorus after it and Thundurus were seen causing violent thunderstorms throughout the Unova Region.
Tornadus gains an alternate form in the upcoming games Pokémon Black 2 and White 2 after being obtained in the side game Pokémon Dream Radar (known in Japan as Pokémon AR Searcher). Tornadus`s Therian Forme resembles a bird, and its original form is called the Incarnate Forme.</description>
<picture>64394.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="27463" type="appears in" update="2020-01-07">
<name>Voltolos</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Thundurus is known as the Bolt Strike Pokémon. He is based on Raijin, the god of thunder and lightning. Thundurus can only be encountered in Pokémon White, after being seen causing massive thunderstorms around the Unova region. After it has been encountered once, it roams freely throughout the entire region until it is finally captured or defeated. The spikes on its tail discharge immense bolts of lightning. It flies around the Unova region firing off lightning bolts.
It was said to have been banished by Landorus after it and Tornadus were seen causing violent thunderstorms throughout the Unova Region.
Thundurus gains an alternate form in the upcoming games Pokémon Black 2 and White 2 after being obtained in the side game Pokémon Dream Radar (known in Japan as Pokémon AR Searcher). Thundurus`s Therian Forme resembles a dragon, and its original form is called the Incarnate Forme.</description>
<picture>64395.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="27495" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-10-27">
<name>Zuruggu (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ash met Kikuyo who runs a Pokémon Day Care near Shippo City where she watches over Pokémon eggs. As thanks for helping out her granddaughter Yuri (Isshu) sort out her kindergarten class, she gave Ash a Pokémon egg. Kikuyo told Ash to raise it well so that it would be a great Pokémon. That Pokémon egg later hatched into Ash`s Zuruggu while Ash was en-route to Castelia City.
While resting, Iris`s Kibago noticed that the egg was beginning to glow but got too excited and caused the egg to fall down the nearby cliff and almost get smashed by a rock. Thankfully, Pikachu`s Quick Attack was fast enough to rescue the egg in time. After hatching, Ash`s Zuruggu`s initial attitude was very overbearing as Pikachu attempted to greet it but it used headbutt on Pikachu. Ash then sent out his other Pokémon but Ash`s Zuruggu ended up fighting them as well. Ash tried to capture it after battling his other Pokémon but it refused to be caught by him at that time.
After its encounter with a group of Dentula, Ash`s other Pokémon came to Ash`s Zuruggu rescue as it was greatly over matched. Ash could tell that it was beginning to trust him. Dent then suggested that Ash`s Zuruggu battle Iris`s Kibago as all the other Pokémon were too strong. Both Pokémon agreed but they ended up knocking each other out at the same time. Ash`s Zuruggu was finally caught after the battle as it had grown to like Ash.</description>
<picture>64406.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30495" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-13">
<name>Emonga (Iris)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Iris`s Emolga is a very sly and sneak Pokémon who likes to think things through before it decides upon taking any action. It uses its Attract move to its advantage as it`s a good way to convince other Pokémon to agree with it once they have fallen under the influence of the attack.
Iris and friends first encountered it when Iris`s Axew lost one of the apples it was eating and chased it down the hill. Iris ran after get Kibago only to come across the Emonga who had picked up the apple Iris`s Axew was chasing after. Iris`s Emolga noticed that Iris was carrying a lot more apples and realized that if it returned the one apple to Iris`s Axew that Iris might reward it by giving it a lot more of the apples she was carrying.
Bianca who was with Iris and friends at the time, quickly fell in love with the Emonga and wanted to catch it but after an uncomfortable hug, Emonga quickly learned that it didn`t want to be caught by Bianca and it shocked her. Still determined to capture it, Bianca followed it for a while until Emonga finally made its intentions clear that it wanted to be caught by Iris. Iris`s Emolga jumped into Iris`s arms and then allowed itself to be caught by her Poké Ball.
Don George Tournament - Raimon Town
Stephan`s Sawk battled against Iris`s Emolga in the second round of the Don George Battle Tournament in Raimon Town but Emonga`s Static ability proved to be the deciding factor in the match. The Static ability ended up paralyzing Stephan`s Sawk and it was then a sitting target for Iris`s Emolga`s Volt Switch which knocked it out. Iris`s Emolga`s win eliminated Stephan from the tournament.</description>
<picture>68629.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40474" type="appears in" update="2012-02-09">
<name>Dread Grangil</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Damon is one of the few descendants of the People of the Vale. As a young boy, he and his mother, Juanita, travelled to the ruins of his people`s kingdom. Juanita expressed her wish that their old home would be resurrected, which inspired Damon. He searched for Victini in hopes of resurrecting his people`s old kingdom by using Victini`s power.</description>
<picture>81218.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40475" type="appears in" update="2012-02-09">
<name>Janta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Juanita is Damon and Carlita`s mother. She sells Victini keepsakes and souvenirs at a small shop in Eindoak Town. She originally supported Damon`s plan to resurrect the Kingdom of the Vale, but then tried to stop him when she realized the effect it took on Victini.</description>
<picture>81219.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40476" type="appears in" update="2012-02-09">
<rating votes="2">6.08</rating>
<name>Carlita</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Carlita is Damon`s younger sister. She is also a Pokémon trainer that competed in the Harvest Festival battle tournament in Eindoak Town. She quickly defeated Cilan with her Hydreigon, but was defeated in the next round by Ash and his Scraggy. When Carlita and Hydreigon looked as if they were going to win, Victini helped by lending power to Scraggy, who then defeated Hydreigon.
After losing, she befriended the gang and told them about the history behind Victini. They also befriended Victini and Carlita helped attempt to save it from Damon`s plan to use its power.</description>
<picture>81220.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40477" type="appears in" update="2012-02-09">
<name>Momont</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mannes is the mayor of Eindoak Town. He is also a descendent of the People of the Vale. He informs Ash, Iris, and Cilan of the town`s history as well as the People of the Vale.</description>
<picture>81221.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40478" type="appears in" update="2012-02-08">
<name>Manouque</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Manouque is a young man living in a village in the wilderness where the People of the Earth eventually settled. He joins Shade and Kajin as they travel to Eindoak to assist Damon in his plan.</description>
<picture>81222.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40479" type="appears in" update="2012-02-08">
<name>Kajin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kajin is the head of a village in the wilderness where the People of the Earth eventually settled. He joins Shade and Manouque as they travel to Eindoak to assist Damon in his plan.</description>
<picture>81223.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40480" type="appears in" update="2012-02-08">
<name>Shade</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shade is a little girl living in a village in the wilderness where the People of the Earth eventually settled. She befriended Damon when he saved her Shimama, and later joins Manouque and Kajin as they travel to Eindoak to assist him in his plan.</description>
<picture>81224.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40481" type="appears in" update="2012-02-08">
<name>Dunouque</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dunouque is a young man living in a village in the tundra where the People of the Earth eventually settled. He joins Aude and Yajin as they travel to Eindoak to assist Damon in his plan.</description>
<picture>81225.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40482" type="appears in" update="2012-02-08">
<name>Aude</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aude is a little boy living in a village in the tundra where the People of the Earth eventually settled. He befriended Damon when he saved him from an iceberg, and later joins Dunouque and Yajin as they travel to Eindoak to assist him in his plan.</description>
<picture>81226.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40483" type="appears in" update="2012-02-08">
<name>Yajin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yajin is the head of a village in the tundra where the People of the Earth eventually settled. She joins Aude and Dunouque as they travel to Eindoak to assist Damon in his plan.</description>
<picture>81227.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40484" type="appears in" update="2012-02-08">
<name>Mako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mako participated in the Eindoak Harvest Festival Commemoration Battle, and was defeated by Ash.</description>
<picture>81228.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40485" type="appears in" update="2012-02-08">
<name>Jalorda (Mako)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mako`s Serperior was defeated by Pikachu in the Eindoak Harvest Festival Commemoration Battle.</description>
<picture>81229.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40486" type="appears in" update="2012-02-08">
<name>Tatsuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tatsuki participated in the Eindoak Harvest Festival Commemoration Battle. He defeated Iris, but was then defeated by Ash.</description>
<picture>81230.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40487" type="appears in" update="2012-02-08">
<name>Enbuoh (Tatsuki)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tatsuki`s Emboar defeated Iris`s Emolga in the Eindoak Harvest Festival Commemoration Battle, before getting defeated by Ash`s Oshawott.</description>
<picture>81231.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40488" type="appears in" update="2012-02-08">
<name>Leak</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leak participated in the Eindoak Harvest Festival Commemoration Battle, and was defeated by Ash.</description>
<picture>81232.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40489" type="appears in" update="2012-02-08">
<name>Daikenki (Leak)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leak`s Samurott was defeated by Ash`s Tepig in the Eindoak Harvest Festival Commemoration Battle.</description>
<picture>81233.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40490" type="appears in" update="2012-02-08">
<name>Giaru (Momont)</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mannes` Klink is used in combination with his other Gear Pokémon evolutions to power his flying machine and his instrument.</description>
<picture>81234.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40491" type="appears in" update="2012-02-08">
<name>Gigiaru (Momont)</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mannes` Klang is used in combination with his other Gear Pokémon evolutions to power his flying machine and his instrument.</description>
<picture>81235.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40492" type="appears in" update="2012-02-08">
<name>Gigigiaru (Momont)</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mannes` Klinklang is used in combination with his other Gear Pokémon evolutions to power his flying machine and his instrument.</description>
<picture>81236.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40493" type="appears in" update="2012-02-08">
<name>Lanculus (Dread Grangil)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Damon`s Reuniclus is only seen in the Zekrom movie. It traveled with him in the wilderness and tried to protect Victini from being freed when Pikachu and Ash attempted to free it.</description>
<picture>81238.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40494" type="appears in" update="2012-02-08">
<name>Symboler (Dread Grangil)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Damon`s Sigilyph was used to control the Sword Castle while it moved in the air. It helped focus the energy from Victini to power the movements of the Sword Castle.</description>
<picture>81239.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40495" type="appears in" update="2012-02-08">
<name>Gothiruselle (Dread Grangil)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Damon`s Gothitelle is only seen in the Reshiram movie. It traveled with him to the icelands and tried to protect Victini from being freed when Pikachu and Ash attempted to free it.</description>
<picture>81240.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40497" type="appears in" update="2012-02-08">
<name>Sazandora (Carlita)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Carlita used her Hydreigon in the Eindoak Town Harvest Festival Battle Tournament. In the Zekrom movie, Hydreigon is alternate colored but in the Reshiram movie it is normally colored.</description>
<picture>81241.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40498" type="appears in" update="2012-02-08">
<rating votes="2">1.10</rating>
<name>Golugh (Janta)</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Juanita`s Golurk is Juanita main Pokémon and partner that assists her with her stand in Eindoak Town. In the Reshiram movie, Juanita`s Golurk is Alternate Colored while in the Zekrom movie it is normally colored.</description>
<picture>81242.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="61714" type="appears in" update="2013-11-21">
<name>Ou-sama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146175.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="130958" update="2011-12-10">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>100</length>
<airdate>2011-07-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131094" update="2011-06-23">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131095" update="2011-06-23">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134609" update="2011-11-04">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Next Episode Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134786" update="2011-11-12">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>6</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Extended Trailer</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
