<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8287" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-04-08</startdate>
<enddate>2011-07-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hen Semi (2011)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Abnormal Physiology Seminar (TV)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Hen Zemi (2011)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Hen Semi TV</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">変ゼミ (2011)</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7431" type="Other">Hen Semi</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="5587" approval="2" total="7">Detroit Metal City</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="126709">This series is a loose psychological study/comedy of sexual deviancy, and the character designs lend a lot to the appeal. Many people will be grossed out, but as this isn`t a hentai most of the topics are talked about with comical visual analogs and not in vivid detail. 

I enjoyed it, and I`d watch more of it, but there`s very little in the way of an evolving story line so it`s difficult to recommend people stick with it as there`s no real pay off. Definitely watch the OVA first to see if you`re going to enjoy the entire series.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="558440">You know what I felt after completing this anime? It felt something like, after 19 years of being a NEET, you`ve finally got yourself a girlfriend. A perfect girlfriend. The one you`ve always dream`t and jacked off to [imaginatively].

Then one day, she asked you if you want to do it with her. But shit. Heaven shit. You lost your dick. For whatever reason, your dick disappeared. Don`t ask me where it went into. It just did.

I could cry tears of blood now.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="455194">Im not done yet, but the first few episedes were great so far.
If you are at least a litte perverted, you will have you laught.
and W(hy)TF does the Professor`s face look like it looks?!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="394403">Absolutely hilarious and extremely disturbing on multiple levels!! hahaha you have got to see this assuming you dont mind disturbing content.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://kc.kodansha.co.jp/hensemi/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3326" type="Music">Yokoyama Masaru</name>
<name id="719" type="Animation Work">Xebec</name>
<name id="7475" type="Character Design">Chikaoka Sunao</name>
<name id="17317" type="Original Work">Tagro</name>
<name id="682" type="Direction">Kato Takao</name>
<name id="21630" type="Chief Animation Direction">Watanabe Masanori</name>
<name id="3662" type="Series Composition">Kouno Takamitsu</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr17317 [Tagro]`s risqué comedy manga series Hen Semi, serialised in Morning 2.
http://anidb.net/ch17280 [Matsutaka Nanako] is a normal university student, who happens to enroll in the Abnormal Physiology Seminar. She tries to keep her mental state sound, but other abnormal classmates start to influence her personality...</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1203">4.19</permanent>
<temporary count="1212">6.17</temporary>
<review count="1">5.50</review>
</ratings>
<picture>66233.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12333</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10187</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4883</identifier>
<identifier>ovsoej</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://kc.kodansha.co.jp/hensemi/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Hen_Zemi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>変ゼミ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2113</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>339216</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13436</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="235" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-05">
<name>waitress</name>
<description>A female attendant who serves customers in a restaurant, café, or similar.
Source: Wiktionary</description>
<picurl>163704.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="520" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-14">
<name>nopan</name>
<description>The character foregoes underwear.</description>
<picurl>162753.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2072" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>maid</name>
<description>A maid is a female employed in domestic service. They usually wear uniforms. Since their nature is to be obedient and serve their goshujin-sama (master), they are one of the most desired types of women in Japan, a dream of every Japanese man, particularly http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku]. Often seen in so-called Maid Cafes in Akihabara, where male customers can for a little time enjoy the feeling of being served by a woman. The male gender opposite is the butler.</description>
<picurl>4954.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2667" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>university</name>
<description>Since college/university students are typically at least eighteen years old, with stories covering mature everyday life topics, you will find the college setting quite often in seinen and josei anime.
Topics that can now be covered - as compared to High School settings - are higher education (i.e. coping with higher intellectual stress), the more adult party life (i.e. alcohol, smoking, sex), the issues of daily life vs. studying - especially when having to work to pay for bills, and finally the possible friction between those in and out of college.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2703" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>wakamezake</name>
<description>Wakamezake is a sexual act in which sake is poured into the valley that appears in a woman`s lap when her legs are closed. Her partner then drinks the sake from there. The word may also be used to refer to the sake which is drunk in this act. The name derives from the idea that the woman`s pubic hair in the sake is supposed to resemble soft seaweed (wakame) floating in the ocean.</description>
<picurl>161634.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2725" parentid="2848" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-20">
<name>ahegao</name>
<description>A term for the weird face occasionally seen in adult games/anime/manga. Canonically, ahegao has eyes rolled up, mouth open and tongue sticking out. Sometimes also referred to as "fucked silly".</description>
<picurl>175637.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2828" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-26">
<name>borderline porn</name>
<description>Breaks the bounds of "excessive fanservice".
While the physical interactions and dialogue between characters may be extremely sexual, the most sexual situations do *not* have sex itself take place.
Specifically descriptive of containing all the plentiful features of (excessive) fanservice in addition to the interactions between characters being quite sexual — at most, sexual in NATURE only. This means physical touching such as groping, molesting, or bondage will focus primarily on the revealed (i.e. nude) upper portion of the body or through/over clothing on the lower half of the body. This is all WITHOUT actual sex acts (penetration, etc.) taking place.</description>
<picurl>214855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2889" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>nyotaimori</name>
<description>Nyotaimori (女体盛り, "female body presentation"), often referred to as "body sushi", is the practice of serving sashimi or sushi from the body of a woman, typically naked.</description>
<picurl>148623.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6115" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-02">
<name>omimai</name>
<description>Visiting a sick person (as in a hospital or at home).
The protagonist or any other character caught a cold so his friends go visit him. In a school setting this is used as a plot device to allow fellow students to show their concern, and it is also a pertinent excuse to get out of school.</description>
<picurl>160896.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6494" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>half-length episodes</name>
<description>Half-length episodes are regular episodes that are somewhat shorter than the standard length. This includes episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length; shows with episodes up to and including 10 minutes are http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes] instead.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="17280" type="main character in" update="2010-04-30">
<rating votes="26">6.83</rating>
<name>Matsutaka Nanako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47188.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17281" type="main character in" update="2010-04-30">
<rating votes="23">3.79</rating>
<name>Musashi Komugi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47189.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17282" type="main character in" update="2010-04-30">
<rating votes="27">4.64</rating>
<name>Mizukoshi Miwako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47190.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6305" picture="223494.jpg">Takaguchi Yukiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17283" type="main character in" update="2010-04-30">
<rating votes="28">7.71</rating>
<name>Makiko Gregory</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47191.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1528" picture="223648.jpg">Kawaragi Shiho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17284" type="main character in" update="2010-04-30">
<rating votes="17">3.29</rating>
<name>Ichikawa Hishiyasu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47193.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3140" picture="24125.jpg">Mori Norihisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17285" type="main character in" update="2010-04-30">
<rating votes="16">2.26</rating>
<name>Taguchi Yesterday</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47194.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="434" picture="41082.jpg">Shiraishi Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17286" type="main character in" update="2010-04-30">
<rating votes="20">1.83</rating>
<name>Meshiya Kenji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47195.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="293" picture="185431.jpg">Matsuyama Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29057" type="main character in" update="2011-05-03">
<rating votes="22">5.63</rating>
<name>Katou Anna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70857.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="357" picture="32000.jpg">Shintani Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="128664" update="2011-03-23">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-04-08</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">不偏論者たちから見た世界の事象に関する考察</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Study of Wordly Events as Seen by the Advocates of Universalism</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuhen-ron-sha-tachi Kara Mita Sekai no Jishou ni Kansuru Kousatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129297" update="2011-04-19">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">食と嗜好から見る快楽様相に関する考察</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Observing Pleasure Caused By Food and One`s Tastes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoku to Shikou kara Miru Kairaku Yousou ni Kansuru Kousatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129436" update="2011-04-19">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">家族機能が人格形成に与える影響に関する考察</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Observations on the Effects of Family Functions on the Development of Personality</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kazoku Kinou ga Jinkaku Keisei ni Ataeru Eikyou ni Kansuru Kousatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129437" update="2011-04-19">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">集団への奉仕者とそれを受容する側の幸福感の差異に関する考察</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Observations on the Difference of Happiness of Those Serving the Group and Those Receiving That Service</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuudan e no Houshi-sha to Sore o Juyousuru Gawa no Koufuku-kan no Sai ni Kansuru Kousatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129438" update="2011-04-19">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">社会的比較における貞操観念に関する考察</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Observations on the Concept of Virtue Based on Social Comparison</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shakai-teki Hikaku ni okeru Teisou Kannen ni Kansuru Kousatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129756" update="2011-05-02">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-04-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129757" update="2011-05-02">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-04-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130010" update="2011-05-10">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-05-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">極限状態における衝動行為と脅迫行為に関する考察</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Observations on Impulsive and Threatening Actions in Extreme Situations</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyokugen Joutai ni Okeru Shoudou Koui to Kyouhaku Koui ni Kansuru Kousatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130087" update="2011-05-10">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-06-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">主観的自己観察の結果と自己開示に関する考察</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Observations on the Results of Subjective Self-Inspection and Self-Release</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shukan-teki Jiko Kansatsu no Kekka to Jiko Kaiji ni Kansuru Kousatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130088" update="2011-05-10">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幼児体験が与える特質的性質と自己成長感に関する考察</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Observations on the Effects of Childhood Experiences on Personality Traits and the Feeling of Self-Development</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youji Taiken ga Ataeru Tokushitsu-teki Seishitsu to Jiko Seichou-kan ni Kansuru Kousatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130089" update="2011-05-10">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">特定の人間関係へ向ける依存性と信頼性の関係に関する考察</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Observations on the Relationship of Dependence and Trust in Specific Human Relations</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokutei no Ningen Kankei e Mukeru Izon-sei to Shinrai-sei no Kankei ni Kansuru Kousatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130668" update="2011-06-12">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-06-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">間接的な接触による心理的影響に関する考察</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Observations on the Psycholocigal Effects of Indirect Interactions</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kansetsu-teki na Sesshoku ni Yoru Shinri-teki Eikyou ni Kansuru Kousatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130791" update="2011-06-10">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">不偏論者たちが抱く『愛』に関する考察</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Observations on Impartial Advocates Harbouring `Love`</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuhen-ron-sha-tachi ga Idaku "Ai" ni Kansuru Kousatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130792" update="2011-06-10">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">特定の人物からの愛情表現への対処行動に関する考察</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Observations on Coping With a Particular Expression of Love From Someone</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokutei no Jinbutsu kara no Aijou Hyougen e no Taisho Koudou ni Kansuru Kousatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130793" update="2011-06-12">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-06-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">抑制された欲求が及ぼす心理的及び身体的効果に関する考察</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Observations on the Psychological and Physical Effects of Suppressed Desires</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yokuseisareta Yokkyuu ga Oyobosu Shinri-teki Oyobi Shintai-teki Kouka ni Kansuru Kousatsu</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
