<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8290" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-03-16</startdate>
<enddate>2011-03-16</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Spelunker-sensei</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Spelunker Is a Teacher</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">スペランカー先生</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="7318" approval="7" total="7">Boku, Otaryman.</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="553382">The entirety of this OVA is based on the old school NES game Spelunker. If you don`t know about it, then this OVA is going to be the worst thing ever. If you want to gain any enjoyment from this, you`re going to have to take the effort to learn a little bit about the game, and even then it`s a 4-koma style comedy that`s not for everyone. Watch with caution.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.enterbrain.co.jp/cp/spelunker/</url>
<creators>
<name id="21007" type="Direction">Ashina Minoru</name>
<name id="23382" type="Animation Work">Studio Pu Yukai</name>
<name id="23384" type="Music">Micky Miki</name>
<name id="21054" type="Character Design">Takehara Minoru</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch29549 [Spelunker-sensei] is a school teacher who dies even when he catches a cold or slips and falls on the ground. The anime follows his everyday interactions with his colleagues and students.
— written by Singan
Note: the main character is a parody on the protagonist of the NES platform game Spelunker.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="236">2.20</permanent>
<temporary count="237">4.63</temporary>
<review count="1">1.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>66236.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12363</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10406</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.enterbrain.co.jp/cp/spelunker/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>スペランカー#.E3.82.B9.E3.83.9A.E3.83.A9.E3.83.B3.E3.82.AB.E3.83.BC.E5.85.88.E7.94.9F_.E3.83.95.E3.83.A9.E3.83.83.E3.82.B7.E3.83.A5.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1DVD</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>338781</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2069" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-15">
<name>delinquent</name>
<description>Delinquents - Every school has them, but not all anime with school setting make delinquents a central topic. There are several versions of these delinquents, though some are grounded on a misunderstanding:
* The student with a really bad image and attitude, based on his real criminal actions outside of the school and is even feared by teachers.
* The primitive "class bully" that pushes around ("clobbers") his classmates for no apparent reason, possibly extorting lunch money.
* The student with an sinister complexion or "evil eye", but is actually a "good" student (unfoundedly feared character).
* The rebellious student, who does not care for studying, but is otherwise docile. Called a "delinquent" as a joke.</description>
<picurl>243713.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2805" parentid="2798" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>4-koma manga</name>
<description>Yonkoma manga (4コマ漫画, four cell manga, or 4-koma for short), a comic-strip format, generally consists of gag comic strips within four panels of equal size ordered from top to bottom. (They also sometimes run right-to-left horizontally or use a hybrid 2x2 style, depending on the layout requirements of the publication in which they appear.) Though the word yonkoma comes from the Japanese, the style also exists outside of Japan in other Asian countries as well as in the English-speaking market.</description>
<picurl>70558.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3265" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-09">
<name>death is cheap</name>
<description>Important characters will have a terrible tendency to die dramatically, but will not, under any circumstances, stay dead. This tends to cheapen the dramatic death of a character to the point of being little more than a flesh wound if overused. If you ever hear passing mention of any form of afterlife in a series, be warned that the value of "dead" has become a whole lot less all of a sudden. Similarly, if the entire supporting cast is being killed off left and right, expect a resurrection by the end of the current arc. This trope became so common in some series that most people are more likely to be shocked if a character does not come back from the dead than when it does.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3870" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2016-09-11">
<name>resurrection</name>
<description>At least one character in this anime is brought back from the dead or from a near-death experience. This is achieved by either very advanced technology or simply magic.</description>
<picurl>191152.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4148" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-11">
<name>late for school</name>
<description>A common device for a series opening or Establishing Character Moment. Things begin in a frantic rush which usually results in taking short cuts, such as eating breakfast on the run. The classic image is of someone running down the street with a slice of toast hanging out of their mouth, dragging their backpack with one hand while trying to put on their jacket or sweater one-handed with the other, bumping into important people in a manner that gets the plot started.
Basically, they`re never on time for school. While some are Heavy Sleepers, it would appear that they may have simply set their alarm clocks so as to give them insufficient time to get to class. 
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>161002.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4343" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2009-09-21">
<name>main character dies</name>
<description>At least one of the main characters in the anime dies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="29549" type="main character in" update="2011-06-14">
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<name>Spelunker-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Spelunker Sensei is an enigma -- an incredibly strong fighter, but at the same time, a man so frail that he dies when hit by a baseball, or if he jumps downhill.</description>
<picture>4297.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33421" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-14">
<rating votes="1">1.25</rating>
<name>Onna Sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4296.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="210" picture="71057.jpg">Ueda Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33422" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-14">
<rating votes="1">1.25</rating>
<name>Taiiku Kyoushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4298.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="371" picture="166173.jpg">Kuroda Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33423" type="appears in" update="2011-06-14">
<rating votes="1">1.25</rating>
<name>Takou Furyou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4299.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33424" type="appears in" update="2011-06-14">
<rating votes="2">2.71</rating>
<name>2-C Kano</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4300.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2291" picture="23193.jpg">Kano Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33425" type="appears in" update="2011-06-14">
<rating votes="1">1.25</rating>
<name>3-A Ichiki (Ani)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4301.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="71" picture="171537.jpg">Ichiki Mitsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33426" type="appears in" update="2011-06-14">
<rating votes="1">1.25</rating>
<name>2-C Ichiki (Oto)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4302.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="71" picture="171537.jpg">Ichiki Mitsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33427" type="appears in" update="2011-06-14">
<rating votes="2">2.66</rating>
<name>Waitress Joji</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4303.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2291" picture="23193.jpg">Kano Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33428" type="appears in" update="2011-06-14">
<rating votes="1">1.25</rating>
<name>3-A Morita</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4304.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="22376" picture="59159.jpg">Morita Noriaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33429" type="appears in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="1">1.25</rating>
<name>2-C Miyasaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>4305.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="4041" picture="26004.jpg">Miyasaka Shunzou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="128286" update="2011-02-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-03-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128986" update="2011-03-24">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128987" update="2011-03-24">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128988" update="2011-03-24">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128989" update="2011-03-24">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128990" update="2011-03-24">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128991" update="2011-03-24">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128992" update="2011-03-24">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
