<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8298" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>52</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-04-03</startdate>
<enddate>2012-04-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Metal Fight Beyblade 4D</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">メタルファイト ベイブレード4D</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">メタルファイト ベイブレード 4D</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Beyblade: Metal Fury</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Beyblade Metal Fury</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Beyblade Metal Fury</title>
<title xml:lang="el" type="official">Beyblade Metal Fury</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9048" type="Sequel">Metal Fight Beyblade Zero G</anime>
<anime id="7426" type="Prequel">Metal Fight Beyblade: Baku</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.at-x.com/program_detail/index.html/2719/</url>
<creators>
<name id="8666" type="Original Work">Adachi Takafumi</name>
<name id="1163" type="Animation Work">SynergySP</name>
<name id="4938" type="Character Design">Nagamori Yoshihiro</name>
<name id="4152" type="Series Composition">Hasegawa Katsumi</name>
<name id="4401" type="Direction">Sugishima Kunihisa</name>
<name id="45535" type="Music">Neil Parfitt</name>
</creators>
<description>Taking a break from their latest triumph over Faust and the Spiral Core, Ginga and his friends find themselves saving a boy named Yuuki from a mysterious boy named Johannes. Although Yuuki is a boy genius and an astronomer, he is a Blader who owns Anubius. Yuuki says that he has come to tell Ginga and his friends about the voice of the Star Fragment, and that it must not fall into the hands of evil. He witnessed the Star Fragment fall from the sky one day. That single light dwells within Anubius and he says that he heard the voice of the Star Fragment that evening. A great evil is trying to revive the Black Sun and the Nemesis, the Greek goddess of Revenge, by using the unknown power of the Star Fragment, and destroy the world. They must find the ten legendary bladers (The four seasons is Ginga, Kyouya, Ryuga, (Kenta) and Chris. The five solor sestem bey legendary bladerers Yuuki, King, Aguma, Tiphi, and Dynamies. the one who has Nemesis is Rago.) in order to prevent Nemesis from reviving. In the end, Ginga defeats the God of Destruction with a new special move, Super Cosmic Nova.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="66">3.66</permanent>
<temporary count="71">5.63</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>170624.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12918</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10370</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.at-x.com/program_detail/index.html/2719/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2169</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>339221</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13440</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2863" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>proxy battles</name>
<description>In our terms, a proxy battle is a battle where humans use creatures/robots to do the fighting for them, either by commanding those creatures/robots or by simply evolving them/changing them into battle mode. Often the training aspect is also involved, or in some cases the proxies are nothing more than holographic representatives of some other variation of competition (like for example a card game). While many popular shounen anime fit under this category, it`s not limited to shounen anime.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="6344" type="main character in" update="2009-04-20">
<rating votes="4">1.56</rating>
<name>Hagane Ginga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23650.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2980" picture="147242.jpg">Kanada Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6345" type="main character in" update="2009-04-20">
<rating votes="3">1.63</rating>
<name>Tategami Kyouya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23652.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6346" type="main character in" update="2009-04-20">
<rating votes="3">1.63</rating>
<name>Yumiya Kenta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23653.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6347" type="main character in" update="2009-04-20">
<rating votes="12">4.47</rating>
<name>Amano Madoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23654.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="453" picture="45925.jpg">Shindou Kei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6349" type="main character in" update="2009-04-20">
<rating votes="4">1.63</rating>
<name>Benkei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23656.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29785" type="main character in" update="2011-10-28">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Mizusawa Yuuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2013.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2505" picture="141583.jpg">Makiguchi Mayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="128762" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">星の欠片</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Star Fragment</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hoshi no Kakera</title>
<summary>When a star falls from the sky, a young blader named Yuki is waiting for it. He immediately sets out to find Gingka, but this proves difficult as Gingka has been lured into a battle on an island against his old rival Kyoya.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="129137" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">レジェンドブレーダー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Legendary Bladers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Legend Blader</title>
<summary>Yuki battles with a dark character named Johannes, but Gingka arrives and sends Johannes packing.  Yuki tells the gang the story of a recently fallen star that has chosen certain bladers to be known as Legendary Bladers.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="129443" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦士の資格</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Requirements of a Warrior</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senshi no Shikaku</title>
<summary>When a volcano erupts, Gingka, Yuki and Kyoya change the course of the lava by using their beys and save the village. They leave the island but are shocked when Kenta announces that he is heading out on his own.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="129444" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">覚醒! アヌビウス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Awaken, Anubis!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakusei! Anubis</title>
<summary>After Ryuga defeats Kyoya, Gingka challenges him to a bey battle, but Ryuga quickly defeats him too.  Yuki challenges him to yet another battle but his bey, Mercury Anubius, is battered again and again by Ryuga’s L-Drago Destructor.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="129445" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">エルドラゴデストロイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">L-Drago Destructor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">L-Drago Destroy</title>
<summary>While Gingka and the gang try to make friends, Benkei and Kyoya meet Ryuga at the top of a volcano and Kyoya challenges Ryuga to a bey battle.  Ryuga tells Kyoya that he should not be battling, that he doesn’t even know his bey yet.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="129446" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">怪猫リンクス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Monster Cat, Lynx</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaibyou Lynx</title>
<summary>Gingka and his friends are about to start their quest to find the 8 Legendary Bladers, but they run into Johannes and a battle ensues.  Things look bad for Gingka until Kyoya arrives and joins the battle, driving Johannes off.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="130098" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">新たなる咆哮!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A New Roar!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arata Naru Houkou!</title>
<summary>The Tag Team Tournament continues and the final four teams are determined.  The team of Dashan and Chiyun win their match quickly, but Kyoya and Benkei have a long battle with Motty and Johannes.  In the end Kyoya defeats Johannes to move on.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="130099" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">最強タッグ戦, 登竜門</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Greatest Tag-Team Tournament</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikyou Tag Sen, Douryuumon</title>
<summary>At the Tag Team Championship a series of battles occur in which Dashan and Chiyun are victorious as are Johannes and his new partner, Motty.  When Yuki and Gingka challenge Mei-Mei and Chaoxin, Yuki suffers a serious lack of confidence and almost gives up.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="130100" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">真紅の閃光</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Crimson Flash</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinkou no Senkou</title>
<summary>Johannes breaks into Beylin Temple and is confronted by Gingka and his friends.  Dashan engages the intruder in a bey battle but Johannes quits, claiming that Dashan is not a Legendary Blader and not worth his time.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="130101" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ケンタの決意</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kenta`s Determination</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kenta no Ketsui</title>
<summary>Kenta travels to a remote desert town where he competes against Ryuga in a tournament but loses. He then follows Ryuga on a difficult cross country trek, trying to convince Ryuga that he should lend his strength as a Legendary Blader to Gingka and the others.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="130685" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ビッグバントルネード</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cosmic Tornado</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Big Bang Tornado</title>
<summary>In the second Round of the Tag Team tournament, Gingka and Yuki face Dashan and Chiyun in a mountain top stadium.  Gingka and Yuki win when Gingka creates a new special move, Cosmic Tornado. Next up, it’s Beylin Fist against Kyoya and Benkei.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="130804" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-07-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">新生! チーム・ダンジョン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The New Team Dungeon!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinsei! Team Dungeon</title>
<summary>Aguma and Bao follow Johannes to meet Pluto, who wants Beylin Fist to join him in his dark quest for power. Gingka and his friends travel to Greece where they meet Sophie, Wales, Julian and Klaus.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="130805" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">対決! バベルの塔</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Showdown at the Tower of Babel!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiketsu! Babel no Tou</title>
<summary>After winning the Tag Team Tournament, Bao and Aguma disappear in a helicopter.  They are followed by Johannes into the wilderness where he says he has news about the star fragment in Aguma’s Bey.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="130806" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">土星神(どせいしん)クロノス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The God of Saturn, Kronos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Doseishin Chronos</title>
<summary>Ginka and Yuki travel to an ancient Bey Temple to battle Bao and Aguma of Beylin Fist in the final of the Toryumon Tag Team Tournament.  The Beylin Fist team starts strong and soon has Gingka and Yuki in a tough spot.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="131491" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-07-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スフィア360(スリーシックスゼロ)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Destroyer Dome</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sphere 360</title>
<summary>Masamune and his friends witness an argument amongst the Garcias before their match in the Destroyer Dome and it appears that the family is breaking apart.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="131747" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-08-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">獅子のプライド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Lion`s Pride</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shishi no Pride</title>
<summary>Ryuto leads Gingka and his friends into a temple on Mist Mountain in search of a Star Fragment.  They are unaware that they are being followed by Johannes and the bladers from Beylin Fist, who are also seeking the Fragment.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="131748" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-07-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミストマウンテンの迷宮</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Maze of Mist Mountain</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mist Mountain no Meikyuu</title>
<summary>Gingka and his friends travel to Africa in search of a Legendary Blader that they believe lives in a mysterious place called Mist Mountain. With their guides Nile and Damoure they climb the mountain and come to a maze that was built by an ancient people.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="131749" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-07-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">オレさまこそがチャンピオン!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Am The Champion!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore-sama Koso ga Champion!</title>
<summary>In the final of a battle royal in the Destroyer Dome, six bladers battle to see who will come out on top.  The bladers, King, Jigsaw, Zeo, Toby, tsubasa and Masamune give it their all.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="131750" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-07-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">完成! 新ユニコルノ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The New Striker is Complete!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kansei! Shin Unicorno</title>
<summary>Masamune and his new bey, Blitz Striker, battle against some old foes and new ones in the Destroyer Dome.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="132419" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-09-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ベイスター島の戦い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Battle of Beyster Island</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Beyster-tou no Tatakai</title>
<summary>Gingka and his friends arrive at Beyster Island where they have entered a tournament that has attracted a huge number of strong Bladers.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="132420" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-08-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">四季の戦士(ブレーダー)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Four Season Bladers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiki no Blader</title>
<summary>Dynamis tries to explain to Johannes and his followers that no matter what they do, the heavens will decide what will happen with the resurrection of Hades and Nemesis, not them. A battle ensues and every blader from each side joins in.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="132421" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-08-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ネメシス, 復活の伝説</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Legend of Nemesis`s Revival</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nemesis, Fukkatsu no Densetsu</title>
<summary>Gingka battles Dynamis the Guardian of the temple.  Gingka seems to have chosen the wrong strategy, but admits that he was too caught up in being a legendary Blader and says that he should have been paying more attention.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="132422" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-08-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">神殿の守護者デュナミス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Guardian of the Temple, Dynamis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinden no Shugosha Dynamis</title>
<summary>Gingka and the others reach a temple where they believe a star fragment lies but they cannot open a door that blocks their entrance.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="132890" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-09-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">激烈! 二大バトル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Two Big, Fierce Battles!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekiretsu! Ni Dai Battle</title>
<summary>As the battle of Beyster Island continues, many more bladers are knocked out of the competition.  Gingka catches up with Kenta only to find that he is his next opponent in the tournament.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="132891" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-09-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">姿なき対戦者(ブレーダー)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Unseen Opponent</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sugatanaki Blader</title>
<summary>The Beyster Island Tournament continues as an unseen Blader defeats contestant after contestant through a series of ambushes. When the Blader defeats Zeo and Toby, Masamune swears he will avenge them in the final.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="133023" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-10-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">怪物(モンスター)の正体</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Lion in the Wilderness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Monster no Shoutai</title>
<summary>Kyoya is ambushed by a group of bladers in the mountains but he defeats them all. They apologize, claiming they thought he was a monster that has been terrorizing their village.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="133024" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">荒野を行く獅子(しし)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Lion in the Wilderness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kouya o Iku Shishi</title>
<summary>Kyoya is ambushed by a group of bladers in the mountains but he defeats them all. They apologize, claiming they thought he was a monster that has been terrorizing their village.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="133025" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">オリオンの行方</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Orion`s Whereabouts</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Orion no Yukue</title>
<summary>Gingka asks Chris, the newest Legendary Blader, to join him in his fight against evil, but Chris says he will join whoever pays him the most.  King is enraged by this and Chris’ mocking of Masamune so King challenges him to a battle.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="133818" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-10-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">金星神ケツァルコアトル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The God of Venus, Quetzalcoatl</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kinseishin Quetzalcoatl</title>
<summary>Tithi and Yu agree to a bey battle in the ruins and Tithi proves to be a strong opponent and he defeats Yu.  Kyoya is sure that Tithi is a Legendary Blader and so challenges him to a battle next.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="133930" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-11-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">サジタリオの一撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The God of Destruction`s Revival!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sagittario no Ichigeki</title>
<summary>In Pluto’s lair in Mexico, the powers of the beys of some of the Legendary Bladers are used to begin the revival of Nemesis.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="133931" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-10-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">破壊神, 復活!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The God of Destruction`s Revival!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakaishin, Fukkatsu!?</title>
<summary>In Pluto’s lair in Mexico, the powers of the beys of some of the Legendary Bladers are used to begin the revival of Nemesis.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="133932" update="2014-05-27">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-10-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ネメシスの鼓動</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The God of Venus, Quetzalcoatl</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nemesis no Kodou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135034" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-11-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒き太陽(ネメシス)の申し子</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Child of Nemesis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nemesis no Moushigo</title>
<summary>Gingka and his friends have landed in Mexico and rush to try and stop Nemesis’ Revival.   Inside the temple, Rago, the Child of the Black Son, has already arrived.  Gingka, King, Yuki, Masaune and Madoka make it inside the temple and battles begin.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="135035" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-11-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハデスの呪縛</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Child of Nemesis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hades no Jubaku</title>
<summary>Gingka and his friends have landed in Mexico and rush to try and stop Nemesis’ Revival.   Inside the temple, Rago, the Child of the Black Son, has already arrived.  Gingka, King, Yuki, Masaune and Madoka make it inside the temple and battles begin.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="135036" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-11-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">四つの心(たましい)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Four Hearts</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yottsu no Tamashii</title>
<summary>The battle to stop the revival of Nemesis continues as Kyoya battles Dynamis and Tithi takes on Aguma in a temple in Mexico.  Meanwhile, Gingka, Yuki and Madoka take off to follow a hunch that Gingka has.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="135037" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-12-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">銀河VSクリス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Four Hearts</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ginga vs. Chris</title>
<summary>The battle to stop the revival of Nemesis continues as Kyoya battles Dynamis and Tithi takes on Aguma in a temple in Mexico.  Meanwhile, Gingka, Yuki and Madoka take off to follow a hunch that Gingka has.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="135262" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-12-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">集結! レジェンドブレーダー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Come Together, Legendary Bladers!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuuketsu! Legend Blader</title>
<summary>Gingka defeats Chris in battle but convinces Chris that as a Legendary Blader, Chris is part of a team and not alone anymore.  Aguma is defeated by Tithi and Dynamis gets Aguma to go with him and follow Gingka and the others.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="135263" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-12-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゼウスの結界</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Come Together, Legendary Bladers!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zeus no Kekkai</title>
<summary>Gingka defeats Chris in battle but convinces Chris that as a Legendary Blader, Chris is part of a team and not alone anymore.  Aguma is defeated by Tithi and Dynamis gets Aguma to go with him and follow Gingka and the others.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="135748" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-12-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ディアブロネメシス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Diablo Nemesis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Diablo Nemesis</title>
<summary>In a temple in Mexico, Rago  battles all comers including Gingka and his friends and Ryuga and none of their beys have any effect on Rago’s Diablo Nemesis as it sends them all flying Pegasus.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="135749" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2012-01-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">星の絆</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Diablo Nemesis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hoshi no Kizuna</title>
<summary>In a temple in Mexico, Rago  battles all comers including Gingka and his friends and Ryuga and none of their beys have any effect on Rago’s Diablo Nemesis as it sends them all flying Pegasus.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="137070" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2012-01-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦の地へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To The Final Battle Ground</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen no Chi e</title>
<summary>While the WBBA and all its members are searching the world for signs of Rago and Nemesis, Gingka and his friends are training hard for the battle they know is ahead of them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="137071" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2012-01-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">導かれし運命(さだめ)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To The Final Battle Ground</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Michibikareshi Sadame</title>
<summary>While the WBBA and all its members are searching the world for signs of Rago and Nemesis, Gingka and his friends are training hard for the battle they know is ahead of them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="137072" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2012-01-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">失われた王国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Lost Kingdom</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ushinawareta Oukoku</title>
<summary>Gingka and his friends fly towards the location of Nemesis in the Pacific Ocean, but the helicopter they are travelling in hits a vicious storm.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="137073" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2012-02-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">破壊神(ネメシス)VS竜皇(エルドラゴ)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Lost Kingdom</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nemesis vs. L-Drago</title>
<summary>Gingka and his friends fly towards the location of Nemesis in the Pacific Ocean, but the helicopter they are travelling in hits a vicious storm.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="137074" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2012-02-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">欠けた四季の星座</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Missing Star of the Four Seasons</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaketa Shiki no Seiza</title>
<summary>Gingka and his friends try to help Ryuga who has been badly hurt in a battle with Rago, but it appears they are too late to save him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="137145" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2012-02-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">継がれし光</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Missing Star of the Four Seasons</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsugareshi Hikari</title>
<summary>Gingka and his friends try to help Ryuga who has been badly hurt in a battle with Rago, but it appears they are too late to save him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="140831" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2012-04-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">未来へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Ray of Hope</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mirai e</title>
<summary>Gingka has received the power of all his friends’ beys and he and Pegasus are in a head to head battle with Nemesis.  Gingka fights hard but soon realizes that Pegasus’ power is exactly equal to the power of Nemesis.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="140832" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2012-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">希望の光</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Ray of Hope</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kibou no Hikari</title>
<summary>Gingka has received the power of all his friends’ beys and he and Pegasus are in a head to head battle with Nemesis.  Gingka fights hard but soon realizes that Pegasus’ power is exactly equal to the power of Nemesis.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="140833" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2012-03-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラストバトル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Last Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Last Battle</title>
<summary>Gingka and the rest of the Four Season Legendary Bladers appear to complete Zeus’ Barrier and seal Nemesis away for good, along with Rago and Pluto who are carried down with the destruction of the Lost Kingdom of Hades.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="140834" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2012-03-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハデスの執念</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hades` Persistence</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hades no Shuunen</title>
<summary>Gingka and the rest of the Four Season Legendary Bladers appear to complete Zeus’ Barrier and seal Nemesis away for good, along with Rago and Pluto who are carried down with the destruction of the Lost Kingdom of Hades.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="140835" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2012-03-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">執念の必殺転技</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Flash Sagittario</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuunen no Hissatsu Tengi</title>
<summary>Kenta and his newly evolved bey, Flash Sagittario, battle head to head with Rago and his bey, Diablo Nemesis.  Gingka is convinced that Kenta has been given the powers of the summer constellation legendary Blader from Ryuga.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="140836" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2012-02-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">フラッシュサジタリオ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Flash Sagittario</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Flash Sagittario</title>
<summary>Kenta and his newly evolved bey, Flash Sagittario, battle head to head with Rago and his bey, Diablo Nemesis.  Gingka is convinced that Kenta has been given the powers of the summer constellation legendary Blader from Ryuga.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
