<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="83" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1999-11-17</startdate>
<enddate>1999-11-17</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Jin-Rou</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Jin-Roh, the Wolf Brigade</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Jin Roh</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Загін вовків</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Перевертень</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="synonym">Jin-Roh: La Brigada Lobo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">jr</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Jinroh</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">人狼 JIN-ROH</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Jin-Roh: The Wolf Brigade</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Jin-Roh</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Jin Roh la brigade des loups</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Jin-Roh - Uomini e Lupi</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Jin-Roh</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Оборотни</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">인랑</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="official">Jin Roh the Wolf Brigade</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Jin-Roh: The Wolf Brigade</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="official">Džin Ro: Vilko brigada</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="61" approval="13" total="31">Ghost in the Shell</anime>
<anime id="5310" approval="7" total="16">Sky Crawlers</anime>
<anime id="777" approval="3" total="8">Kidou Keisatsu Patlabor</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="15">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="368986">it`s biutifull anime...
story..2heavy4kids
but... its biutifull anime</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="278370">Unique anime for audiences who like their escapism dark, serious and with a definite mature bent. Not the best anime film I`ve ever seen by far, but there`s nothing else quite like it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="230513">A story that will pull you in because of the awsome way of unique storytelling. it is dark and heavy but breathtaking. It is for the people who like a good (and as said unique) story.

Dp</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="735753">Masterpiece</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="614621">A must see...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="235114">Wonderful drama. One of the most emotional anime of all times.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="219629">There is no similar anime to this one!
Great dark atmosphere, nice story.
Worth a look!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20151105082711/http://www.production-ig.co.jp/works/jin-roh/</url>
<creators>
<name id="131" type="Original Work">Oshii Mamoru</name>
<name id="4523" type="Music">Mizoguchi Hajime</name>
<name id="721" type="Animation Work">Production I.G</name>
<name id="4500" type="Direction">Okiura Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="4500" type="Character Design">Okiura Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="3051" type="Character Design">Nishio Tetsuya</name>
</creators>
<description>In the riot-torn 1960`s Tokyo of an alternate history... a special police force, the Capitol Police Organization (CAPO) has been formed. Within CAPO is the special unit that gets the toughest jobs. Some of the men in the unit, according to rumour, comprise a vigilante group called the Wolf Brigade. http://anidb.net/ch12219 [Fuse], a member of the special unit, broods obsessively about a terrorist girl who blew herself up in front of him. Then he meets the girl`s sister and becomes emotionally involved...
Note: The film premiered in France on 17.11.1999 and was shown at different film festivals in the same year. In Japan the film has been released in theaters on 03.06.2000.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="4973">7.09</permanent>
<temporary count="5000">7.70</temporary>
<review count="6">8.44</review>
</ratings>
<picture>133497.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>161</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>570</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>218</identifier>
<identifier>zcvxsy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20151105082711/http://www.production-ig.co.jp/works/jin-roh/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.productionig.com/contents/works_sp/15_/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Jin-Roh:_The_Wolf_Brigade</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>人狼_JIN-ROH</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3989</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>160063</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7392</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>인랑_(2000년_영화)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>人狼_JIN-ROH</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>jin-roh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7184</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07F9FLLQV</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2640" parentid="2625" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-06-02">
<name>alternative past</name>
<description>An anime that takes place in an alternative past is an anime that clearly does not belong to the future or the present, and isn`t tied particularly closely to our history, or has ties to our history but only as a premise: there are too many things that don`t make sense for the time-period. In some cases there is futuristic technology present, but the overall setting still feels that of the past. However the setting must still take place on Earth, since we can not know if the history of a fantasy world is an alternate one or not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2852" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>thriller</name>
<description>The thriller is a genre of fiction in which tough, resourceful, but essentially ordinary heroes are pitted against villains determined to destroy them, their country, or the stability of the free world. The hero of a typical thriller faces danger alone or in the company of a small band of companions. The protagonist may be a law enforcement agent, a journalist, or a soldier, but typically he or she is cut off from the resources of "their" organization. More often the hero is an ordinary citizen drawn into danger and intrigue by circumstances beyond their control.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214683.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2926" parentid="2874" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>post-war</name>
<description>An armed conflict has ended not too long ago, devastation of the world or society is still evident.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3055" parentid="3876" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>fairy tale</name>
<description>This anime is either based on or contains parts of fairy tales. Usually those parts are highly modified or twisted when compared with the original source.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3166" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-18">
<name>political unrest</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3276" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>plot twists</name>
<description>The plot and story of this anime may seem to be going along a quite predictable path, when suddenly there is a jarring unexpected twist in the plot, taking the viewer by surprise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3718" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>love between enemies</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3850" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-11-23">
<name>downer ending</name>
<description>A finale that ends the story in a way that is usually truly miserable and tragic or a similarly low-key or unhappy ending to a normally "happy" series. 
Cruel examples of the ways this ending happens are all the major characters dying or the "bad guy" winning in a way that there`s no sight of happiness in the end.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3876" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>folklore</name>
<description>Folklore, or simply Lore, are the traditions of a culture, subculture, or group, in the form of legends, music, proverbs, jokes, popular beliefs, fairy tales, stories, tall tales and customs. In usage, there is a continuum between folklore and mythology.
Folklore is generally divided into four areas of study: physical artifacts, transmissible entities and stories, culture and technologies, and behaviors and rituals.
[From Wikipedia]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4153" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-15">
<name>dark</name>
<description>Describes the overall mood in this anime. Dark colours, a non-happy, often tragic story, dark lighting, many night scenes or constantly dark skies, and continuous rain all contribute to setting this mood.
The anime will often be quite depressing to watch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4225" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-02-16">
<name>symbolism</name>
<description>Representation of a more complex concept by a simple thing. Like a red flower for love or a flag for a nation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4314" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-04-11">
<name>psychological</name>
<description>Directed toward dealing with or affecting the mind, especially as a function of awareness, feeling, or motivation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4340" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-26">
<name>suicide</name>
<description>One or several characters in this anime commit suicide.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4343" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2009-09-21">
<name>main character dies</name>
<description>At least one of the main characters in the anime dies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4520" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>betrayal</name>
<description>Friends become enemies.
Strong bonds of trust receive violations of confidence while friendships are faithlessly given up or revealed to have been false from the start.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4753" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-15">
<name>disturbing</name>
<description>Watching the show may cause the viewer to have unpleasant feelings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4887" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2012-04-05">
<name>evil wins</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5609" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-27">
<name>dieselpunk</name>
<description>Dieselpunk is a genre that combines the aesthetics of the diesel-based technology of the interwar period through to the 1950s with retro-futuristic technology and postmodern sensibilities.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5700" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>paramilitary</name>
<description>A paramilitary is a semi-militarized force whose organizational structure, training, subculture, and (often) function are similar to those of a professional military, and which is not included as part of a state`s formal armed forces.
Though a paramilitary is not a military force, it is usually equivalent to a military`s light infantry force in terms of intensity, firepower and organizational structure. A paramilitary may also commonly fall under the command of a military, even despite not being part of the military or play an assisting role for the military in times of war.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5996" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-19">
<name>tragic ending</name>
<description>Up to the very end of the anime the viewer will hope that the story will end well and that the characters will in some way be able to solve the problems.
Not so. The sense of foreboding doom could not be averted. The social or personal calamity strikes mercilessly.
Examples: The catastrophic meteor strike does hit Earth after all. The long sick loved one cannot be saved. After overcoming all obstacles a random cruel event ends the life of the protagonist. A almost forgotten tragedy in the past has repercussions in the present.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6254" parentid="2872" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-23">
<name>terrorism</name>
<description>Terrorism is, in the broadest sense, the use of intentionally indiscriminate violence as a means to create terror among masses of people; or fear to achieve a religious or political aim. It is used in this regard primarily to refer to violence during peacetime or in war against non-combatants (mostly civilians and neutral military personnel). Some definitions now include acts of unlawful violence and war.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10657.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="12219" type="main character in" update="2009-10-10">
<rating votes="18">8.80</rating>
<name>Fuse Kazuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fuse Kazuki is a member of the Special Armed Garrison`s 2nd Company, 3rd Assault Platoon. He is also part of a self-preservation underground cell within the Kerberos which is known as "Jin-Roh".</description>
<picture>37061.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10004" picture="37062.jpg">Fujiki Yoshikatsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12220" type="main character in" update="2011-06-17">
<rating votes="11">5.38</rating>
<name>Amemiya Kei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Amemiya Kei claims to be Agawa Nanami`s elder sister. She`s actually a mole working for Muroto Bunmei`s Public Security Division under the codename "Langhaar". She was once a former Little Red Riding Hood active within the Division Jacobson.</description>
<picture>73641.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="429" picture="17306.jpg">Mutou Sumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108314" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-10">
<name>Agawa Nanami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244376.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1932" picture="65403.jpg">Sendai Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108315" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-10">
<name>Aniya Isao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244377.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30826">Nakagawa Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108316" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-10">
<name>Muroto Bunmei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244378.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4688" picture="29259.jpg">Hirota Kousei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108317" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-10">
<name>Tatsumi Shirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244379.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4484" picture="26762.jpg">Horibe Ryuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108318" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-10">
<name>Toube Hachirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244380.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4438" picture="26713.jpg">Sakaguchi Yoshisada</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108319" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-10">
<name>Henmi Atsushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244381.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4687" picture="27301.jpg">Kinoshita Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108320" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-10">
<name>Handa Hajime</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244382.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36085">Yoshida Yukihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="477" update="2017-05-29">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1999-11-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="478" update="2017-05-29">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>1999-11-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11141" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>40</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Making of</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11614" update="2017-05-29">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>100</length>
<airdate>1999-11-17</airdate>
<rating votes="10">9.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
<summary>In a very different Tokyo from the one we know today, the totalitarian government rules with an iron fist. But a group called "the Sect" is staging demonstrations and challenging the government`s martial law. Constable Fuse of the Capital Police`s Special Unit is on a mission to stop a Sect demonstration when he encounters a girl in the sewers under Tokyo. When he fails to shoot as ordered, he is put on trial, questioned, and "re-conditioned" as a soldier.  The dead girl haunts him, both in his dreams and in the face of her sister, whom Fuse has befriended. But Fuse has made himself a target for some very powerful men. And as the world comes crashing down around him, Fuse is continually challenged to decide what is real and what is right.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>690031</identifier>
<identifier>jin-roh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="166567" update="2017-05-29">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>1999-11-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="166568" update="2017-05-29">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1999-11-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="166569" update="2017-05-29">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>1999-11-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 3 of 3</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
