<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="831" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>6</episodecount>
<startdate>1999-02-25</startdate>
<enddate>1999-07-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shishunki Bishoujo Gattai Robo Z-Mind: The Battling Days of the "Shitamachi" Virgins</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">zmind</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">思春期美少女合体ロボ ジーマイン THE BATTLING DAYS OF THE "SHITAMACHI" VIRGINS</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Z-Mind</title>
</titles>
<creators>
<name id="1352" type="Original Work">Yatate Hajime</name>
<name id="8585" type="Chief Animation Direction">Watanabe Kazuo</name>
<name id="8193" type="Music">Nobuta Kazuo</name>
<name id="915" type="Animation Work">Imagin</name>
<name id="5107" type="Animation Work">Sakai Akio</name>
<name id="657" type="Series Composition">Gobu Fuyunori</name>
<name id="7371" type="Direction">Matsumura Yasuhiro</name>
</creators>
<description>Old school is back! And girl power reigns supreme! Ayame, Sumire, Renge, and Satsuki are charged with the protection of the Earth from a powerful new enemy. But these girls may be in for more than they`ve bargained for!
They`ll have to not only master the experimental mobile armor: Z-Mind, hold down their part time jobs, all this while keeping their lives... normal! But will this be enough to stop the forces of evil from conquering the Earth?</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="57">4.20</permanent>
<temporary count="57">5.60</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>515.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>284</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2731</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>849</identifier>
<identifier>svhqni</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>思春期美少女合体ロボ_ジーマイン</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88148</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1991</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3087" parentid="2274" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>super robot</name>
<description>These robots tend to have almost semi-magical attacks, which seem impossible or non-realistic, and/or perform non-realistic transformation sequences where they seem to gain/lose mass and utterly change their form, even if it means making their super-hard armour bend like plastic sheets.</description>
<picurl>222137.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="8616" update="2008-10-03">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-02-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくら空 鋼鉄の生命体出現</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Metal Life-form in the Cherry Blossom Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakurazora Koutetsu no Seimeitai Shutsugen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8617" update="2008-10-03">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">家族愛 12年目の戦い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Family Love, the Battle of the 12th Year</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kazoku Ai Juuninenme no Tatakai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13550" update="2008-10-03">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-04-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">母の祈り 電磁檻のさつき</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Mother`s Prayer, Satsuki in an Electromagnetic Cage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haha no Inori Denji Ori no Satsuki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13551" update="2008-10-03">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-06-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">驚異 ジーマインMAXパワー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Z-Mind`s Amazing, Maximum Power</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoui Z-Mind Max Power</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13552" update="2008-10-03">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-05-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">発見 謎の第4コクピット</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Discovery of the Mysterious Fourth Cockpit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakken Nazo no Daiyon Cockpit</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13553" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1999-07-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">哀切 虚空に散りゆくひと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tragedy, People Strewn About a Vacant Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aisetsu Kokuu ni Chiriyuku Hito</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
