<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8318" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-10-23</startdate>
<enddate>2011-10-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Magic Tree House</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">マジック・ツリーハウス</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="418149">A great show to see with your family, with a beautiful direction and wonderful landscapes. The movie I dreamed to watch when I was a child!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://magictreehouse.jp/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="1603" type="Direction">Nishikiori Hiroshi</name>
<name id="4233" type="Character Design">Yanagida Yoshiaki</name>
<name id="4233" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yanagida Yoshiaki</name>
<name id="2712" type="Music">Senju Akira</name>
<name id="24032" type="Original Work">Mary Pope Osborne</name>
<name id="960" type="Animation Work">Ajia-dou</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on The Magic Tree House series, award winning series of children books written by American author http://anidb.net/cr24032 [Mary Pope Osborne].
http://anidb.net/ch38446 [Jack] and http://anidb.net/ch38447 [Annie] are young siblings who find a magic tree house on their way home after chasing a weasel. By using the books available in the tree house, they are able to travel through time and space. The two end up with the difficult task of collecting four medallions, each hidden in a different place and epoch, in order to help a sorceress named http://anidb.net/ch38448 [Morgan].
Source: ANN
Note: The movie is based on Amako Ayana`s illustrations for the Japanese edition of the book series, as opposed to Salvatore Murdocca`s illustrations for the orginal American edition. The world premiere took place at Tokyo International Film Festival (October 2011).</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="114">5.29</permanent>
<temporary count="114">6.21</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>76793.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12584</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10690</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5299</identifier>
<identifier>xoacng</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://magictreehouse.jp/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://2011.tiff-jp.net/ja/lineup/works.php?id=75</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Magic_Tree_House_(film)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>マジック・ツリーハウス</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5403</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>340150</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14285</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="566" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-10">
<name>dinosaur</name>
<description>Dinosaurs are vertebrate animals that dominated terrestrial ecosystems for over 160 million years, first appearing approximately 230 million years ago. At the end of the Cretaceous Period, 66 million years ago, non-avian dinosaurs suffered a catastrophic extinction, which ended their dominance on land. Taxonomists consider modern birds to be the direct descendants of theropod dinosaurs.
Since the first dinosaur was recognized in the 19th century, mounted, fossilized dinosaur skeletons have become major attractions at museums around the world. Dinosaurs have become a part of world culture and remain consistently popular, especially among children. They have been featured in best-selling books and films such as Jurassic Park, and new discoveries are regularly covered by the media.
Source: Dinopedia</description>
<picurl>191115.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1500" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>grimoire</name>
<description>A grimoire is a textbook of magic. Such books typically include instructions on how to create magical objects like talismans and amulets, how to perform magical spells, charms and divination and also how to summon or invoke supernatural entities such as angels, spirits, and demons.</description>
<picurl>229110.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1700" parentid="2872" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>pirate</name>
<description>Pirates are people who attack ships on the high seas to rob others of their treasure. Well, at least usually. Other people calling themselves pirates are not unheard of, usually focusing on the freedom and romance involved in the piracy-related tropes and cliches. They may or may not be after the One Piece or a spaceship full of diamonds, too, if that`s what they see as treasure. Real-life pirates were extremely common a few centuries ago, and countries even sponsored their own pirates, called "privateers", to attack ships with flags of other countries. Nowadays, however, very few actual pirates still exist, and they rely more on terrorism and guerrilla warfare than anything else, demanding ransom in exchange for hostages instead of openly attacking the enemies with their swords. Another, more modern meaning for the word refers to people who illegally download copyrighted works they are not entitled to have a copy of. Be whichever it may, there are pirates around here. Arr, avast! Thar be pirates in these dark waters, matey!</description>
<picurl>126791.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1846" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>kodomo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word kodomo refers to a children`s audience roughly for the ages 12 and younger. In Japanese, the word means simply "child", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="38446" type="main character in" update="2011-11-06">
<name>Jack</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2108.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="30406" picture="81128.jpg">Kitagawa Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38447" type="main character in" update="2015-02-24">
<name>Annie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>169199.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30173" picture="79520.jpg">Ashida Mana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38448" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-06">
<name>Morgan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2114.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="38118" picture="139627.jpg">Maya Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50434" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-11-07">
<name>Tracy</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="232" picture="148706.jpg">Shitaya Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50435" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-11-07">
<name>Papa</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="380" picture="158572.jpg">Yamadera Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50436" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-11-07">
<name>Peanuts</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50437" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-11-07">
<name>Bones</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="1986" picture="1919.gif">Iizuka Shouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50438" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-11-07">
<name>Mama</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50439" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-11-07">
<name>Merlin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="282" picture="223615.jpg">Houki Katsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="130961" update="2011-11-06">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>100</length>
<airdate>2011-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133953" update="2011-11-06">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer (43 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168953" update="2015-06-09">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
