<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8323" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-10-02</startdate>
<enddate>2011-12-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kyoukaisen-jou no Horizon</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Horizon on the Middle of Nowhere</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Горизонт посреди пустоты</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Горизонт на границе пустоты</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Хоризонт по средата на нищото</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Kyoukai Senjou no Horizon</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">境界线上的地平线</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="synonym">افقی در ناکجاآباد</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="synonym">افقی در وسط هیچ کجا</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">kyoukaisen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">horizon</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">境界線上のホライゾン</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Horizon in the Middle of Nowhere</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8886" type="Sequel">Kyoukaisen-jou no Horizon II</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9677" approval="7" total="20">Log Horizon</anime>
<anime id="8869" approval="1" total="7">Oda Nobuna no Yabou</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="14">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="467926">For light ultimate fantasy fans.

Great series with tons of characters, first half was mainly focused on character and plot presentation while second half is pure awesomeness.

Beware! This series is the ultimate mix: every stereotype of characters wielding every kind of power/skill ever thought.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="384847">It might require a bit of external reading since first 3 exposition episodes are not doing their job well, but after that the setting, plot and the character interactions are interesting to watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="135862">This anime was probably produced for people who were already fans of, and have read, the book series. If you had, I guess it would be interesting to see some of the scenes played out in animation. If not, you will likely have no idea what people are talking about as very little is actually explained. If you were scratching your head reading the description above about this anime, trying to figure out wth it is actually talking about, you will likely feel the same while watching it too.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="501819">same as other really confused on 1st episode, but if you see through till 6 episode you will got awesome story, usually "bonds" that created a long time ago with Toori and Horizon with all of their friends</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="470321">Not your average start-to-end mindless anime that follows a steady predictable plot. First few episodes seem really random and implies to a lot of things that you dont know about, but yet the later episodes slowly fills in the pieces and gave you the sense of "Ah HA! So that`s what happened!" Very enjoyable, very original, lots of interesting characters and looking forward to 2nd season.

Reminds me of when Mission Impossible first came out and most people was like "huh? What happen?" and then once you THINK about it, you get it. Not for your average viewers that just dont want to bother thinking about what you are watching.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="44864">I started watching this series after 6 episodes were already out. After the first episode or two, I was wondering if I should keep watching as the series was becoming hard to follow with a vast cast of characters introduced all at once, a complicated setting explained in a couple of sentences and a bunch of terms and background information everybody seemed to know except the viewer. But I kept watching. After episode 6, many if not all of the info the show was trying to convey has sinked in. I have a grasp of most of the important characters, the setting and plot. Honestly can`t wait to watch the next episode.

Give it a chance, there`s potential for great stuff in here.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="138173">As many others after the first 3-4 episodes I wondering if I must keep watching, it was too hard to follow but what kept me going was the amazing battles, well after Episode 6 I think, things become better and better with each episodes until Episode 12 that blew me away! one more episode left and now I can say I am glad I didn`t stop watching back then, keep watching folks u wont loose! :D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="504514">Definitely do some extensive research before watching this anime (I recommend Stilts). There is hardly any introduction at all. The content is really heavy, you have to pay atention because you`ll easily miss something important.
Nevertheless, this was most definitely the best thing i have watched so far this year. Great characters, great story, great music, great comedy. There`s nothing to hate about this anime at all, except for the fact that it`s so damn hard to watch. It`s all worth it though.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="127475">To the average viewer, Horizon may be either a nonsensical story-less anime, or a good cute-turned-cool comedy. You can watch the first half of the season mindlessly, but towards the end the story actually becomes less meaningless. At least it still puts a smile on my face throughout the season. Good enough for a launchpad for a second season too.

EDIT: This is an anime worth watching. The animation is fun but to enjoy the actual story you have to do quite a bit of research. This anime is significantly underrated as viewers can`t be bothered to research about the story, and the amount of fanservice which make the superficial viewer think low of it. Do not let this hinder you from enjoying this anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="116115">You should watch this show AFTER acquiring a bit of the background. The light novel it`s based on is actually a huge work with many volumes, but luckily there are good intros like the one by Stilts, just google "Kyoukai Stilts" it`s the first link.
Then, the whole show WILL make a lot more sense and reveal itself as deeper than you`d think.
Also, keep in mind that everything happens in just two days (eps 1-5 in the first day, the rest in the second one) with time overlapping, you will follow different characters` point of view. Hope this helps.

Oh, and the female charachters are undeniably hot.

EDIT: I was asked to provide the actual links, here you are:
http://randomc.net/2012/06/30/kyoukai-senjou-no-horizon-retrospective-part-1-the-premise-the-world-episodes-01-06/
http://randomc.net/2012/07/04/kyoukai-senjou-no-horizon-retrospective-part-2-episodes-07-13-final-impressions/</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="113663">The first 3 episodes might be confusing because the Kyoukai senjou no horizon universe is large and will overwhelm you with information. Here they failed on giving you the time to understand. Afterwards everything slows down and become much easier to follow, although you need to pay attention at times. Near the end and following season 2 you have a really good sci-fi action show. I love the characters, great cast. I ended watching season 2 with a great feeling longing for more.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="508247">this series is only rated so low becuase no one really understood whats going on , what I personally did (and it worked quite well for me  I must say ) , is that I watched the series up until episode 5 ,and then went to its wiki and found out everything I dont know about .Once I got whats going on , I felt it has a good amount of orginality that makes it watch worthy.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="260717">http://kyoukaisen.tumblr.com/neta1

USE THIS. Everything starts to make just a little more sense. This anime is already amazing, with great animation and music, but understanding the smaller nuances really brings things to life.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://genesis-horizon.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3405" type="Series Composition">Urahata Tatsuhiko</name>
<name id="5371" type="Direction">Ono Manabu</name>
<name id="10106" type="Music">Katou Tatsuya</name>
<name id="9890" type="Chief Animation Direction">Fujii Tomoyuki</name>
<name id="726" type="Animation Work">Sunrise</name>
<name id="14275" type="Character Design">Aikei Yukiko</name>
<name id="11678" type="Character Design">Suzuki Kanta</name>
<name id="9890" type="Character Design">Fujii Tomoyuki</name>
<name id="14204" type="Character Design">Nishizawa Shin`ya</name>
<name id="24066" type="Original Work">Kawakami Minoru</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a light novel series written by http://anidb.net/cr24066 [Kawakami Minoru] and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr28785 [Satoyasu].
In the far future, humans abandon the devastated Earth and move to the upper world Tenjo. But Tenjo and the law of causation collapse in a war and humans return to Earth, which has turned into an uninhabitable planet except for the Shinshu area.
Shinshu is too small to accommodate all the humans, so they duplicate the area and create Juso Sekai in a parallel world. In order to rebuild Tenjo and the law of causation, the returned humans start reproduction of the history from 10,000 BC onward. When the reproduction proceeds to 1413 AD, a war breaks out in Shinshu and Juso Sekai falls onto the original world.
The humans living in Juso Sekai lose their land and invade the original world. People in Shinshu surrender and the land is divided by the invaders from Juso Sekai. They try to resume the history reproduction from 1457 AD onward, but the update of the history terminates in 1648 AD. The rumour of an impending apocalypse begins to spread around the world.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2000">4.76</permanent>
<temporary count="2022">6.60</temporary>
<review count="2">4.99</review>
</ratings>
<picture>231159.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12868</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22113</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>10456</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4962</identifier>
<identifier>nedlbk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://genesis-horizon.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Horizon_in_the_Middle_of_Nowhere</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>境界線上のホライゾン</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2254</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>340094</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13742</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2875</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2011/horizon</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=IAatO-2tPTU</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=5shCdRqL3no</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=ZndP_qGGveo</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=gPnph7XPIPI</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=lgwFB5pgvq8</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=g1iKR9Wrk8s</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=fsvpmiShlSo</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=6jtmjVzWaw8</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=COf0pulnKis</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=zTvvtmDhYgs</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=Wxs5f7hJZtQ</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=G0dSjiLwU6M</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=WkNBE3hJ5Yw</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=Uu0_dBJSKI8</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=WdLyhSfRl34</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=B_eRJiiLPCU</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>horizon-in-the-middle-of-nowhere</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="904" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-18">
<name>eccentric</name>
<description>Because normal people are no fun.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2346" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-14">
<name>angel</name>
<description>An angel is a supernatural being, said to be the messenger of God. They are often depicted as human beings with a pair of white feathered wings and sometimes with a halo.
In contrast, a fallen angel who has turned evil will be depicted with black wings.</description>
<picurl>35521.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2829" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-21">
<name>shower scene</name>
<description>The anime contains a shower scene, obligatory for ecchi anime. The person under the shower will most likely be female — providing "fanservice".</description>
<picurl>208635.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3252" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>history is written by the victors</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3295" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>world domination</name>
<description>"Gee, Brain, what do you want to do tonight?"
"The same thing we do every night, Pinky: try to take over the world!"
A main objective for one of the characters is absolute control of not just one country, but a whole planet!</description>
<picurl>38878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3378" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>redemption</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3635" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-01-01">
<name>sea battles</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3843" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>saving the world</name>
<description>While villains love to take over the world or cause the end of the world as we know it, the heroes are most likely motivated by the polar opposite, saving the world. A fairly simple plot/motivation related to for great justice and what not, this trope is pretty broad and very common for many stories not focused on character interaction only.
Source: TV Trope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3898" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-11">
<name>science and magic coexist</name>
<description>In this anime science and magic do not exclude each other. Magic here is actually very advanced, artefact- and/or ritual-based science.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3929" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-09">
<name>sociocultural evolution</name>
<description>Describes how cultures and societies develop over time, based on both cultural evolution and social evolution.
A post-apocalyptic or a Utopian setting would show very interesting changes in human behaviour, mental state, or simply daily life.</description>
<picurl>191062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3953" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-06">
<name>in medias res</name>
<description>In medias res, also medias in res (Latin for "into the midst of affairs (lit. into mid-affairs)"), refers to a literary and artistic technique where the narrative starts in the middle of the story instead of from its beginning. It is generally a plot-driven concept rather than a character-driven one; though characters are commonly used to provide the backstory. The characters, setting, and conflict are often introduced through a series of flashbacks or through characters relating past events to each other.
Probably originating from an oral tradition, the technique is a convention of epic poetry, one of the earliest and most prominent examples in Western literature being Homer`s Odyssey and Iliad. Virgil`s Aeneid began the tradition in literature of imitating Homer, continued in Torquato Tasso`s Jerusalem Delivered, John Milton`s Paradise Lost and "Inferno" from Dante`s Divine Comedy. George Lucas`s Star Wars saga was told using in medias res.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4048" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>Japanese mythology</name>
<description>Japanese mythology is a system of beliefs that embraces Shinto and Buddhist traditions as well as agriculture-based folk religion. The Shinto pantheon alone consists of an uncountable number of kami (Japanese for "gods" or "spirits").
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4461" parentid="6234" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-21">
<name>seven deadly sins</name>
<description>The seven deadly sins, also known as the capital vices or cardinal sins, is a grouping and classification of vices of Christian origin. Behaviors or habits are classified under this category if they directly give birth to other immoralities. According to the standard list, they are pride, greed, lust, envy, gluttony, wrath, and sloth, which are also contrary to the seven virtues. These sins are often thought to be abuses or excessive versions of one`s natural faculties or passions (for example, gluttony abuses one`s desire to eat).
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>205317.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5518" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-03">
<name>flat chest jokes</name>
<description>Jokes about the (supposedly or actually) flat chest of a character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5850" parentid="2869" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-13">
<name>absurdly powerful student council</name>
<description>A student council is a student-managed body inside a school which engages in administrative affairs, usually usually working in a partnership with management, staff and parents, for the benefit of the whole school environment. In real life, a student council holds no actual power; however, in many anime/manga, they have an insane amount of power, which usually allows them to overrule nearly everyone else (the school board, the mayor, the prime minster, you name it). In those cases, that device is explored as a major source of slapstick comedy.</description>
<picurl>70561.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6005" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-10-17">
<name>battle of wits</name>
<description>There is some intellectual battle between the characters. They each might attempt to discern what the other knows and/or could be planning. Then, rather than simply relying on the use of raw power, try to deduce an effective strategy to foil their opponent(s). The battle of wits can be in the center of the intrigue or just a side story.
Examples: Death Note, Code Geass</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6021" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>gender bender</name>
<description>Term used to refer to a person who takes on the role of their opposite gender. This often only reaches to the extent of cross-dressing (involving physical appearance and clothing only), but in rarer cases, involves a total gender swap (which seems to be more common in anime) - where the willing or unwilling victim receives a body opposite of their original gender (either permanently or temporarily), with all natural parts per their new body fully (or just all-out amply) included.
Example of cross-dressing gender bender: "Maria+Holic"
Examples of body-swap gender bender: "Kashimashi: Girl meets Girl", "Birdy the Mighty Decode"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6028" parentid="2876" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-10-12">
<name>Shintoism</name>
<description>Shintoism presents a blessed being or creature that governs over areas of terrain, general space of existence, or an individual object (be it alive or inanimate). Everything has its own "spiritual essence".
Defined as the earliest Japanese thoughts of an unified religion, the word Shinto comes from the Chinese hanzi "神道", combining two kanji: "shin" (神), meaning gods or spirits; and "tō" (道), meaning a philosophical path or study.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6234" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>motifs</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1717" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-06-02">
<rating votes="360">9.12</rating>
<name>Johannes Krauser II</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27095.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="30906" type="main character in" update="2011-12-25">
<rating votes="40">6.41</rating>
<name>Horizon Ariadust</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A cybernetic doll that works at the Blue Thunder bakery. She strongly resembles a girl killed ten years age.
Later it had discovered that she is the Armor of Deadly Sins. Because both of her masters were died, she was ordered to suicide. Students of Musashi try to prevent this From happening so they start a war</description>
<picture>73039.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="245" picture="46862.jpg">Chihara Minori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30907" type="main character in" update="2012-01-04">
<rating votes="43">5.95</rating>
<name>Aoi Toori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tori is the Head of Musashi Ariadust Academy`s Supreme Federation and President of the student council. His athletics and grades are average, and he`s both self and publicly recognized as an incompetent leader. However, because he doesn`t know the meaning of being depressed and has an incredibly cheerful attitude, he`s very respected nonetheless. He knows a lot of strip jokes, and often plays the fool.</description>
<picture>73040.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32120" type="main character in" update="2011-12-25">
<rating votes="59">7.32</rating>
<name>Neit Mitotsudaira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nate Mitotsudaira is a knight of Hexagone Française and successor of the Mitotsudaira Clan. Half-human, half-wolf. Although she cannot transform into a wolf form, she possesses the form`s great strength. She uses her special weapon, her silver chains, to great effect.
Because of her chivalrous nature and strong sense of duty, Nate feels very protective of the land on the Musashi, which technically falls within her family`s domain.
She is against the idea of saving horizon. But after being defeated by a silly method of using Mukai Suzu as a bait, she joins the team.
Source: kyoukaisen.tumblr.com</description>
<picture>73037.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32121" type="main character in" update="2011-12-25">
<rating votes="33">6.74</rating>
<name>Honda Masazumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The vice president of the student council. She`s very serious, skilled in debate, and aiming to become a politician. In the past she underwent gender reassignment surgery in order to succeed the family name, but certain circumstances forced her to stop the process part way. Her lack of breasts is a result of the surgery, but Tori treats her as a girl with a tiny chest.</description>
<picture>73034.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32122" type="main character in" update="2011-12-25">
<rating votes="50">7.32</rating>
<name>Asama Tomo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Shinto priestess of the Sengen Shrine and a childhood friend of Tori and Kimi. She uses the bow and arrow as her weapon and can shoot with high precision with the aid of Konoha, her artificial left eye.</description>
<picture>73036.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32123" type="main character in" update="2012-01-04">
<rating votes="70">7.83</rating>
<name>Aoi Kimi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Toori`s older sister. Both she and Toori were born on the same year, so they are of the same grade level. Bad with ghosts. Is a follower in the god of eroticism and dance. Dislikes her name, "Kimi" for some reason, so she changes it habitually. Though she calls Toori a foolish little brother, she also has another side that cares for him.
She was the person who tried to take Toori back to normal life after Horizon`s Death. Its said that she only cried for Toori and so she never complains about any other pain, since she believes they are not comparable to that time earlier.
Source: kyoukaisen.tumblr.com</description>
<picture>73035.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33174" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="33">6.49</rating>
<name>Adele Barrufet</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65300.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3622" picture="214935.jpg">Oohashi Ayuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33175" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-01">
<rating votes="11">4.52</rating>
<name>Kiyonari Urukiaga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65255.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="371" picture="166173.jpg">Kuroda Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33176" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-25">
<rating votes="16">6.97</rating>
<name>Shirojiro Bertoni</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Works as one of the youngest merchants in the Musashi Business Administration, and is contracted to the god of commerce. Makes decisions using profitability as his basis. In other words - a miser. He is The Partner of Heidi and only she can convince her to do something he is not interested about by saying "its about money"</description>
<picture>1697.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33177" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-25">
<rating votes="7">5.16</rating>
<name>Toussaint Neshinbara</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Toussaint Neshinbara has a very dry personality that penetrates even the thickest atmosphere of tomfoolery, yet is also fond of history, an aspiring novelist, and a romanticist. Is in charge of strategics planning and command during wartime.</description>
<picture>1694.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3712" picture="240126.jpg">Tamura Mutsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33178" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="6">4.52</rating>
<name>Noriki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1702.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="99" picture="139554.jpg">Hirakawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33179" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-25">
<rating votes="24">6.44</rating>
<name>Heidi Oogezavalour</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Heidi Augesvarer is Shirojiro Bertoni`s partner, both in business and in personal life. Although she constantly has a smile on, she is as much of a miser as Shirojiro is. She is always accompanied by her Maus named Erimaki.
Source: kyoukaisen.tumblr.com</description>
<picture>1699.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33180" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-25">
<rating votes="35">6.66</rating>
<name>Marga Naruze</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A black-haired, 6-winged white magic user. Also affiliated with the manga club. Her personality is rather rebellious, but she always puts Margot above all else.</description>
<picture>65280.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22170" picture="226837.jpg">Nitta Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33181" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-25">
<rating votes="35">6.80</rating>
<name>Margot Night</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A blonde, 6-winged black magic user, as well as Naruze`s lover. Always smiling. Freely uses her abilities in flight, characteristic of magicians. Pursues a career in the transportation industry.
Source: kyoukaisen.tumblr.com</description>
<picture>65256.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33182" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="15">7.13</rating>
<name>Kazuno</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1966.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="357" picture="32000.jpg">Shintani Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33183" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-25">
<rating votes="30">8.29</rating>
<name>Mukai Suzu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Suzu Mukai is a blind girl who acts as a "stopper" for the intense cast surrounding her. Highly perceptive, and is able to detect phenomena that escape most people`s attention.
She was the Childhood Friend of Toori and Horizon and it seems that she has feelings for Toori.</description>
<picture>1700.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33184" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-01">
<rating votes="15">3.21</rating>
<name>Azuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1944.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="330" picture="171543.jpg">Morinaga Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33185" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-25">
<rating votes="16">6.23</rating>
<name>Tenzou Crossunite</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A highly talented ninja, excelling in Ninjutsu and intelligence. Though very nice in character, he is also quite the pervert, openly declaring his love for blonde-haired, big-breasted women.</description>
<picture>65251.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33186" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="24">6.24</rating>
<name>Naomasa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65283.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="453" picture="45925.jpg">Shindou Kei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35274" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-25">
<rating votes="8">2.41</rating>
<name>Innocentius</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Innocentius is the representative of K.P.A.Italia, and Pope-President of the top school, K.P.A. Scuola; holds a lot of influence around the whole world. Owner of the Armor of Deadly Sins, Steisos Porneia (Lust). Highly ambitious; intends to expand his power and influence under the pretext of recreating history.</description>
<picture>1969.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35553" type="appears in" update="2011-12-25">
<rating votes="30">7.24</rating>
<name>Oriotorai Makiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Makiko Oriotorai Class 3-Plum`s homeroom teacher. Self-centered in both speech and action, but is a very personable teacher who always thinks of her students. Has incredible physical power, to the point where she is called a "Real Amazon". Loves alcohol.
Source: kyoukaisen.tumblr.com</description>
<picture>1689.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="208" picture="20458.jpg">Shiraishi Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35554" type="appears in" update="2011-12-25">
<rating votes="11">6.36</rating>
<name>Miriam Poke</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Confined to a wheelchair; thus, conducts studies at home. Has a strong character, is very tactless, and will say anything that comes to her mind. However, she has very gentle eyes.</description>
<picture>1946.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1676" picture="144276.jpg">Matayoshi Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35555" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="3">4.48</rating>
<name>Yoshinao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1952.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="231" picture="23486.jpg">Madono Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35556" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="8">5.81</rating>
<name>Sanyou Mitsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1949.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="550" picture="151677.jpg">Shimizu Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35557" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="4">1.68</rating>
<name>Itou Kenji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1710.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2145" picture="82117.jpg">Miyashita Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35558" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="2">3.04</rating>
<name>Ohiroshiki Ginji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65313.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="434" picture="41082.jpg">Shiraishi Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35559" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-20">
<rating votes="49">6.49</rating>
<name>Honda Futayo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Futayo Honda is a student of Mikawa, and is Masazumi Honda`s second cousin. She is Tadakatsu Honda`s daughter, one of the Four Divine Matsudaira Kings, and is the head of the Mikawa Security Force. Because she has only ever received combat training from Tadakatsu, she is incredibly clueless about the world.
She starts a battle with Musashi students against the idea to save Horizon, but was defeated by Aoi Kimi. Kimi convinces her that she has to serve Horizon since she is the princess of her land, so then she joins the Musahi Team.</description>
<picture>1967.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35560" type="appears in" update="2011-12-25">
<rating votes="18">7.17</rating>
<name>"Musashi"</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Musashi is an automaton managing the vessel of the same name where Toori Aoi and the others reside. She is the captain of each and every one of the eight ships making up the Musashi. Possesses a characteristic sharp tongue.</description>
<picture>1950.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35561" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="7">4.60</rating>
<name>Tachibana Muneshige</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1971.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35562" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="30">6.78</rating>
<name>Tachibana Gin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1976.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1798" picture="20493.jpg">Kotobuki Minako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35563" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="3">7.11</rating>
<name>Sakai Tadatsugu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65335.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2231" picture="235895.jpg">Kusunoki Taiten</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36601" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="2">2.69</rating>
<name>Galileo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1970.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="267" picture="25729.jpg">Koyama Tsuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36602" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="3">6.27</rating>
<name>Honda Tadakatsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1962.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2361" picture="228618.jpg">Kusumi Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36603" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<name>Honda Masanobu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1953.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="4689" picture="170829.jpg">Takada Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36604" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="2">2.14</rating>
<name>Matsudaira Motonobu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1959.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="27" picture="26123.jpg">Hayami Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36605" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="7">7.07</rating>
<name>Blue Thunder Tenshu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1957.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="4008" picture="65413.png">Yamada Miho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36606" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="3">3.84</rating>
<name>Nenji</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54117.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="99" picture="139554.jpg">Hirakawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36607" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="3">3.28</rating>
<name>Hassan Furubushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1690.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36610" type="appears in" update="2011-12-03">
<name>K.P.A. Italia</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The former Italy that now rules over the Aki; in control of the Setouchi region.</description>
</character>
<character id="36611" type="appears in" update="2011-09-10">
<name>Seitokai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="36614" type="appears in" update="2011-11-02">
<rating votes="3">5.14</rating>
<name>Jizurisuzaku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>1984.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="38177" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="2">3.40</rating>
<name>Persona-kun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1947.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="38178" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="3">2.80</rating>
<name>Konishi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1956.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="436" picture="90853.jpg">Kobushi Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38179" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="2">6.21</rating>
<name>Kuromo no Kemono</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1980.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="330" picture="171543.jpg">Morinaga Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38182" type="appears in" update="2011-12-03">
<rating votes="2">4.25</rating>
<name>El Azul</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Tres Espana Heavy-class Aerial Gods of War. With wings expanded, it is roughly 10 meters long. Operated by means of assimilating a person.</description>
<picture>1985.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="38183" type="appears in" update="2011-12-03">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Jun Bahamut Kyuu Koukuu Toshi Kan - Musashi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>An airship city. There are two ships in the middle, flanked by 3 ships on each side, for a total of 8 ships, over 7 kilometers in length overall.</description>
<picture>1988.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="38184" type="appears in" update="2011-10-28">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Zaragoza</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>1997.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="38185" type="appears in" update="2011-10-28">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Alicant</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>1992.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="38274" type="appears in" update="2011-11-02">
<rating votes="2">6.73</rating>
<name>Yuurei (?) no Shoujo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76122.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="550" picture="151677.jpg">Shimizu Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38275" type="appears in" update="2011-11-02">
<name>Musashi Ariadust Gakuin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="38276" type="appears in" update="2011-11-02">
<name>Sannen Ume Gumi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Class 3-Plum of Musashi Ariadust Academy.</description>
</character>
<character id="38277" type="appears in" update="2011-12-03">
<name>Musashi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The only independent territory in the Far East, and where the main characters reside; an airship city.</description>
</character>
<character id="38282" type="appears in" update="2011-11-02">
<name>Sannen Take Gumi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Class 3-Bamboo of Musashi Ariadust Academy.</description>
</character>
<character id="38329" type="appears in" update="2011-12-04">
<name>Mikawa</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Far East`s representative country.
Source: genesis-horizon.wikia.com</description>
</character>
<character id="38330" type="appears in" update="2011-12-04">
<name>Seiren</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>An organization established by the world`s superpowers, responsible for smooth conduction of history recreation. An abbreviation of "Seifu Renmei".
Source: genesis-horizon.wikia.com</description>
</character>
<character id="38331" type="appears in" update="2011-11-03">
<name>Blue Thunder</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>A snack shop located on Musashi.</description>
</character>
<character id="38332" type="appears in" update="2011-11-03">
<rating votes="5">7.87</rating>
<name>Hanami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2061.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38333" type="appears in" update="2011-11-03">
<rating votes="2">1.72</rating>
<name>Chimpira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An Archdevil Thug who lives on Musashi. He is part of the Shinagawa Archdemon Group.</description>
<picture>2063.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="371" picture="166173.jpg">Kuroda Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38334" type="appears in" update="2011-11-03">
<name>Shinagawa Majin Kai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="38335" type="appears in" update="2011-11-03">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Sakakibara Yasumasa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2065.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2145" picture="82117.jpg">Miyashita Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38336" type="appears in" update="2011-12-03">
<name>Tres Espana</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The territory of Shimoseki, currently under provisional rule, under the warlords Ootomo and Ouchi, as well as Spain.</description>
</character>
<character id="39229" type="appears in" update="2011-12-03">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Erimaki</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2739.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="39230" type="appears in" update="2011-12-03">
<rating votes="14">5.74</rating>
<name>"Shinagawa"</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2743.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39231" type="appears in" update="2011-12-03">
<name>P.A. Oda</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Provisional ruler of the Kinki~Tokai region in the Far East, composed of the Sengoku warlord clan, Oda, and the Ottoman Empire. Currently allied with Mikawa and in partial secession from the Testament Union.</description>
</character>
<character id="39232" type="appears in" update="2011-12-03">
<name>Kyokutou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The stage of the story, and the only inhabitable area on the earth. Formerly called the Divine States, it was renamed to the Far East as a result of a certain disturbance. It is currently divided into territories under provisional rule by each superpower.</description>
</character>
<character id="39233" type="appears in" update="2011-12-04">
<name>Matsudaira Shitennou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The four who directly serve Mikawa`s ruler, Matsudaira Motonobu. Members: Honda Tadakatsu, Sakai Tadatsugu, Ii Naomasa, and Sakakibara Yasumasa.
Source: genesis-horizon.wikia.com</description>
</character>
<character id="39234" type="appears in" update="2011-12-04">
<name>Zantei Gikai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>An organization comprised of adults who have already graduated from Musashi Ariadust Academy. Though able to influence the student council and the chancellor`s board, their words do not have any sway or authority to them.
Source: genesis-horizon.wikia.com</description>
</character>
<character id="39235" type="appears in" update="2011-12-03">
<name>Mikawa Keigo Tai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The only other armed group permitted by the Testament Union, other than itself. Activities are restricted to defense and escort work. Honda Futayo is currently serving as its head.</description>
</character>
<character id="39236" type="appears in" update="2011-12-03">
<rating votes="2">6.09</rating>
<name>Souchou Rengou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The organization within the Musashi Ariadust Gakuin that deals with military affairs.</description>
</character>
<character id="39261" type="appears in" update="2011-12-03">
<name>Shinshuu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="39263" type="appears in" update="2011-12-03">
<name>Juusou Shinshuu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="43067" type="appears in" update="2012-07-15">
<rating votes="4">2.20</rating>
<name>Diego Velazquez</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91008.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="43425" type="appears in" update="2012-07-15">
<rating votes="22">5.35</rating>
<name>Juana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91009.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43426" type="appears in" update="2012-07-15">
<rating votes="4">5.40</rating>
<name>Flores Valdes</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>5462.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="81" picture="41282.jpg">Sanpei Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43427" type="appears in" update="2012-07-15">
<rating votes="2">3.04</rating>
<name>Pedero Valdes</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>5464.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="5040" picture="88977.jpg">Kawahara Yoshihisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43428" type="appears in" update="2012-07-15">
<rating votes="2">3.04</rating>
<name>Hironaka Takakane</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91010.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43429" type="appears in" update="2012-07-15">
<rating votes="4">4.77</rating>
<name>Era Yosae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>5458.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43430" type="appears in" update="2012-07-15">
<rating votes="2">3.04</rating>
<name>Achiyuki Byakko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>91011.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48302" type="appears in" update="2012-08-30">
<name>Uzui</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48303" type="appears in" update="2012-08-30">
<rating votes="5">6.98</rating>
<name>"Asakusa"</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93197.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48304" type="appears in" update="2012-08-30">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Yoshinao no Tsuma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93196.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1917" picture="151688.jpg">Natsuki Rio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48305" type="appears in" update="2012-08-30">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Sewayaku no Joseito</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93194.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48306" type="appears in" update="2012-08-30">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Teitoku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93195.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="436" picture="90853.jpg">Kobushi Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48407" type="appears in" update="2012-09-03">
<name>Hachidairyuuoh</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Hachidairyuuoh (八大竜王, Eight Great Dragon Kings/Lords) is the traditional term used for the eight wielders of the Logismoi Óplo (Mortal Sin Armaments).</description>
</character>
<character id="48409" type="appears in" update="2012-09-03">
<name>San Lorenzo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="48410" type="appears in" update="2012-09-03">
<name>Godaichou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Godaichou (五大頂, Five Great Peaks) is a group of six warriors which act as the main armed force of P.A. ODA. They are also called as the Rokutenmagun (六天魔軍, Six-Demon Army), although two of the members are counted as one, thus the "five" in "Five Great Peaks". They are considered to be the private army of Nobunaga Oda himself.</description>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="132458" update="2012-11-09">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-08-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">OP Teaser</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132459" update="2012-11-09">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-08-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2 (Toori Ver.)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132460" update="2011-08-12">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-04-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">PV (Short Ver.)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132461" update="2011-08-12">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2011-04-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">PV (Full Ver.)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132718" update="2013-01-01">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-08-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2 (Horizon Ver.)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132937" update="2011-12-31">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="10">3.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夜天下の暗躍者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Covert Ops Under the Night`s Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yoru Tenka no Anyaku Mono</title>
<summary>The firework show is drawing near, but the fireworks may not be quite what everyone had expected. The few remaining residents of Mikawa are forcing the Platonic Plate Reactor to meltdown, and they’ll stop anyone who dares get in their way.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>586394</identifier>
<identifier>horizon-in-the-middle-of-nowhere</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="132938" update="2011-12-31">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="11">2.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">町中の遊撃者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Commandos in Town</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Machijuu no Yuugeki Mono</title>
<summary>Toori and his friends are busy preparing for his big day, each in their own way. Meanwhile, Masazumi is investigating the history behind Remorse Way.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>586392</identifier>
<identifier>horizon-in-the-middle-of-nowhere</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="132939" update="2015-09-07">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="12">2.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">食事場の清純者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Innocents at the Table</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shokujiba no Seijun Mono</title>
<summary>This episode focuses on April 20th through the eyes of Honda Masazumi. Despite a difficult past and a despairing outlook on the future, he desperately wants to become a good politician who understands the people.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>586030</identifier>
<identifier>horizon-in-the-middle-of-nowhere</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="132940" update="2011-12-31">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="18">2.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">境界線前の整列者達</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Those Lined Up Before the Horizon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoukaisen Mae no Seiretsu Mono-tachi</title>
<summary>Oriotorai has instructed her students to try and hit her during P.E. No one’s even coming close until Toori shows up and baffles her so badly that he manages to sneak in a grope attack. He then announces his plans to ask Horizon out.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>586028</identifier>
<identifier>horizon-in-the-middle-of-nowhere</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="133611" update="2011-11-07">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133864" update="2011-12-31">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-06</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">告白場の代弁者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Advocate at the Confession Grounds</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokuhaku Ba no Daibensha</title>
<summary>Musashi is caught in the middle of dirty politics, with the Testament Union trying to take the upper hand. After carefully reviewing their current situation, Toori and his classmates decide what their first course of action should be.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>586398</identifier>
<identifier>horizon-in-the-middle-of-nowhere</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="133865" update="2011-12-31">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-30</airdate>
<rating votes="9">4.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">月下の卒業者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Graduates Under the Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekka no Sotsugyousha</title>
<summary>Muneshige fights valiantly to prevent the reactors from going critical, but to no avail. Lord Motonobu announces that the only way to stop the apocalypse is to gather all nine Armours of Deadly Sins, one of which is located inside of P-01s.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>586396</identifier>
<identifier>horizon-in-the-middle-of-nowhere</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="133949" update="2013-04-04">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-10-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134283" update="2013-04-04">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-10-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134707" update="2011-12-31">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スタートラインのラッパ吹き</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Trumpeter at the Start Line</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Start Line no Rappafuki</title>
<summary>Adele puts her father’s old mechanic shell to good use, serving as a shield for her fellow students as they charge through enemy fire. Naruse and Margot have an aerial battle with one of Tres España’s Gods of War.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>586406</identifier>
<identifier>horizon-in-the-middle-of-nowhere</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="134708" update="2011-12-31">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-28</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">高嶺の花</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Summit`s Flower</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Takane no Hana</title>
<summary>Kimi fights and defeats Futayo before convincing her to side with the group wanting to save Horizon. King Yoshinao promotes Toori and Horizon to viceroys before Toori and his friends run off to save Horizon.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>586404</identifier>
<identifier>horizon-in-the-middle-of-nowhere</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="134709" update="2011-12-31">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">全域の支持者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ruler of the Land</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zen`iki no Shijisha</title>
<summary>Masazumi must debate with Toori on why Musashi should rescue Horizon. The debate goes so well that the Pope President intervenes and personally begins debating with Masazumi.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>586402</identifier>
<identifier>horizon-in-the-middle-of-nowhere</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="134710" update="2011-12-31">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-13</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">武蔵の騎士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Musashi`s Knights</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Musashi no Kishi</title>
<summary>The students of Musashi must prove to one another and the various factions that they are capable of waging war against the Testament Union and potentially the entire world.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>586400</identifier>
<identifier>horizon-in-the-middle-of-nowhere</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="134955" update="2012-01-17">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-11</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">武蔵の不可能男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Musashi`s Mr. Impossible</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Musashi no Fukanou Otoko</title>
<summary>Nate and Naomasa rescue Toori, but things take a turn for the worse when Innocentius uses Staseis Porneia.  Toori uses his "Impossible" powers to help pull his men out of a bind. Meanwhile, Futayo is out getting her rematch with Muneshige.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>586408</identifier>
<identifier>horizon-in-the-middle-of-nowhere</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="134956" update="2015-09-07">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-18</airdate>
<rating votes="5">9.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">平行線上への相対者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Opposition Against Crossing over the Parallel Lines</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Heikousen-jou e no Soutai Mono</title>
<summary>Futayo continues her battle with Muneshige and arises victorious. Toori makes it to Horizon, but she doesn’t want to be rescued. Toori must not only convince her to leave with him, but also figure out how to defeat the Disintegration Wall.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>586410</identifier>
<identifier>horizon-in-the-middle-of-nowhere</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="134971" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">境界線上の整列者達</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Those Lined Up Above the Horizon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoukaisen-jou no Seiretsu Monotachi</title>
<summary>Horizon, with the help of Tori, shows the Catholic Church and K.P.A Italia, the power of Lype Katarripsi.  Afterwards, they are greeted with the arrival of a new set of problems.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>589152</identifier>
<identifier>horizon-in-the-middle-of-nowhere</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="135058" update="2013-04-04">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-11-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135861" update="2019-03-15">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2011-08-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">極東なるほど講座 其の1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sensei`s Lesson 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyokutou Naruhodo Kouza Sono 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135862" update="2012-11-09">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キャラクター紹介 «武蔵»編1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Characters Introduction 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Character Shoukai: "Musashi" Hen 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135951" update="2012-07-13">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-12-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136394" update="2013-01-01">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-11-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">BD Sale Announcement CM 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136395" update="2013-01-01">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-09-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">BD Sale Announcement CM 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136749" update="2019-03-15">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キャラクター紹介 «武蔵»編2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Characters Introduction 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Character Shoukai: "Musashi" Hen 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137444" update="2019-03-15">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キャラクター紹介 «武蔵»編3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Characters Introduction 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Character Shoukai: "Musashi" Hen 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137466" update="2012-07-13">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-12-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137467" update="2012-07-13">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-10-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138143" update="2013-01-01">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-03-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">BD Volume 5 Bonus CD CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138184" update="2019-03-15">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キャラクター紹介 «武蔵»編4</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Characters Introduction 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Character Shoukai: "Musashi" Hen 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="140949" update="2012-12-27">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-11-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="140950" update="2012-07-13">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-10-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="140951" update="2013-04-04">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-10-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145352" update="2013-01-01">
<epno type="4">T12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145353" update="2013-01-01">
<epno type="4">T11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145354" update="2013-01-01">
<epno type="4">T10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145355" update="2013-01-01">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-03-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">BD Volume 5 Bonus CD CM 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145364" update="2013-01-01">
<epno type="4">T13</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Unknown Pre-Air PV</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
