<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8351" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-06-24</startdate>
<enddate>2011-06-24</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Oretachi ni Tsubasa wa Nai: Under the Innocent Sky. - Hada-iro Ritsu Kyuu-wari Zou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Ore-tachi ni Tsubasa wa Nai: Hada-iro Ritsu Kyuu-wari Zou!?</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">俺たちに翼はない -under the innocent sky. 肌色率九割増</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">We Without Wings: More than 90% Flesh-Toned</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8112" type="Other">Oretachi ni Tsubasa wa Nai: Under the Innocent Sky.</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.project-navel.com/oretsuba_r/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1055" type="Animation Work">Nomad</name>
<name id="4418" type="Character Design">Ishii Kumi</name>
<name id="3662" type="Series Composition">Kouno Takamitsu</name>
<name id="1011" type="Original Work">Navel</name>
<name id="11255" type="Direction">Ushiro Shinji</name>
<name id="4418" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ishii Kumi</name>
<name id="7023" type="Music">Acchorike</name>
</creators>
<description>The maids at the Alexander Restaurant have a day off and decide to visit a beautiful hot springs located in the mountains. http://anidb.net/ch25425 [Mochizuki Kinako], http://anidb.net/ch25424 [Hino Eriko], http://anidb.net/ch25421 [Tamaizumi Hiyoko], http://anidb.net/ch30952 [Yamashina Miyako], http://anidb.net/ch30955 [Takauchi Masako], http://anidb.net/ch25420 [Watarai Asuka], and the rest of the gang have heard of the ghost of a woman, rumoured to haunt the hot spring. Supposedly the ghost will bestow a blessing in love-related matters when encountered. This leads to high jinks and all sorts of misunderstandings.
— written by foo2
Note: Original video anime (OVA) episode bundled with romance adventure game Ore-tachi ni Tsubasa wa Nai R, a remake of the Ore-tachi ni Tsubasa wa Nai game.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="447">3.23</permanent>
<temporary count="449">5.80</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>72176.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10547</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4997</identifier>
<identifier>tttsui</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.project-navel.com/oretsuba_r/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2822" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>skirt flipping</name>
<description>Naughty characters — usually boys — flip the skirts of female protagonists to ascertain what panties they are wearing (also see Pantsu category).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3444" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>hot springs visit</name>
<description>An onsen is a term for hot springs in the Japanese language, though the term is often used to describe the bathing facilities and inns around the hot springs. Often the cast of a show somehow ends up going to an onsen because of various reasons, such as winning a lottery ticket. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters nude and raise the DVD sales.
Another cheap variant is the http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160784.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="25420" type="main character in" update="2010-12-31">
<rating votes="31">6.32</rating>
<name>Watarai Asuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61718.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4602" picture="26936.jpg">Yoshida Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25421" type="main character in" update="2010-12-31">
<rating votes="30">6.98</rating>
<name>Tamaizumi Hiyoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61719.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="594" picture="156858.jpg">Ono Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25422" type="main character in" update="2011-04-19">
<rating votes="33">6.87</rating>
<name>Ootori Naru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61721.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25423" type="main character in" update="2011-04-19">
<rating votes="22">6.11</rating>
<name>Haneda Kobato</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61720.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1676" picture="144276.jpg">Matayoshi Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25424" type="main character in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="22">5.63</rating>
<name>Hino Eriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69365.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2344" picture="37361.jpg">Asai Kiyomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25425" type="main character in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="25">6.77</rating>
<name>Mochizuki Kinako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69363.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1665" picture="19756.jpg">Takahashi Chiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26258" type="appears in" update="2010-12-31">
<rating votes="2">7.77</rating>
<name>DJ Condor</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26259" type="appears in" update="2011-06-24">
<rating votes="19">5.40</rating>
<name>Chitose Shuusuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69361.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="552" picture="23199.jpg">Miura Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26260" type="appears in" update="2011-06-24">
<rating votes="20">8.13</rating>
<name>Narita Hayato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69362.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26261" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="8">4.57</rating>
<name>Morisato Kazuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69368.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3295" picture="38451.jpg">Ogihara Hideki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26262" type="appears in" update="2011-06-24">
<rating votes="16">2.59</rating>
<name>Haneda Takashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69360.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26263" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="16">7.04</rating>
<name>Karube Karuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69369.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="258" picture="17080.jpg">Ishikawa Hideo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26264" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="10">4.88</rating>
<name>Ootori Kakeru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69367.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30929" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-15">
<rating votes="26">6.17</rating>
<name>Alice</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69888.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="410" picture="228116.jpg">Aoki Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30931" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="20">7.11</rating>
<name>Kasuga Harue</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69366.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2058" picture="48262.jpg">Ootsuda Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30933" type="appears in" update="2011-04-15">
<rating votes="14">5.87</rating>
<name>Kouda Ai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69890.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="215" picture="151687.jpg">Nakajima Saki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30952" type="main character in" update="2011-04-15">
<rating votes="14">6.88</rating>
<name>Yamashina Miyako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69891.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6305" picture="223494.jpg">Takaguchi Yukiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30954" type="appears in" update="2011-04-15">
<rating votes="12">5.99</rating>
<name>Hayashida Misaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69892.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="618" picture="223541.jpg">Okajima Tae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30955" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-15">
<rating votes="16">6.01</rating>
<name>Takauchi Masako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69900.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2801" picture="23195.jpg">Komatsu Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31207" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-15">
<rating votes="7">6.83</rating>
<name>Yoneda Yuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69903.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1928" picture="151689.jpg">Hagiwara Emiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33845" type="appears in" update="2011-06-24">
<rating votes="13">5.01</rating>
<name>Kikkawa Akira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74187.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2011" picture="233461.jpg">Tomonaga Akane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33846" type="appears in" update="2011-06-24">
<rating votes="6">8.35</rating>
<name>Haneda Youji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69360.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="129020" update="2011-06-30">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129483" update="2011-04-12">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131422" update="2011-06-30">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-06-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131423" update="2011-06-30">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-06-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
