<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8374" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-09-03</startdate>
<enddate>2011-09-03</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gekijouban Tennis no Ouji-sama: Eikoku Shiki Teikyuu Shiro Kessen!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The Prince of Tennis - Showdown in England`s Tennis Fortress</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">劇場版テニスの王子様 英国式庭球城決戦!</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5750" type="Prequel">Tennis no Ouji-sama: Zenkoku Taikai Hen - Final</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.tenipuri.jp/gekijo/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1271" type="Animation Work">M.S.C</name>
<name id="721" type="Animation Work">Production I.G</name>
<name id="3573" type="Character Design">Ishii Akiharu</name>
<name id="783" type="Work">NAS</name>
<name id="1895" type="Original Work">Konomi Takeshi</name>
<name id="2136" type="Direction">Tada Shunsuke</name>
<name id="3721" type="Music">Watanabe Cheru</name>
</creators>
<description>Seigaku travels to England to play a tournament representing Japan but they are attacked by a group of street tennis players who were banned from playing official tournaments because of their rough play.
Note: The new film marks the 10th anniversary of the http://anidb.net/a56 [anime].</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="173">4.65</permanent>
<temporary count="176">6.36</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>134297.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12859</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10731</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://tenipuri-movie.com/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tenipuri.jp/gekijo/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.production-ig.co.jp/works/tenipuri-uk/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>339551</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13835</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2752" parentid="2881" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tennis</name>
<description>Tennis is yet another sport involving hitting a ball. Were it not for the copious amounts of grass involved in certain varieties, it seems hard to imagine that people would pay it any attention at all.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2809" parentid="2831" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>United Kingdom</name>
<description>The United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, commonly known as the United Kingdom (UK) or Britain, is a sovereign country in western Europe. Lying off the north-western coast of the European mainland, the UK includes the island of Great Britain, the north-eastern part of the island of Ireland and many smaller islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>64254.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7198" type="main character in" update="2015-03-12">
<rating votes="216">7.29</rating>
<name>Echizen Ryouma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>169968.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="570" picture="151691.jpg">Minagawa Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7199" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-03-12">
<rating votes="151">7.67</rating>
<name>Tezuka Kunimitsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>169963.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7201" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-25">
<rating votes="67">5.34</rating>
<name>Ooishi Shuuichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ooishi is a third year student at Seishun Academy (Seigaku) and the co-captain of the tennis club. Along with Kikumaru Eiji he is part of Seigaku`s "Golden Pair," a doubles team that made it to Nationals the year before the series takes place.</description>
<picture>72296.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="465" picture="56019.jpg">Kondou Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7202" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-03-12">
<rating votes="153">7.66</rating>
<name>Fuji Shuusuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fuji Shuusuke is a third year student at Seishun Academy. He is given the title "tensai", or genius, due to his tactical skill on the tennis court. He is in the same class as Kikumaru Eiji, and is Eiji`s good friend. Fuji is a leap year baby (his birthday is on February 29), and thus he can only properly celebrate his birthday once every four years. Fuji is cheerful and easygoing, with a penchant for playfully teasing those around him.</description>
<picture>169965.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1442" picture="18829.jpg">Kaida Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7203" type="appears in" update="2015-03-12">
<rating votes="110">5.80</rating>
<name>Kikumaru Eiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kikumaru Eiji is a third year student at Seishun Academy (Seigaku). He is part of Seigaku`s "Golden Pair" along with Ooishi Shuuichirou. Using his acrobatic play he can return almost any ball, even those that seem out of human reach. Eiji is also known to have the sharpest vision on the team, with an exceptional talent for seeing moving objects.</description>
<picture>169969.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52" picture="19811.jpg">Takahashi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7208" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-25">
<rating votes="89">4.60</rating>
<name>Kaidou Kaoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaidou Kaoru is known as "Viper" to his teammates, though Momoshiro prefers to call him "Mamushi." He is known for constantly making a "fshuuuu", sound, similar to a snake, while exhaling. Kaidou trains rigorously, increasing the training program given to him by Inui to give him unbeatable endurance. He has a deep rivalry with Momoshiro, in which they constantly try to one-up each other. He normally plays singles, though he eventually pairs with Inui, who help Kaidou train at first.</description>
<picture>72300.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="332" picture="47528.jpg">Kiyasu Kouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7209" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-25">
<rating votes="87">5.35</rating>
<name>Momoshiro Takeshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Momo is known as Seigaku`s "number one rascal". As the player who is the most open and friendly with everyone, Momoshiro is connected to everyone on the team on some level. Momoshiro is the closest to a true friend to Echizen Ryouma, as the two spend much time together eating hamburgers or playing street tennis. Momoshiro and Kaidou Kaoru are eternal rivals, and constantly try to out-do each other. Momoshiro`s special play is called the "Dunk Smash", where he jumps very high and smashes the ball onto his opponent`s court. He can also use the "Bullet Serve" and "Jack-Knife". During the Nationals, Momoshiro shows his skill of reading the wind movements, ball, and his opponent. Momoshiro is known to have the best insight on the court of Seigaku.</description>
<picture>72298.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="183" picture="16992.jpg">Onosaka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7210" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-19">
<rating votes="66">3.08</rating>
<name>Kawamura Takashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kawamura is a soft-spoken person off the court, very gentle and shy, though still outspoken and stubborn when he takes a decision. However, he becomes extremely aggressive and loud once he grabs his racket, or any racket. This change in his personality is marked by him shouting "Burning!!!" "Great!!!" "Baby!" His personality along with these keywords when he holds a racket is most likely just for comic relief, but his personality change does have a large impact on his skills, becoming the powerhouse of Seigaku. Son of a sushi chef, he works hard in order to take over his family`s sushi restaurant.</description>
<picture>72299.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3887" picture="88970.jpg">Kawamoto Naru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7211" type="appears in" update="2011-05-25">
<rating votes="59">4.53</rating>
<name>Inui Sadaharu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Inui Sadaharu is a highly intelligent player, who uses "Data Tennis." He constantly collects and analyses data while in and outside of the tennis court in order to determine statistics, weaknesses, and other factors, and he is able to calculate the probability of certain shots being made during matches. While he collects data pertaining to tennis, he also collects personal pieces of data, such as favourite things, personal habits, and where they have been, which makes others feel awkward. In addition to his data tennis, Inui`s play style includes his extremely fast serves the Sonic Serve and later the Waterfall Serve. Inui`s data tennis style dates back to his elementary school days, when he learned it from his doubles partner Yanagi Renji.</description>
<picture>72295.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="592" picture="170729.jpg">Tsuda Kenjirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7212" type="appears in" update="2009-05-25">
<rating votes="18">4.15</rating>
<name>Ryuuzaki Sumire</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ryuuzaki Sumire is the coach of Seigaku`s tennis club, as well as one of the school`s maths teachers. It was thanks to her that Echizen Nanjirou was able to develop his skills. She is the grandmother of Sakuno. She also has a sort-of rivalry with her ex-mentor, Banda Mikiya a.k.a. Banji, who is the coach for Yamabuki. She is always there to yell, but is also considered to be a great and reliable coach.</description>
<picture>25584.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="383" picture="24124.jpg">Okohira Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9768" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-03-12">
<rating votes="133">6.84</rating>
<name>Atobe Keigo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62583.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23217" type="appears in" update="2010-10-14">
<rating votes="13">8.10</rating>
<name>Seishun Gakuen Chuutoubu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>56818.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="23330" type="appears in" update="2015-03-12">
<rating votes="3">3.43</rating>
<name>Hiyoshi Wakashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>169961.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2230" picture="21782.jpg">Iwasaki Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23334" type="appears in" update="2010-10-17">
<rating votes="7">1.61</rating>
<name>Kabaji Munehiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>57086.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3141" picture="65575.jpg">Tsuruoka Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23338" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-03-12">
<rating votes="45">9.07</rating>
<name>Kirihara Akaya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62586.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="143" picture="23260.jpg">Morikubo Shoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23345" type="appears in" update="2015-03-12">
<rating votes="2">5.71</rating>
<name>Marui Bunta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62582.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="4665" picture="27220.jpg">Takahashi Naozumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23358" type="appears in" update="2010-10-18">
<rating votes="11">4.08</rating>
<name>Mukahi Gakuto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>57128.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="381" picture="186189.jpg">Hoshi Souichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23360" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-05-02">
<rating votes="34">7.62</rating>
<name>Niou Masaharu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>57130.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="606" picture="18011.jpg">Masuda Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23365" type="appears in" update="2015-03-12">
<rating votes="51">7.86</rating>
<name>Oshitari Yuushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62575.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="280" picture="170840.jpg">Kiuchi Hidenobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23367" type="appears in" update="2010-10-18">
<rating votes="1">1.43</rating>
<name>Sakaki Tarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>57143.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23368" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-03-12">
<rating votes="21">7.77</rating>
<name>Sanada Gen`ichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>169964.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2231" picture="235895.jpg">Kusunoki Taiten</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23370" type="appears in" update="2015-03-12">
<rating votes="16">5.23</rating>
<name>Shishido Ryou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>170008.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3953" picture="25794.jpg">Kusuda Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23376" type="appears in" update="2015-03-12">
<rating votes="1">2.14</rating>
<name>Yagyuu Hiroshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62578.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="28403" picture="54086.jpg">Tsuda Eisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23377" type="appears in" update="2015-03-12">
<rating votes="10">8.05</rating>
<name>Yanagi Renji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62579.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2796" picture="23212.jpg">Takemoto Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23379" type="appears in" update="2011-10-10">
<rating votes="30">8.35</rating>
<name>Yukimura Seiichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67835.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4696" picture="27345.jpg">Nagai Sachiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23409" type="appears in" update="2011-05-25">
<name>Hirakoba Rin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72303.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23426" type="appears in" update="2011-10-10">
<rating votes="30">8.16</rating>
<name>Ootori Choutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67875.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26364" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-03-12">
<rating votes="17">8.63</rating>
<name>Kite Eishirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>169962.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2802" picture="176252.jpg">Shingaki Tarusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32743" type="appears in" update="2015-03-12">
<name>Chitose Senri</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62577.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="6077" picture="10491.jpeg">Oosuka Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32748" type="appears in" update="2015-03-12">
<name>Oshitari Kenya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>169966.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32750" type="appears in" update="2011-05-25">
<rating votes="12">8.09</rating>
<name>Tooyama Kintarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72313.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="372" picture="141584.jpg">Sugimoto Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32751" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-03-12">
<rating votes="50">8.29</rating>
<name>Shiraishi Kuranosuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>169967.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3709" picture="84359.jpg">Hosoya Yoshimasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34024" type="appears in" update="2011-06-28">
<name>Watanabe Osamu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74407.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36588" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-10">
<name>Keith</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67882.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28985" picture="68037.jpg">Saotome Taichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36589" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-10">
<name>Shiu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67896.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28984" picture="67961.jpg">Daitou Shunsuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36590" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-10">
<name>Peter</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67895.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="470" picture="17419.jpg">Irino Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="129214" update="2012-10-06">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>90</length>
<airdate>2011-09-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133159" update="2011-09-24">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
