<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8419" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-10-07</startdate>
<enddate>2011-12-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Boku wa Tomodachi ga Sukunai</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">I Don`t Have Many Friends</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">У меня мало друзей</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">나는 친구가 적다</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">В мене мало друзів</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="synonym">من دوستان زیادی ندارم</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">haganai</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">僕は友達が少ない</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Haganai</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">ชมรมคนไร้เพื่อน</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">我的朋友很少</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="official">بوکو وا توموداچی گا سکونای</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9342" type="Sequel">Boku wa Tomodachi ga Sukunai Next</anime>
<anime id="8522" type="Side Story">Boku wa Tomodachi ga Sukunai: Yaminabe wa Bishoujo ga Zannen na Nioi</anime>
<anime id="9206" type="Side Story">Boku wa Tomodachi ga Sukunai: Relay Shousetsu wa Ketsumatsu ga Hanpanai</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9310" approval="83" total="132">Yahari Ore no Seishun LoveCome wa Machigatte Iru.</anime>
<anime id="9305" approval="74" total="91">Ore no Kanojo to Osananajimi ga Shuraba Sugiru</anime>
<anime id="11480" approval="12" total="17">Netoge no Yome wa Onnanoko ja Nai to Omotta?</anime>
<anime id="7903" approval="8" total="22">Denpa Onna to Seishun Otoko</anime>
<anime id="3651" approval="7" total="27">Suzumiya Haruhi no Yuuutsu</anime>
<anime id="8179" approval="6" total="19">Mayo Chiki!</anime>
<anime id="7525" approval="4" total="25">Ore no Imouto ga Konna ni Kawaii Wake ga Nai</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="15">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="416723">wasn`t expecting much when I started watching... turned out to be one of my favorites this season.  lol at every episode, but also appreciated the depth of emotions below the surface.  great series, but too short!  hope there`s a second season.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="22000">it`s not a typical harem anime, in fact it doesn`t really run in that fashion.  It does have that flavor at times, but in all honesty, the show is a comedy and a great one at that.  Light hearted and smile worthy.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="21063">one of the more tolerable harem shows of the era. still, there were several moments where i felt extremely bored and glad i had nothing better to do than to watch this.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="21092">I must first state that I would only recommend this show if one can tolerate a fairly large degree of "in-your-face" ecchi fanservice, that is not quite as pronounced in the original light novels, but perhaps more a consequence of the animated medium. If undeterred (or interested) by that fact, this is an amusing showcase of a boy and his harem (effectively) that are either so eccentric or misunderstood that they have no friends, and their resulting chemistry is unusual enough to create numerous awkward and sometimes hilarious scenarios; made even better by the talented voice cast, and rather good animation. However, it must be said that the plot of the show is woefully thin, and may not return for a 2nd season, which many are unlikely to be upset about.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="176590">Its basically "jerks doing jerkish things".
Overall funny, sometimes heartwarming and ecchi. Will appeal to the usual anime fan.
Weak points are probably the somewhat unrelatable characters, particularly its attention-sucking MC. You may argue lack of development too, but there is some.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="211996">They hit a lot of weird corners on the counterculture block on this show, most of you will have fun watching it :) Definitely a good show.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="95465">It has narrated mecha-hentai. What`s not to like?</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="135495">A nice show all in all. Just recently caught up to it on my watch list and noticed the artwork is well done, the storys are a bit wild but it gels with the characters and its a funny trip though the episodes. Only problem I found was in the lack of any closure in the ending, sure we found out who was who, but there wasnt anything more than that so it was a massive cliffhanger with no idea what was going on, but then again there is Season 2. I`d just prefer it if there could be some closure and opening between having a major time off air...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="567315">Ok, I`m not sure I`ve EVER watched an anime as quickly as I watched this one. XD 10 episodes in one night, plus one special, and the other two and the second special the next day. Only reason I didn`t go through all of it at once was because I had class in the morning..
I digress. This anime is one of the funniest and most entertaining experiences I have had in a long while. While I enjoyed the earlier episodes the most, especially the first time they played Monster Hunter together, the entire series was great.
As mentioned with the Monster Hunter episode, my favorite moments are when they do "make-believe" episodes with some type of role play reflecting what is actually going on in real life, to hilarious results. However, the main overarching story is great as well. All characters have their flaws, but you learn to love them despite it (and some of them because of it.) An all around awesome anime that I rate very highly if you need something fun to watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="218662">good character design,funny stories,lovely girls in differet styles, you must go to watch it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="157883">This show is by far my favorite this season, and it`s the one that I`m the most eager for the new episode each week.  All the characters are awesome and likeable, and the crazy hijinx are genuinely funny without feeling cliche.  It`s a harem show on the surface, but it`s far from a run-of-the-mill harem show and the guy is much more likeable than the typical spineless indecisive boy.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="466955">THIS.
ANIME.
IS.
PURE.
GOLD.
This and Nichijou are the best comedy animes of 2011. The humor and the romance makes this anime very awesome! It`s worth watching for everyone.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="350281">A clever deconstruction of contemporary harem anime which pioneered the "hate polygon" genre.
Underneath the ecchi comedy exterior lies a deep philosophical exploration of the themes of friendship, nostalgia, social commentary and isolation.
Look beyond the cover and watch this must see masterpiece.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/haganai/1st/index-j.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="28474" type="Animation Work">AIC Build</name>
<name id="3405" type="Series Composition">Urahata Tatsuhiko</name>
<name id="6242" type="Chief Animation Direction">Fujii Maki</name>
<name id="15901" type="Character Design">Watanabe Yoshihiro</name>
<name id="27061" type="Original Work">Hirasaka Yomi</name>
<name id="6276" type="Direction">Saitou Hisashi</name>
<name id="2431" type="Music">Tom-H@ck</name>
<name id="15901" type="Chief Animation Direction">Watanabe Yoshihiro</name>
<name id="4418" type="Character Design">Ishii Kumi</name>
<name id="7781" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nakamura Naoto</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a light novel series by http://anidb.net/cr27061 [Hirasaka Yomi] with illustrations by http://anidb.net/cr24691 [Buriki].
http://anidb.net/ch32433 [Hasegawa Kodaka], a half-Japanese / half-British boy, has recently transferred to a Catholic high school, the St. Chronica`s Academy, and as always, finds it impossible to make friends there due to his naturally blond hair, inherited from his dead English mother, which makes him look like a dangerous delinquent to his prejudiced peers. One day after school, he enters the classroom witnessing the equally solitary and very abrasive girl http://anidb.net/ch32428 [Mikazuki Yozora] while she speaks to her imaginary friend Tomo. They decide that the best way to improve their social standing is to form a club — the http://anidb.net/ch37939 [Rinjinbu] (Neighbour`s Club) — just to make friends and learn social skills.
Five other members soon join, starting with the school`s well-connected and arrogant idol http://anidb.net/ch32430 [Kashiwazaki Sena], who has many male admirers but no female friends due to jealousy. http://anidb.net/ch32431 [Kusunoki Yukimura], a student often dressed as a maid, who idealises and follows Kodaka in the hope of learning to become manlier. http://anidb.net/ch32432 [Kobato], Kodaka`s younger sister who is attending St. Chronica`s middle school division and has a penchant for darkness, vampires and the macabre ever since she started watching an anime called Full Metal Necromancer. http://anidb.net/ch32429 [Shiguma Rika], a perverted underclassman and well-known scientific genius, who speaks in the third person and was saved by Kodaka during a failed experiment, thereafter trying to repay him with sex. And finally http://anidb.net/ch32434 [Takayama Maria], a precocious 10-year-old teacher and nun at the academy, who becomes the club adviser.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="5202">6.02</permanent>
<temporary count="5243">7.25</temporary>
<review count="6">6.49</review>
</ratings>
<picture>178917.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12983</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10719</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4967</identifier>
<identifier>enqnxn</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/haganai/1st/index-j.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Boku_wa_Tomodachi_ga_Sukunai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>僕は友達が少ない</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2270</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>340177</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13788</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/3199</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2011/bokuhatomodachigasukunai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="618" parentid="2565" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>trap</name>
<description>A trap is a plot device where a male character is mistaken for a female, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the male (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the male, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the male character as a female; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through his behaviour, and/or language. A male character misinterpreted by others as female, without action from the male (explicitly feminine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t1637 [reverse trap].
Note: the tag image is from http://anidb.net/a10475 [Himegoto].</description>
<picurl>161537.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1065" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-05">
<name>heterochromatic eyes</name>
<description>Heterochromia Iridis is a condition where one eye is a different color from the other, or one eye is more than one color.
Characters with different eye-colour may not necessarily have the medical condition itself, as the state of different-coloured eyes can be caused by various other reasons such as possession by spiritual entities, indication of special powers or artificial changes.</description>
<picurl>63229.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1133" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>otaku</name>
<description>Otaku, derived from a Japanese term for another`s house or family (お宅, otaku), appeared in the 1980s. In the anime http://anidb.net/a77 [Macross], first aired in 1982, the term was used by http://anidb.net/ch7418 [Lynn Minmay] as an honorific term.
In modern Japanese slang, the term otaku refers to a fan of any particular theme, topic, or hobby. Common uses are anime otaku (a fan of anime), cosplay otaku and manga otaku (a fan of Japanese comic books), pasokon otaku (personal computer geeks), geemu otaku (playing video games), and wota (pronounced ota, previously referred to as idol otaku) that are extreme fans of http://anidb.net/t2438 [idols], heavily promoted singing girls. There are also tetsudou otaku or denshamania (railfans) or gunji otaku (military geeks).
While these are the most common uses, the word can be applied to anything (music otaku, martial arts otaku, cooking otaku, etc).
Some of Japan`s otaku use the term to describe themselves and their friends semi-humorously, accepting their position as fans, and some even use the term proudly, attempting to reclaim it from its negative connotations. In general colloquial usage however, most Japanese would consider it undesirable to be described in a serious fashion as otaku; many even consider it to be a genuine insult.
The negativity which modern society shows towards otaku and otaku culture is historically partly attributed to Miyazaki Tsutomu, who became known as The Otaku Murderer in 1989. His bizarre murders fueled a moral panic against otaku. However, the public appearance of most otaku is the major reason for them to be shunned by society today.</description>
<picurl>52482.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1136" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-18">
<name>transfer student</name>
<description>A transfer student is a student who changes from one institution or course to another at the same level. Their arrival, when not at the beginning of the school year, tends to cause a stir.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1403" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-10">
<name>nun</name>
<description>A nun is a member of a religious community of women, typically one living under vows of poverty, chastity, and obedience. She may have decided to dedicate her life to serving all other living beings, or she might be an ascetic who voluntarily chose to leave mainstream society and live her life in prayer and contemplation in a monastery or convent. The term "nun" is applicable to Catholics (eastern and western traditions), Orthodox Christians, Anglicans, Lutherans, Jains, Buddhists, Taoists, Hindus and some other religious traditions.
Source: Wiktionary</description>
<picurl>165755.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1637" parentid="2565" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>reverse trap</name>
<description>A reverse trap is a plot device where a female character is mistaken for a male, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the female (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the female, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the female character as a male; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through her behaviour, and/or language. A female character misinterpreted by others as male, without action from the female (explicitly masculine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a reverse trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t618 [trap].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2396" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-08">
<name>swimsuit</name>
<description>A swimsuit is one of several kinds of garments designed to be worn by people engaging in water-based activities or sports or during certain activities under sunlight. Most kinds of swimsuit reveal a large portion of the body surface area, but exceptions exist. The more revealing kinds may also be worn as undergarment in sports that require wetsuits, or when there is a need to display the body, as in the case of beauty pageants or bodybuilding contests.
There is a very wide range of styles of modern swimsuits, which vary in relation to body coverage and materials. The choice of style of swimsuit is dependent on current fashions, community standards of modesty, and plain personal preference. Swimsuits for men usually expose the chest, while those for women do not usually do so; however, many women prefer to engage in water or sun activities with their torso uncovered, in a practice commonly described as toplessness or topfreedom. Since the early twentieth century a naturist movement has developed in western countries that seeks a return to non-sexual nakedness when swimming and during other appropriate activities; in some places around the world, nude beaches have been set aside for people who choose to engage in normal beach activities in the nude, and such beaches may or may not enforce nudity onto their goers.
In anime, it is common for at least one episode to feature the characters in swimsuits, usually as an excuse for gratuitous fanservice; when that happens, the episode is usually labeled a pool or beach episode, after the place the characters went to. Swimsuits, and in particular one-piece swimsuits, are a very common fetish in Japan; while the reason for that is uncertain, a common folk explanation is the fact that boys throughout their entire adolescence are commonly exposed to their female classmates wearing them, in what might be called an experiment in sexual discovery waiting to happen.</description>
<picurl>149786.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2566" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-31">
<name>loli</name>
<description>Lolita (often also just abbreviated to loli) refers originally to a novel by Vladimir Nabokov. The book is internationally famous for its controversial subject: the narrator and protagonist, middle aged Humbert Humbert, becomes obsessed and sexually involved with a 12-year-old girl named Dolores Haze.
Nowadays the name "Lolita" describes a sexually precocious young girl.
Related to this is http://anidb.net/t2415 [lolicon], the Japanese abbreviation of the English phrase "Lolita Complex". Sometimes written as "roricon" or "rorikon" due to the inexact mapping between Japanese and English phonemes. This is the term used to describe the fetish/fascination some mature people have for underage girls. There is an entire industry in Japan devoted to providing legal but schoolgirl-themed pornography, taking advantage of the cute childlike appearance some Japanese women maintain well into their twenties.
Because the characters in anime are often young by convention, many fans think that a character can only be Lolicon if she is twelve or younger. Exceptions are granted if the other character in the relationship is a lot older.
One particular device used to skirt the boundaries of taste and legality is the exotic being (alien, creature of magic, robot or the like) which takes the form of an underage human girl, but is in fact for all other practical purposes an adult.
Another reason why lolicon is fetishized by people may be because some of them just view it as a substitute for their fetish for flat-chested, but otherwise well-developed, women.
Source: Wikipedia / TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2664" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-07">
<name>catholic school</name>
<description>A setting for this anime is a school run by the nuns and/or priests of the Church Of Rome.
Religious instruction may be an integral part of the plot. Religious icons - particularly crosses and crucifixes are usually prominent.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2784" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>sudden girlfriend appearance</name>
<description>Sudden Girlfriend Appearance anime involve a sudden change in the main character`s life where (s)he suddenly gets confronted with an individual (s)he`s sexually attracted to, the two of them inevitably becoming a couple.</description>
<picurl>210066.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2825" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-28">
<name>pseudo blowjob</name>
<description>A character is sucking or licking a banana, ice pop, sausage, or similar item in an erotic way.</description>
<picurl>160588.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2865" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>summer festival</name>
<description>The summer festival is used to show off the female protagonists in traditional Japanese clothing — the yukata — a casual form of kimono.
The festivities include food stalls (cotton candy, candy apples, choco bananas, taiyaki), various games (scoop goldfishes), and a fireworks display.</description>
<picurl>161023.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2909" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>karaoke</name>
<description>Obligatory national pastime for students in any anime with school setting. Amateur singing to subtitled music videos.
The word itself is a compound of the Japanese words for "empty orchestra".</description>
<picurl>160894.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3092" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-02">
<name>important haircut</name>
<description>When a character cuts off his or her hair, it often symbolizes a rite of passage or bout of character growth. A princess striking out on an adventure, or a new recruit at boot camp, for instance. Hair is something that takes time and effort to grow, so parting with it voluntarily can be a powerful act.
This is particularly a big deal when women get haircuts. Yet in fiction, even an accidental hair slicing can leave a character with a surprisingly even cut.
In many religions (Western Christianity, Ancient Egyptian religion, and others) priests and/or monks cut/shave their hair. Roman Catholic nuns also tend to cut and mantain their hair short under their veils when they enter the nunneries. The cutting of one`s own hair is also a part of Buddhist mythology, specifically something done by Siddhartha himself early on in his path to enlightenment, so anime examples might draw from this as an allusion. There are also some cultures, including Native American and many Asians, where a person would cut his or her hair as an act of grief, disgrace, or even rebellion. In the Confucian tradition, hair (like the rest of your body) is considered a gift from your parents and may not be damaged without a very good reason. Furthermore, prisoners and psychiatric patients commonly have their heads shaved, often to prevent the spread of lice, but sometimes also as a demeaning measure.
Source: TVTRope</description>
<picurl>169641.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3107" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-10-12">
<name>unfoundedly feared character</name>
<description>Due to some strange misunderstanding, or some other unfounded reason the character in the anime is feared by his contemporaries.
Example: A male student with an "evil eye" is mistaken for a delinquent, and thus feared by the students in his class.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3395" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-18">
<name>promise</name>
<description>A dramatically-made promise that serves as foreshadowing. The promise will eventually be called in and action will be required.
Whether they succeed, fail or refuse to keep their promise depends almost entirely on the idealism-level of the story. Other factors, such as whether they were told what they had to do, or if it was a Leonine Contract, may come into play. Even Releasing from the Promise is usually a scene of high drama.
Source: TVTropes</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3721" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-07">
<name>RPG elements</name>
<description>The anime shows elements of a `R`ole `P`laying `G`ame, either as part of a parody or because the anime is actually based on an RPG.
Typical elements: When collecting items, beating opponents, or levelling up a distinct (often childishly sounding) sound cue is played. A HUD (`H`eads `U`p `D`isplay) may also be presenting in combat, showing vital player and "enemy" statistics.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4116" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-13">
<name>eternal blush</name>
<description>It is no ordinary blush it is a blush that does not disappear.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4386" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-19">
<name>eating Pocky</name>
<description>Pocky (ポッキー) is a Japanese snack food produced by the Ezaki Glico Company of Japan. Pocky was first sold in 1966, and consists of a biscuit stick coated with chocolate. It was named after the Japanese onomatopoetic word for the sound Pocky makes when bitten, pokkin (ポッキン). The original was followed by "Almond Pocky" in 1971, with an almond coating, and "Strawberry Pocky" in 1977. Today, the product line includes such variations as milk, mousse, green tea, honey, banana and coconut flavored coatings, and themed products such as "Decorer Pocky," with colourful decorative stripes in the coating, and "Men`s Pocky," a dark (bittersweet) chocolate and "mature" version.
Source: Wikipedia
It`s marketed in Germany under the name Mikado (Note: NOT the game, the snack).</description>
<picurl>73630.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6021" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>gender bender</name>
<description>Term used to refer to a person who takes on the role of their opposite gender. This often only reaches to the extent of cross-dressing (involving physical appearance and clothing only), but in rarer cases, involves a total gender swap (which seems to be more common in anime) - where the willing or unwilling victim receives a body opposite of their original gender (either permanently or temporarily), with all natural parts per their new body fully (or just all-out amply) included.
Example of cross-dressing gender bender: "Maria+Holic"
Examples of body-swap gender bender: "Kashimashi: Girl meets Girl", "Birdy the Mighty Decode"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6046" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>pool episode</name>
<description>An episode playing at the pool, mostly in school, sometimes outside of it when the cast does not have a chance for a beach episode.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version of the http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode].
Other variants are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160904.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7075" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-05-07">
<name>adapted into Japanese movie</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a Japanese movie.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="6998" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="26">7.38</rating>
<name>EVA-02</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Evangelion Unit 02, built by Nerv Germany, is the first Production Model Eva. It is piloted by Souryuu Asuka Langley and is the first Evangelion built specifically for combat. The Eva`s armour is primarily red with yellow and white on the arms and head. The head armour has two movable sections, one covering both the jaw and lower eyes and the other above the upper pair of eyes. These plates are hinged and can shift, displaying the Eva`s eyes underneath. This is first seen underwater during the fight with Gaghiel. As a result of being constructed by Nerv Germany, and also as an accommodation for its three-quarters-German pilot, its default language setting is German. Unit 02 features a different progressive knife from earlier Eva units as well as an internal weapon rack in the right shoulder binder which fires dartlike weapons.
Unlike Unit 01, it only goes truly "berserk" once, just before its destruction. It has achieved an unusually high sync ratio with its pilot(s), on two other occasions: once in combat against the 6th angel Gaghiel, and once under the influence of the 17th Angel. It is known to contain the maternal part of the soul of Asuka`s mother.
Unit 02 has blue blood, which is first seen when the fourteenth Angel, Zeruel, cuts off its arms. It has brown skin and four orange eyes, first seen when the MP Evas tear it apart.</description>
<picture>30415.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="9902" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-04-17">
<rating votes="63">4.09</rating>
<name>Cecily Cambell</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cecily Cambell is a 3rd generation knight from The Knight Guards of Housman, the Third City, of the Independent Trade Cities. Her grandfather, a former nobleman who became a knight was one of the founders of the Independent Trade Cities during the Valbanil War which since then, the Cambell family have served as knights protecting the city`s independence. When her father died of an illness, Cecily took up the role of the head of house, and thus became a knight.
When the anime begins, she is portrayed as inadequate and doesn`t fight well. Cecily later improves significantly. However, the manga and light novels depict her as a strong, smart girl with great leadership skills; the viewers are shown this in an early chapter when she leads a group of knights and mercenaries against a band of thieves and monsters. This version of Cecily learns from her mistakes quickly and is a skilled sword fighter. In both versions, she is prideful person and takes offense of any negative remark from Luke. As the series progresses, she develops romantic feelings toward Luke.</description>
<picture>36441.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="9903" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="34">3.73</rating>
<name>Luke Ainsworth</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Luke Ainsworth, the titular character, is a blacksmith of great skill and renown and is also a talented swordsman. Possessing dark brown hair and blue eyes, he is arrogant, private and often insensitive to others. He lives with Lisa, who aids him in his work and often accompanies him on his business. He comes to know Cecily after saving her repeatedly from certain death. Luke wields a Japanese katana and employs a unique sword-fighting style, which is uncommon in a land where most people use a longsword and shield. He also possesses extraordinary blacksmith skills, as well as the magical ability to forge a katana in the midst of a battle.
When Cecily sees his katana cut a sword in two, the same sword that shattered her own, she desires one of her own and persistently asks him to forge one for her. While he often comments on her pride and hotheaded personality and her large breasts, he comes to like and admire Cecily. Her will to protect the city and everyone within it reminds him of Lisa Oakwood, the love of his youth who was slain before his eyes by Valbanil.</description>
<picture>36442.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="17522" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-10-14">
<rating votes="195">5.55</rating>
<name>Saori Vageena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saori Vageena is one of the active female members of the anime forum that Kirino wound up frequenting, and organized the get-together in Akihabara where she met Kirino and Kuroneko for the first time. She is the peacemaker of the group, and her friendly disposition helps to defuse tensions between Kirino and Kuroneko, keeping their arguments about each other`s tastes from getting out of hand. She tends to speak in a very quirky way, always using a very polite and antiquated mode of Japanese generally heard today only in samurai movies. Not much is known about her for certain, not even her real name (Saori Vageena is her handle on the anime board and evidently a pseudonym), but brief scenes of her at home show her in what looks a large mansion, attended by maids and butlers, implying that she is very wealthy, although neither the Kousaka siblings nor Kuroneko seem to be aware of this.</description>
<picture>55757.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="17524" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="354">4.22</rating>
<name>Kousaka Kyousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kousaka Kyousuke is the main protagonist of the series, and acts as the narrator. He is a fairly ordinary second-year high school student who wishes for nothing more than a peaceful life until he accidentally discovers his little sister Kirino`s otaku hobbies. Even though Kirino is mean and disrespectful to him, he tries to be a good elder brother to her, giving her advice as best he can, and helping her to continue in her hobbies and make new friends. He is a responsible and reliable person who cares deeply about the welfare of his sister and of his friends.</description>
<picture>55755.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="17525" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-12-17">
<rating votes="913">4.89</rating>
<name>Kousaka Kirino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kousaka Kirino is the main heroine of the series. She is a 14-year old girl who seems normal on the outside, but is in secret a hardcore otaku obsessed with anime and visual novel eroges, especially those involving little sisters. She works part-time as a model, which is how she managed to purchase her most impressive collection of figurines, visual novels, and anime DVDs. She has a talent for writing, and loves track and field.
She is initially cold and disrespectful towards her brother Kyousuke, but after he discovers her secret hobby and he supports her in it, they gradually grow closer.</description>
<picture>53292.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="17526" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-04-21">
<rating votes="1020">8.54</rating>
<name>Gokou Ruri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kuroneko (a.k.a. Gokou Ruri) was one of the anime otaku girls Kirino had met in a gathering organized by Saori. Though their tastes in anime and games greatly differ, they nevertheless began to be good friends. She also became a good friend to Kyousuke, and it is hinted that she may have feelings for him. As befits the Kuroneko epithet, she is usually seen wearing a black Gothic Lolita-style dress, and is sharp-tongued and antisocial.
She enters Kyousuke`s high school later in the series, and joins the Game Club at his urging, displaying her considerable talents at writing and graphic design.</description>
<picture>55756.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="32428" type="main character in" update="2017-05-11">
<rating votes="440">5.69</rating>
<name>Mikazuki Yozora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A cruel and selfish black-haired girl who says she understands and respects bullying but resents being called a bully herself, Yozora`s difficult personality drives away anyone who might wish to make friends with her before she meets http://anidb.net/ch32433 [Kodaka]. She is physically abusive towards, and often argues with, http://anidb.net/ch32430 [Sena] and manipulative towards http://anidb.net/ch32434 [Maria], who she cons into giving up an empty room for the use of the http://anidb.net/ch37939 [Neighbor`s Club], and http://anidb.net/ch32431 [Yukimura], who she fools into working for the club as a cross-dressing cosplay maid. The only person she can`t insult is http://anidb.net/ch32429 [Rika], as Rika takes whatever insult she gives her and deflects it back with a dirty joke that leaves her tired - to the point where she just does what Rika says (like cross-dress for example) rather than argue.
She is Kodaka`s childhood friend, though at the time, he believed that she was a boy, calling her "Sora"; her nickname for him was "Taka." On the day that Kodaka moved, she intended to wear a skirt and reveal her gender to him but was too embarrassed to do so. Kodaka eventually recognized her after she had to cut her hair short due to it catching on fire. She seems to have feelings for Kodaka.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>76319.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32429" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-26">
<rating votes="361">7.36</rating>
<name>Shiguma Rika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A freshman and highly capable mad scientist. She was saved by http://anidb.net/ch32433 [Kodaka] when she fell unconscious during a disastrous lab experiment, and begs to repay his kindness with sex; she joined the http://anidb.net/ch37939 [Neighbor`s Club] just to get closer to him.
Although there are many adult themes in the series, she is the most sexually forward member. This was clearly highlighted in her first speaking appearance, when she described the attractions of rape to Kodaka in the middle of a stunned class. She has a habit of inserting any sexual innuendo possible in her sentences, to the point where she finds it normal to convert any innocent thought into something perverted. As a fujoshi, she is a passionate consumer of BL doujinshi and magazines, is comically aroused by intercourse between mecha, and is delighted when http://anidb.net/ch32431 [Yukimura] offers to have sex with Kodaka. Rika is proud of her perverseness, as she says that she would be a boring person if people only thought of her as a genius girl. To compound her eccentricity, she speaks in the third person.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>76322.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="304" picture="17139.jpg">Fukuen Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32430" type="main character in" update="2017-05-11">
<rating votes="513">7.77</rating>
<name>Kashiwazaki Sena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The wealthy blonde daughter of the school`s headteacher, Sena shows a dislike of all things "ordinary". She is both attractive and academically successful, but her resulting arrogance leads her to be disliked by her female peers. Their admiration eludes her, much as she desires it; she treats her male classmates only as servants to be used, although many of them would like to be her boyfriend. Nonetheless, she holds http://anidb.net/ch32433 [Kodaka] to a higher standard. Kodaka concludes that she is the weirdest member of the club, as she is able to warrant weird and disgusted looks not only from http://anidb.net/ch32428 [Yozora] and http://anidb.net/ch32432 [Kobato], but also from http://anidb.net/ch32431 [Yukimura] and http://anidb.net/ch32429 [Rika].
She enjoys playing video games, including dating sims and eroge, partially because they allow her to make female (if virtual) friends. She is generally fascinated by the girls in these games and has also taken a liking to Kobato. Yozora calls her "Meat" (肉 Niku - due to her large breasts?), an insulting nickname which she secretly likes because it was the first she had ever received.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>76320.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32431" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-26">
<rating votes="233">5.56</rating>
<name>Kusunoki Yukimura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>First introduced as a stalker of http://anidb.net/ch32433 [Kodaka]. "His" first meeting with the http://anidb.net/ch37939 [Neighbor`s Club] resulted in gender confusion, as "his" appearance is decidedly feminine despite "his" assertions of male hood (which are ultimately shown to be false, when her true biological gender is finally revealed).
A gullible student with low self-esteem, she admiringly believes Kodaka to be a romantic and masculine criminal who lives life the way he wants to, and eagerly pledges to become his underling on the basis that she can learn to become less effeminate through him; however, she also appears to harbor a crush on Kodaka. She fittingly refers to Kodaka as "aniki". She tends to do everything Kodaka says to the extreme; when Kodaka asked her to bring http://anidb.net/ch32434 [Maria] something healthy to eat, Yukimura brought a protein shake and tried to force it down her throat until she finished it all.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>76321.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25804" picture="71817.jpg">Yamamoto Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32432" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-22">
<rating votes="409">7.65</rating>
<name>Hasegawa Kobato</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch32433 [Kodaka]`s younger sister; she is a student in middle school, but nonetheless joins the http://anidb.net/ch37939 [club]. She is very close to her brother, who she calls "An-Chan", and behaves in a jealous and clingy way whenever she feels that he is not giving her the attention she deserves, to the point where it is obvious that she has a brother complex. She sees http://anidb.net/ch32434 [Maria] as a rival for Kodaka`s brotherly affections and so often gets into fights with the latter. Despite being older than Maria she has smaller breasts than her, which Maria is always eager to point out.
She has a penchant for darkness, vampires and the macabre ever since she started watching an anime called Full Metal Necromancer. As a result she often speaks in an affected fashion, and claims to be known as "Reisys VI Felicity Sumeragi", an ancient vampire who has lived for ten thousand years, and wears a gothic dress and red contacts, but this facade quickly breaks down when she gets emotionally worked up and she speaks in a strong Kyushu accent. Indeed, her behavior does not for the most part differ from that of a regular girl (procrastinating with her homework, staying inside when it is hot, etc.) which Kodaka points out, causing her to be embarrassed and slightly lose character.
Moreover, she is not very good at mathematics, taking a long time to solve a question Kodaka posed to her, and displays rather limited vocabulary, frequently getting words wrong.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>76323.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32433" type="main character in" update="2017-05-11">
<rating votes="275">5.13</rating>
<name>Hasegawa Kodaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The protagonist, a transfer student who has not been able to make friends in his first month at St. Chronica`s. Of all of the members of the club, he is the most gentle, balanced and socially competent in personality; but his unusual hair color, inherited from his late English mother, leads classmates to assume he is a violent and abusive delinquent and spread defamatory rumors about him. Because of his long experience of antagonism, Kodaka has become accustomed to fighting and can defend himself quite well.
His father is working in the United States, and so he takes care of his younger sister alone at home, which has also made him a good cook. His childhood was characterized by frequent movement, and as a result he has few memories related to home life and close friendships; however, though he does not realize it at first, he and http://anidb.net/ch32428 [Yozora] were childhood friends before his family moved.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>76318.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2225" picture="192115.jpg">Kimura Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32434" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-26">
<rating votes="214">4.13</rating>
<name>Takayama Maria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Maria is the supervising teacher of the http://anidb.net/ch37939 [Neighbors Club]; she is a ten-year old nun. While she`s a child genius she is also very rude and immature, and often uses a variety of expletives when annoyed. She develops a sibling-like relationship with http://anidb.net/ch32433 [Kodaka], who regularly makes her packed lunches, and is affectionate with him, much to http://anidb.net/ch32432 [Kobato`s] annoyance. She is also gullible, which http://anidb.net/ch32428 [Yozora] uses to her advantage, and at some point, Kobato uses it to win an argument.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>76324.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37431" type="appears in" update="2011-10-07">
<rating votes="11">6.36</rating>
<name>Asada-sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65591.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28861" picture="65897.jpg">Seri Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37741" type="appears in" update="2017-05-11">
<rating votes="5">6.35</rating>
<name>Hawk</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68894.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2225" picture="192115.jpg">Kimura Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37742" type="appears in" update="2017-05-11">
<rating votes="10">6.68</rating>
<name>Kashiwazaki Sena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68912.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37743" type="appears in" update="2017-05-11">
<rating votes="7">7.57</rating>
<name>Night</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68910.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37744" type="appears in" update="2011-10-14">
<rating votes="7">7.24</rating>
<name>Fujibayashi Akari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68914.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37745" type="appears in" update="2011-10-14">
<rating votes="2">2.58</rating>
<name>Suzuki Masaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68915.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="567" picture="80605.jpg">Asanuma Shintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37746" type="appears in" update="2011-10-14">
<rating votes="4">5.78</rating>
<name>Nagata Yukiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68916.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="89" picture="148709.jpg">Yahagi Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37930" type="appears in" update="2011-10-21">
<rating votes="3">4.33</rating>
<name>Natsumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71160.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="37931" type="appears in" update="2017-05-11">
<rating votes="8">5.46</rating>
<name>Sora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71161.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37932" type="appears in" update="2011-10-21">
<rating votes="7">5.79</rating>
<name>Lace</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71162.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3202" picture="24193.jpg">Nakamura Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37933" type="appears in" update="2011-11-24">
<rating votes="7">5.03</rating>
<name>Guernica</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77534.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5023" picture="62245.jpg">Obata Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37939" type="appears in" update="2011-10-22">
<rating votes="4">9.65</rating>
<name>Rinjinbu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Rinjinbu is a club at St. Chronica`s Academy founded by Mikazuki Yozora specifically designed for people who don`t have very many friends. They try to learn how to build friendships through cooking together, playing games, and other group activities.</description>
</character>
<character id="37940" type="appears in" update="2012-01-09">
<name>Kashiwazaki Semoponume</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The http://anidb.net/ch37939 [Rinjinbu]`s main character in Kirameki School Life 7. His name was originally going to be http://anidb.net/ch32430 [Kashiwazaki Sena] but http://anidb.net/ch32428 [Mikazuki Yozora] changed it at the last minute by randomly picking a bunch of characters to create the given name Semoponume.</description>
</character>
<character id="38372" type="appears in" update="2017-05-11">
<rating votes="6">5.66</rating>
<name>Hasegawa Kodaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76696.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2225" picture="192115.jpg">Kimura Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38373" type="appears in" update="2011-11-03">
<rating votes="8">5.78</rating>
<name>Shiguma Rika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76697.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="304" picture="17139.jpg">Fukuen Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38374" type="appears in" update="2017-05-11">
<rating votes="9">5.67</rating>
<name>Kashiwazaki Sena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76698.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38375" type="appears in" update="2012-10-03">
<rating votes="8">5.88</rating>
<name>Takayama Maria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>This is Maria as she appears when she plays Romancing Saga XIV. The design of her clothing is a very obvious parody of Index from To Aru Majutsu no Index.</description>
<picture>76699.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38376" type="appears in" update="2011-11-03">
<rating votes="6">3.95</rating>
<name>Kusunoki Yukimura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76700.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25804" picture="71817.jpg">Yamamoto Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38377" type="appears in" update="2017-05-11">
<rating votes="9">6.43</rating>
<name>Mikazuki Yozora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76701.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38589" type="appears in" update="2017-05-11">
<rating votes="8">7.27</rating>
<name>Taka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76946.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28861" picture="65897.jpg">Seri Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38590" type="appears in" update="2012-01-26">
<rating votes="19">6.55</rating>
<name>Kashiwazaki Pegasus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is http://anidb.net/ch32430 [Sena`s] father and the chairman of St. Chronica`s. He is a friend of Kodaka`s father, and pulled strings so that http://anidb.net/ch32433 [Kodaka] could attend the school. He`s embarrassed by the unusual pronunciation of his first name (which normally would be pronounced "Tenba"). He constantly badmouths Kodaka`s father, but only because he truly values him as a best friend. He seems intent to betroth Sena to Kodaka, often saying that he considers Kodaka to be "a man I can entrust Sena to". He`s a wealthy man always seen wearing traditional clothing, and is quite weak to alcohol.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>76948.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38591" type="appears in" update="2017-05-11">
<rating votes="34">6.55</rating>
<name>Stella</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76949.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38987" type="appears in" update="2011-11-24">
<rating votes="3">3.54</rating>
<name>Mizuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77533.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="39020" type="appears in" update="2011-11-25">
<rating votes="4">6.32</rating>
<name>Lace</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77589.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3202" picture="24193.jpg">Nakamura Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39021" type="appears in" update="2011-11-25">
<rating votes="4">2.97</rating>
<name>Marina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77591.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="51991" type="appears in" update="2013-02-22">
<rating votes="66">5.89</rating>
<name>Takayama Kate</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130544.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="132536" update="2012-11-06">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132564" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="26">6.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">僕達は友達が出来ない(´･ω･`)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Can`t Make Any Friends</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bokutachi wa Tomodachi ga Dekinai</title>
<summary>Yozora and Kodoka are loners at school. In order to make friends with other misfits, they start the Neighbors Club.  Soon, a third member joins the club: Sena, a popular girl who annoys Yozora to no end.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="133183" update="2012-11-08">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133718" update="2015-10-23">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133719" update="2011-12-23">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133722" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-04</airdate>
<rating votes="17">6.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">今度はSAGAがガチな戦いヽ(`Д´)ノ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This Time, the SAGA Is a Serious Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kondo wa SAGA ga Gachi na Tatakai</title>
<summary>Rika gets the group to play a new RPG. Of course, the gang’s manic dynamic is as much a problem in the virtual world as it is in the real one. Later, Kodaka must deal with a surprising new Club member.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="133723" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-28</airdate>
<rating votes="18">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">後輩達は遠慮がないΣ(゜ロ゜;</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Underclassmen Don`t Hold Back</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kouhaitachi wa Enryo ga Nai</title>
<summary>The Club gets a couple of new freshmen members: Yukimura, who’s been following Kodaka around to learn some lessons in manliness, and Rika, an awkward young scientist.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="133724" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-21</airdate>
<rating votes="22">7.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">市民プールはフラグがない(;´Д`)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">There Are No Flags at the Swimming Pool</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shimin Pool wa Flag ga Nai</title>
<summary>Kodaka tries to give Sena a swimming lesson, but some obnoxious guys hanging out by the pool make the situation even more uncomfortable than it already is. Luckily, Kodaka’s got Sena’s back.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="133725" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="21">7.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">電脳世界は神様が居ない(ﾟДﾟ)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">There`s No God in the Electric World</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dennou Sekai wa Kamisama ga Inai</title>
<summary>Yozora, Kodaka, and Sena try to bond over some co-op video game action. Unfortunately, the girls are way better at bashing each other than working as a team.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="134607" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-11</airdate>
<rating votes="16">6.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カラオケボックスは客が少ない(つд⊂)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">There Aren`t Many Customers at the Karaoke Box</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Karaoke Box wa Kyaku ga Sukunai</title>
<summary>When the Neighbors Club heads out to sing some karaoke, the whole group ends up divided between multiple rooms. Later, Yozora gets jealous when she hears that Sena’s dad wants to meet Kodaka.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="134760" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-18</airdate>
<rating votes="18">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">携帯電話は着信が少ない_|￣|o</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Cell Phone Doesn`t Get Many Calls</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Keitai Denwa wa Chakushin ga Sukunai</title>
<summary>With summer break approaching, the gang decides to use their cell phones to keep in touch. Sena decides to get the same model as Kodaka`s - a choice which drives Yozora totally insane.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="134863" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-25</airdate>
<rating votes="17">5.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スクール水着は出番がない\(^o^)/</title>
<title xml:lang="en">School Swimsuits Don`t Appear</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sukuuru Mizugi wa Deban ga Nai</title>
<summary>Kobato’s burning up, thanks to a busted A/C. Inspired by her favorite anime, she decides to wear more season-appropriate attire. Later, the Neighbors Club heads to the pool to cool off.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="134949" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-02</airdate>
<rating votes="19">7.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">理事長は追想が切ない(-_-)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The President`s Recollections Are Painful</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rijichou wa Tsuisou ga Setsunai</title>
<summary>Sena takes Kodaka and Kobato to meet her father, Pegasus. They decide to spend the night - and lots and lots of awkward situations ensue.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="134951" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="18">4.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">僕達は友達が少ない(`･ω･´)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Don`t Have Many Friends</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bokutachi wa Tomodachi ga Sukunai</title>
<summary>The origins of the Neighbors Club – and a few gender-bending secrets – are finally revealed! What on Earth will happen next!?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="134952" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-16</airdate>
<rating votes="18">6.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">女子は浴衣姿がな, 超可愛い(ﾟ∀ﾟ)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girls Are Super-Cute in Yukatas</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Joshi wa Yukatasugata ga na, Chou Kawaii</title>
<summary>It’s festival time! Kodoka talks to Sena about hair dye, and Yozora’s hair becomes a casualty of a fireworks display!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="134953" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-09</airdate>
<rating votes="16">6.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">合宿は皆が寝ないヽ(ﾟ∀ﾟ)ﾉ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">No One Sleeps at Camp</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gasshuku wa Minna ga Nenai</title>
<summary>The gang heads to Sena’s summer home, where they spend hours romping on the beach. Later, the group settles in for some ghost stories. Unfortunately, after the chilling tales, everyone’s too scared to go to the bathroom alone.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="135465" update="2015-10-23">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-12-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144027" update="2018-02-04">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>2012-03-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Air Recital Event Digest</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145307" update="2012-11-06">
<epno type="4">T16</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145308" update="2012-11-06">
<epno type="4">T15</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145309" update="2012-11-06">
<epno type="4">T14</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145310" update="2012-11-06">
<epno type="4">T13</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145311" update="2012-11-06">
<epno type="4">T12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145312" update="2012-11-06">
<epno type="4">T11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145313" update="2012-11-06">
<epno type="4">T10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145314" update="2012-11-06">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145315" update="2012-11-06">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145316" update="2012-11-06">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145317" update="2012-11-06">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145318" update="2012-11-06">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145319" update="2012-11-06">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145320" update="2012-11-06">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145321" update="2012-11-06">
<epno type="4">T18</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD&amp;BD CM 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145322" update="2012-11-06">
<epno type="4">T17</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD&amp;BD CM 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
