<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8437" restricted="false">
<type>Music Video</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2005-12-14</startdate>
<enddate>2005-12-14</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Passion</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">Passion</title>
</titles>
<description>Partially animated music video of Passion (English version is called Sanctuary) performed by http://anidb.net/cr4739 [Utada Hikaru]. Animation by http://anidb.net/cr738 [Studio 4°C].</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="193">4.79</permanent>
<temporary count="193">5.64</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>208507.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6666</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Passion_(Utada_Hikaru_song)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Passion_(宇多田ヒカルの曲)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Passion_(宇多田光單曲)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=kT-YtuzNqIY</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5980" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-24">
<name>live-action imagery</name>
<description>This anime incorporates still images and/or video footage of real-world objects and locations into the animation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="130205" update="2011-05-19">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2005-12-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
