<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="85" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2001-04-03</startdate>
<enddate>2001-09-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Star Ocean Ex</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">SoEx</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">スターオーシャンEX</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Star Ocean EX</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="638798">Even though the story of Eleanor had some real drama to it, the way the story as a whole was told by the game was better. I wish they could`ve used more of the game`s music than just renditions of Rena`s locket. And it sucks they never got to Energy Nede. Fans Only</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="2323" type="Series Composition">Kanemaki Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="683" type="Series Composition">Sekijima Mayori</name>
<name id="2744" type="Direction">Watanabe Hiroshi</name>
<name id="7807" type="Character Design">Kurata Ayako</name>
<name id="5353" type="Original Work">Azuma Mayumi</name>
<name id="6647" type="Music">Sakuraba Motoi</name>
</creators>
<description>In an endless sea of stars, at the edge of the universe, a single fateful encounter is about to take place. For the gods have set forth on a quest to destroy the universe. And a deadly meteorite, which they hurled into the vastness of space, has collided with an unsuspecting planet, Expel - putting the wheels of fate into motion. Now, two people are about to cross paths, and their meeting will force them to endure both the gods and their devilish advisors.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1157">4.29</permanent>
<temporary count="1171">6.79</temporary>
<review count="3">6.44</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221641.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>796</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1005</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>386</identifier>
<identifier>niorfv</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Star_Ocean:_The_Second_Story_(manga)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>スターオーシャンEX</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>234350</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4540</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7488</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="153" parentid="1609" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>dark elf</name>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1609" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-03-01">
<name>elf</name>
<description>The origin of Elves (Norse; álfar(elves), álfr(elf)) can be found in ancient Norse mythology, in which, elves are described as divine, or near-divine, race of humanoids (Vættir), likened to the Æsir. In common description they are described as sage and immortal beings occupying the threshold between humans and the gods. In some cases humans that were beloved by the gods became elves within their lives. Ancient Elves are delineated into a pair of similar but distinct races; Light Elves (Ljósálfar) and Dark Elves (Svartálfar), each originating from separate homes within the nine worlds of Yggdrasil. Within the Poetic Edda the differences are commonly ascribed as:
"There is one place there that is called the Elf Home (Álfheimr which is the elven city). People live there that are named the light elves (Ljósálfar). But the dark elves (Dökkálfar) live below in earth, in caves and the dark forest and they are unlike them in appearance - and more unlike them in reality. The Light Elves are brighter than the sun in appearance, but the Dark Elves are blacker than pitch." (Snorri, Gylfaginning 17, Prose Edda)</description>
<picurl>63489.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2345" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-02-06">
<name>zettai ryouiki</name>
<description>"Absolute Territory" (絶対領域, Zettai Ryouiki in Japanese) describes the area of uncovered thigh between the skirt and the knee sock.
As per usual for fandom who obsess about costumes, this can be considered a moe attribute and thus, present prominently in character designs and schoolgirl outfits. The term originates from http://anidb.net/a22 [Neon Genesis Evangelion] to designate an area of Absolute Terror, although it`s had considerable semantic drift. In this case, it may jokingly refer to the fact it emphasizes a shorter skirt without actually becoming creepy and showing the underpants.
As if that wasn`t enough, some even categorize it into five "Grades", from E to A. Only the top two (A and B) are considered true Zettai Ryouiki and they are only usable by female characters. Some researchers additionally introduce Grade S, the highest one which consists of Grade A plus further requirements to personality and hairstyle.
Just to make it clear, Zettai Ryouiki is made up of three components: socks, skin, and skirt. An Action Girl may trade the latter for hotpants but if it doesn`t include knee-highs and thighs, it`s not Zettai Ryouiki. Panty Shot is an entirely different zone.
For more information on sock lengths in general, see also: http://anidb.net/t6419 [hosiery]
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>165582.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2801" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>RPG</name>
<description>Any anime that is based on a role-playing game aka RPG. A role-playing video game is a video game which includes elements of non-electronic role-playing games. The player assumes control of one or several fictional characters (a party) who have joined forces in order to perform quests and overcome a great number of challenges and enemies, usually monsters inspired by fantasy, and, to a lesser extent, science fiction and classic mythology. During the course of the game the characters, or avatars, which are generally defined by quantized characteristics, evolve and improve in that their various attributes increase, as well as by gaining more powerful artefacts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3285" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>journey</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3314" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-10">
<name>fate</name>
<description>Fate — The predestined path of all things. The outcome is inevitable and the consequences predetermined. Whether or not the protagonist ultimately decides to follow this path shall weigh heavily on their soul.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3836" parentid="3314" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-28">
<name>the chosen one!</name>
<description>One of the characters in the anime is the "chosen one", the one to bring about change, the only one to "set things right" in a "good" ending, or bring about complete destruction in a "bad" ending.</description>
<picurl>66957.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3863" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-05">
<name>competition</name>
<description>Some sort of confrontation occurs in this show. The protagonists "duke it out" via various competitions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5355" parentid="3863" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-13">
<name>tournament</name>
<description>A competition involving a large number of participants. Such competitions may range from friendly, moderated sporting events to anything-goes, all-out fights to the death.
All participants take part in the tournament in want or need of the final goal and possible prizes; which depending on genre, may range from a boastful record at school to great riches and/or the granting of a wish. 
Depending on the type of tournament, contestants will either act alone, be permitted a team, or construct a team of chance throughout the ongoing competition.</description>
<picurl>227699.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7852" type="main character in" update="2009-06-01">
<rating votes="8">3.87</rating>
<name>Rena Lanford</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A native of the planet of Expel, she often ventures into the Shingo Forest. One day, a monster appears in the forest and attacks her; she is saved by Claude. In accordance to local legends, she believes Claude to be the "Legendary Warrior." She now accompanies Claude on his quest. Rena is a sweet-natured girl with a pensive, thoughtful side as well as the power to heal. She is devoted to Claude almost from the start, and slowly falls in love with him as the journey comes on.</description>
<picture>26890.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2138" picture="21613.jpg">Iizuka Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7853" type="main character in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="6">4.91</rating>
<name>Claude C. Kenni</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>After an accident causes him to wind up on the underdeveloped planet of Expel, Claude rescues Rena Lanford from a monster and is thought to be the "Legendary Warrior of Light" by the residents of the local village. He is now on a quest to investigate the Sorcery Globe, which he hopes will help him return to his own world. Claude has some skill in hand-to-hand combat and picks up swordsmanship fairly quickly, even learning Dias` Kuuhazan attack after seeing it once. Having grown up in the shadow of his famous father, Claude is humble and has a lot of self-doubts, but he grows stronger through his adventures, as does his growing friendship, and love, for Rena.</description>
<picture>30885.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2039" picture="41388.jpg">Wakabayashi Naomi</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="4586" picture="21115.jpg">Yuuki Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7855" type="main character in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="7">6.36</rating>
<name>Celine Jules</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A treasure hunter from the village of Mars, she is a powerful wielder of Heraldic Magic, but has a fear of bugs, which is used as a running gag throughout the series. She accompanies Claude and Rena on their journey, but often seems to be more interested in teasing Claude and Rena about their growing love for each other.</description>
<picture>31968.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3398" picture="224826.jpg">Kingetsu Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7876" type="main character in" update="2015-02-24">
<rating votes="6">6.20</rating>
<name>Ashton Anchors</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ashton is a swordsman possessed by a two-headed dragon. Ashton himself is noisy and can be clumsy, but he is a capable fighter and can act courageously when the need arises. Regularly plagued with bad luck, people avoided him and he lived a lonely existence. After meeting Claude, Rena, and Celine, who offered him genuine friendship, he claims that they are the reason the dragons are infused with his body as an excuse to travel with them. Though Ashton is angry when he learns Gyoro and Ururun have been taking over his body, when he receives the King`s Teardrop that would remove them he can`t go through with it because it would cause them die and he is too fond of them. When he meets Precis, he falls in love with her but she only has eyes for Claude.</description>
<picture>169365.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7877" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="5">4.48</rating>
<name>Dias Flac</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dias lived in the same town as Rena and considers her his little sister, though they are unrelated. After his family was killed by bandits, he left Arlia to spend time traveling and training to become stronger. When he finds someone worthy of his skills, he is quick to test their might. As a result of his horrible tragedies, Dias often appears anti-social, rebellious, and spiteful.</description>
<picture>39018.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7878" type="main character in" update="2009-07-25">
<rating votes="4">4.96</rating>
<name>Gyoro</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gyoro, the red head, and Ururun, the blue, are the names of the heads of the two-headed dragon that are fused with the body of Ashton Anchors. Though they originally shared one body, the heads are capable of independent thought and are considered separate individuals though they also speak as one. They have the ability to possess Ashton, speaking through him and using his body to fight. Gyoro attacks with fire, while Ururun uses a freezing attack. When Gyoro and Ururun fully possess Ashton, his eyes glow the color of the head speaking and his speech becomes more arrogant to match their personalities. Ashton doesn`t remember what happens while he is possessed, and is furious when he learns that they have been doing so. Still, he chooses not to remove them when given the opportunity, because it would kill them.</description>
<picture>32004.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1981" picture="1918.gif">Usui Takayasu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7880" type="main character in" update="2009-06-01">
<rating votes="4">4.56</rating>
<name>Ururun</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gyoro, the red head, and Ururun, the blue, are the names of the heads of the two-headed dragon that are fused with the body of Ashton Anchors. Though they originally shared one body, the heads are capable of independent thought and are considered separate individuals though they also speak as one. They have the ability to possess Ashton, speaking through him and using his body to fight. Gyoro attacks with fire, while Ururun uses a freezing attack. When Gyoro and Ururun fully possess Ashton, his eyes glow the color of the head speaking and his speech becomes more arrogant to match their personalities. Ashton doesn`t remember what happens while he is possessed, and is furious when he learns that they have been doing so. Still, he chooses not to remove them when given the opportunity, because it would kill them.</description>
<seiyuu id="78" picture="16686.jpg">Shimura Tomoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7881" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="5">4.71</rating>
<name>Precis F. Newman</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Precis is a young girl inventor from the town of Linga. She is a brilliant inventor capable of putting together contraptions very quickly, however they don`t always work the way she plans. She is good friends with a girl named Eleanor, who is inflicted with a fatal disease. To save her friend, Precis goes alone into an area of monsters to get the cure. Precis has a crush on Claude, whom she thinks of as her prince, and is blind to Ashton`s being in love with her.</description>
<picture>32003.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2205" picture="186188.jpg">Hanba Tomoe</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7882" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="4">3.64</rating>
<name>Bowman Jean</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dr. Bowman lives in Linga, and is said to be the most knowledgeable man in town when it comes to medicine. He was once a prestigious professor and connected to the Lacour`s researchers. He also knew Leon`s parents, but left Lacour while Leon was still a toddler.</description>
<picture>32005.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="455" picture="17356.jpg">Matsumoto Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7883" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="2">5.72</rating>
<name>Leon D.S. Geeste</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young prodigy in the capital of Lacour, Leon often acts egotistical, vain, and bratty due to the high accolades showered on him. When out of his "safety zone" or faced with a challenge he can`t overcome, Leon acts more like the child he is and loses his usual egotism.</description>
<seiyuu id="3921" picture="206017.jpg">Mitsuhashi Kanako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7884" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-06-23">
<rating votes="5">4.65</rating>
<name>Opera Vectra</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Opera is an adventurous woman who journeys to find her true love, Ernest. Opera, as well as Ernest, are from the planet Tetragenes, and are stranded on Expel. She will go anywhere to find him, just to be near him. Opera is very brave, passionate, and devoted.
Note: interestingly enough, this character`s name actually has absolutely nothing in common with the similarly called car (the Opel`s "Vectra" model, which was produced from 1988 to 2008). Star Ocean EX is an animated adaptation of a video game ("Star Ocean II: The Second Story" entry of the famous franchise, to be precise) and this character was planned to be named "Opera" right from the very beginning of the development of the said title, quite a few years before anime adaptation was made. The extreme similarity between this character`s name and the car`s model name is purely coincidental due to bad translation.</description>
<picture>63747.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1682" picture="41033.jpg">Matsumoto Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7885" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-25">
<rating votes="4">2.99</rating>
<name>Ernest Raviede</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Like Opera, Ernest is from the planet Tetragenes, and is stranded on Expel. Ernest is an archaeologist, and is very passionate about his profession. Though he deeply loves Opera, he can not abandon his job. Though he often leaves her behind while researching, he trusts that she will always meet up with him.</description>
<picture>32002.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2016" picture="240331.jpg">Yanaka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7886" type="appears in" update="2009-06-01">
<rating votes="1">6.95</rating>
<name>Yuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="435" picture="188447.jpg">Matsumoto Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="4288" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-05-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">空破斬</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kuhazan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuuhazan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4289" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">紋章術師</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heraldic Magic</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Monshou Jutsushi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4290" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔石</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Magic Stone</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maseki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4291" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-04-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">遭遇 ~コンタクト~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Encounter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Souguu: Contact</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4292" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-04-03</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">時空転送</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Transport</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jikuu Tensou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4880" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-05-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">双頭竜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Two-Headed Dragon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soutou Ryuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4881" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-05-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">異邦人 テトラジュネス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tetragenes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ihoujin: Tetragenes</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4882" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-05-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">涙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Teardrop</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Namida</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4883" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-05-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">潮風 ハーリー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Harley</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiokaze: Harley</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4884" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-06-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幽霊船</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ghost Ship</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuureisen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4885" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-06-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">発明少女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Invention Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hatsumei Shoujo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4886" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">月光花 メトークス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Metox</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekkoubana: Metox</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4887" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-06-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暴走</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rampage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bousou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4888" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔剣 ラクール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lacour</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maken: Lacour</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4889" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">疑惑</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Suspicion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Giwaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4890" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">少年 レオン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Leon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shounen: Leon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4891" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">遺跡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ruins</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iseki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4892" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">要塞</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fortress</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yousai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4893" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">孤独</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Solitude</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kodoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4894" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">希望</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Faith</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kibou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4895" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">再会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reunion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4896" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">仲間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Friends</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nakama</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4897" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦 ラクールホープ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lacour Hope</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen: Lacour Hope</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4898" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">機械城</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Machine Castle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikaijou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4899" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">光輝石 エナジーストーン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Energy Stone</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Terukouseki: Energy Stone</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4900" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇者 クロード</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Man Of Valor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusha: Valor</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84341" update="2007-10-14">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="87816" update="2008-01-26">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="87826" update="2008-01-27">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
