<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8505" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-06-15</startdate>
<enddate>2011-06-15</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Asobi ni Iku yo! Asobi ni Oide</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">あそびにいくヨ! あそびにおいで</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Cat Planet Cuties OVA</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7400" type="Parent Story">Asobi ni Iku yo!</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1"/>
<url>http://www.asoiku.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="2995" type="Animation Work">AIC Plus+</name>
<name id="2382" type="Character Design">Morishima Noriko</name>
<name id="1648" type="Direction">Ueda Youichi</name>
<name id="2382" type="Chief Animation Direction">Morishima Noriko</name>
<name id="3399" type="Music">Kikuya Tomoki</name>
<name id="19832" type="Original Work">Kamino Okina</name>
<name id="2836" type="Series Composition">Takayama Katsuhiko</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a light novel series by http://anidb.net/cr19832 [Kamino Okina].
It is already summer and the Catians decide to study the games on Earth. To make things more interesting, http://anidb.net/ch17530 [Manami] suggests that each participant should wage a precious item and whenever a person wins a round they may choose one of these items as a reward. While http://anidb.net/ch17528 [Aoi] and Manami covet a special item waged by http://anidb.net/ch17529 [Kio], their priorities change when they are risking to let a DVD with embarrassing scenes of both get into the wrong hands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1136">3.80</permanent>
<temporary count="1143">6.26</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>73551.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11965</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9618</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>29998</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.asoiku.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Asobi_ni_iku_yo!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>あそびにいくヨ!#OVA</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2227</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>340236</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="760" parentid="2274" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>robot helper</name>
<description>In a http://anidb.net/t2846 [science fiction] setting, the robot helper is, in a comedic sense, pretty much equivalent to what the "cute comic relief http://anidb.net/t1835 [animal sidekick]" is in a fantasy setting. The usually small machine has artificial intelligence, enabling it to support their owner / master with advice or help with menial tasks.
http://anidb.net/t1278 [Androids] should not be considered robot helpers since these are far more complex; use the android tag instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1969" parentid="2756" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-23">
<name>mahjong</name>
<description>Mahjong is a tile-based game, which was developed in China during the Qing dynasty. It is commonly played by four players.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>215287.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2756" parentid="2881" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>board games</name>
<description>People here play a board game. It can vary from chess and Go, to Monopoly, to Dungeons and Dragons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2916" parentid="2756" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-12">
<name>shougi</name>
<description>Japanese chess.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2917" parentid="2756" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>chess</name>
<description>Chess is a game for two players. It is played on a square board, made of 64 smaller squares, with eight squares on each side. Each player starts with sixteen pieces (eight pawns, two each of knights, bishops, and rooks, and one king and queen). One player`s pieces are a light color, he is called "White", and the other player`s pieces are a dark color, he is called "Black".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4112" parentid="3842" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-14">
<name>excessive censoring</name>
<description>There are basically two cases to which this term can be applied to:
1) creative censorship
The TV station airing the anime does its best to remove most ecchi parts from the show, using various and original methods. Usually, an uncensored BD/DVD is released later. Apart from the publisher`s greed - sometimes the censorship is used intentionally to make a scene look more obscene than it actually is.
2) convenient censorship
Another case of it - more often known under the term of "convenient censoring/ship" - is a blatant substitute for mosaic/steam/etc. over nether regions. This applies both to normal shows with occasional nudity as a normal part of human life (or just occasional flash of fanservice), as well as to heavy ecchi / borderline hentai shows where /literally/ everything is a fair (and far more "obscene" no matter how to look at it) game, except that misinterpreted taboo nonsense coming from §175 of JPC.</description>
<picurl>169459.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5484" parentid="6191" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-02-14">
<name>poker</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6191" parentid="2881" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-05">
<name>card games</name>
<description>A card game is any game using playing cards as the primary device with which the game is played, be they traditional or game-specific. Countless card games exist, including families of related games (such as poker). A small number of card games played with traditional decks have formally standardized rules, but most are folk games whose rules vary by region, culture, and person.
Many games that are not generally placed in the family of card games do in fact use cards for some aspect of their gameplay. Similarly, some games that are placed in the card game genre involve a board. The distinction is that the gameplay of a card game primarily depends on the use of the cards by players (the board is simply a guide for scorekeeping or for card placement), while board games (the principal non-card game genre to use cards) generally focus on the players` positions on the board, and use the cards for some secondary purpose.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="17527" type="main character in" update="2013-08-01">
<rating votes="96">7.18</rating>
<name>Eris</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A 16-year-old scout for the Catian people exploring Earth. Tall and well endowed, she has easily befriended many people, and regular cats she has met on Earth. Initially most do not believe her to be an alien, but she shows Kio the proof directly with her technology, ears and tail. While she is learning the ways of Earth, she is also a competent fighter who employs strategies and technologies not seen on Earth. Her interactions with Kio are closer and more emotional, potentially due to the fact she is 16 and about to enter her first heat. With the kindness and interest he has shown, she has selected him as a mate. Eris was forced to take chemicals to end her first heat prematurally as it was causing disruption to her duties as an ambassador and representative of Catians on Earth, with high expectations for her second heat and another chance to mate with Kio. She develops feelings for Kio after she found out he risked his life to save her when she was captured. When Aoi admitted that she was jealous of her closeness to Kio, she finally kisses him in the last episode, after Eris reveals due to Catian law they could all be Kio`s lovers, she did not bear any ill will towards her and is happy that somebody else shares the same feelings as she does.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>47660.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17528" type="main character in" update="2011-04-06">
<rating votes="66">6.70</rating>
<name>Futaba Aoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She seems to have romantic feelings for Kio but is actually a member of the special branch of the Japanese immigration office. She possesses the unique ability to warp in weaponry as needed and is dispatched on missions that range from dealing with oversea smugglers (as seen in the action-packed opening scenes) to eliminating alien threats and those who harbor them. What`s more, she`s like a completely different person when it comes to business, so much that she`ll scare the crap out of her messenger for making remarks about her and Kio. She apparently has the uncanny ability to come out of any situation alive and unscathed too, earning her the nickname Akuuon Momiji 「悪運紅葉」 that is feared by many. Akuuon means bad luck (for those who cross her path), whereas Momiji describes the colour of leaves changing in fall.</description>
<picture>48147.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17529" type="main character in" update="2013-08-01">
<rating votes="47">1.78</rating>
<name>Kakazu Kio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kakazu Kio is a kindhearted, yet sophisticated teenage boy. Kio is easily able to accept the proof that his new friend is an alien, and that both his other friends are secret agents. He knows how to handle firearms, though he is not sure what business his Uncle Yuichi is in to have them. He displays a strong sense of justice, and is willing to take action when he feels it is needed. This sense, and his treatment of others, draws the attention of his female friends. He is unsure about his reaction to all that interest, and their attention begins to cause complications for Kio. Eris the Catian in particular has decided that she wishes to be his mate as she is about to come into her first heat. In the final episode of the anime, he temporarily becomes a catboy.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>48148.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3712" picture="240126.jpg">Tamura Mutsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17530" type="main character in" update="2013-08-01">
<rating votes="62">7.16</rating>
<name>Kinjou Manami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A tomboy, childhood friend, and next door neighbor of Kio. Since she was young she wanted to join the CIA, where her room is filled with listening equipment and guns. She was in the CIA recruitment program operating under the supervisor codenamed JACK, but believes she is no longer a candidate after helping rescue Eris. She also lives at the Catian Embassy under its diplomatic immunity. She has feelings for Kio, but believes he sees her as just one of the guys and that she "let her chance slip by", so she roots for Aoi to get him before "that alien steals him away". She wears a watch with a noticeable scratch on it, which it got the day she realized she was in love with Kio; she will often rub the scratch when nervous. She has a noticeable fascination with guns, to the point where Kio refers to her as a gun otaku. She is often very pushy when it comes to helping Aoi make progress with her relationship with Kio, because she does not wish to see Aoi`s chance to slip by as she believes hers has. She finally kisses him in the last episode, after Eris reveals due to Catian law they could all be Kio`s lovers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>47657.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18126" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-01">
<rating votes="45">7.73</rating>
<name>Coone</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Catian Starship Captain, has a commanding bust. She is in charge of the contingent responsible for establishing diplomatic relations with Earth`s leaders.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>48638.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18127" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-01">
<rating votes="41">6.52</rating>
<name>Melwin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Catian Starship First Officer.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>48639.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18128" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-01">
<rating votes="44">6.86</rating>
<name>Chaica</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Catian Starship Crew. She stands guard over the Catian Embassy whenever Eris and company are out.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>48640.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1798" picture="20493.jpg">Kotobuki Minako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18449" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-01">
<rating votes="25">5.53</rating>
<name>Antonia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Antonia Lirimonie Norfedras Papanorgas Arecroteles Cnorses Morfenoss is a wealthy 12 year old, leader of the Underside of Kitten Paw cult and rarely seen without wearing a pair of cat ears. She grows attached to Kio in the last episode due to him becoming a cat boy.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>50307.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5886" picture="30429.jpg">Nomizu Iori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18450" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-01">
<rating votes="19">7.25</rating>
<name>Sara</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of Antonia`s personal maids. She has short, blonde hair and an eyepatch over her right eye. She has an undeniable weakness toward anything cute and catlike and forms an attachment toward one of Eris` Assist-A-Roids. Apparently, it was because of this weakness that she was unable to maintain her former job as a mercenary soldier.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>50306.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18451" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-01">
<rating votes="15">4.92</rating>
<name>Jens</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Dogisian in charge of the underground relations between her home planet and governments through Earth. After knowing about the arrival of Catians on the planet, she devises schemes to prevent establishment of official diplomatic relations between them, including trying to eliminate Eris and her friends.
[i]Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>54382.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18453" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-02">
<rating votes="22">7.12</rating>
<name>Itokazu Maki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kio`s teacher and leader of Beautiful Contact Japan Sect. Due to the fact Elis doesn`t represent the stereotypical alien (tentacles, green skin, etc), she firmly believes that Elis, despite the obvious, is not really an alien.</description>
<picture>54383.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3006" picture="226210.jpg">Hirata Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18454" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-01">
<rating votes="21">6.11</rating>
<name>Maya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of Antonia`s personal maids. She had long, reddish hair and a small scar on her lower-left cheek. Not much is known about her, but she apparently has some connections with the KGB as she was able to procure ICBMs to be made into a spacecraft.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>50305.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2945" picture="177565.jpg">Ishizuka Sayori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19791" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-02">
<rating votes="13">5.67</rating>
<name>Miyagi Yuuichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kio`s uncle.</description>
<picture>54384.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32" picture="16618.jpg">Tachiki Fumihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20112" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-01">
<rating votes="28">7.77</rating>
<name>Durel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Catian Starship Doctor. Her personality is reminiscent of Star Trek`s Mr. Spock as she views things in a calm, and logical manner. Her comment about Eris being fortunate in having a partner (Kio) for her first heat leads to Manami becoming extremely flustered and jealous.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>52127.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="252" picture="149852.jpg">Shindou Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20170" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-02">
<rating votes="8">6.87</rating>
<name>Assistroid</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Assistroid, short for assistant android, are helpers to the Catians. They were created from soil, which was rearranged through nanomachines and as such can perform various advanced operations, including teleport.
Although highly advanced they are not provided with a language function and usually express themselves through the use of placards.
Since Elis created 20 such assistroids and they all look the same, they were given later on numbers to differentiate between them.</description>
<picture>54380.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="21335" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-01">
<rating votes="15">5.58</rating>
<name>Ooshiro Arisa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of Kio`s classmates and a member of the film club.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>54464.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="539" picture="228668.jpg">Aizawa Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21336" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-01">
<rating votes="17">4.13</rating>
<name>Ishimine Aiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of Kio`s classmates and a member of the film club.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>54465.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1932" picture="65403.jpg">Sendai Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21337" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-01">
<rating votes="32">5.66</rating>
<name>Ichika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ichika appearred for the first time in episode 7. She`s shown to have some sort of connection with Jen and the Dogisians. Furthermore she can use power cards to improve abilities, whether they are hers or of someone else. After the credits on episode 12 of the anime adaption, it is revealed that she is an "immortal" Catian and discusses other lifeforms over the phone to an unidentified male.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>54658.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="411" picture="17475.jpg">Takagaki Ayahi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21431" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-08">
<rating votes="6">1.36</rating>
<name>Muttley</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An assistroid of the Dogisian race. As part of his cooling system he produces a kind of wheezing snicker. His character was modelled after the Hanna-Barbera character Muttley, who appeared in Wacky Races, and his same trademark snicker.</description>
<picture>54659.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19477" picture="50701.jpg">Kondou Hironori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21444" type="appears in" update="2013-08-01">
<rating votes="4">3.66</rating>
<name>Fukuhara Satoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of Kio`s classmates and a member of the film club.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>67877.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="21451" type="appears in" update="2011-07-17">
<rating votes="4">3.66</rating>
<name>Eizoubu Buchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The president of the film club.</description>
<picture>75668.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="21452" type="appears in" update="2013-08-30">
<rating votes="5">5.84</rating>
<name>Sadayan</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sadayan is Kio`s personal assistroid.</description>
<picture>142100.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="21453" type="appears in" update="2011-01-07">
<rating votes="4">6.11</rating>
<name>Chiba-chan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chiba-chan is Futaba`s personal assistroid. He is based on the actor Chiba Shin`ichi, also known as Sonny Chiba.</description>
<picture>62192.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="21454" type="appears in" update="2011-01-07">
<rating votes="6">5.33</rating>
<name>Kin-chan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kin-chan is Futaba`s personal assistroid. He is based on the actor Kinnosuke Yorozuya.</description>
<picture>62194.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="21455" type="appears in" update="2010-10-11">
<rating votes="4">7.10</rating>
<name>Yun-Fat</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yun-Fat is Manami`s personal assistroid. He is based on the actor Chow Yun-Fat.</description>
<picture>54671.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="130907" update="2013-04-05">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2011-06-15</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Come Drop By</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Come Drop By</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Come Drop By</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130909" update="2018-07-05">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-06-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130910" update="2011-06-16">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-06-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131016" update="2011-06-18">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-06-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Owari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131161" update="2011-07-06">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2011-06-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ichika Special</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
