<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8508" restricted="true">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>6</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-12-22</startdate>
<enddate>2016-02-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Euphoria</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ユーフォリア</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">유포리아</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">euphoria</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="2400" approval="6" total="15">Gantz</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="617782">if you like Guro + BDSM youll definitely like this</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="267233">This is basically different scenarios, but doesn`t include the full story (at this time). I expect there will be at least 6 episodes total (one per main heroine).  A bit tame compared to what I`ve seen, but might be a bit extreme for your average viewer.  The visual novel explains much better what is going on.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://entacom.org/clockup/product/dvd/euphoria.htm</url>
<creators>
<name id="918" type="Original Work">ClockUp</name>
<name id="32114" type="Direction">Ayano Kunio</name>
<name id="32114" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ayano Kunio</name>
<name id="32321" type="Animation Work">Majin</name>
<name id="42564" type="Character Design">Citizen</name>
<name id="33720" type="Direction">Matano Ryuuzou</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the erotic game by http://anidb.net/cr918 [ClockUp].
They wake up in a white room remembering nothing.
The protagonist http://anidb.net/ch34834 [Takatou Keisuke] and 6 others are locked up in these hidden white rooms. His childhood friend http://anidb.net/ch34839 [Hokari Kanae], classmate http://anidb.net/ch34835 [Andou Miyako], underclassmate http://anidb.net/ch34837 [Makiba Rika], English teacher http://anidb.net/ch34836 [Aoi Natsuki], same year http://anidb.net/ch34838 [Byakuya Rinne], and classmate http://anidb.net/ch34840 [Manaka Nemu]. While still confused about their unusual situation, a "mystery voice" suddenly speaks to them: "A game has now started." In order to escape the room, Keisuke is the "unlocker" and one heroine the "keyhole". With an assigned act, he must "use the key".
Source: necrosistranslations.wordpress.com</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="589">4.21</permanent>
<temporary count="600">5.94</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>68274.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13245</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10851</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5028</identifier>
<identifier>rmtvoq</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.a1c.jp/~majin/product/eupho06.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.a1c.jp/~majin/product/eupho05.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://entacom.org/clockup/product/dvd/euphoria.htm</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.a1c.jp/~majin/product/eupho01.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.a1c.jp/~majin/product/eupho02.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.a1c.jp/~majin/product/eupho03.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.a1c.jp/~majin/product/eupho04.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14481</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6540</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="363" parentid="2901" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-07-14">
<name>nostril hook</name>
</tag>
<tag id="893" parentid="2729" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-12">
<name>dominatrix</name>
<description>A dominatrix is a woman, typically a paid professional, who takes the dominant role in BDSM activities. A dominatrix may be of any sexual orientation, which does not necessarily limit the genders of her submissive partners. The role of a dominatrix may not even involve physical pain toward the submissive; her domination can be verbal, involving humiliating tasks, or servitude. The umbrella term for BDSM activities involving a dominatrix is female dominance, female domination, or simply femdom.
Source: Wikipedia.</description>
<picurl>230370.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1894" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-04">
<name>shota</name>
<description>Shotacon, sometimes shortened to shota, is a Japanese slang portmanteau of the phrase Shoutarou complex and describes an attraction to young boys, or an individual with such an attraction. Outside Japan, the term is less common and most often refers to a genre of manga and anime wherein pre-pubescent or pubescent male characters are depicted in a suggestive or erotic manner.
In a general sense, this is the same as http://anidb.net/t2566 [loli], just replace young girls with young boys.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>35399.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2225" parentid="2729" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-14">
<name>whipping</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2578" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-12">
<name>vulgar</name>
<description>Talking (and acting) in a way that is considered uncultivated, bawdy, common, coarse or unrefined, or "taboo" according to existing cultural standards. Includes boorish manners and obtrusive display of carnal "assets".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2615" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-25">
<name>18 restricted</name>
<description>This isn`t really an "audience".
While some anime might feature sexual content they still might not be considered pornography. This category is meant only for when the content is clearly *not* intended for minors. The distinction is made by whether the content is sold only to adults.</description>
<picurl>67867.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2697" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-05">
<name>voyeurism</name>
<description>Voyeurism is the sexual interest in or practice of spying on people engaged in intimate behaviors, such as undressing, sexual activity, or other actions usually considered to be of a private nature. The principal characteristic of voyeurism is that the voyeur does not normally interact directly with the subject of his/her interest, who is often unaware of being observed. The essence of voyeurism is the observing but may also involve the making of a secret photograph or video of the subject during an intimate activity. When the interest in a particular subject is obsessive, the behavior may be described as stalking.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162189.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2702" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-16">
<name>mammary intercourse</name>
<description>Mammary intercourse is a sex act, performed as foreplay or as non-penetrative sex, that involves the stimulation of the male penis by the female breasts. Commonly, this sex act involves the man placing his penis in the woman`s cleavage and thrusting between her breasts, while the breasts are squeezed around the penis for additional stimulation, and fellatio may also be performed in combination. Mammary intercourse is also commonly known as titty-fucking or titfuck in the United States, as well as tit wank or French fuck in the United Kingdom. The Japanese term, paizuri (from oppai, breasts, and the verb suru, used in this context to describe the sexual act), is commonly used in the anime fandom. A variant term is "naizuri" (a pun on nai, the negative of the verb aru, indicating existence/presence), which describes an attempt to do a paizuri, but with insufficient cleavage.</description>
<picurl>174692.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2704" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-15">
<name>cum play</name>
<description>Fetish of sorts where the focus is of the semen that is ejaculated. This can include snowballing, drinking copious amounts of semen, eating it off food, using it to brush one`s teeth, acting as a urinal for semen, gargling it, rinsing one`s mouth with it, or any other act where semen is involved that does not have to do with fertilization of an egg.
This should not be used if one cannot visibly see semen in scenes or if the scene is extremely short.</description>
<picurl>236279.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2705" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-20">
<name>creampie</name>
<description>The act of a man ejaculating inside a girl`s vagina, leaving the semen oozing out of her.</description>
<picurl>160720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2706" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>masturbation</name>
<description>Manual erotic stimulation of the genitals or other erogenous regions, often to orgasm, either by oneself or a partner.</description>
<picurl>210612.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2707" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-20">
<name>internal shots</name>
<description>Internal shots are pictures that display the interior of the body of a living being, either through the skin, kind of as an "x-ray" of sorts, or from the inside, as if the camera was also inside. This is generally used during sex scenes to display the inside of any area being penetrated. Those shots may happen either by making an area of the body transparent or by displaying the same area again, but from the inside; the latter method is shown in the picture.</description>
<picurl>213307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2710" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-18">
<name>squirting</name>
<description>Squirt, a small, quick stream, a jet when girl gets orgasm.</description>
<picurl>227795.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2711" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-25">
<name>urination</name>
<description>Urination, also known as micturition, voiding, peeing, weeing, pissing, and more rarely, emiction, is the ejection of urine from the urinary bladder through the urethra to the outside of the body. In healthy humans the process of urination is under voluntary control. In infants, some elderly individuals, and those with neurological injury or extreme psychological problems, urination may occur as an involuntary reflex. In other animals, in addition to expelling waste material, urination can mark territory or express submissiveness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2712" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>sex toys</name>
<description>A sex toy is an object or device that is primarily used to facilitate human sexual pleasure, such as a dildo or vibrator.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2713" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>oral</name>
<description>Oral sex is sexual activity involving the stimulation of the genitalia of a sex partner by the use of the mouth, tongue, teeth or throat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2714" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>point of view</name>
<description>Point of view pornography (POV) is adult entertainment that is filmed as if the watcher had experienced the sex-acts themselves.</description>
<picurl>161100.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2715" parentid="7220" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-11">
<name>rape</name>
<description>Rape means to force someone to engage in sexual interaction without their consent. If the rape is not successfully executed (both fellatio and penetration did not occur), tag with http://anidb.net/t7238 [attempted rape] instead.</description>
<picurl>212186.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2717" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>anal</name>
<description>Sodomy, buggery, buttsex, cornholing, or the poop-chute polka. Call it whatever you like, but somebody is getting something stuck where the sun does not shine.</description>
<picurl>173755.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2718" parentid="2715" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male rape victim</name>
<description>Contrary to the more common situation, the rape victim is a male instead of a female. 
A common situation in hentai anime, a male character, commonly a lucky http://anidb.net/t1931 [harem lead], is sexually overpowered by their enticing and overly seductive female counterparts. These situations are usually undesired by the male character... though as a viewer, one might wonder why.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2721" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-13">
<name>public sex</name>
<description>Public sex refers to sexual acts that take place in public or semi-public places.</description>
<picurl>175406.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2722" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-21">
<name>doggy style</name>
<description>Bang her from behind and use her boobies as a steering wheel!</description>
<picurl>161394.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2724" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-15">
<name>double penetration</name>
<description>Double penetration is a situation during which someone is simultaneously penetrated by two penises or strap-ons.</description>
<picurl>172771.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2725" parentid="2848" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-20">
<name>ahegao</name>
<description>A term for the weird face occasionally seen in adult games/anime/manga. Canonically, ahegao has eyes rolled up, mouth open and tongue sticking out. Sometimes also referred to as "fucked silly".</description>
<picurl>175637.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2727" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>stomach stretch</name>
<description>Visible abdominal distortion from objects or anatomy pressing out from within the vaginal or anal cavity. Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t2935 [stomach bulge] or http://anidb.net/t775 [pregnancy].</description>
<picurl>178246.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2728" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>fisting</name>
<description>To insert a fist into a sexual area of the human body.</description>
<picurl>172774.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2733" parentid="2715" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-20">
<name>enjoyable rape</name>
<description>This anime features a rape scene during which the raped character also reaches orgasm or somehow else derives sexual pleasure from the act.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2746" parentid="2901" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-26">
<name>shibari</name>
<description>Not to be confused with Hojoujutsu (捕縄術) or Nawajutsu (縄術), which is the traditional Japanese martial art of restraining a person using cord or rope.
More commonly known as Kinbaku (緊縛) in Japan, Shibari is the word for "erotic bondage" or Kinbaku-bi which means "beautiful bondage". Kinbaku (also Sokubaku) is a Japanese style of sexual bondage or BDSM which involves tying up the bottom using simple yet visually intricate patterns, usually with several pieces of thin rope usually hemp or jute (generally 6 mm or 8 mm in diameter). The person`s body can also be hanging from the rope while tied to it.
The word Shibari came into common use in the West at some point in the 1990s to describe the bondage art Kinbaku. Shibari (縛り) is a Japanese word that literally means "to tie" or "to bind". It is used in Japan to describe the artful use of twine to tie objects or packages.
In anime/manga, Shibari or Kinbaku is often seen as a tool of rape or torture, rather than intended for a concept of bondage aesthetics.</description>
<picurl>161702.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2781" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>first kiss</name>
<description>The first kiss plays a role in this anime. Especially for the female cast this can be quite an important moment, so that stealing ones first kiss is serious for them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2816" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sexual fantasies</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime let their imaginations run wild thinking about another character.
Yes, they are thinking about sex, and in an ecchi anime these thoughts are often perverted, leading to a nosebleed. But it may also be romanticising simply being husband and wife, and everything that implies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2823" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>paper clothes</name>
<description>Worn clothing appears paper-thin and takes little abuse to be shredded or torn from the body. This is common in ecchi anime where the main storyline involves some type of fighting but consists primarily of dialogue and fanservice (Ikkitousen and Platonic Heart). Various girls’ clothing exploding as if made of rice paper is a very enticing prospect.</description>
<picurl>150776.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2893" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>female teacher</name>
<description>Any kind of female teacher will do, even if she only does home visits. Female teachers imply mature women (even if they sometimes look like schoolgirls) dressed in what women would typically wear when doing official business (like a blouse, pinstripe dress with side front slit), but of course, not limited to that. Furthermore, school nurses also count as female teachers unless they`re actually wearing a nurse outfit, which they almost never are.
Almost completely exclusive to hentai animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2894" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>female student</name>
<description>Pretty much exclusive to hentai shows only unless an ecchi show has implied sex and/or a strong indicator of nudity. A character is considered a student if she goes to school, doesn`t matter if it`s high school, college or homeschooling, but she should be of appropriate age for a student; a housewife going to college should not get this category.</description>
<picurl>210611.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2896" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-23">
<name>deflowering</name>
<description>Deflowering is the act of breaking the hymen of a female who hadn`t yet had vaginal intercourse. This tag can be applied only to pornographic anime in which a female is seen being deflowered; most often, one knows she had been a virgin because blood is seen coming out of her vagina during sex or after it, but her word on the matter is also considered valid.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2900" parentid="2712" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-20">
<name>dildos - vibrators</name>
<description>These are toys that are used for sexual pleasure.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2901" parentid="2729" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-09">
<name>bondage</name>
<description>Bondage is the use of restraints for the sexual pleasure of the parties involved. It may be used in its own right, as in the case of rope bondage and breast bondage, or as part of sexual activity or BDSM activity. When a person is sexually aroused by bondage, it may be considered a paraphilia, known as vincilagnia (from Latin vincio, to bind or fetter with chains, and lagneia, lust).
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42021.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2902" parentid="2729" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-11">
<name>facesitting</name>
<description>Facesitting, also known as queening, or kinging, is a sexual practice in which one partner sits on or over the other`s face, typically to allow or force oral-genital or oral-anal contact. It is common for this position to form part of BDSM, involving dominance and submission, though this need not be the case. Within a BDSM or D/S context, facesitting can be an especially intense form of erotic humiliation.</description>
<picurl>191151.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2903" parentid="2848" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-21">
<name>scat</name>
<description>Coprophilia, also called scatophilia or scat, is a sexual fetish involving feces. This anime depicts defecation in the context of said fetish, be it as minor as a burst of brown liquid caused by an enema or as major as actual ingestion of pieces of excrement.
Scatophilia is a fairly common motif in Japanese animated pornography, and has even spawned a fairly successful meme inside the fandom, in which http://anidb.net/a735 [Yakin Byoutou] (more commonly known in the western world as Night Shift Nurses) character http://anidb.net/ch28915 [Nanase Ren] appears on screen with the superimposed line: "how can you say you love her if you can`t even eat her poop?"
Because, really, how can you? How dare you?</description>
<picurl>126784.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2905" parentid="2729" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-14">
<name>erotic torture</name>
<description>Erotic torture involves deliberately using (almost) any form of physical or excessive psychological abuse to inflict physical and/or mental pain, with the goal of inducing sexual pleasure. Examples include, among others, hot wax on skin, nipple clamps, electricity, extreme verbal and derogatory abuse, forced public exhibition, etc.
This is distinct from the common, non-erotic http://anidb.net/t6730 [torture], which is generally for the purpose of inflicting pain, to either fulfill a desire of the torturer, or to apply coercion to compel action from the victim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2921" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-12">
<name>throat fucking</name>
<description>The act of actively thrusting one`s penis into a persons mouth and throat.</description>
<picurl>236088.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2995" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-18">
<name>nipple penetration</name>
<picurl>166106.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3027" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-10">
<name>sex tape</name>
<description>A sex tape is a camera recording of sexual acts, regardless of the actual storage medium. Such recordings are sometimes made against the will or even knowledge of the depicted persons.
While most of them are made solely for personal use, a sex tape may be released (or threatened to be released) to damage the reputation of the depicted, to blackmail them or merely to make a profit.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3244" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-04-08">
<name>sexually dominant</name>
<description>Sexually dominant is a designation applied to those able to assertively assume and maintain control over the actions of their partner(s) during sexual activity, actively steering it towards their own intents and preferences and possibly to the detriment of those of their partner(s).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3267" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>everybody dies</name>
<description>Not necessarily everyone, but a good portion of the characters kick the bucket.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3976" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-18">
<name>impregnation</name>
<description>At least one of the character is impregnated during the anime. This is confirmed by the characters, or the character is later shown as pregnant. Merely shouting "I`ll become pregnant!" or something similar during sex is not impregnation.
A porn anime can be tagged with impregnation only when all of the following conditions are met:
* She must be shown having sex in such a way that she can become pregnant
* She must be known as http://anidb.net/t775 [pregnant] after the fact, be it the pregnant stomach, pregnancy test, verbal confirmation, doctor`s report, etc
* Having an abortion after the event, does not change the fact that an impregnation still occurred
* http://anidb.net/t2705 [Creampies] are not a necessary criteria to have an impregnation, and impregnations do not automatically result from a creampie.
If she is impregnated by a non-human, the http://anidb.net/t7148 [impregnation with larvae] tag may also apply.</description>
<picurl>221652.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4049" parentid="2721" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-13">
<name>outdoor sex</name>
<description>Popular place for sex in visual novels and manga.</description>
<picurl>175405.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4492" parentid="2715" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>gang rape</name>
<description>Gang rape occurs when a group of people (at least 2) participate in the rape of a single victim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4560" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-02-23">
<name>psychological manipulation</name>
<description>Psychological manipulation is a type of social influence that aims to change the perception or behaviour of others through underhanded, deceptive, or even abusive tactics. By advancing the interests of the manipulator, often at the other`s expense, such methods could be considered exploitative, abusive, devious, and deceptive. 
Social influence is not necessarily negative. For example, doctors can try to persuade patients to change unhealthy habits. Social influence is generally perceived to be harmless when it respects the right of the influenced to accept or reject it, and is not unduly coercive. Depending on the context and motivations, social influence may constitute underhanded manipulation.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5406" parentid="2729" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-02">
<name>submission</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5527" parentid="2729" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-07-17">
<name>spanking</name>
<description>Spanking someone`s butt as torture or for sexual pleasure.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5589" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>youji play</name>
<description>Paraphilic condition in which sexual/erotic arousal is dependent on impersonating a baby in diapers and being treated as a baby.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5593" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-13">
<name>branching story</name>
<description>The whole series consists of alternative stories, starting at the same point, branching off to different endings. It is like a normal dating sim, where you have different choices to meet different girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5665" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-12-04">
<name>trapped</name>
<description>The anime takes place inside a building or some kind of landform from which the characters can`t get out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5669" parentid="2711" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-12">
<name>golden shower</name>
<description>A sexual act involving one person urinating onto the body of or into the mouths of other people.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5750" parentid="2724" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-15">
<name>triple penetration</name>
<description>Triple penetration is a situation during which someone is simultaneously penetrated by a minimum of three penises or strap-ons. Usually, this means one oral penetration, one vaginal penetration, and one anal penetration. Triple penetration happens most often during http://anidb.net/t2719 [gang bang] and particularly http://anidb.net/t4492 [gang rape] scenes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5786" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-27">
<name>erotic asphyxiation</name>
<description>Erotic asphyxiation, also called breath control play, is the intentional restriction of oxygen to the brain for sexual arousal.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5984" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-09-10">
<name>girly tears</name>
<description>Usually girly tears are the ones not shed by men (duh). 
Like when a (stereotypical) girl watches something and cries her makeup out, a (stereotypical) dude just says, proclaiming his masculinity: "Meh, yet another soap opera bulls..t, I`ll be in my garage fixing my ride while playing heavy metal on a burning guitar ...with my teeth! And where`s my beer, woman?".
So that`s how it goes: girly tears are for girls and sissies! Chuck Norris forbid a guy would weep watching something that has this tag! Now 20 push-ups!
P.S. The opposite of "manly tears". Or is it? Let`s face it - it`s all subjective (and relative, and context-dependent).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6083" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>master-servant relationship</name>
<description>To some genres, this would suggest a genuine pairing where one person exists to serve another person, such as in some action/dramas where the pair becomes united by destiny as partners — fighting or battles between different pairs/partners will usually be a dominant part of the story.
In other genres, this suggests a relationship where one person may be occupied as or even forcefully treated as a servant or slave to the other who designates themself the master — these services usually apply anywhere from tsundere/romantic-comedies to ecchi or to the more extreme in hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6218" parentid="2704" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-13">
<name>gokkun</name>
<description>Gokkun is a sexual activity in which a person, not necessarily but usually a female, swallows semen directly from a penis or from a container. The Japanese word "gokkun", whose meaning is close to "gulp" in English, is an onomatopoeia resembling the sound made by swallowing.</description>
<picurl>234875.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6268" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>fellatio</name>
<description>Fellatio is oral sex performed upon the penis. It may be performed to induce male orgasm and ejaculation of semen, or it may be used as foreplay prior to sexual intercourse.</description>
<picurl>165408.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6355" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-06">
<name>water sex</name>
<description>Sexual acts taking place in water: i.e. sea, pool, bath, shower, etc.</description>
<picurl>178296.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6389" parentid="2707" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-19">
<name>cervix penetration</name>
<description>The cervix/womb of a female is visibly penetrated. Very likely invoked in conjunction with the http://anidb.net/t2707 [internal shots] tag.
Source: EHWiki</description>
<picurl>213277.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6999" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-18">
<name>pregnant sex</name>
<description>Pregnant sex involves having sex with a pregnant individual.
Engaging in at least 1 pregnant sex scene is not sufficient in and of itself for tagging http://anidb.net/t775 [pregnant] on the character; only tag pregnant sex at the anime level in such a case. A character only shown pregnant for a small segment of their total appearance(s) should not be tagged as pregnant. Pregnancy and/or pregnant sex typically follows after an http://anidb.net/t3976 [impregnation] or http://anidb.net/t7148 [impregnation with larvae] scene.</description>
<picurl>10483.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7221" parentid="7220" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>psychological sexual abuse</name>
<description>Psychological sexual abuse is the exercise of sexual coercion through non-physical means, such as verbal sexual behaviour, stalking, and emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="34834" type="main character in" update="2011-10-12">
<rating votes="14">7.61</rating>
<name>Takatou Keisuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68267.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42533">Kuroi Neko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34835" type="appears in" update="2011-07-20">
<rating votes="23">5.68</rating>
<name>Andou Miyako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75825.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16110" picture="240470.jpg">Azuma Karin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34836" type="main character in" update="2011-07-20">
<rating votes="49">6.22</rating>
<name>Aoi Natsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75826.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14822" picture="150922.jpg">Misonoo Mei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34837" type="main character in" update="2011-07-20">
<rating votes="26">5.17</rating>
<name>Makiba Rika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75828.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32710" picture="156288.jpg">Konoha</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34838" type="main character in" update="2011-07-20">
<rating votes="39">7.32</rating>
<name>Byakuya Rinne</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75829.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16111" picture="47259.jpg">Sugihara Matsuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34839" type="main character in" update="2011-07-20">
<rating votes="39">7.12</rating>
<name>Hokari Kanae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75824.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="35863" picture="173054.jpg">Himari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34840" type="main character in" update="2011-07-20">
<rating votes="98">8.72</rating>
<name>Manaka Nemu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75827.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="26074" picture="156343.jpg">Aozora Ramune</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="131074" update="2011-08-29">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2011-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真中合歓 地獄始動編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Manaka Nemu: Hell`s Start Chapter</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Manaka Nemu: piekielna rozgrywka rozpoczęta.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Manaka Nemu - Jigoku Shidou Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135173" update="2011-12-04">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136462" update="2012-01-17">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2012-03-30</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">帆刈叶 楽園終焉編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hokari Kanae: Paradise`s Demise Chapter</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Hokari Kanae: koniec raju.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hokari Kanae - Rakuen Shuuen Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138442" update="2012-04-03">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158410" update="2014-03-17">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2014-06-27</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">白夜凛音 輪廻転生編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Byakuya Rinne: Reincarnation Chapter</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Byakuya Rinne: Odrodzenie.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Byakuya Rinne - Rinnetenshou Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="164623" update="2014-12-04">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2015-02-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蒔羽梨香 葵菜月 蘇る地獄絵図編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Makiba Rika, Aoi Natsuki, and the Resurrected Visage of Hell Chapter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Makiba Rika, Aoi Natsuki - Yomigaeru Jigoku Ezu Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171152" update="2015-09-04">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2015-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地下の戦慄ゲーム, 地上のスカトロ地獄. 笑う黒幕は......幼なじみ!?編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dreadful Games in the Basement, the Scatology Hell on the Surface. The Mastermind Is... Our Childhood Friend!? Chapter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chika no Senritsu Game, Chijou no Scatolo Jigoku. Warau Kuromaku wa...... Osananajimi!? Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="173590" update="2015-12-01">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2016-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">目指す楽園は神聖なる儀式の先に. 救世主の母は...白夜凛音!?編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Paradise We Desire Is Only a Holy Ritual Away. The Mother of the Saviour Is... Byakuya Rinne?! Chapter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mezasu Rakuen wa Shinsei Naru Gishiki no Sakini. Kyuuseishu no Haha wa... Byakuya Rinne!? Hen</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
