<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8517" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>6</episodecount>
<startdate>2015-02-28</startdate>
<enddate>2018-05-05</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kidou Senshi Gundam: The Origin</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">機動戦士ガンダムTHE ORIGIN</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Mobile Suit Gundam: The Origin</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">기동전사 건다 더 오리진</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">机动战士高达 起源</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="715" type="Sequel">Kidou Senshi Gundam</anime>
<anime id="14496" type="Summary">Kidou Senshi Gundam: The Origin - Zen`ya Akai Suisei</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="21063">Any fan of the original Gundam series needs to see this prequel series.

If you`re new to the franchise, this can also serve as an alternative (chronological) start but you will miss quite a few details. The Origin doesn`t really explain how humanity ended up in space, and the consequences (newtypes). Edit, part of this gets covered in episode 2. I personally find MSG:origin more approachable than the rest of the franchise because of LESS focus on mechas.
Alternatively, you might want to start with... the MSG summary movie trilogy, 0083 Stardust, Z , ZZ, char`s counterattack, and Unicorn. Hope I got that order right. basically watch this series last.

MSG is far from being my favorite franchise(bleh, mechas) but I enjoyed this as a space opera in the same vein as LoGH. Great storyboard and A/V production values for such a niche title.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.gundam-the-origin.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="5230" type="Original Work">Yasuhiko Yoshikazu</name>
<name id="4214" type="Character Design">Kotobuki Tsukasa</name>
<name id="5230" type="Character Design">Yasuhiko Yoshikazu</name>
<name id="1352" type="Original Work">Yatate Hajime</name>
<name id="147" type="Original Work">Tomino Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="659" type="Direction">Imanishi Takashi</name>
<name id="2691" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nishimura Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="5230" type="Chief Direction">Yasuhiko Yoshikazu</name>
<name id="680" type="Music">Hattori Takayuki</name>
</creators>
<description>What was the tragedy that decided the fates of Char Aznable, the man later nicknamed the "Red Comet" as an ace pilot of the Zeon forces, and his sister Sayla Mass?
The two siblings` journeys, brought on by the sudden death of their father Zeon Zum Deikun who was a leader of the Spacenoids, are depicted in the four episodes of "Chronicle of Char and Sayla."
The Zabi family who seize control of Side 3 and lead the Principality of Zeon, the early days of many renowned Zeon ace pilots who later fight in the One Year War, the secrets of mobile suit development, conflicts with the Earth Federation Forces, and the road leading to the outbreak of war—all will be revealed.
Source: Official website</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="408">9.23</permanent>
<temporary count="410">8.19</temporary>
<review count="3">8.88</review>
</ratings>
<picture>155664.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13105</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10937</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gundam-the-origin.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Mobile_Suit_Gundam:_The_Origin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>機動戦士ガンダム_THE_ORIGIN</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4939</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>358871</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>349231</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>353441</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>355314</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>356775</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>356776</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18006</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3145" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-14">
<name>impact event</name>
<description>An impact event is a collision between celestial objects causing measurable effects. Impact events have physical consequences and have been found to regularly occur in planetary systems, though the most frequent involve asteroids, comets or meteoroids and have minimal impact. When large objects impact terrestrial planets like the Earth, there can be significant physical and biospheric consequences, though atmospheres mitigate many surface impacts through atmospheric entry. Impact structures are dominant landforms on many celestial solid objects and present the strongest empirical evidence for their frequency and scale. In fiction, an impact event is a common way to end the world as we know it, either through the impact itself or through its aftermath, and it may happen either naturally or through human hands; this may include man-made objects, such as space debris and fictional space colonies.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3216" parentid="2626" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-25">
<name>Universal Century</name>
<description>Refers to the Universal Century timeline in Gundam anime. Gundam anime with this tag all belong in the same universe.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4538" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>long episodes</name>
<description>Long episodes are regular episodes that are much longer than the standard 25-30 minutes, usually 45-60 minutes. 
Not to be used if a show has occasional 45-60 minute specials. Also not to be confused with an OVA or music video with multiple (otherwise unrelated) full-length http://anidb.net/t7241 [bundled episodes] consolidated into a single episode video track.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5929" parentid="2846" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>space opera</name>
<description>Space opera is a sub-genre of fiction that emphasizes romantic adventures in space. Space opera generally involves large-scale conflicts between opponents with powerful abilities and technology. The genre will often be melodramatic, sometimes playing music that can be nothing short of awesome. Warfare and a battle of wits are usually less emphasized, preferring romance (with exceptions, e.g. Ginga Eiyuu Densetsu). Some space operas tend to be formulaic and sometimes even prosaic, often employing very simple devices and somewhat obvious strategies. An example of this would be the infamous laws of physics in the Macross universe, in which the main male lead will hardly ever get hit in battle.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6004" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>development hell</name>
<description>Due to unforeseen circumstances, the production or release of this anime has been pushed back, stalled, or cancelled one or more times from when it was first announced.
While some of them have eventually been completed, others might have only had a trailer released or have been changed into another format (e.g. a TV series turned into an OVA).
Common reasons for a work to become stuck in development hell include creative differences, legal issues, financial problems, scheduling conflicts or the death of an involved creator.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="3971" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-10">
<rating votes="107">7.89</rating>
<name>Amuro Ray</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Amuro is the hero of our story, and the pilot of the mighty mobile suit RX-78 Gundam. As the series begins, he is a civilian living at the Side 7 research colony, the neglected son of a Federation Forces engineer. When Zeon mobile suits attack the colony, Amuro commandeers the prototype Gundam and defeats the invaders. He soon finds himself part of the substitute crew of the Federation warship White Base, and this moody young man begins to develop strong bonds with his newfound "family." Meanwhile, Amuro`s increasing fighting skills suggest that he has potential far beyond that of ordinary mortals...
Source: Official Site</description>
<picture>85679.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="3974" type="appears in" update="2012-04-10">
<rating votes="332">9.00</rating>
<name>Char Aznable</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Known as the "Red Comet" for his high-speed attack tactics, Char is the most famous of Zeon`s ace mobile suit pilots. He earned his nickname by destroying five Federation battleships during the Battle of Loum, and after the attack on Side 7, he becomes the dreaded nemesis of the White Base crew. However, defeating the Federation isn`t the only thing on Char`s mind, and his distinctive mask hides the face of a young man bent on his own personal quest for revenge. As the story continues, Char begins putting his own complicated schemes into motion, even as he becomes distracted by his growing rivalry with the Gundam`s pilot.
Source: Official Site</description>
<picture>85692.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="413" picture="151647.jpg">Ikeda Shuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10951" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-05-06">
<rating votes="37">7.98</rating>
<name>Lalah Sune</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>This young woman is a test subject of the Flanagan Institute, a Zeon research organization created to investigate the gifted humans known as "newtypes." While the exploits of pilots like Char and Amuro have led to speculation that they may be newtypes, Lalah`s powers are obvious and undeniable, and accompanied by a profound spiritual awareness. However, despite her gentle nature, Lalah is fiercely loyal to the man who saved her life - Char Aznable, the scheming "Red Comet."</description>
<picture>87316.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="44367" type="appears in" update="2012-05-05">
<rating votes="7">3.58</rating>
<name>Zenna Zabi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87248.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="67497" type="main character in" update="2015-12-10">
<rating votes="7">8.96</rating>
<name>Casval Rem Deikun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155665.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="322" picture="17159.jpg">Tanaka Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67498" type="main character in" update="2015-12-10">
<rating votes="3">7.62</rating>
<name>Artesia Som Deikun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155666.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27977" picture="76416.jpg">Han Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67499" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-12-11">
<name>Zeon Zum Deikun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155667.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="562" picture="17888.jpg">Tsuda Eizou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67500" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-16">
<rating votes="2">4.02</rating>
<name>Jimba Ral</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155668.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="173" picture="150067.jpg">Chafuurin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67501" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-16">
<rating votes="2">3.35</rating>
<name>Degwin Sodo Zabi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155669.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9288" picture="34149.jpg">Urayama Jin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67502" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-12-11">
<rating votes="3">7.61</rating>
<name>Astraia Tor Deikun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155670.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="447" picture="224407.jpg">Tsunematsu Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67503" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-16">
<rating votes="2">9.67</rating>
<name>Ramba Ral</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155671.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3162" picture="151662.jpg">Kiyama Shigeo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67504" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-12-11">
<rating votes="2">7.08</rating>
<name>Gihren Zabi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155672.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2782" picture="23189.jpg">Ginga Banjou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67505" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-16">
<rating votes="2">4.02</rating>
<name>Sasro Zabi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155673.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17634" picture="237832.jpg">Fuji Shinshuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67506" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-12-11">
<rating votes="2">6.46</rating>
<name>Dozle Zabi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155675.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67507" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-12-10">
<rating votes="3">6.28</rating>
<name>Kycilia Zabi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155676.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67508" type="appears in" update="2014-05-16">
<rating votes="1">7.91</rating>
<name>RTX-65 Guntank Shoki-gata</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>155677.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="67509" type="appears in" update="2014-05-17">
<rating votes="1">7.91</rating>
<name>Chikyuu Renpousei Chian`iji Soukou Bus</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>155678.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="71453" type="appears in" update="2015-12-11">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Crowley Hamon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>164616.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72839" type="appears in" update="2015-01-26">
<name>Rozelshia Deikun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>167972.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="72840" type="appears in" update="2015-01-26">
<name>Tachi O`Hara</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>167973.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="72841" type="appears in" update="2015-01-26">
<name>Donovan Matogros</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>167974.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="72842" type="appears in" update="2015-01-26">
<name>Clamp</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>167975.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="95020" type="appears in" update="2018-04-13">
<name>MW-01 Mobile Worker 01-shiki Shokikei</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>216169.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="95021" type="appears in" update="2018-04-13">
<name>MW-01 Mobile Worker 01-shiki Koki-gata (Mash-ki)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>216171.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="95022" type="appears in" update="2018-04-13">
<name>MW-01 Mobile Worker 01-shiki Koki-gata (Ral-ki)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>216172.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="95026" type="appears in" update="2018-04-13">
<name>YMS-03 Waff</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>216174.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="95027" type="appears in" update="2018-04-13">
<name>MS-04 Bugu (Ramba Ral-ki)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>216175.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="95028" type="appears in" update="2018-04-13">
<name>MW-01 Mobile Worker 01-shiki Saigo-ki-gata</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>216177.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="95029" type="appears in" update="2018-04-13">
<name>MW-01 Mobile Worker 01-shiki Saigo-ki-gata Uchuu Shiyo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>216178.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="95030" type="appears in" update="2018-04-13">
<name>MS-06S Char Senyo Zaku II</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>216182.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="164335" update="2015-02-28">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>65</length>
<airdate>2015-02-28</airdate>
<rating votes="5">9.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">青い瞳のキャスバル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blue-Eyed Casval</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aoi Hitomi no Casval</title>
</episode>
<episode id="166795" update="2015-10-31">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>2015-10-31</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">哀しみのアルテイシア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Artesia`s Sorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kamashimi no Artesia</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172958" update="2016-05-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>70</length>
<airdate>2016-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暁の蜂起</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dawn of Rebellion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akatsuki no Houki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="177728" update="2016-10-31">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>70</length>
<airdate>2016-11-19</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">運命の前夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eve of Destiny</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unmei no Zen`ya</title>
</episode>
<episode id="182451" update="2017-08-29">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>85</length>
<airdate>2017-09-02</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">激突 ルウム会戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Clash at Loum</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitotsu Loum Kaisen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="182452" update="2018-05-01">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>85</length>
<airdate>2018-05-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">誕生 赤い彗星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rise of the Red Comet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tanjou Akai Suisei</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
