<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="852" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>43</episodecount>
<startdate>1995-10-12</startdate>
<enddate>1996-09-12</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kaitou Saint Tail</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Mysterious Thief Saint Tail</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Таинственная грабительница Сент-Тэйл</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">圣少女</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">怪盗 セイント・テール</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Saint Tail</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Lisa e Seya un solo cuore per lo stesso segreto</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">천사소녀 네티</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">A Ladra Meimi</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="354" approval="20" total="21">Kamikaze Kaitou Jeanne</anime>
<anime id="7469" approval="5" total="6">Magic Kaito</anime>
</similaranime>
<creators>
<name id="2529" type="Music">Matsuo Hayato</name>
<name id="782" type="Work">Tokyo Movie</name>
<name id="1119" type="Work">Asahi Housou</name>
<name id="3514" type="Work">Kyokuichi Tokyo Movie</name>
<name id="1966" type="Chief Direction">Nabeshima Osamu</name>
<name id="10087" type="Original Work">Tachikawa Megumi</name>
<name id="7628" type="Character Design">Abe Junko</name>
</creators>
<description>School girl http://anidb.net/ch7757 [Haneoka Meimi] transforms into the mysterious thief http://anidb.net/ch7762 [Saint Tail], and steals back what was stolen or taken dishonestly. She`s assisted by a classmate and sister-in-training, http://anidb.net/ch14409 [Mimori Seira], whose position in the church after school each day allows her to hear the troubles of those who have been wronged and have come to pray to God.
While Saint Tail steals to right the wrongs done to innocent people, she`s a thief to the police force. Her classmate Asuka Daiki Jr., called http://anidb.net/ch13858 [Asuka Jr.], and son of http://anidb.net/ch14414 [Detective Asuka], is hot on her trail. Saint Tail delivers notices of her planned capers to Asuka Jr., to give him a fair chance to catch her.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="228">6.35</permanent>
<temporary count="234">7.09</temporary>
<review count="3">7.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>131385.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>307</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1567</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>279</identifier>
<identifier>llwolj</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Saint_Tail</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>怪盗セイント・テール</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1668</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89003</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>268</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>천사소녀_네티</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>怪盜St._Tail</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1403" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-10">
<name>nun</name>
<description>A nun is a member of a religious community of women, typically one living under vows of poverty, chastity, and obedience. She may have decided to dedicate her life to serving all other living beings, or she might be an ascetic who voluntarily chose to leave mainstream society and live her life in prayer and contemplation in a monastery or convent. The term "nun" is applicable to Catholics (eastern and western traditions), Orthodox Christians, Anglicans, Lutherans, Jains, Buddhists, Taoists, Hindus and some other religious traditions.
Source: Wiktionary</description>
<picurl>165755.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1835" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-17">
<name>animal sidekick</name>
<description>Every mahou shoujo anime needs them, the cute little critters that are supposed to help the protagonists but in reality are nothing but useless bystanders most often abused for gags. Kids love them but they can also often turn into an annoyance.</description>
<picurl>227760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2664" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-07">
<name>catholic school</name>
<description>A setting for this anime is a school run by the nuns and/or priests of the Church Of Rome.
Religious instruction may be an integral part of the plot. Religious icons - particularly crosses and crucifixes are usually prominent.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2845" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-04-30">
<name>blackmail</name>
<description>In general usage, blackmail is a crime involving unjustified threats against a person or organization in order to make a gain or harm or cause material loss to them unless a demand is met. It may be considered similar to or a form of extortion, although some jurisdictions will consider them as separate crimes. Most often, blackmail involves the threat of revealing some secret to a given third party, which may be another person, a rival organization, or a state institution such as the police, or to the general public. In anime and related media, and more specifically in pornographic works, blackmail is also a device used to coerce people, generally female and often schoolgirls, into having sex with another or others; in such cases, it may be considered similar to or a form of rape.</description>
<picurl>136031.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4170" parentid="5626" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-08-08">
<name>police are useless</name>
<description>The civilian law enforcement representatives do not seem to be of much use, when trying to take on the usually vastly superior foes.
The "helpless" and often clumsy antics of the police can be used as a comedy element.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5172" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-05">
<name>vigilante</name>
<description>A vigilante is a civilian, or rarely organization, acting in a law enforcement capacity or in the pursuit of self-perceived summary justice without legal authority.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5626" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>adults are useless</name>
<description>For when adults can`t do anything right.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5882" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>secret identity</name>
<description>The (usually main) protagonist has a secret identity that he or she desperately tries to keep secret.
This can lead to all sorts of amusing misunderstandings, thus is used as comedy element in some anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5988" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>living with the villain</name>
<description>Both, hero and villain have their secret identities. They live next door, go to the same school, work at the same place or even are best friends. But little do they know that in another part of their life they are the worst enemies. And yet they just do not recognize each other when they are out of their costumes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6248" parentid="2872" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>thievery</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7757" type="main character in" update="2010-01-27">
<rating votes="5">7.60</rating>
<name>Haneoka Meimi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>By day, Meimi is a typical orange-haired fourteen year old student at St. Paulia`s Private School. At school, her strong point is physical education, but she`s rather poor at math.
By night she transforms into the mysterious (yet magical) thief, Saint Tail. Saint Tail wears a long ponytail and is usually dressed in purple-black. In this guise, she takes back what bad people have stolen. She is given information by her classmate, and nun-in-training, Seira, of misdeeds.</description>
<picture>3975.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="42888" picture="17271.jpg">Sakurai Tomo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7762" type="main character in" update="2013-01-27">
<rating votes="4">7.44</rating>
<name>Saint Tail</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>By day, Meimi is a typical orange-haired fourteen year old student at St. Paulia`s Private School. At school, her strong point is physical education, but she`s rather poor at math.
By night she transforms into the mysterious (yet magical) thief, Saint Tail. Saint Tail wears a long ponytail and is usually dressed in purple-black. In this guise, she takes back what bad people have stolen. She is given information by her classmate, and nun-in-training, Seira, of misdeeds.</description>
<picture>59760.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="42888" picture="17271.jpg">Sakurai Tomo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13858" type="main character in" update="2010-01-26">
<name>Asuka Daiki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Daiki Asuka is a fourteen year old at St. Paulia`s Private School, and is a top student in his class. His physical strength and motor skills are lacking.
Called Asuka Jr. by his classmates, Daiki Asuka is the son of Detective Tomoki Asuka. Because his father has been unable to catch Saint Tail, and doesn`t place any emergency on this thief`s capture, Asuka Jr. takes to task. He plans to one-up his father by catching Saint Tail.
After his getting close enough to photograph Saint Tail, Asuka Jr. is awarded a badge from the mayor, which allows him to go anywhere to investigate. With this, he is able to assist the police in Saint Tail`s capture. Asuka Jr. is given notice beforehand of Saint Tail`s crimes, at his own request. As she slips away from him caper after caper, Saint Tail becomes the object of Asuka Jr.`s thoughts.
Very dense about relationships, Asuka Jr. fails to see Meimi`s growing feelings for him. He often argues with Meimi (whom he calls Haneoka), over Saint Tail and his inability to catch her. Asuka Jr. begins to think of Meimi when he sees Saint Tail, and viceversa, and is torn between which of the two he`s falling in love with.</description>
<picture>40839.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="389" picture="56097.jpg">Okano Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14409" type="main character in" update="2010-01-26">
<name>Mimori Seira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mimori Seira is a fourteen-year-old student at St. Paulia`s Private School and a nun-in training at the school`s church. Classmate and best friend of Haneoka Meimi, she is the only person who knows the real identity of Saint Tail. After school Seira spends her time at the chapel as a nun; there many people come to her and talk about their problems, usually involving something being stolen or going missing. She relays this information to Meimi/Saint Tail, asking her to help these people recover their valued possessions.</description>
<picture>41998.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14410" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-26">
<rating votes="1">5.52</rating>
<name>Ruby</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ruby is Meimi`s cute, brown pet hedgehog. She is introduced early on in the anime series. She was bought by a man, then Meimi stole her to protect the gem that the man made her swallow. Ruby knows Meimi is Saint Tail, and has been on a caper with her, inspiring a "hedgehog magic spell."
Ruby wears a black ribbon similar to Saint Tail`s, and speaks by saying "Kyuu." Meimi has to keep Ruby hidden from Asuka Jr. so he won`t recognize her from a previous caper.</description>
<picture>41999.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="556" picture="17848.jpg">Koorogi Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14411" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-26">
<name>Takamiya Rina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takamiya Rina is a transfer student to St. Paulia`s Private School. Rina becomes interested in Asuka Jr. and his mission to catch Saint Tail. Because she is related to the mayor, Rina is able to take over Asuka Jr.`s investigations. Because of Rina`s strong sense of justice, she wants to become a police woman. Catching Saint Tail would assist in her ambitions. Rina is taller than Asuka Jr., making the young detective uncomfortable standing beside her. She also has a boyish and bullyish nature.
Because of Meimi`s athletic abilities and other circumstances, Rina suspects her to be Saint Tail. She makes a bet with Asuka Jr. that if Meimi is Saint Tail, then Asuka Jr. has to be Rina`s boyfriend. The two are disillusioned when Rina catches Saint Tail, but the magical thief uses her magic to switch a guard in her place. The knocked-out guard, dressed as Saint Tail, fools Asuka Jr. and Rina into thinking that Saint Tail is really an older man, and Rina stops stalking Meimi over the issue.</description>
<picture>42000.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="492" picture="17483.jpg">Nagashima Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14412" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Haneoka Gen`ichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haneoka Gen`ichirou is Meimi`s father and a first-class magician. He`s always experimenting with new magic tricks to use in his shows, and hopes that Meimi will follow in his footsteps and go into a magical profession.</description>
<picture>42001.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14413" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Haneoka Eimi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haneoka Eimi is Meimi`s mother. She hopes Meimi will follow in her own footsteps and do something athletic. Eimi used to be a thief herself, but is now a house wife.</description>
<picture>42002.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12449" picture="42003.jpg">Enomoto Chieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14414" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Asuka Tomoki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Asuka Jr.`s father, and a detective at the local police department. While capturing Saint Tail is one of his duties, he normally leaves it to his son and focuses on more serious criminals. He is sometimes seen arresting the ones Saint Tail has stolen from, having investigated their backgrounds.
It was known that he also once fell in love with Saint Venus (Eimi) during his age of pursuing her.</description>
<picture>42004.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14415" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Sawatari Manato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sawatari Manato is a student at St. Paulia`s Private School, and is a photographer on the school paper. He`s popular with the girls on campus, but becomes interested in Meimi after she shows interest in his photography (rather than in his looks as other girls do). Unknown to Sawatari, Meimi`s interest was false, as she was trying to obtain information for a theft. He also seems to have an interest in Meimi`s friend Seira.
Asuka Jr. and Rina both call Sawatari by the name "Saruwatari" when mad with him. Saru is the Japanese word for monkey.</description>
<picture>42005.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14416" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A friend and classmate of Meimi`s. At first she may seem quiet, but the truth is she loves to gossip.</description>
<picture>42006.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2068" picture="28743.jpg">Iwao Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14417" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Ryouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A friend and classmate of Meimi`s. She is vigorous and a bit firm. She constantly uses trendy language.</description>
<picture>42007.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="556" picture="17848.jpg">Koorogi Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14418" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Sendou Maju</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Maju is the adopted daughter of the thief Rosemary. Using lavender to hypnotize others, Maju is able to convince her victims to hand over their valuables while believing they were stolen by Saint Tail. She discovers Saint Tail`s identity by hypnotizing her.</description>
<picture>42008.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="70" picture="171604.jpg">Kanai Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14419" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<name>Sendou Kabako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sendou Kabako is also known as the thief Rosemary. Rival of Meimi`s mother, she is said to have stolen everything that the Fallen Angel returned. Maju is her adopted daughter.</description>
<picture>42009.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12450" picture="42010.jpg">Kouda Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="8745" update="2005-01-23">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1995-10-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">登場!キュートな大泥棒!? あなたのハート盗みます.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Cutest Little Thief!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toujou! Cute na Oodorobou!? Anata no Heart Nusumimasu.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8746" update="2005-01-23">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1995-10-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">芽美の恋人は ハリネズミ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Meimi`s Love?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meimi no Koibito wa Harinezumi!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8747" update="2005-01-23">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1995-11-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピンチ! 落し物にご用心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Danger! Beware of Lost Objects!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pinch! Otoshimono ni Goyoujin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8748" update="2005-01-23">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1996-01-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">神秘! ローザ王女の鏡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mystical Princess Rosa`s Mirror</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinpi! Rosa Oujo no Kagami</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8749" update="2005-01-23">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1996-03-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">思い出の ハーモニカを盗め!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Steal the Memorable Harmonica!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omoide no Harmonica o Nusume!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8750" update="2005-01-23">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1995-11-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">コンテスト会場は 大混乱!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Contest Hall in Chaos!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Contest Kaijou wa Daikonran!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8751" update="2005-01-23">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1996-02-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">中華の鉄人を盗め!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Steal the Chinese Iron Chef!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chuuka no Tetsujin o Nusume!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8752" update="2005-01-23">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1995-10-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">素敵なライバル アスカJr.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wonderful Rival!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suteki na Rival! Asuka Jr.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8753" update="2005-01-23">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1996-03-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">UFO現る!? 街は大さわぎ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The U.F.O. Appears!? A Town in Panic!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">UFO Arawaru!? Machi wa Oosawagi!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8754" update="2005-01-23">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1995-10-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ウェディングヴェールは 大嫌い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Hate Wedding Veils!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wedding Veil wa Daikirai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8755" update="2005-01-23">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1996-03-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">幻の怪鳥の卵を 取り戻せ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Get Back the Phantom Bird Egg!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maboroshi no Kaichou no Tamago o Torimodose!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8756" update="2005-01-23">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1996-01-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛と涙の プラットホーム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Platform of Love and Tears</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai to Namida no Platform</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8757" update="2005-01-23">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1996-01-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">宝石泥棒を追え! 迷犬リトル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Run After a Jewel Thief! Litle, The Naughty Dog</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Houseki Dorobou o Oe! Meiken Little</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8758" update="2005-01-23">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1995-12-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">仰天! 大トカゲのサンタ?!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Surprise! The Large Lizard Santa Claus?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gyouten! Ootokage no Santa?!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8759" update="2005-01-23">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1995-12-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スクープ写真で 学院祭大騒動</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Big Scoop! An Uproar at the School Festival!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Scoop Shashin de Gakuinsai Oosoudou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8760" update="2005-01-23">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1995-11-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">幸せ伝説!? 時計台の大騒動</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Legend of Happiness?! The Clock Tower Commotion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiawase Densetsu!? Tokeidai no Oosoudou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8761" update="2009-09-01">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1995-12-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">告白... しちゃった!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You... Confessed??</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokuhaku... Shichatta!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8762" update="2005-01-23">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1995-11-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">強敵現わる! 転校生リナ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">New Student Rina, A Formidable Enemy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyouteki Arawaru! Tenkousei Rina</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8763" update="2005-01-23">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1995-11-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">涙!なみだの 初ランデブー!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A First Rendezvous of Tears?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Namida! Namida no Hatsu Rendezvous!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8764" update="2005-01-23">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1996-02-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さわると危険! 超電流の罠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Danger, Do Not Touch! Super Electric Trap</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sawaru to Kiken! Choudenryuu no Wana</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8765" update="2005-01-23">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1996-02-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">彗星大接近! 地球最後の夜!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Comet Approaches! The Earth`s Final Night??</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suisei Daisekkin! Chikyuu Saigo no Yoru!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8766" update="2005-01-23">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1996-02-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">バレンタインの ハート泥棒!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Heart Thief on St. Valentine`s Day??</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Valentine no Heart Dorobou!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8767" update="2005-08-31">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8768" update="2005-08-31">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending (instrumental version)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8769" update="2005-08-31">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10198" update="2005-01-25">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1996-06-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">月の宝石を盗め!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Steal the Jewel of the Moon!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuki no Houseki o Nusume!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10199" update="2008-05-10">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1996-03-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ニセ予告状!? 秘密の香水の罠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Fake Calling Card? The Secret of the Perfume Trap</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nise Yokokujou!? Himitsu no Kousui no Wana</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10200" update="2008-05-10">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1996-03-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">許せない! 家を壊す悪者たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unforgivable! The Bad Guys Destroy a House</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yurusenai! Ie o Kowasu Warumono-tachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10201" update="2005-01-23">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1996-04-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">強敵! エリート女刑事と対決</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Strong Foe! Confronting Elite Detective</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyouteki! Elite Onna Keiji to Taiketsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10202" update="2009-09-01">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1996-04-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">芽美が 大富豪の息子と婚約!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Meimi is Engaged to a Multi-Millionaire`s Son!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meimi ga Daifugou no Musuko to Kon`yaku!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10203" update="2005-01-26">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1996-05-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">市長の陰謀! 白鳥を盗め (前)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mayor`s Ambition! Stealing a Swan (Part 1)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shichou no Inbou! Hakuchou o Nusume (Zenpen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10204" update="2005-01-25">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1996-05-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">美少女アイドルを救え!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Save the Pretty Idol Girl!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bishoujo Idol o Sukue!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10205" update="2005-01-25">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1996-06-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">女子マラソン選手の 靴を盗め</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Steal a Woman`s Marathon Running Shoes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Joshi Marathon Senshu no Kutsu o Nusume</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10206" update="2005-01-25">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1996-05-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">市長の陰謀! 白鳥を盗め (後)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mayor`s Ambition! Stealing a Swan (Part 2)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shichou no Inbou! Hakuchou o Nusume (Kouhen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10207" update="2005-01-25">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1996-06-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">正体がバレる! 芽美危機一髪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Her True Character Revealed! Meimi`s Critical Moment</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoutai ga Bareru! Meimi Kiki Ippatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10208" update="2005-01-25">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1996-06-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">少女剣士の願い! 名刀を盗め</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Swordswoman`s Wish! To Steal the Excellent Sword</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoujo Kenshi no Negai! Meitou o Nusume</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10209" update="2005-01-25">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1996-07-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">サラブレッドを取り戻せ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Return the Thoroughbred!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Thoroughbred o Torimodose!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10210" update="2006-03-29">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1996-07-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">"幸福の樹"を取り戻せ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Get Back the "Tree of Happiness"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Koufuku no Ki" o Torimodose!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10211" update="2005-01-25">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1996-07-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">自然の宝・美しき蝶を守れ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Precious Creature of Nature : Save the Beautiful Butterfly!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shizen no Takara Utsukushiki Chou o Mamore!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10212" update="2006-03-29">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1996-08-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">"白いイルカ"を 海へ帰せ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">"White Dolphin" - Return to the Sea!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Shiroi Iruka" o Umi e Kaese!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10213" update="2005-01-25">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1996-09-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">母の敵(かたき)! ローズマリーの陰謀</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mom`s Enemy! Rosemary`s Conspiracy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haha no Kataki! Rosemary no Inbou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10214" update="2005-01-25">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1996-08-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">爆笑! ドタバタ探偵団大活躍</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Burst of Laughter! The Detective Team Does a Great Job!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bakushou! Dotabata Tanteidan Daikatsuyaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10215" update="2005-01-25">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1996-09-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">最後の闘い! アスカを救え</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Final Battle! Save Asuka Jr.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo no Tatakai! Asuka o Sukue</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10216" update="2005-01-25">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1996-08-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">強敵!? かわいい悪魔のワナ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Formidable Foe!? A Mischievous Pixie`s Trap!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyouteki!? Kawaii Akuma no Wana!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10217" update="2005-01-25">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1996-08-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">母の秘密! 女怪盗の復しゅう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mom`s Secret! A Female Thief`s Vengeance!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haha no Himitsu! Onna Kaitou no Fukushuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10218" update="2005-01-25">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1996-07-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">幻の名画! 帰って来た女探偵</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Phantasmal Masterpiece! A Woman Detective is Back</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maboroshi no Meiga! Kaette Kita Onna Tantei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="98465" update="2009-04-01">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Third Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="98466" update="2009-04-01">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Second Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="98467" update="2009-04-01">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Second Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="98468" update="2009-04-01">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">First Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="98469" update="2009-04-01">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">First Ending - Long Version</title>
</episode>
<episode id="98470" update="2009-04-01">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">First Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
