<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8522" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-09-22</startdate>
<enddate>2011-09-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Boku wa Tomodachi ga Sukunai: Yaminabe wa Bishoujo ga Zannen na Nioi</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">我的朋友很少OAD</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">haganai ova</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">僕は友達が少ない 闇鍋は美少女が残念な臭い(;´∀`)</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">我的朋友很少 黑暗火锅是美少女的遗憾臭味(;´∀`)</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8419" type="Parent Story">Boku wa Tomodachi ga Sukunai</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="15901" type="Character Design">Watanabe Yoshihiro</name>
<name id="27061" type="Original Work">Hirasaka Yomi</name>
<name id="6276" type="Direction">Saitou Hisashi</name>
<name id="15901" type="Chief Animation Direction">Watanabe Yoshihiro</name>
<name id="2431" type="Music">Tom-H@ck</name>
<name id="28474" type="Animation Work">AIC Build</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a light novel series by http://anidb.net/cr27061 [Hirasaka Yomi] with illustrations by http://anidb.net/cr24691 [Buriki].
One day the members of the Rinjinbu, the Neighbour`s Club, decide to have a nabe after school. However, what was supposed to be a fun and enjoyable experience with friends turns into a battle of survival after everything was added to the soup base, creating something that should not exist in this world.
Note: Bundled with the seventh special-edition volume of the Boku wa Tomodachi ga Sukunai light novel series.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2174">3.47</permanent>
<temporary count="2191">6.11</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>76081.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13249</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10897</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5167</identifier>
<identifier>sepplz</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Boku_wa_Tomodachi_ga_Sukunai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>僕は友達が少ない</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13955</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1065" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-05">
<name>heterochromatic eyes</name>
<description>Heterochromia Iridis is a condition where one eye is a different color from the other, or one eye is more than one color.
Characters with different eye-colour may not necessarily have the medical condition itself, as the state of different-coloured eyes can be caused by various other reasons such as possession by spiritual entities, indication of special powers or artificial changes.</description>
<picurl>63229.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1403" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-10">
<name>nun</name>
<description>A nun is a member of a religious community of women, typically one living under vows of poverty, chastity, and obedience. She may have decided to dedicate her life to serving all other living beings, or she might be an ascetic who voluntarily chose to leave mainstream society and live her life in prayer and contemplation in a monastery or convent. The term "nun" is applicable to Catholics (eastern and western traditions), Orthodox Christians, Anglicans, Lutherans, Jains, Buddhists, Taoists, Hindus and some other religious traditions.
Source: Wiktionary</description>
<picurl>165755.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1471" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-19">
<name>bad cooking</name>
<description>The character is hopelessly terrible at cooking, and any attempts he or she makes at making even the simplest dishes are spectacular failures.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2072" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>maid</name>
<description>A maid is a female employed in domestic service. They usually wear uniforms. Since their nature is to be obedient and serve their goshujin-sama (master), they are one of the most desired types of women in Japan, a dream of every Japanese man, particularly http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku]. Often seen in so-called Maid Cafes in Akihabara, where male customers can for a little time enjoy the feeling of being served by a woman. The male gender opposite is the butler.</description>
<picurl>4954.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2996" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-31">
<name>dreamworld trip</name>
<description>A dreamworld trip is a "visit" to a dreamworld, a place that only exists in the mind of an asleep and dreaming person, or, more generally, any place in someone`s mind or other world that isn`t part of reality; in anime, this means the characters` reality, not our own.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6063" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-28">
<name>hallucination</name>
<description>Hallucinations can occur when excessive amount of drugs (normally illegal) are consumed / injected / smoked. A person hallucinating cannot differentiate between reality &amp; falsehoods. Surroundings &amp; environment looks crazy, bright and colourful. Everything seems to be moving.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="32428" type="main character in" update="2017-05-11">
<rating votes="440">5.69</rating>
<name>Mikazuki Yozora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A cruel and selfish black-haired girl who says she understands and respects bullying but resents being called a bully herself, Yozora`s difficult personality drives away anyone who might wish to make friends with her before she meets http://anidb.net/ch32433 [Kodaka]. She is physically abusive towards, and often argues with, http://anidb.net/ch32430 [Sena] and manipulative towards http://anidb.net/ch32434 [Maria], who she cons into giving up an empty room for the use of the http://anidb.net/ch37939 [Neighbor`s Club], and http://anidb.net/ch32431 [Yukimura], who she fools into working for the club as a cross-dressing cosplay maid. The only person she can`t insult is http://anidb.net/ch32429 [Rika], as Rika takes whatever insult she gives her and deflects it back with a dirty joke that leaves her tired - to the point where she just does what Rika says (like cross-dress for example) rather than argue.
She is Kodaka`s childhood friend, though at the time, he believed that she was a boy, calling her "Sora"; her nickname for him was "Taka." On the day that Kodaka moved, she intended to wear a skirt and reveal her gender to him but was too embarrassed to do so. Kodaka eventually recognized her after she had to cut her hair short due to it catching on fire. She seems to have feelings for Kodaka.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>76319.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32429" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-26">
<rating votes="361">7.36</rating>
<name>Shiguma Rika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A freshman and highly capable mad scientist. She was saved by http://anidb.net/ch32433 [Kodaka] when she fell unconscious during a disastrous lab experiment, and begs to repay his kindness with sex; she joined the http://anidb.net/ch37939 [Neighbor`s Club] just to get closer to him.
Although there are many adult themes in the series, she is the most sexually forward member. This was clearly highlighted in her first speaking appearance, when she described the attractions of rape to Kodaka in the middle of a stunned class. She has a habit of inserting any sexual innuendo possible in her sentences, to the point where she finds it normal to convert any innocent thought into something perverted. As a fujoshi, she is a passionate consumer of BL doujinshi and magazines, is comically aroused by intercourse between mecha, and is delighted when http://anidb.net/ch32431 [Yukimura] offers to have sex with Kodaka. Rika is proud of her perverseness, as she says that she would be a boring person if people only thought of her as a genius girl. To compound her eccentricity, she speaks in the third person.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>76322.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="304" picture="17139.jpg">Fukuen Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32430" type="main character in" update="2017-05-11">
<rating votes="513">7.77</rating>
<name>Kashiwazaki Sena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The wealthy blonde daughter of the school`s headteacher, Sena shows a dislike of all things "ordinary". She is both attractive and academically successful, but her resulting arrogance leads her to be disliked by her female peers. Their admiration eludes her, much as she desires it; she treats her male classmates only as servants to be used, although many of them would like to be her boyfriend. Nonetheless, she holds http://anidb.net/ch32433 [Kodaka] to a higher standard. Kodaka concludes that she is the weirdest member of the club, as she is able to warrant weird and disgusted looks not only from http://anidb.net/ch32428 [Yozora] and http://anidb.net/ch32432 [Kobato], but also from http://anidb.net/ch32431 [Yukimura] and http://anidb.net/ch32429 [Rika].
She enjoys playing video games, including dating sims and eroge, partially because they allow her to make female (if virtual) friends. She is generally fascinated by the girls in these games and has also taken a liking to Kobato. Yozora calls her "Meat" (肉 Niku - due to her large breasts?), an insulting nickname which she secretly likes because it was the first she had ever received.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>76320.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32431" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-26">
<rating votes="233">5.56</rating>
<name>Kusunoki Yukimura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>First introduced as a stalker of http://anidb.net/ch32433 [Kodaka]. "His" first meeting with the http://anidb.net/ch37939 [Neighbor`s Club] resulted in gender confusion, as "his" appearance is decidedly feminine despite "his" assertions of male hood (which are ultimately shown to be false, when her true biological gender is finally revealed).
A gullible student with low self-esteem, she admiringly believes Kodaka to be a romantic and masculine criminal who lives life the way he wants to, and eagerly pledges to become his underling on the basis that she can learn to become less effeminate through him; however, she also appears to harbor a crush on Kodaka. She fittingly refers to Kodaka as "aniki". She tends to do everything Kodaka says to the extreme; when Kodaka asked her to bring http://anidb.net/ch32434 [Maria] something healthy to eat, Yukimura brought a protein shake and tried to force it down her throat until she finished it all.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>76321.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25804" picture="71817.jpg">Yamamoto Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32432" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-22">
<rating votes="409">7.65</rating>
<name>Hasegawa Kobato</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch32433 [Kodaka]`s younger sister; she is a student in middle school, but nonetheless joins the http://anidb.net/ch37939 [club]. She is very close to her brother, who she calls "An-Chan", and behaves in a jealous and clingy way whenever she feels that he is not giving her the attention she deserves, to the point where it is obvious that she has a brother complex. She sees http://anidb.net/ch32434 [Maria] as a rival for Kodaka`s brotherly affections and so often gets into fights with the latter. Despite being older than Maria she has smaller breasts than her, which Maria is always eager to point out.
She has a penchant for darkness, vampires and the macabre ever since she started watching an anime called Full Metal Necromancer. As a result she often speaks in an affected fashion, and claims to be known as "Reisys VI Felicity Sumeragi", an ancient vampire who has lived for ten thousand years, and wears a gothic dress and red contacts, but this facade quickly breaks down when she gets emotionally worked up and she speaks in a strong Kyushu accent. Indeed, her behavior does not for the most part differ from that of a regular girl (procrastinating with her homework, staying inside when it is hot, etc.) which Kodaka points out, causing her to be embarrassed and slightly lose character.
Moreover, she is not very good at mathematics, taking a long time to solve a question Kodaka posed to her, and displays rather limited vocabulary, frequently getting words wrong.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>76323.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32433" type="main character in" update="2017-05-11">
<rating votes="275">5.14</rating>
<name>Hasegawa Kodaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The protagonist, a transfer student who has not been able to make friends in his first month at St. Chronica`s. Of all of the members of the club, he is the most gentle, balanced and socially competent in personality; but his unusual hair color, inherited from his late English mother, leads classmates to assume he is a violent and abusive delinquent and spread defamatory rumors about him. Because of his long experience of antagonism, Kodaka has become accustomed to fighting and can defend himself quite well.
His father is working in the United States, and so he takes care of his younger sister alone at home, which has also made him a good cook. His childhood was characterized by frequent movement, and as a result he has few memories related to home life and close friendships; however, though he does not realize it at first, he and http://anidb.net/ch32428 [Yozora] were childhood friends before his family moved.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>76318.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2225" picture="192115.jpg">Kimura Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32434" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-26">
<rating votes="214">4.13</rating>
<name>Takayama Maria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Maria is the supervising teacher of the http://anidb.net/ch37939 [Neighbors Club]; she is a ten-year old nun. While she`s a child genius she is also very rude and immature, and often uses a variety of expletives when annoyed. She develops a sibling-like relationship with http://anidb.net/ch32433 [Kodaka], who regularly makes her packed lunches, and is affectionate with him, much to http://anidb.net/ch32432 [Kobato`s] annoyance. She is also gullible, which http://anidb.net/ch32428 [Yozora] uses to her advantage, and at some point, Kobato uses it to win an argument.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>76324.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37939" type="appears in" update="2011-10-22">
<rating votes="4">9.65</rating>
<name>Rinjinbu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Rinjinbu is a club at St. Chronica`s Academy founded by Mikazuki Yozora specifically designed for people who don`t have very many friends. They try to learn how to build friendships through cooking together, playing games, and other group activities.</description>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="131424" update="2011-09-27">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2011-09-22</airdate>
<rating votes="8">2.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OAD</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133779" update="2011-10-09">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2011-09-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">僕は友達が少ない ぷれりゅーど</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Prelude</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boku wa Tomodachi ga Sukunai Prelude</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
