<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8557" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2012-02-11</startdate>
<enddate>2012-02-11</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Dragon Age: Blood Mage no Seisen</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ドラゴンエイジ -ブラッドメイジの聖戦-</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Dragon Age: Dawn of the Seeker</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Dragon Age: Úsvit hledačů</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="31431">The part everyone was worried about (the graphics) ended up being the only good part. I didn`t like the voice acting and the story was weak. Some say that if you played and liked Dragon Age 2 then you will like this.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.dragonagemovie.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="10669" type="Direction">Sori Fumihiko</name>
<name id="4642" type="Music">Takahashi Tetsuya</name>
<name id="8475" type="Character Design">Nakayama Daisuke</name>
<name id="32873" type="Original Work">BioWare</name>
<name id="32874" type="Original Work">Electronic Arts</name>
<name id="38584" type="Work">OXYBOT</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on BioWare`s Dragon Age fantasy role-playing game (RPG) franchise.
In a time of darkness and barbarism, the Chantry has arisen - a religious order seeking to bring stability to a world corrupted by sinister magic. Led by the Divine, the Chantry`s Templar warriors ruthlessly restrain the Mages and their magical cabals. But when the Templars fail, the most elite order of the Chantry takes charge - the Seekers!</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="356">3.11</permanent>
<temporary count="356">5.47</temporary>
<review count="1">3.83</review>
</ratings>
<picture>81789.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13604</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11705</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.dragonagemovie.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.funimation.com/dragon-age-movie</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://dragonagemovie.com</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Dragon_Age:_Dawn_of_the_Seeker</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ドラゴンエイジ_-ブラッドメイジの聖戦-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>341349</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14390</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=jpjuLbhBWII</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=70z4PtpYWC8</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=mHguitjj6Pk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1609" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-03-01">
<name>elf</name>
<description>The origin of Elves (Norse; álfar(elves), álfr(elf)) can be found in ancient Norse mythology, in which, elves are described as divine, or near-divine, race of humanoids (Vættir), likened to the Æsir. In common description they are described as sage and immortal beings occupying the threshold between humans and the gods. In some cases humans that were beloved by the gods became elves within their lives. Ancient Elves are delineated into a pair of similar but distinct races; Light Elves (Ljósálfar) and Dark Elves (Svartálfar), each originating from separate homes within the nine worlds of Yggdrasil. Within the Poetic Edda the differences are commonly ascribed as:
"There is one place there that is called the Elf Home (Álfheimr which is the elven city). People live there that are named the light elves (Ljósálfar). But the dark elves (Dökkálfar) live below in earth, in caves and the dark forest and they are unlike them in appearance - and more unlike them in reality. The Light Elves are brighter than the sun in appearance, but the Dark Elves are blacker than pitch." (Snorri, Gylfaginning 17, Prose Edda)</description>
<picurl>63489.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2355" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>dragon</name>
<description>Very intelligent mythical beings - a cross between a very large lizard and a dinosaur - that breath fire, and have a knack for kidnapping damsels, thus distressing them. In Fantasy anime this perceptive species often lives secluded from human civilisation, protectors of long lost knowledge. Dragons seem to be on the verge of extinction.</description>
<picurl>32579.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2647" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>high fantasy</name>
<description>Generally a serious and epic story set in an invented world. The world may be more or less based on real world environments or history. Typical fantastical elements are usually dominating, such as elves, dwarves, magicians, invented languages, quests; just to name a few.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2649" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>dark fantasy</name>
<description>Focus set on darker themes in a fantasy setting, sometimes leaning towards horror elements. Bleak and pessimistic tones often dominate. Dark supernatural beings like vampires may play a significant role.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2801" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>RPG</name>
<description>Any anime that is based on a role-playing game aka RPG. A role-playing video game is a video game which includes elements of non-electronic role-playing games. The player assumes control of one or several fictional characters (a party) who have joined forces in order to perform quests and overcome a great number of challenges and enemies, usually monsters inspired by fantasy, and, to a lesser extent, science fiction and classic mythology. During the course of the game the characters, or avatars, which are generally defined by quantized characteristics, evolve and improve in that their various attributes increase, as well as by gaining more powerful artefacts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4424" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>American derived</name>
<description>A work which was created as a continuation/remake of an American based franchise or cartoon series. These works are completely Japan original, but which lack roots within Japanese media.
See also: http://anidb.net/t3714 [cartoon remake]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5890" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-10">
<name>medieval</name>
<description>Setting is placed in the so called "dark ages". It can be either European style, oriental style or Chinese/Japanese style of castles, armour, ways of fighting etc.. 
Also the average education is weak, superstition is high and fights are settled on foot or horseback. Furthermore the level to technology is rather low.
Note: The perceived low level of cultural and technological evolution may be offset by an influx of magic (fantasy stories) or very sophisticated technology that the inhabitants choose to make less obvious to the viewer.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="37009" type="main character in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="4">5.94</rating>
<name>Cassandra Pentaghast</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cassandra Pentaghast is a Nevarran royal and Seeker of the Chantry.</description>
<picture>59633.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23356" picture="63011.jpg">Kuriyama Chiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39919" type="main character in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="2">2.73</rating>
<name>Regalyan D`Marcall</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Regalyan D`Marcall, also known as Galyan, is specializing in healing magic, and is described as a humorous gentleman with a sharp mind.</description>
<picture>78920.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29880" picture="78922.jpg">Tanihara Shousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39920" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="2">4.41</rating>
<name>Knight Commander</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Knight-Commander Martel is the head of the Templar Order in Orlais. Distrustful of the Seekers of Truth, he does not get along with the High Seeker Aldren.</description>
<picture>78923.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8808" picture="33233.jpg">Gackt</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40053" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-30">
<rating votes="1">2.27</rating>
<name>Avexis</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79172.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3202" picture="24193.jpg">Nakamura Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40054" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-08">
<rating votes="2">3.94</rating>
<name>Byron</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Byron is a member of the Seekers of Truth and Cassandra Pentaghast`s mentor. Although he`s harsh with his training, Byron treats and cares for Cassandra like she was his own daughter.
Byron is a great Seeker, and Seekers are trained to suspect everyone. They must remain ever vigilant to rout out corruption and protect the Chantry.</description>
<picture>79174.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1621" picture="28482.jpg">Komura Tetsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40055" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="1">1.13</rating>
<name>Divine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Divine Justinia V is the current leader of the Andrastian Chantry, since her ascension in 9:34 Dragon.</description>
<picture>79176.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40056" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-30">
<rating votes="1">1.47</rating>
<name>First Enchanter</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79177.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40057" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="1">7.77</rating>
<name>Frenic</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Frenic is the leader of the blood mages.</description>
<picture>79178.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4841" picture="55063.jpg">Iwasaki Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40058" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="2">7.02</rating>
<name>Daishikyou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Callista is the Grand Cleric of Orlais.</description>
<picture>79179.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4956" picture="28490.jpg">Matsutani Kaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40059" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-30">
<rating votes="1">1.47</rating>
<name>High Seeker</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79180.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40060" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="1">3.72</rating>
<name>Lazarro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is an information trader.</description>
<picture>79181.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4425" picture="26689.jpg">Sugino Hiroomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40061" type="appears in" update="2011-12-30">
<name>Seekers</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Seekers of Truth are a secretive faction within the Andrastian Chantry that answer directly to the Divine in Val Royeaux. Not much is known about the organization, its history or responsibilities, but it does appear that they act as a check and balance to the power of the Templar Order, acting in a secretive, investigative and interrogative capacity to root out corruption and protect the Chantry from internal and external threats, much like the inquisition in real life. They also may become involved in the hunting of particularly cunning apostates. Templars fear and despise the Seekers, as they must usually involve themselves when the templars are failing in their duties.</description>
<picture>3337.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="40062" type="appears in" update="2011-12-30">
<rating votes="1">1.47</rating>
<name>Chantry</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Chantry is the dominant religious organization across Thedas, whose philosophy is based upon the life and teachings of the prophet Andraste.</description>
<picture>3342.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="40063" type="appears in" update="2011-12-30">
<rating votes="1">7.77</rating>
<name>Circle of Magi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Circle of Magi is the dominant organization for the training of mages within nations of Thedas. They are governed and monitored by the Chantry and without counting those of Tevinter Imperium, there are 14 Circles of Magi in Thedas. The Circle is allowed to take any child (usually age 6 to 12) from their families as soon as they show signs of magical ability. Even a royal child would be taken by the Circle should they show magical ability. The Circle then raises the child until they are a young adult, at which time they must either undergo the Harrowing or be made Tranquil.</description>
<picture>3354.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="40064" type="appears in" update="2011-12-30">
<rating votes="1">1.13</rating>
<name>Templars</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Templar Order is a military order of the Chantry that, amongst their duties, hunts apostates and maleficars and watches over the mages from the Circle of Magi. While they are officially deemed a force of defenders by the Chantry, established to protect the communities of the faithful from magical threats, they are in fact an army unto themselves; well-equipped, highly disciplined and devoted to the destruction of non-believers in the name of the Maker.</description>
<picture>3355.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="43244" type="appears in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="1">5.71</rating>
<name>Blood Mages</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>4634.png</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="133151" update="2011-09-24">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-09-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133152" update="2018-03-29">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>90</length>
<airdate>2012-02-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
<summary>A brash young Seeker - Cassandra - is accused of treason as she fights a conspiracy that threatens the realm’s most powerful religious order. With her life on the line, she must clear her name and expose those working to destroy the Divine.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="133156" update="2011-09-24">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-07-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Behind the Scenes</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133157" update="2011-09-24">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-07-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Exclusive Teaser</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135529" update="2011-12-25">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-12-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136662" update="2012-01-27">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-01-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Production Update 01</title>
</episode>
<episode id="141174" update="2012-07-22">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-02-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">TVCM 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
