<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8583" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2012-01-08</startdate>
<enddate>2012-03-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Rinne no Lagrange: Flower Declaration of Your Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="synonym">La flor de Rin-ne</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Lag-rin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">lagrange</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">rinne no lagrange</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">輪廻のラグランジェ Flower declaration of your heart</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Lagrange: The Flower of Rin-ne</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">윤회의 라그랑주</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">轮回的拉格朗日</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9108" type="Sequel">Rinne no Lagrange: Flower Declaration of Your Heart - Kamogawa Days</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="10766" approval="6" total="10">Cross Ange: Tenshi to Ryuu no Rondo</anime>
<anime id="5383" approval="6" total="7">Blue Drop: Tenshi-tachi no Gikyoku</anime>
<anime id="13625" approval="1" total="4">Hisone to Masotan</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="219300">It`s good. I don`t know why everyone is acting like it`s a new thing for a series to feel like another or seem like a clone but it`s 2012 now every new show is based, at some level, on every series before it. This show has a good `feel` the music is fantastic, animation is flowy and vibrant. Are there technical issues in the story line and plot? Well sure but what doesn`t when you really analyze it. What it comes down to is: Did it make you happy? Why cant we watch something as a new series with it`s own merits and not discount it because it`s like something else,</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://lag-rin.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="7617" type="Music">Suzuki Saeko</name>
<name id="30214" type="Music">Tomisiro</name>
<name id="719" type="Animation Work">Xebec</name>
<name id="16276" type="Character Design">Norita Takushige</name>
<name id="8985" type="Character Design">Kobayashi Chizuru</name>
<name id="4313" type="Series Composition">Suga Shoutarou</name>
<name id="721" type="Original Work">Production I.G</name>
<name id="7992" type="Direction">Suzuki Toshimasa</name>
<name id="3613" type="Chief Direction">Satou Tatsuo</name>
<name id="14380" type="Chief Animation Direction">Norita Takushige</name>
<name id="8985" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kobayashi Chizuru</name>
<name id="17085" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kutsuzawa Youko</name>
<name id="16510" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tsurukubo Hisako</name>
<name id="16276" type="Chief Animation Direction">Norita Takushige</name>
<name id="9895" type="Chief Animation Direction">Matsumura Takuya</name>
</creators>
<description>* An original series developed by http://anidb.net/cr721 [Production I.G].
Kamogawa is a seaside city in the Chiba prefecture. There lives http://anidb.net/ch35716 [Kyouno Madoka], a student at http://anidb.net/ch40699 [Kamogawa Girls` High School], and the only member of the http://anidb.net/ch40700 [Jersey Club]. Madoka prides herself on being bright and energetic, and spends much of her time helping people.
However, her life changes one day when the mysterious girl http://anidb.net/ch35717 [Lan] asks her to "pilot a robot". In order to protect the citizens of Kamogawa, Madoka agrees and engages in battle against extraterrestrial invaders.
Madoka and Lan are later joined by http://anidb.net/ch35718 [Muginami], and the trio works together to protect the Kamogawa seas, piloting robots called Vox.
~ translated and adapted from official site by Cranston
Note: The first episode premiered at a special event at Kamogawa Auditorium on 23.12.2011. The first regular TV broadcast started on 08.01.2012.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1412">4.74</permanent>
<temporary count="1422">6.53</temporary>
<review count="3">4.94</review>
</ratings>
<picture>78230.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13290</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11227</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>14583</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5026</identifier>
<identifier>tnkvzj</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://lag-rin.com/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.production-ig.co.jp/works/lag-rin/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.viz.com/anime/streaming/lagrange</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Rinne_no_Lagrange</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>輪廻のラグランジェ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2390</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>340777</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13986</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="28" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-16">
<name>baseball</name>
<description>Baseball is like a complicated version of Rounders. It involves hitting a ball with a stick, then running around several bases placed in the form of a diamond on a field. Big in the US, and also in Japan.</description>
<picurl>29801.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1482" parentid="2751" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-08">
<name>wrestling</name>
<description>Wrestling is a fight between two people without weapons, in which each person tries to beat their opponent. Wrestlers use clinching, holding, locking, and leverage. It resembles ritual fighting as it avoids things that will likely lead to serious injury. It is similar to military hand-to-hand combat or self-defence systems.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1759" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>carefree</name>
<description>A [b]carefree[b] person is free of worries, cares or concerns. This does not necessarily imply that they have no responsibilities or are negligent towards them; they are simply able to live out their lives in tranquility regardless of what happens.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2751" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-27">
<name>combat</name>
<description>Combat involves a violent conflict with the goal to establish dominance over an opponent.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2816" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sexual fantasies</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime let their imaginations run wild thinking about another character.
Yes, they are thinking about sex, and in an ecchi anime these thoughts are often perverted, leading to a nosebleed. But it may also be romanticising simply being husband and wife, and everything that implies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2945" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-03-03">
<name>Japan centre of the world</name>
<description>A crisis is about to hit the Earth, but only Japan can resolve the world-wide threat. Thus the story revolves around the happenings in Japan, almost exclusively — the rest of the world and all other nations are irrelevant secondary cast for the most part.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3277" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-28">
<name>bendy lasers</name>
<description>Lasers — of all things — bend at strange angles, are profusely in effect in this anime. Usually seen in a space setting, as part of a weapon system on spaceships.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5459" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>poverty</name>
<description>It refers to the condition of not having the means to afford basic human needs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="35716" type="main character in" update="2012-07-26">
<rating votes="57">6.88</rating>
<name>Kyouno Madoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kyouno Madoka is the sole member of a Jersey Club who often helps out other clubs and people in need and is passionate about her home town of Kamogawa. She has a habit of saying "maru" (meaning `circle`; in Japan these are used to indicate correct answers on tests) when she finishes helping someone. She soon discovers she has the ability to pilot a strange robotic aircraft known as the Vox Aura, which she previously encountered ten years ago when she almost drowned. She names this Vox unit Midori, after its green colour. In Season 2, she is in her last year of high school and has not thought what she is going to do for the future. She still helps out with the Jersey Club and her uncle`s new beach cafe.</description>
<picture>46689.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16763" picture="45795.jpg">Ishihara Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35717" type="main character in" update="2012-07-26">
<rating votes="58">6.84</rating>
<name>Lan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lan is an alien who was sent to protect Madoka and the aircraft. She is not used to earth culture and often picks up terms from the strangest sources. She was initially unable to properly utilize her Vox unit as the knowledge of a supposed fate concerning Vox pilots caused her to become afraid. However, Madoka helps her overcome her fear and she becomes able to use her Vox unit, Vox Lympha, which she names Orca. She is particularly jealous towards Muginami, who shows a lot of interest in Madoka, which leads to her joining the Jersey Club and begin living with Madoka. Due to her luxurious upbringing as princess of the planet Le Garite, Lan has few understanding of the commoners` lifestyle. She returns in Season 2. Though she looks that same, Madoka pointed out she grew up a little bit.</description>
<picture>46691.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21733" picture="152476.jpg">Seto Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35718" type="main character in" update="2012-07-26">
<rating votes="43">6.61</rating>
<name>Muginami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Muginami is another Ovid pilot who transfers in Madoka`s class and joins the Jersey Club. Although she appears to have a slow-witted personality, she is actually sharp and perceptive. Born on a Prison Planet, she views Villagiulio as an older brother and by his orders, she infiltrated the Pharos base to steal one of the Ovids, thus she ends up becoming the pilot of Vox Ignis, which she nicknamed Fupo. After being betrayed and abandoned by Villagiulio, Muginami finds herself a new place among Madoka and her friends. After Villagiulio`s second skimish, she and her Vox took him and retreated into space. She returns in Season 2. Fupo is now equipped with a energy cape she uses as a shield.</description>
<picture>46706.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35719" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-18">
<rating votes="11">6.68</rating>
<name>Kirius</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46707.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35720" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-18">
<rating votes="16">5.43</rating>
<name>Izo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46716.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35721" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-18">
<rating votes="10">3.73</rating>
<name>Array</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46705.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20249" picture="186289.jpg">Matsuoka Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37437" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-07">
<rating votes="9">1.41</rating>
<name>Moid</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65604.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1692" picture="224934.jpg">Okitsu Kazuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37438" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-07">
<rating votes="41">5.61</rating>
<name>Nakaizumi Youko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65605.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37439" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-07">
<rating votes="12">6.03</rating>
<name>Iwabuchi Machiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65606.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1876" picture="66007.jpg">Asakura Azumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37799" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-16">
<rating votes="9">5.97</rating>
<name>Kondou Michi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69514.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20025" picture="132938.jpg">Mimori Suzuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37800" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-16">
<rating votes="9">5.97</rating>
<name>Nogami Sachi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69513.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29400" picture="157186.jpg">Yamaguchi Rikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37801" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-16">
<rating votes="3">6.78</rating>
<name>James Row</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69505.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="60" picture="171602.jpg">Kawada Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37802" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-16">
<rating votes="3">6.08</rating>
<name>Uehara Haruka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69502.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37803" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-16">
<name>Watabe Eri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69500.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37804" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-16">
<rating votes="9">5.53</rating>
<name>Tadokoro Shouzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69499.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="68" picture="16675.jpg">Yasumura Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37805" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-16">
<rating votes="3">2.20</rating>
<name>Serizawa Souta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69469.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12623" picture="151646.jpg">Iguchi Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37806" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-16">
<rating votes="6">6.18</rating>
<name>Nakaizumi Hiroshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69455.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="373" picture="191382.jpg">Hamada Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38629" type="appears in" update="2011-11-11">
<rating votes="3">9.94</rating>
<name>Vox Aura</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>76970.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="38630" type="appears in" update="2011-11-11">
<name>Vox Rympha</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>76971.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="38631" type="appears in" update="2011-11-11">
<rating votes="3">9.94</rating>
<name>Vox Ignis</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>76972.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="38632" type="appears in" update="2011-11-11">
<name>Libertas</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>76973.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="38633" type="appears in" update="2011-11-11">
<name>Voluntas</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>76974.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="38634" type="appears in" update="2011-11-11">
<name>Teneritas</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>76975.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="38635" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-11">
<rating votes="6">5.07</rating>
<name>Iwa Ayane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76976.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38636" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-11">
<rating votes="8">6.97</rating>
<name>Kuzuhara Tomoe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76977.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7789" picture="34523.jpg">Moriya Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38637" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-11">
<rating votes="8">4.94</rating>
<name>Igarashi Shouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76978.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5886" picture="30429.jpg">Nomizu Iori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38638" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-11">
<rating votes="5">6.50</rating>
<name>Takakura Erika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76979.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="83" picture="38901.jpg">Nanri Yuuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40699" type="appears in" update="2012-01-18">
<name>Kamogawa Joshi Koukou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="40700" type="appears in" update="2012-09-02">
<name>Jersey-bu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The purpose of the Jersey Club, which they wear a jersey as a sign of their membership, is to help out other clubs and people in need. Madoka who is passionate about her home town of Kamogawa, is the current head captain of the club who was inspired by Yoko to join the Jersey Club after her mother died trying to save someone.</description>
</character>
<character id="40860" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-01-27">
<rating votes="4">7.26</rating>
<name>Nao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>80639.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40861" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-01-27">
<rating votes="4">7.26</rating>
<name>Amane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>80635.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40862" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-01-27">
<rating votes="4">5.56</rating>
<name>Reika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>80640.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40864" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-01-27">
<rating votes="4">5.56</rating>
<name>Setsu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>80643.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="41105" type="appears in" update="2012-02-05">
<name>Aruvirium</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>81080.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="41106" type="appears in" update="2012-02-05">
<name>Torirok</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>81081.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="41108" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-05">
<rating votes="20">6.84</rating>
<name>Astelia Lisamarie de Rochefall</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81083.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12266" picture="56026.jpg">Kanemoto Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41109" type="appears in" update="2012-02-05">
<name>Pharos</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="41110" type="appears in" update="2012-02-05">
<name>Kiss</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="41111" type="appears in" update="2012-02-05">
<rating votes="1">5.58</rating>
<name>Fin E Ld Si Laffinty</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81085.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21733" picture="152476.jpg">Seto Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41112" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-13">
<rating votes="12">5.02</rating>
<name>De Metorio le Vilajulio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81529.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41113" type="appears in" update="2012-02-05">
<name>Vilajulio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81087.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41320" type="appears in" update="2012-02-13">
<name>Aruviteio</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>81526.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="41321" type="appears in" update="2012-02-13">
<rating votes="4">7.36</rating>
<name>Grania</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81527.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="423" picture="37799.jpg">Nakajima Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41322" type="appears in" update="2012-02-13">
<rating votes="3">1.00</rating>
<name>Fin E Ld Shi Diselmain</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81528.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42323" type="appears in" update="2012-03-11">
<rating votes="8">7.95</rating>
<name>De Metorio le Yurikano</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>83426.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="101" picture="16709.jpg">Ise Mariya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42324" type="appears in" update="2012-03-11">
<name>Magregur</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>83427.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42325" type="appears in" update="2012-03-11">
<name>Magfort</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>83428.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42326" type="appears in" update="2012-03-11">
<name>Magdora</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>83429.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="135896" update="2012-02-09">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ようこそ, 鴨川へ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to Kamogawa!</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Bem-Vinda A Kamogawa!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youkoso, Kamogawa e!</title>
<summary>As a girl named Kyouno Madoka rescues a girl from drowning, she finds her school uniform missing and later returned by a strange girl. Later that night, Madoka is questioned by her cousin, Nakaizumi Youko, about something. The next day, Madoka once again meets the girl, who introduces herself as Lan and asks Madoka to pilot a robotic aircraft known as an Ovid at an offshore base. As Madoka touches the Ovid and experiences a flashback of sorts, an enemy Ovid from outer space, piloted by a man named Array, appears and attacks the base. Lan reveals herself to be an alien sent to protect Madoka and the Ovid, the two of which are linked together. Madoka agrees to pilot the Ovid, which responds to her emotions and changes into a robotic form to fight against Array, defeating him using Madoka`s knowledge of club activities.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="135969" update="2012-02-09">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-01-29</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鴨川スイマーズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Swimmers of Kamogawa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kamogawa Swimmers</title>
<summary>Muginami transfers into Madoka`s class, which causes worry for the organisation. Later, Youko and one of the organization`s representatives talk to Madoka`s teacher about her piloting Midori. Youko agrees to let Madoka continue piloting Midori on the condition that she is allowed to continue living at home and attending school. Soon afterwards, Madoka and Muginami participate in an open swimming contest whilst Lan keeps watch on a boat. Spotting her, Muginami decides to play a prank on Lan and tip her into the sea, unaware that she is unable to swim. Realising her mistake, Muginami helps Madoka rescue Lan and performs CPR on her. Afterwards, Madoka invites Muginami to join the Jersey Club, much to Lan`s annoyance. Both Muginami and Lan decide to help out at Madoka`s family restaurant, with their individual traits attracting many customers. After becoming jealous after Madoka allows Muginami to live with her, Lan also decides to transfer into Madoka`s class, join the Jersey Club and start living with Madoka. Meanwhile, a glitch in security allows Array to escape imprisonment and rejoin his allies, who are making a deal with another enemy.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="135970" update="2012-02-09">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鴨川にランの花咲く</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lan Blooms in Kamogawa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kamogawa ni Lan no Hanasaku</title>
<summary>As Madoka rushes to fight against the enemy Ovid to protect her town, Lan becomes conflicted about a legend Madoka doesn`t know of, the fear of which prevents her from being able to pilot her own Vox Lympha. As the enemy, Kirius, tries to ask Madoka to come to her planet, she refuses and the fight resumes. Feeling Madoka is in danger, Lan overcomes her fear and pilots the Lympha, but finds herself up against Izo. As Lan expresses her guilt towards dragging Madoka into this, Madoka lifts her spirits, enabling her to overcome her fears and transform Lympha into its fighter mode, allowing her to come to Madoka`s aid, forcing the enemy to retreat. Afterwards, Madoka and Lan decide to name their Vox units Midori and Orca respectively.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="135971" update="2012-02-09">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-01-15</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鴨川スピリット</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kamogawa Spirit</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Espírito De Komogawa!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kamogawa Spirit</title>
<summary>As Madoka returns in the Ovid, known as Vox Aura, she is shocked to learn that she is to do a second mission. As Youko decides to infiltrate the base, Madoka briefly runs into another Ovid pilot named Muginami before regrouping with Lan to perform the next mission to fight against another enemy Ovid piloted by a man named Izo. As Madoka finds herself struggling, with her doubt causing the Vox to shut down, she receives a call from Youko who encourages her to finish what she started. As Madoka launches a counterattack on the enemy, another enemy Ovid appears.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="135972" update="2015-01-12">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-12-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135973" update="2015-01-12">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-12-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136699" update="2012-01-30">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鴨川ロリータ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Lolita in Kamogawa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kamogawa Lolita</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136700" update="2012-01-30">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-02-19</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">曇り のち 鴨川</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cloudy Skies, Followed by Kamogawa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kumori Nochi Kamogawa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136701" update="2012-01-30">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-02-12</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">風と火と水と鴨川と</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Wind, Fire, and Water Above Kamogawa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaze to Hi to Mizu to Kamogawa to</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136702" update="2012-01-30">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-02-05</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鴨川に来た男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Man Who Came to Kamogawa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kamogawa ni Kita Otoko</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137387" update="2012-02-27">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">またいつの日か, 鴨川で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Until We Meet Again, in Kamogawa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mata Itsu no Hi ka, Kamogawa de</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137388" update="2012-02-27">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-03-18</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鴨川絶対防衛ライン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kamogawa`s Last Line of Defense</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kamogawa Zettai Bouei Line</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137389" update="2012-02-27">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-03-11</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらば鴨川</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goodbye, Kamogawa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saraba Kamogawa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137390" update="2012-02-27">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-03-04</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勝浦発→鴨川行</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Departing Katsuura, Heading to Kamogawa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Katsuura Hatsu -&amp;gt; Kamogawa Iki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138227" update="2012-10-06">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-03-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カモガワガールズトーク</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kamogawa Girls Talk</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138228" update="2012-10-06">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2012-03-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Behind of Lagrange 『輪廻のラグランジェ』製作発表会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Behind the Lagrange 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Behind of Lagrange: "Rinne no Lagrange" Seisaku Happyoukai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139251" update="2012-10-06">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かもがわ流真剣白刃取り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kamogawa Ryuu Shinken Shirahadori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="140146" update="2012-10-06">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カモガワプールサイドにて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kamogawa Poolside Nite</title>
</episode>
<episode id="140633" update="2012-10-06">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-07-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カモガワ初恋物語</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kamogawa Hatsukoi Monogatari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="140634" update="2012-10-06">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-06-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かもがわゴースト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kamogawa Ghost</title>
</episode>
<episode id="143690" update="2012-10-06">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-08-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かもがわ&amp;lt;かつうらデイズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kamogawa: Katsuura Days</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144353" update="2012-10-01">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2012-08-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Behind of Lagrange PV·CM集</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Behind the Lagrange 6 - PV Collection</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Behind of Lagrange: PV, CM Shuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144354" update="2012-09-28">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2012-06-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Behind of Lagrange 石原夏織 鴨川に行く &amp;lt;後編&amp;gt;</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Behind the Lagrange 5 - Ishihara Kaori, Kamogawa ni Iku! Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Behind of Lagrange: Ishihara Kaori, Kamogawa ni Iku - Kouhen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144355" update="2012-09-28">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2012-06-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Behind of Lagrange 石原夏織 鴨川に行く &amp;lt;前編&amp;gt;</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Behind the Lagrange 4 - Ishihara Kaori, Kamogawa ni Iku! Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Behind of Lagrange: Ishihara Kaori, Kamogawa ni Iku - Zenpen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144356" update="2012-09-28">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-05-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Behind of Lagrange NISSAN JUKEアートカー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Behind the Lagrange 3 - NISSAN Juke ArtCar</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Behind of Lagrange: Nissan Juke Art Car</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144357" update="2012-09-28">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2012-04-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Behind of Lagrange ウォクス·アウラ ヒューマンスケールモデル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Behind the Lagrange 2 - Human Scale Model</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Behind of Lagrange: Vox Aura Human Scale Model</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
