<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8606" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2012-01-21</startdate>
<enddate>2012-01-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">.hack//Sekai no Mukou ni</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ドット ハック</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ドットハック セカイの向こうに</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">.hack//The Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">.hack//Beyond the World</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">.hack//Versus: The Thanatos Report</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Злам - Поза Світом</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ドット ハック セカイの向こうに</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="official">.злам// Поза «World`-ом»</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7883" type="Other">.hack//Quantum</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="14523" approval="1" total="2">Itai no wa Iya nano de Bougyoryoku ni Kyokufuri Shitai to Omoimasu.</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="31111">While it does start a little slow like most .hack ovas/series it`s still a very good show. The 3D graphics were a little strange at first but actual fit the movie. Enjoyed it greatly.
Only bad part is it made me wish modern games could capture the same look and felling as the movie portrayed.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="371670">I didn`t expect much because of its low rating but what I got was a very decent movie with amazing animation. CG looked strange at first in the normal world but in the virtual reality it became stunning. I think it`s the best movie about VR I`ve seen so far, sadly underrated. :)</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.hack.channel.or.jp/themovie/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3756" type="Work">Flying Dog</name>
<name id="3512" type="Work">Bandai Namco Games</name>
<name id="1048" type="Work">Hakuhodo DY Media Partners</name>
<name id="28215" type="Animation Work">CyberConnect2 sai</name>
<name id="22969" type="Direction">Matsuyama Hiroshi</name>
<name id="2727" type="Character Design">Ozaki Tomomi</name>
<name id="8909" type="Character Design">Hosokawa Seiichirou</name>
<name id="2728" type="Character Design">Toi8</name>
<name id="46652" type="Music">Fukuda Chikayo</name>
<name id="48627" type="Character Design">Fujimoto Miki</name>
</creators>
<description>In 2024, children have lived their entire lives since birth in a world connected by networks. A cheerful 14-year-old middle school girl named http://anidb.net/ch35918 [Yuuki Sora] has no interest in games, but her friends get her to go into the popular network game The World. However, due to a certain incident in The World, anomalies start occurring in the real world.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="543">5.64</permanent>
<temporary count="549">6.77</temporary>
<review count="1">3.50</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221181.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13373</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11375</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>15219</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5115</identifier>
<identifier>bzxnzn</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.hack.channel.or.jp/themovie/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>.hack//The_Movie</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ドットハック_セカイの向こうに</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2419</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>341071</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14019</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="380" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-08">
<name>whale</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2538" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-02">
<name>playing video games</name>
<description>Video games are electronic games played on a video screen, normally a television or a built-in screen when played on a handheld machine.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2788" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-21">
<name>confession</name>
<description>Someone confesses his/her love to someone else.</description>
<picurl>160903.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2801" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>RPG</name>
<description>Any anime that is based on a role-playing game aka RPG. A role-playing video game is a video game which includes elements of non-electronic role-playing games. The player assumes control of one or several fictional characters (a party) who have joined forces in order to perform quests and overcome a great number of challenges and enemies, usually monsters inspired by fantasy, and, to a lesser extent, science fiction and classic mythology. During the course of the game the characters, or avatars, which are generally defined by quantized characteristics, evolve and improve in that their various attributes increase, as well as by gaining more powerful artefacts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2839" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>virtual world</name>
<description>A virtual world is a place where the character interacts with a computer (or some other device)-simulated environment, be it real or imagined. The condition for a virtual reality to exist is the existence of an originating "real" (source/anchor) world for the character. In some cases, a virtual reality where characters can get harmed physically is depicted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4465" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-08">
<name>stereoscopic imaging</name>
<description>This anime was shown in cinema rooms with stereoscopic 3D capabilities, released on Blu-ray 3D, or available for other stereoscopic 3D capable devices like the Nintendo 3DS or the Sharp AQUOS "NERV Edition" SH-06D smartphone. It was either produced in stereo 3D (e.g. "Baby Princess 3D Paradise Love") or produced in 2D and later converted from 2D to 3D (e.g. "Koukaku Kidoutai Stand Alone Complex: Solid State Society"). At any rate, it was at some point officially available with stereoscopic 3D depth effect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5943" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-14">
<name>misunderstanding</name>
<description>Suggests that a large portion of storyline revolves around a rather large misunderstanding between two or more characters, usually forming long lasting situations of separation or hostility between all those involved.
A large portion of the story may be dedicated to gradually working all parties into a mutual understanding to true intentions or changes of heart.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="35918" type="main character in" update="2011-08-23">
<rating votes="2">7.06</rating>
<name>Yuuki Sora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48926.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3784" picture="171238.jpg">Sakuraba Nanami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35919" type="main character in" update="2011-08-23">
<rating votes="1">7.98</rating>
<name>Tanaka Kakeru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48944.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29626" picture="78589.jpg">Matsuzaka Toori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35920" type="main character in" update="2011-08-23">
<rating votes="1">7.98</rating>
<name>Okano Tomohiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48914.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29625" picture="78237.jpg">Tanaka Kei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62452" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-19">
<rating votes="1">7.98</rating>
<name>Eleanor</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147393.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="62453" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-19">
<rating votes="1">7.98</rating>
<name>David Steinberg</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147392.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="62454" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-19">
<rating votes="1">7.98</rating>
<name>Yuuki Hiyori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147391.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62455" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-19">
<rating votes="1">7.98</rating>
<name>Yuuki Takefu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147390.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="604" picture="154161.jpg">Ogata Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62456" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-19">
<rating votes="1">7.98</rating>
<name>Hasebe Kaho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147389.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="80" picture="228656.jpg">Fukui Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62457" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-19">
<rating votes="1">7.98</rating>
<name>Tokura Chieko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147388.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="133652" update="2012-06-14">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>110</length>
<airdate>2012-01-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="143769" update="2012-09-08">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2012-06-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">タナトスレポート</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Thanatos Report</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Thanatos Report</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
