<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8652" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-10-04</startdate>
<enddate>2012-03-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sengoku Paradise: Kiwami</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">戦国☆パラダイス-極-[きわみ]</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="7230" approval="1" total="2">Tono to Issho</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://sengk.jp/pc/</url>
<creators>
<name id="29315" type="Series Composition">Oota Guiya</name>
<name id="29314" type="Original Work">G-mode</name>
<name id="11871" type="Character Design">Haneda Kouji</name>
<name id="30334" type="Animation Work">LMD</name>
<name id="29319" type="Animation Work">Milky Cartoon</name>
<name id="18042" type="Character Design">Okuyama Suzuna</name>
<name id="6265" type="Direction">Kikuchi Katsuya</name>
<name id="35246" type="Music">El</name>
<name id="44823" type="Music">Abe Ryuudai</name>
</creators>
<description>It is the age of Warring States, after the death of Toyotomi Hideyoshi. The various military leaders of the land have split east and west, and strive against each other for hegemony. The Eastern Army proclaims http://anidb.net/ch36657 [Tokugawa Ieyasu] as supreme commander, while in the west, the commanders gather around http://anidb.net/ch36662 [Ishida Mitsunari].
http://anidb.net/ch36651 [Date Masamune], http://anidb.net/ch36661 [Sanada Yukimura], http://anidb.net/ch36658 [Honda Tadakatsu], http://anidb.net/ch36653 [Ootani Yoshitsugu]... These and other heroes of the time prepare to take up arms. Some for ambition, others for their comrades. The stage is set for the curtain to rise once more over Sekigahara!
At least, that`s the way it should be. However, these warlords get along unusually well with each other.
~ translated and adapted from official site by Cranston</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="56">2.19</permanent>
<temporary count="56">4.67</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>54522.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13536</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11547</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4944</identifier>
<identifier>hnkidn</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/sgpk/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>戦国☆パラダイス_-極-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2307</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>340781</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13921</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2687" parentid="2641" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-02-05">
<name>Sengoku period</name>
<description>The Sengoku period (戦国時代, Sengoku jidai) or Warring States period in Japanese history was a time of social upheaval, political intrigue, and nearly constant military conflict that lasted roughly from the middle of the 15th century to the beginning of the 17th century. The name "Sengoku" was adopted by Japanese historians in reference to the Warring States period in Chinese history (Sengoku jidai (戦国時代) in Japanese) which preceded the unification of China. Likewise, the Sengoku period in Japan would eventually lead to the unification of political power under the Tokugawa shogunate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="36650" type="main character in" update="2011-12-20">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Ii Naomasa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78732.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25068" picture="70119.jpg">Kajikawa Shouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36651" type="main character in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Date Masamune</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78733.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="174" picture="41158.jpg">Kakihara Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36652" type="main character in" update="2011-12-20">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Katou Kiyomasa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78734.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17523" picture="223264.jpg">Yamamoto Kanehira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36653" type="main character in" update="2011-12-20">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Ootani Yoshitsugu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78735.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23534" picture="74510.jpg">Murata Taishi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36654" type="main character in" update="2011-12-20">
<name>Ukita Hideie</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78736.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54514" picture="215991.jpg">Hori Taiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36655" type="main character in" update="2011-12-20">
<rating votes="2">3.26</rating>
<name>Kobayakawa Hideaki</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78737.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4715" picture="223209.jpg">Imai Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36656" type="main character in" update="2011-12-20">
<name>Shima Kiyooki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78739.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5040" picture="88977.jpg">Kawahara Yoshihisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36657" type="main character in" update="2017-11-12">
<name>Tokugawa Ieyasu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78742.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36658" type="main character in" update="2011-12-20">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Honda Tadakatsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78743.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29318" picture="10176.jpeg">Sagawa Naoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36659" type="main character in" update="2011-12-20">
<rating votes="4">4.32</rating>
<name>Kai-hime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78744.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23608" picture="65179.jpg">Mochizuki Rei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36660" type="main character in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Naoe Kanetsugu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78750.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4620" picture="171990.jpg">Kanbara Daichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36661" type="main character in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Sanada Yukimura</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1701.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2575" picture="139952.jpg">Eguchi Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36662" type="main character in" update="2017-11-16">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Ishida Mitsunari</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78754.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36663" type="main character in" update="2011-12-20">
<name>Tachibana Muneshige</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78755.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36680" picture="153752.jpg">Saitou Souma</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="133688" update="2011-11-01">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2011-11-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">虹之架橋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Niji no Kakyou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133689" update="2011-10-28">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2011-11-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪戯南瓜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itazura Kabocha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133690" update="2011-10-28">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2011-10-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">晩秋茶会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Banshuu Yakkai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133691" update="2011-10-28">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2011-10-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">健康診断</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kenkou Shindan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133692" update="2011-10-28">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2011-10-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">必勝祈願</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hisshou Kigan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135296" update="2012-01-22">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2011-12-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">温泉自慢</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onsen Jiman</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135297" update="2011-12-12">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2011-12-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">頂上決戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Choujou Kessen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135298" update="2011-12-12">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2011-12-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">聖夜秘話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seiya Hiwa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135299" update="2011-12-12">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2011-12-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">料理将軍</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryouri Shougun</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135300" update="2011-12-12">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2011-12-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛猫日和</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aibyoubiyori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135301" update="2011-12-12">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2011-11-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">迷走遠足</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meisou Ensoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135302" update="2011-12-12">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2011-11-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">薔薇之如</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bara no Goto</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136539" update="2012-03-19">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-03-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 26</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136540" update="2012-03-19">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-03-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 25</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136541" update="2012-03-19">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-03-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 24</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136542" update="2012-03-19">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-03-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 23</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136543" update="2012-01-22">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-02-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">絢爛雛祭</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 22</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136544" update="2012-01-22">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-02-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪友介抱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 21</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136545" update="2012-01-22">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-02-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛之甘味</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 20</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136546" update="2012-01-22">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-02-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">童心残照</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 19</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136547" update="2012-03-19">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-01-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">鬼外福内</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 18</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136548" update="2012-01-22">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-01-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">三成之宝</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 17</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136549" update="2012-01-22">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-01-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">再会竹馬</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 16</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136550" update="2012-01-22">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-01-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">天下御免</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 15</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136551" update="2012-01-22">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-01-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">歌留多遊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 14</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Karuta Asobi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136552" update="2012-01-22">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2011-12-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大忘年会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 13</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daibounenkai</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
