<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8661" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-10-13</startdate>
<enddate>2011-12-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gudaguda Fairies</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Gdgd Youseis</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">gdgd妖精s[ぐだぐだフェアリーズ]</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">gdgd Fairies</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9473" type="Sequel">Gudaguda Fairies 2</anime>
<anime id="13582" type="Other">Guda Men</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="10010" approval="5" total="5">Tesagure! Bukatsumono</anime>
<anime id="4777" approval="2" total="10">Lucky Star</anime>
<anime id="8471" approval="2" total="4">Popee the Performer</anime>
<anime id="12714" approval="2" total="4">Forest Fairy Five</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="477898">This show is hilarious, the game spoof and Fusako may have been the funniest things i have seen in the past few years. If danshi koukousei is good, this is even better. I don`t care for the animation for either of them, but they`re both absolutely hilarious, but GDGD is even funnier, as almost all the gags are remarkably memorable. I would pay no heed to the rating, as that`s just a knee jerk reaction to the animation, I got to believe, if you delve past the first three episodes - and they`re short, you`ll most likely find the show hilarious.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://enet-dvd.com/enet/sp/gdgdf/</url>
<creators>
<name id="29707" type="Music">Inoue Jun`ichi</name>
<name id="29708" type="Character Design">Sugahara Souta</name>
<name id="29708" type="Direction">Sugahara Souta</name>
<name id="29709" type="Series Composition">Ishidate Koutarou</name>
</creators>
<description>The fully computer-animated series centers around three little fairies who live inside the trees in Fairy Forest. They have weak magical powers, but they also have the Mental and Time Room where they can freely use magic, as well as the Afure Lake with which they can peer into other worlds.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="126">4.98</permanent>
<temporary count="127">6.00</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>79748.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13451</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11809</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.mxtv.co.jp/gdgdf/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://gdgdfairy.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Gdgd_Fairies</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Gdgd妖精s</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2297</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>340822</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13959</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>gdgd-fairies</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="34">
<externalentity>
<url>https://ch.nicovideo.jp/gdgd</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="780" parentid="2849" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-23">
<name>fairy</name>
<description>A fairy is a type of mythical being or legendary creature in European folklore, a form of spirit, often described as metaphysical, supernatural, or preternatural.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>206567.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3721" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-07">
<name>RPG elements</name>
<description>The anime shows elements of a `R`ole `P`laying `G`ame, either as part of a parody or because the anime is actually based on an RPG.
Typical elements: When collecting items, beating opponents, or levelling up a distinct (often childishly sounding) sound cue is played. A HUD (`H`eads `U`p `D`isplay) may also be presenting in combat, showing vital player and "enemy" statistics.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4228" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-09">
<name>subtle OP ED sequence change</name>
<description>A (small) part of the opening or ending sequence changes after a certain episode, usually to reflect a plot milestone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6494" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>half-length episodes</name>
<description>Half-length episodes are regular episodes that are somewhat shorter than the standard length. This includes episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length; shows with episodes up to and including 10 minutes are http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes] instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6717" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-07-26">
<name>improvised dialogue</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="36797" type="main character in" update="2011-09-17">
<rating votes="5">6.95</rating>
<name>Korokoro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>56326.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1511" picture="173601.jpg">Akesaka Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36798" type="main character in" update="2011-09-17">
<rating votes="2">2.14</rating>
<name>Shirushiru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>56319.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1609" picture="19579.jpg">Mizuhara Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36799" type="main character in" update="2011-09-17">
<rating votes="2">2.14</rating>
<name>Pikupiku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>56320.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20025" picture="132938.jpg">Mimori Suzuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40322" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-09">
<rating votes="2">8.54</rating>
<name>Mochida Fusako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Woman from another world.</description>
<picture>79710.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1511" picture="173601.jpg">Akesaka Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40323" type="appears in" update="2012-01-09">
<rating votes="2">6.82</rating>
<name>Korokoro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Grown-up Korokoro.</description>
<picture>79711.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1511" picture="173601.jpg">Akesaka Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40324" type="appears in" update="2012-01-09">
<rating votes="2">7.76</rating>
<name>Shirushiru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Grown-up Shirushiru.</description>
<picture>79712.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1609" picture="19579.jpg">Mizuhara Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="133998" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">睡眠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sleep</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suimin</title>
<summary>Todays talk is about sleep, the fairies discuss how much sleep is needed to be efficient and the different type of sleepers.  In  The Room of Spirit and Time a dangerous game of magic shiritori is played.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>588006</identifier>
<identifier>gdgd-fairies</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="134248" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-10-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">小さな幸せ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Little Happiness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chiisana Shiawase</title>
<summary>Is luck getting to sleep in for a while and not be late?  Is happiness finding money in your coat pocket? The girls discuss what is luck and happiness and have a bungee jump bread-eating contest.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>588004</identifier>
<identifier>gdgd-fairies</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="134326" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-10-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ウワサ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rumours</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uwasa</title>
<summary>pkpk can`t stop sneezing.  People say if you sneeze it`s because people are saying something about you.  But what are they saying about pkpk?  You can see right here!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>588002</identifier>
<identifier>gdgd-fairies</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="134745" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-11-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">待ち時間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Waiting Time</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Machijikan</title>
<summary>srsr is 10 minutes late to the meeting.  There`s a deep and terrifying reason why she`s always late...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>587998</identifier>
<identifier>gdgd-fairies</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="134746" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナミダ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tears</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Namida</title>
<summary>pkpk was crying last night and now her eyes are swelled up.  Tears are strange; you cry when you`re happy and when you`re sad.  This discussion of tears reveals a terrifying plot!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>588000</identifier>
<identifier>gdgd-fairies</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="135074" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-11-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">前回までのgdgd妖精s</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Previously on Gudaguda Fairies</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zenkai Made no Gudaguda Fairies</title>
<summary>The fairies play real-life version of party games.  But things get out of hand when the monkeys they`re playing with start evolving...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>587996</identifier>
<identifier>gdgd-fairies</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="135075" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-11-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一日一善</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Everyday Good Deed</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ichinichi Ichizen</title>
<summary>Shiru wants to do good deeds every day but wants low risk, high reward.   Then the girls play a game that will change them forever.  Finally, they peak into another word.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>587940</identifier>
<identifier>gdgd-fairies</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="135280" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-12-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ことわざ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sayings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kotowaza</title>
<summary>Shr-chan dislikes the phrase “the grass greener on the other side.”   So the fairies attempt to figure out what it actually means.  The girls attempt to do a gdgd live broadcast and come up with different ways to attract viewers.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>587942</identifier>
<identifier>gdgd-fairies</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="135281" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-12-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">趣味</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hobby</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shumi</title>
<summary>pk-chan is looking for a hobby but the focus seems to be only on shopping.  The fairies build their ideal house and one seems to take it ideas from a famous plumber.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>587988</identifier>
<identifier>gdgd-fairies</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="135404" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-12-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">終わりなき追憶の彼方に~Eternal~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beyond the Horizon of Endless Recollection: Eternal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Owarinaki Tsuioku no Kanata ni ~Eternal~</title>
<summary>It’s been 10 years and kr-chan has returned to the tree house she shared with her other fairies.   She must enlist the help of Fusako to sober up shr-chan so they can attempt to bring pk-chan back to life.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>587994</identifier>
<identifier>gdgd-fairies</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="135405" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-12-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">前回までの未公開妖精s</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Previously on Unreleased Fairies</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zenkai Made no Mikoukai Fairies</title>
<summary>To make their magic stronger the Fairies decide to practice outside the time room.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>587992</identifier>
<identifier>gdgd-fairies</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="135406" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2011-12-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">最後の3日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Last Three Days</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo no 3-ka</title>
<summary>pk-chan is looking for a hobby but the focus seems to be only on shopping.  The fairies build their ideal house and one seems to take it ideas from a famous plumber.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>587990</identifier>
<identifier>gdgd-fairies</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150747" update="2013-11-05">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">森のバックステージ 9-12</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Woods Backstage 9-12</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mori no Backstage 9-12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150748" update="2013-11-05">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">森のバックステージ 5-8</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Woods Backstage 5-8</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mori no Backstage 5-8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150749" update="2013-11-05">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">森のバックステージ 1-4</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Woods Backstage 1-4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mori no Backstage 1-4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150750" update="2013-05-25">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>8</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">未公開アフレ湖 3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unreleased Dub Lake 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mikoukai Afure Mizuumi 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150751" update="2013-05-25">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>10</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">未公開アフレ湖 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unreleased Dub Lake 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mikoukai Afure Mizuumi 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150752" update="2013-05-25">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>6</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">未公開アフレ湖 1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unreleased Dub Lake 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mikoukai Afure Mizuumi 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150753" update="2013-05-25">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">マルチアングルティータイム (全員)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Multi-Angle Tea Time - All together</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Multi-Angle Tea Time (Zen`in)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150754" update="2013-05-25">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">マルチアングルティータイム (コロちゃん)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Multi-Angle Tea Time - Koro-chan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Multi-Angle Tea Time (Koro-chan)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150755" update="2013-05-25">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">マルチアングルティータイム (シルちゃん)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Multi-Angle Tea Time - Shiru-chan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Multi-Angle Tea Time (Shiru-chan)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150756" update="2013-05-25">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">マルチアングルティータイム (ピクちゃん)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Multi-Angle Tea Time - Piku-chan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Multi-Angle Tea Time (Piku-chan)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150757" update="2013-05-25">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">エピローグ・ロングver</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Epilogue Long ver</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Epilogue Long Ver</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150758" update="2013-05-25">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-10-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150759" update="2013-05-25">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-10-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="182128" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617755</identifier>
<identifier>gdgd-fairies</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
