<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8667" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2012-01-03</startdate>
<enddate>2012-03-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Natsume Yuujinchou Shi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Natsume Yujincho (4)</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">夏目友人帐4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">ny4</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">夏目友人帳 肆</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Natsume`s Book of Friends (4)</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">นัตสึเมะกับบันทึกพิศวง ภาค 4</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">夏目友人帐 肆</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="12009" type="Sequel">Natsume Yuujinchou Go</anime>
<anime id="8286" type="Prequel">Natsume Yuujinchou San</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="132589">This just keeps getting better and I think it would have been wonderful if the company had made this series an epic. I`d like to see more development but doesn`t disappoint at all..until u wonder where the rest of it is -_-</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="261477">do i really need to recommend this, it`s the 4th season, everyone should know already how awesome this anime is!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="85705">Wonderful serie.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="70726">Yet again this super relaxing anime and yet again too short!!
4 seasons and not even one was disappointing, in fact the opposite, they keep getting more and more great!!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.nasinc.co.jp/jp/natsume-anime/</url>
<creators>
<name id="982" type="Animation Work">Brain`s Base</name>
<name id="15726" type="Character Design">Takada Akira</name>
<name id="2315" type="Series Composition">Murai Sadayuki</name>
<name id="783" type="Work">NAS</name>
<name id="3542" type="Original Work">Midorikawa Yuki</name>
<name id="6006" type="Music">Yoshimori Makoto</name>
<name id="15726" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takada Akira</name>
<name id="4359" type="Direction">Oomori Takahiro</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a manga by http://anidb.net/cr3542 [Midorikawa Yuki], serialised in http://anidb.net/cr23820 [LaLa DX] in 2005, before switching to http://anidb.net/cr30454 [LaLa] in 2008.
http://anidb.net/ch1806 [Natsume Takashi] has been able to see yokai since his early days. His grandmother, http://anidb.net/ch1808 [Reiko], possessed the Yujin-chou, a list of names of yokai sworn to fealty. Ever since Takashi inherited the list, he has been constantly attacked by yokai.
Takashi, however, has decided to return to the yokai their names. Together with his self-proclaimed bodyguard http://anidb.net/ch1807 [Nyanko], Takashi has met and come to know many yokai.
~ translated and adapted from official site by Cranston</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2288">8.90</permanent>
<temporary count="2304">8.39</temporary>
<review count="1">7.50</review>
</ratings>
<picture>77535.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13600</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11665</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5007</identifier>
<identifier>fepctl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.nasinc.co.jp/jp/natsume-anime/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/natsume4/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Natsume's_Book_of_Friends</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>夏目友人帳</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2367</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>340882</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14201</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>natsume-yujin-cho-4</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1136" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-18">
<name>transfer student</name>
<description>A transfer student is a student who changes from one institution or course to another at the same level. Their arrival, when not at the beginning of the school year, tends to cause a stir.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1500" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>grimoire</name>
<description>A grimoire is a textbook of magic. Such books typically include instructions on how to create magical objects like talismans and amulets, how to perform magical spells, charms and divination and also how to summon or invoke supernatural entities such as angels, spirits, and demons.</description>
<picurl>229110.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1835" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-17">
<name>animal sidekick</name>
<description>Every mahou shoujo anime needs them, the cute little critters that are supposed to help the protagonists but in reality are nothing but useless bystanders most often abused for gags. Kids love them but they can also often turn into an annoyance.</description>
<picurl>227760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2253" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-24">
<name>kitsune</name>
<description>Kitsune is the Japanese word for http://anidb.net/t191 [fox], which are a common subject of Japanese folklore. This term in English specifically refers to kitsune as demon foxes or fox spirits. Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t1814 [foxpersons], a http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin] with fox characteristics.
Stories depict them as intelligent beings and as possessing magical abilities that increase with their age and wisdom. Foremost among these is the ability to assume human form.</description>
<picurl>226225.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2481" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-08">
<name>teleportation</name>
<description>Teleportation is the transfer of matter from one point to another, possibly a distant one, without application of force, and generally instantly. This contradicts scientific law as we know it, and is therefore nowadays impossible. Sometimes it appears as a paranormal or supernatural ability, and sometimes it is shown in science fiction through technological devices backed up by scientific laws yet to be discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3328" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>melancholic</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3502" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-04-14">
<name>troubled male lead</name>
<description>The male lead character will be in some sort of trouble within himself or only he is able to know of the trouble.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3590" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-03-17">
<name>transforming guardian</name>
<description>Guardian-like characters in this anime, e.g. Guardian Angels, will actually transform into another usually "powered up" version of themselves.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3663" parentid="6347" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-14">
<name>body takeover</name>
<description>A person`s body is taken over by some foreign intelligence. It`s not brainwashing, because they still have control of their own mind — but that`s all they have. Either they`ve been reduced to a spectator in their own body, or their soul has been booted out of their body entirely. Either way, the rest of the cast will soon find he`s not himself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3815" parentid="2851" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>human cannibalism</name>
<description>Cannibalism is the practice of an individual of a species eating parts or the whole of another individual of the same species; as such, human cannibalism is when a human eats the flesh, organs, or other parts of another human being.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3876" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>folklore</name>
<description>Folklore, or simply Lore, are the traditions of a culture, subculture, or group, in the form of legends, music, proverbs, jokes, popular beliefs, fairy tales, stories, tall tales and customs. In usage, there is a continuum between folklore and mythology.
Folklore is generally divided into four areas of study: physical artifacts, transmissible entities and stories, culture and technologies, and behaviors and rituals.
[From Wikipedia]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4148" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-11">
<name>late for school</name>
<description>A common device for a series opening or Establishing Character Moment. Things begin in a frantic rush which usually results in taking short cuts, such as eating breakfast on the run. The classic image is of someone running down the street with a slice of toast hanging out of their mouth, dragging their backpack with one hand while trying to put on their jacket or sweater one-handed with the other, bumping into important people in a manner that gets the plot started.
Basically, they`re never on time for school. While some are Heavy Sleepers, it would appear that they may have simply set their alarm clocks so as to give them insufficient time to get to class. 
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>161002.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4481" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>protection complex</name>
<description>A character has a protection complex if the character is overly protective of other characters, beyond what would be considered a "normal" or "expected" duty of care.
The magnitude of overprotection can vary. It can be as low as constantly nagging someone to "stay safe". It can be as extreme as the protector making it their mission in life to protect the other character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4564" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-06-01">
<name>spirits</name>
<description>Spirits will appear throughout this anime. These will often be depicted as small orbs of glowing light, or transparent images of the deceased.
Not to be mistaken with "I see dead people", these spirits will usually appear at the location of their departure when the characters have gotten close to the truth surrounding their death. Or as plot element, when a spirit will often stay close to a character as a sort of "Guardian Angel". Although they are never actually seen, their presence is sometimes felt.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5781" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-08-01">
<name>exorcism</name>
<description>Eviction of demons or other spiritual entities from a person or place which they are believed to have possessed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5882" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>secret identity</name>
<description>The (usually main) protagonist has a secret identity that he or she desperately tries to keep secret.
This can lead to all sorts of amusing misunderstandings, thus is used as comedy element in some anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6050" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-11">
<name>human - non-human relationship</name>
<description>The relationship between a human and a non-human — be it alien, or artificial — is explored in this anime.
This usually means between a male human and a female (humanoid) alien or AI (avatar).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6347" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>body and host</name>
<description>When a foreign entity like that of a symbiote, body snatcher, puppeteer parasite, or even a hacker (when regarding machines like robots and computers) enters/outright hijacks a body, the possessed subject becomes what is usually called: the host.
The basic purpose of the host varies on what the point was for it to have been hijacked in the first place. Sometimes it`s used as a disguise, other times it`s used as a decoy and destraction, even simply being used as a weapon and piece of armor that the possessor uses to cause sheer chaos and destruction, but sometimes... a host can be used for fetish fuel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1806" type="main character in" update="2016-11-23">
<rating votes="448">7.98</rating>
<name>Natsume Takashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main character of the story. Like his grandmother, http://anidb.net/ch1808 [Natsume Reiko], Takashi has the ability to see spirits. He has inherited the Book of Friends, a book of names that no one but Reiko, Takashi, and other spirits can read. Because of Takashi`s strong resemblance to Reiko, he is often mistaken for her, causing spirits who hate Reiko to chase him constantly. He decided to dissolve the Book by giving all the names back to their owners. He is accompanied by the spirit http://anidb.net/ch10380 [Madara], nicknamed "Cat" because of the spirit`s appearance, and has promised that to pass the book on to Cat when he dies.</description>
<picture>31015.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1807" type="main character in" update="2016-11-23">
<rating votes="640">8.91</rating>
<name>Nyanko-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A mysterious feline spirit. Madara was sealed in to a shrine, before accidentally getting released by Natsume. Because he was trapped for so long, Madara has shaped in to a "fortune cat" or manekineko, leading Natsume to nickname him Cat. In this form, other people could see him, leading for Natsume having to ask his guardians if he could keep him. He is a powerful spirit, who protects Natsume from others, and teaches him spells on occasion. They often fight each other, which leads to Natsume punching Madara on the face and knocking him out. Despite his protests of not being a cat, he likes to play with cat toys. Natsume is more respectful to Madara in the anime, calling him "nyanko-sensei" (master cat). Natsume has promised the Book of Friends to him when he dies.</description>
<picture>16394.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1808" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-13">
<rating votes="112">8.22</rating>
<name>Natsume Reiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Natsume`s grandmother, from whom he inherited the ability to see spirits. When Reiko was young, she was considered a freak by everyone else because of her ability. Since she believed no human could ever understand her, she turned to the spirits for companionship. Reiko`s power was extraordinarily powerful, and so she bullied spirits in to obeying her by playing games with them. If they lost, she would make them give her their names. Reiko gathered the names in to the Book of Friends, and commanded most spirits, except for Madara, who beat her in a game. Reiko died when she was young, so no one remembered her.</description>
<picture>31023.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1809" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-22">
<rating votes="105">7.48</rating>
<name>Tanuma Kaname</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Another student that had recently moved into the area. He is sickly and quite susceptible to illnesses. Like Natsume Takashi, he is able to detect spirits, but to a lesser degree limited to seeing merely shadows and sensing slight presence of spirits.</description>
<picture>31017.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="403" picture="74821.jpg">Horie Kazuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1810" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-13">
<rating votes="139">5.93</rating>
<name>Sasada Jun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The class president of Takashi`s class. Sasada believes that Takashi can see spirits, and constantly asks him questions about it, to which he replies that he doesn`t have such an ability. Much to Takashi`s chagrin, she wants to come along with him when he`s visiting spirits.</description>
<picture>31018.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1811" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-22">
<rating votes="93">5.98</rating>
<name>Natori Shuuichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A man who is also able to see spirits. He is a famous actor and exorcist and has a lizard tattoo that moves around on his body.</description>
<picture>31016.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3700" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-20">
<rating votes="115">7.80</rating>
<name>Taki Tooru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A new girl at school who doesn`t talk much because of a curse a Youkai has placed on her, which Natsume later helps her to break. She`s an omniyojist. She can`t actually see youkai but she is able to once she uses a stick to draw a magic circle. One of Natsume`s friends, Nishimura, has a crush on her, but thinks that she and Natsume are going out.</description>
<picture>68118.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3788" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-23">
<rating votes="42">4.48</rating>
<name>Kitamoto Atsushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kitamoto Atsushi is a classmate of Natsume, and best friend to Nishimura Satoru. He is a sensible and rational person. Although Natsume initially rejects Atsushi`s overtures of friendship because of his fears of his ability being found out, he eventually becomes friends with Atsushi and Satoru, although they still hang around more with each other than Natsume.</description>
<picture>31020.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2226" picture="23215.jpg">Suganuma Hisayoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3789" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-23">
<rating votes="50">4.67</rating>
<name>Nishimura Satoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nishimura Satoru is a classmate of Natsume, and best friend to Kitamoto Atsushi. He is funny and easy-going, with a slightly perverted side. Although Natsume initially rejects Satoru`s overtures of friendship because of his fears of his ability being found out, he eventually becomes friends with Satoru and Atsushi, although they still hang around more with each other than Natsume.</description>
<picture>31019.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2225" picture="192115.jpg">Kimura Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3790" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-24">
<rating votes="126">8.55</rating>
<name>Fujiwara Touko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>19666.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="229" picture="152363.jpg">Itou Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3791" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-24">
<rating votes="79">8.02</rating>
<name>Fujiwara Shigeru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>19667.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2224" picture="21768.jpg">Itou Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10360" type="appears in" update="2009-07-13">
<rating votes="28">5.95</rating>
<name>Chobi-hige</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31009.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="694" picture="52187.jpg">Choo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10365" type="appears in" update="2009-07-13">
<rating votes="20">5.00</rating>
<name>Hitotsume no Chuukyuu Youkai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31001.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="293" picture="185431.jpg">Matsuyama Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10366" type="appears in" update="2009-07-13">
<rating votes="20">5.24</rating>
<name>Ushikao no Chuukyuu Youkai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31002.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4481" picture="26754.jpg">Shimozaki Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10367" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-23">
<rating votes="128">8.44</rating>
<name>Hinoe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hinoe is a powerful youkai whose form is a human woman. She is madly in love with Natsume Reiko. Being knowledgeable, she often acts as Natsume Takashi`s mentor. Hinoe enjoys teasing Natsume and Madara.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>30995.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="319" picture="228606.jpg">Okamura Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10370" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-13">
<rating votes="99">8.04</rating>
<name>Hiiragi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31013.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="271" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10372" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-09-11">
<rating votes="66">8.44</rating>
<name>Kogitsune</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>30993.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="10377" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-05">
<rating votes="41">8.37</rating>
<name>Misuzu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>30986.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="371" picture="166173.jpg">Kuroda Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10380" type="main character in" update="2009-07-13">
<rating votes="198">8.91</rating>
<name>Madara</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31024.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30370" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-22">
<rating votes="42">3.11</rating>
<name>Matoba Seiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Matoba Seiji is the head of one of the major exorcism clans, the Matoba Clan. In order to hunt them, he shows ayakashi, and sometimes even humans, no mercy. He takes great interest in Natsume. Cold hearted and rational. He uses ayakashi as bait to exorcise other ones and wants stronger ones to protect humans (although he doesn`t mind hurting humans too when they`re in his way). Ayakashis are just replaceable tools for him. He mainly uses a bow and arrow against them and if he finds their sealing troublesome, he prefers eliminating them. In the past one of the Matoba clan offered his right eye to an ayakashi for assistance, but in the end he never gave it. Ever since than the heads of the clan has had their right eye targetted by that ayakashi. Matoba Seiji still has his eye, but (according to his words) has a horrible scar.</description>
<picture>6314.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34323" type="appears in" update="2018-08-19">
<rating votes="56">7.91</rating>
<name>Natsume Takashi (Shounen Jidai)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222544.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34334" type="appears in" update="2016-11-25">
<rating votes="21">6.58</rating>
<name>Joshikousei Nyanko-sensei</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195142.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34335" type="appears in" update="2016-11-27">
<rating votes="13">6.14</rating>
<name>Kappa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kappa, whose name remains unknown, is a youkai whom http://anidb.net/a5787 [Natsume] usually helped when he was dehydrated. Because of that, kappa always tried to help Natsume in any way he could.</description>
<picture>79827.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9360" picture="171916.jpg">Chikiri Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34349" type="appears in" update="2018-08-19">
<rating votes="17">7.26</rating>
<name>Sasago</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222560.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1742" picture="20193.jpg">Honda Chieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34350" type="appears in" update="2018-08-19">
<rating votes="17">5.97</rating>
<name>Urihime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222561.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4705" picture="158550.jpg">Higuchi Akari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34509" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-27">
<rating votes="26">3.76</rating>
<name>Nanase</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195208.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="542" picture="60897.jpg">Doi Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40249" type="appears in" update="2016-11-27">
<rating votes="3">3.58</rating>
<name>Agohige no Aru Youkai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195215.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18755" picture="49459.jpg">Akazawa Ryouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40250" type="appears in" update="2016-11-27">
<rating votes="3">3.57</rating>
<name>Matoba no Buka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195220.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="378" picture="46436.jpg">Oota Tetsuharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40368" type="appears in" update="2016-11-27">
<rating votes="3">5.65</rating>
<name>Rokka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195213.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2062" picture="188714.jpg">Ichijou Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40369" type="appears in" update="2016-11-27">
<rating votes="3">4.14</rating>
<name>Tsubo ni Fuujirareta Sarumen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195214.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4726" picture="54694.jpg">Kawamoto Kunihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40883" type="appears in" update="2016-11-27">
<rating votes="4">2.23</rating>
<name>Amana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195217.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="588" picture="41015.jpg">Orikasa Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40884" type="appears in" update="2016-11-27">
<rating votes="4">6.44</rating>
<name>Kemari</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195219.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2980" picture="147242.jpg">Kanada Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40886" type="appears in" update="2016-11-27">
<rating votes="4">5.50</rating>
<name>Yobiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195223.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4270" picture="197671.jpg">Nakagawa Keiichi</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="229" picture="152363.jpg">Itou Miki</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="422" picture="17278.jpg">Nakano Yuuto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40887" type="appears in" update="2016-11-27">
<rating votes="3">3.07</rating>
<name>Takahiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195221.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4270" picture="197671.jpg">Nakagawa Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40888" type="appears in" update="2016-11-27">
<rating votes="4">6.07</rating>
<name>Youko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195222.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1439" picture="223493.jpg">Takahashi Ao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40889" type="appears in" update="2016-11-27">
<rating votes="3">4.99</rating>
<name>Karikami</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195218.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8941" picture="33307.jpg">Sasaki Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40972" type="appears in" update="2016-11-28">
<rating votes="13">8.14</rating>
<name>Ogata Yuriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195243.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41101" type="appears in" update="2016-11-28">
<rating votes="3">1.92</rating>
<name>Ogata Fusae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195242.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19171" picture="50010.jpg">Umeda Kikumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41103" type="appears in" update="2016-11-28">
<rating votes="3">1.60</rating>
<name>Kyoushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195244.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11199" picture="40290.jpg">Okabe Suzune</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41104" type="appears in" update="2016-11-28">
<rating votes="3">2.37</rating>
<name>Kurokama no Youkai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195245.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3157" picture="24155.jpg">Nishimatsu Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41297" type="appears in" update="2016-11-28">
<rating votes="8">8.36</rating>
<name>Natsume-gata Nyanko-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195241.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41298" type="appears in" update="2016-11-28">
<rating votes="3">2.12</rating>
<name>Kemonomen no Youkai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195246.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="272" picture="233512.jpg">Naitou Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42095" type="appears in" update="2016-11-29">
<rating votes="4">5.44</rating>
<name>Houzuki</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195286.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42096" type="appears in" update="2016-11-29">
<rating votes="3">5.44</rating>
<name>Fuzuki-gami</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195285.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="451" picture="17347.jpg">Touchi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42899" type="appears in" update="2016-11-29">
<rating votes="7">3.31</rating>
<name>Aoi Miyoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The daughter of a family http://anidb.net/ch1806 [Natsume] lived with when he was younger.</description>
<picture>195284.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27977" picture="76416.jpg">Han Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42900" type="appears in" update="2016-11-29">
<rating votes="2">4.66</rating>
<name>Miyoko no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch42899 [Aoi Miyoko]`s father. http://anidb.net/ch1806 [Natsume] lived with their family when he was younger.</description>
<picture>195288.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="626" picture="170604.jpg">Muraji Manabu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42901" type="appears in" update="2012-10-11">
<rating votes="2">3.74</rating>
<name>Miyoko no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch42899 [Aoi Miyoko]`s mother. http://anidb.net/ch1806 [Natsume] lived with their family when he was younger.</description>
<picture>126719.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17018" picture="203446.jpg">Sonoda Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42902" type="appears in" update="2012-03-27">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Miyoko no Yuujin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch42899 [Aoi Miyoko]`s friend.</description>
<seiyuu id="27264" picture="74664.jpg">Hayashi Saori</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="31682" picture="85326.jpg">Negoro Shouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49798" type="appears in" update="2016-11-27">
<rating votes="6">3.25</rating>
<name>Nanase (Shoujo Jidai)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195209.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4010" picture="25938.jpg">Nagata Yoriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49799" type="appears in" update="2016-11-27">
<rating votes="2">5.66</rating>
<name>Mikage</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195210.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="280" picture="170840.jpg">Kiuchi Hidenobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49800" type="appears in" update="2016-11-27">
<rating votes="3">4.17</rating>
<name>Kotengu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195212.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="316" picture="25472.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49801" type="appears in" update="2016-11-27">
<rating votes="3">1.93</rating>
<name>Akki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195216.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4425" picture="26689.jpg">Sugino Hiroomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49802" type="appears in" update="2016-11-29">
<rating votes="3">2.25</rating>
<name>Roujin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195291.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3363" picture="24393.jpg">Taniguchi Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49803" type="appears in" update="2012-10-11">
<rating votes="3">3.07</rating>
<name>Shirokasa</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126713.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4481" picture="26754.jpg">Shimozaki Hiroshi</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="378" picture="46436.jpg">Oota Tetsuharu</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="9360" picture="171916.jpg">Chikiri Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49804" type="appears in" update="2016-11-29">
<rating votes="3">1.84</rating>
<name>Kokui</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195287.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18755" picture="49459.jpg">Akazawa Ryouta</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="4726" picture="54694.jpg">Kawamoto Kunihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49805" type="appears in" update="2016-11-29">
<rating votes="3">3.57</rating>
<name>Shinpan no Youkai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195292.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="293" picture="185431.jpg">Matsuyama Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49806" type="appears in" update="2016-11-29">
<rating votes="2">5.08</rating>
<name>Natsume no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195290.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49807" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-10-11">
<rating votes="2">4.89</rating>
<name>Natsume no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126722.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49808" type="appears in" update="2016-11-29">
<rating votes="4">2.23</rating>
<name>Mushikui</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195289.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2230" picture="21782.jpg">Iwasaki Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="135228" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-01-03</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">とらわれた夏目</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Natsume Captured</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Torawareta Natsume</title>
<summary>Natsume is jumped by a group of Youkai trying to steal the Book of Friends for their master. Once captured, Natsume discovers that an old problem is back in a big way.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>588978</identifier>
<identifier>natsume-yujin-cho-4</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="135729" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">東方の森</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Eastern Forest</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Touhou no Mori</title>
<summary>Natsume, now trapped in the mansion, is trying to keep the Monkey Mask youkai from revealing the Book of Friends to Matoba. While Hinoe and Misuzu attempt to find the strange youkai’s master.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>588980</identifier>
<identifier>natsume-yujin-cho-4</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="135730" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-01-17</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">小さきもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Little Ones</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chiisaki Mono</title>
<summary>After Natsume returned Amana’s name, she accused him of stealing her ring.  He has three days to find and return it before she burns down his house.  To make matters worse, the ring is trapped in the hair of a migratory youkai, and Nyanko-sensei is unable to use his powers.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>589470</identifier>
<identifier>natsume-yujin-cho-4</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="135731" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-01-24</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">代答</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stand-In</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai Kotae</title>
<summary>Natsume is at home early one evening when he hears a knock on the door.  He sees Tohko outside, asking to be let in.  But when he opens the door, there`s nobody there, and a gust of wind rushes past.  Another Youkai is after the book of friends!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>589472</identifier>
<identifier>natsume-yujin-cho-4</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="135732" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-01-31</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">過ぎし日の君に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To You, From Bygone Days</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sugishihi no Kimi ni</title>
<summary>An old classmate Yuriko, remembers her time watching Natsume and how he was a little weird.  A clingbug from Natsume’s past reminds him of the time he spent running from a youkai with a grudge.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>589474</identifier>
<identifier>natsume-yujin-cho-4</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="136024" update="2012-06-29">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-01-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136025" update="2012-06-29">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-01-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136713" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-02-07</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">硝子のむこう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Other Side Of The Glass</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Garasu no Mukou</title>
<summary>Natsume overhears whispers that a powerful youkai is reviving, later that evening he is trapped in a bottle as an offering.  Humans can’t see or hear him, so Nyanko-sensei decides to help the “best” way he can…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>589476</identifier>
<identifier>natsume-yujin-cho-4</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="136981" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-02-14</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人と妖の間[はざま]で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Gap Between Humans and Youkai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hito to Ayakashi no Hazama de</title>
<summary>Natsume’s greatest fear has come true.  Someone not involved in the world of youkai is hurt because of him. Natori needs Natsume to regain his composure or they will be eaten by Omibashira!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>589478</identifier>
<identifier>natsume-yujin-cho-4</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="137160" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-02-28</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">月分祭</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Moon-Splitting Festival</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsukiwakesai</title>
<summary>Every 10 years the followers of Houdzuigami and Fudzukigami have a battle to determine the fate of the land.   Natsume is approached by the followers of Houdzukigami to act as their missing god.  Natori has been given the job of finding the missing god or seal Fuduzkigami before he wins.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>589482</identifier>
<identifier>natsume-yujin-cho-4</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="137161" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-02-21</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">惑いし頃に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">When I Was Deceived</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Madoishi Koro ni</title>
<summary>Natsume is walking home one day when he`s accosted by a flying Tengu, who lifts him up into the sky!  Meanwhile, Nyanko-sensei is stuck in a well, where Nanase tells him a story about how she learned to never get close to a youkai.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>589480</identifier>
<identifier>natsume-yujin-cho-4</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="137394" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-03-20</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">記憶の扉</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Door of Memories</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kioku no Tobira</title>
<summary>Natsume is going home for the last time, but first he must stop by his relative’s house to get the key.  But he is cautious, as inside is a youkai that tormented Natsume, and a girl that has always resented him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>589488</identifier>
<identifier>natsume-yujin-cho-4</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="137395" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-03-13</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一枚の写真</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Single Photo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ichimai no Shashin</title>
<summary>Natsume gets a call from a relative: his parents home is being sold.  He tells himself that it doesn`t matter, and that he`s forgotten his past.  But he`s not nearly as over it as he thinks...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>589486</identifier>
<identifier>natsume-yujin-cho-4</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="137396" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-03-06</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">祀られた神様</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The God, Enshrined</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Matsurareta Kamisama</title>
<summary>While being swept down the river, Natsume managed to feel the presences of Hudzuki-gami.  Natori must make the choice to follow Natsume instincts or seal Fudzuki-gami.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>589484</identifier>
<identifier>natsume-yujin-cho-4</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138049" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-03-27</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">遠き家路</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Long Way Home</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tooki Ieji</title>
<summary>Natsume is possessed by a spirit.  Obsessed with returning home, he remembers the events that occured just after his father`s death.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>589490</identifier>
<identifier>natsume-yujin-cho-4</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148678" update="2014-09-02">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>70</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Live Special 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148679" update="2014-09-02">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>85</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Live Special 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="182456" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>589662</identifier>
<identifier>natsume-yujin-cho-4</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
