<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8689" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2012-12-28</startdate>
<enddate>2012-12-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ao no Exorcist Gekijouban</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">青の祓魔師[エクソシスト] -劇場版-</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Blue Exorcist: The Movie</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8148" type="Parent Story">Ao no Exorcist</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="5">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="457755">Just like the series, loved it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="309568">\(*-.-*)/
So cute but why does it always end with a tear drop?!
OOOO I would be friends with it too!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="102269">Cute, heartwarming, visually beautiful and sad.
It will move you if you are a human being in heart and open to reminding of life`s lessons. 
And one that can get past its biggest letdown- very, very easily  predictive. Right from the first minutes, and to the very end - given all the set pieces - nothing one couldn`t anticipate. 

But nevertheless - recommended to fans for sure, but not sure if others who haven`t seen the series will jump into it right from the start.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="242877">Not a bad movie, but it brings nothing new to the story. Still, fans of Blue exorcist [such as myself] will enjoy it. I still love Rin so much!!! Best fictional boyfriend =)))</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="106569">Ao Exo gekijouban is very well made on every front: art design, BG paintings, narrative flow, cuteness, sexiness, comedy, CGI compositing, and blood-boiling shounen manga action.

If A-1 Pictures` next titles are as good as this,
there`s a real possibility that A-1 Pictures will outdo even the venerable Ghibli.

Ao Exo gekijouban feels almost as well made as a Ghibli title but at the same time feels more contemporary and "relevant", if you are going to watch only one anime movie this year, watch this.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.ao-ex.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="10834" type="Character Design">Sasaki Keigo</name>
<name id="4549" type="Direction">Takahashi Atsushi</name>
<name id="1303" type="Work">A-1 Pictures</name>
<name id="23050" type="Original Work">Katou Kazue</name>
<name id="10834" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sasaki Keigo</name>
<name id="6722" type="Music">Sawano Hiroyuki</name>
</creators>
<description>The atmosphere in True Cross Academy is lively and boisterous in the days leading up to the grand festival held once every 11 years. During this time, http://anidb.net/ch25808 [Okumura Rin] is entrusted with the responsibility of suppressing the berserk Phantom Train. In the midst of his mission, he meets a devil whose appearance is that of a young boy.
~ translated and adapted from official site by Cranston</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1398">5.94</permanent>
<temporary count="1407">7.12</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>93872.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13631</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11737</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>13677</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5170</identifier>
<identifier>lvnruk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.ao-ex.com/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.ao-ex.com/trailer/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>青の祓魔師_(アニメ)#.E5.8A.87.E5.A0.B4.E7.89.88</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4450</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>343319</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15188</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4481" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>protection complex</name>
<description>A character has a protection complex if the character is overly protective of other characters, beyond what would be considered a "normal" or "expected" duty of care.
The magnitude of overprotection can vary. It can be as low as constantly nagging someone to "stay safe". It can be as extreme as the protector making it their mission in life to protect the other character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5543" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-05-13">
<name>magic school</name>
<description>A school where magic is taught.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5781" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-08-01">
<name>exorcism</name>
<description>Eviction of demons or other spiritual entities from a person or place which they are believed to have possessed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5843" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>sibling yin yang</name>
<description>In real life, siblings hardly ever act the same. Fiction sometimes takes this to an extreme.
Enter Sibling Yin Yang, the occurrence of siblings that are nearly polar opposites. If he`s cool and reckless, she`s responsible and thoughtful. If she`s a spiky-haired hooligan, he`s the nerdy wimpy one. If he`s an immature brat, she`s... well, you get the picture.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="25808" type="main character in" update="2019-11-09">
<rating votes="107">6.84</rating>
<name>Okumura Rin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The fifteen year-old protagonist of the story, Rin is the son of Satan born from a human woman and is the inheritor of Satan`s powers. His powers were sealed at birth into the demon-slaying blade Kurikara, or Koumaken, by Mephisto Pheles, allowing him to live a normal human life for about 15 years. Rin became aware of his true identity after Kurikara could no longer seal the blue flames he inherited from Satan, setting a chain of events that led to the death of his guardian, Father and Exorcist Fujimoto Shiro, at the hands of Satan who attempted to drag Rin back to the demon realm. Exorcist Mephisto Pheles confronted Rin after Shiro`s funeral with several exorcists, giving Rin the option to kill them all or die. Rin instead demanded to become an exorcist, an idea that amused Mephisto. Rin was then enrolled personally by Mephisto into the True Cross Academy Exorcist School, and since been pursuing his goal to become a Paladin and to defeat Satan. He is currently an Exwire and attempting to gain the title of Meister as a "Knight" (an exorcist who fights with a sword).
Rin can tap into the power he has inherited from Satan through the use of a demon-slaying katana, called Kurikara or Koumaken. The sheath acts as a portal to Gehenna (the demon world) which when drawn returns Rin to his demon form. While in his human form, Rin exhibits a number of physical traits that are signs of his demonic nature, such as sharper-looking teeth, slightly pointed ears, and a black, fur tufted tail (which he keeps hidden in his shirt). As a demon, Rin gains two blue flames that float above his head, long, elf-like ears, and his eyes turn bright blue. In both forms Rin can control incredibly destructive bright blue flames, the trademark sign of anything related to Satan. However, when he draws Kurikara, the magnitude of the flames dramatically increases and often leads to Rin being "consumed" by his own flames and losing his mind. Rin also has a demon Familiar Cat Sith, Kuro, who was initially Father Fujimoto`s.</description>
<picture>91393.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25809" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-09">
<rating votes="70">5.03</rating>
<name>Okumura Yukio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rin`s younger twin brother. Though Satan`s powers were expected to be split between them, due to the weakness of Yukio`s body at birth, Yukio did not inherit any of Satan`s powers. Yukio received a Mashou at birth from his brother, allowing him to become aware of demons since he can remember. Yukio secretly trained to become an Exorcist since age seven in order to protect Rin (through the help of Fujimoto). While both Yukio and Rin are in their first year at True Cross Academy, Yukio is already an instructor at the Exorcist cram school who teaches Anti-Demon Pharmacology to Rin`s class. It is often stated that Yukio is a genius, having already acquired the title "Meister" in both the Dragoon and Doctor class, while ordinarily most people would aim for Meister in one class (both are still fully qualified exorcists). He is currently ranked a Middle First class exorcist.</description>
<picture>91394.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25813" type="appears in" update="2011-05-15">
<rating votes="22">4.94</rating>
<name>Amaimon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71599.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="174" picture="41158.jpg">Kakihara Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25815" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-23">
<rating votes="55">7.38</rating>
<name>Mephisto Pheles</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91397.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25816" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-23">
<rating votes="38">2.58</rating>
<name>Miwa Konekomaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91399.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25817" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-23">
<rating votes="47">4.68</rating>
<name>Suguro Ryuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Suguro Ryuji (nicknamed "Bon") is Rin`s rival and the prodigy in the class. He was the child of the Cursed Temple which was destroyed by Satan 16 years ago. Bon takes everything seriously and is trying his hardest in order to become an Exorcist powerful enough so he could one day defeat Satan ( a goal he claims Rin stole from him) and rebuild his Temple. Currently Bon is trying to acquire the title of Meister in both Aria (a person who recites holy texts to kill certain demons) and Dragoon (a person who fights with guns and other heavy artillery).</description>
<picture>91402.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="259" picture="17082.jpg">Nakai Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25818" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-23">
<rating votes="40">2.39</rating>
<name>Shima Renzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91401.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25819" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-23">
<rating votes="75">4.49</rating>
<name>Moriyama Shiemi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shiemi is Rin`s class mate and friend. Before she met Rin, Shiemi tended her grandmother`s garden while her mother ran an Exorcist only shop inside True Cross Academy. During her encounter with Rin and Yukio, they were able to discover that Shiemi was having her life force leached out by a Demon. After Yukio exorcised the demon, Shiemi finally decided to become an Exorcist and started to attend class. It was later revealed that Shiemi had talent in becoming a Tamer, as she was able to summon a Greenman Spirit during class. It is apparently a rare talent to possess amongst the Exorcists, where there are only a few who can control demons and fight.</description>
<picture>91400.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25820" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-23">
<rating votes="63">5.61</rating>
<name>Kamiki Izumo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91396.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25821" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-23">
<rating votes="52">7.98</rating>
<name>Fujimoto Shirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Father Fujimoto was Rin and Yukio`s guardian and was also considered to be one of the most powerful Exorcists in the world. He was thought to be the only man in the world that was able to sustain possession by Satan himself and thus Satan was constantly after his body. Fujimoto was able to fight off Satan`s attempts at possessing his body through sheer willpower. However after receiving a mental shock from what Rin had said, Satan was finally able to take over his body and later killed him.</description>
<picture>91395.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25822" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-10">
<rating votes="71">7.27</rating>
<name>Kirigakure Shura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kirigakure Shura is an Upper First Class Exorcist and Rin`s mentor. She trained under the guidance of Fujimoto Shiro to obtain the title "Meister" in Knight and can draw a demon sword from a symbol above her chest when she states "Devour the Seven Princesses, slay the Serpent". Frequently chipper and obnoxious, Shura is carefree about her job, known for drinking and oversleeping. She appears to harbor a dark past, as she claimed Shiro "came and rescued" her.</description>
<picture>93868.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33128" type="appears in" update="2011-07-14">
<rating votes="14">4.88</rating>
<name>Okumura Rin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72944.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33129" type="appears in" update="2011-07-14">
<rating votes="13">4.37</rating>
<name>Okumura Yukio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72945.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33131" type="appears in" update="2011-06-06">
<rating votes="13">6.76</rating>
<name>Ni-chan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72947.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33750" type="appears in" update="2012-09-10">
<rating votes="39">6.43</rating>
<name>Kuro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93867.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="411" picture="17475.jpg">Takagaki Ayahi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33751" type="appears in" update="2011-06-22">
<rating votes="14">5.63</rating>
<name>Cait Sith</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74025.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="411" picture="17475.jpg">Takagaki Ayahi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34012" type="appears in" update="2011-06-27">
<rating votes="7">5.54</rating>
<name>Tsubaki Kaori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74402.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6848" picture="86100.jpg">Ooguro Kazuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35118" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-01">
<rating votes="23">3.24</rating>
<name>Arthur Auguste Angel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Arthur Auguste Angel is the newly appointed Paladin. He was ordered by the Grigori to to interrogate Mephisto and captured Rin as evidence. According to Shura he`s a saint on the outside and a devil inside. Uses the demon sword Caliburn.
Angel has long blonde hair in a pony tail, with a communicator in his ear, though it is unclear whether or not he wears it all the time. He wears a fancy white suit that is custom made. Rin makes fun of it.
Not much is known about Arthur so far, except that he is extremely loyal to the True Cross Order. He follows the orders of his superiors without questioning them at all, even attempting to kill people when they interfere with his work. He believes that anything related to Satan must be destroyed, as it could only cause harm to let them live. Arthur also seems to be slightly sadistic, as he stabbed Rin completely through the leg to immobilize him during Rin`s trial, while remarking that the wound would heal soon enough. According to Shura, he is a saint on the outside and a devil on the inside, hinting that he may have a malicious personality.
Despite not being seen in combat, it can be assumed that Arthur is extremely powerful, as he was given the rank of Paladin, which only the strongest exorcist in the world can hold. He wields a demon sword, called Caliburn, indicating that he obtained a Meister as a Knight.
His power is hinted at when he was quickly able to overcome Kirigakure Shura, one of the most powerful exorcists seen in the series.
Caliburn his demon blade, seems to be able to talk, and has the personality of a little girl who adores Arthur.
Source: Ao no Exorcist Wikia</description>
<picture>93869.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35169" type="appears in" update="2011-08-08">
<rating votes="6">2.66</rating>
<name>Shiratori Reiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76464.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="493" picture="65381.jpg">Itou Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36381" type="appears in" update="2011-10-24">
<rating votes="13">3.66</rating>
<name>Takara</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takara is a quiet and mysterious exwire. He doesn`t talk much, but when he does, it`s usually through rude ventriloquism.</description>
<picture>73179.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="37593" type="appears in" update="2011-10-08">
<rating votes="7">6.60</rating>
<name>Ukobaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66978.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="38068" type="appears in" update="2011-10-24">
<rating votes="5">2.95</rating>
<name>Onna Kyoushi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A teacher who teaches Fatal Verse, which are words or phrases that can kill demon after they are spoken.</description>
<picture>73094.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="38098" type="appears in" update="2011-10-25">
<rating votes="8">3.50</rating>
<name>Caliburn</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Arthur Auguste Angel`s speaking sword.</description>
<picture>73450.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="38099" type="appears in" update="2011-10-25">
<rating votes="6">3.15</rating>
<name>Yunokawa-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73454.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="38248" type="appears in" update="2011-10-31">
<rating votes="8">3.68</rating>
<name>Hamster</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75700.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="38529" type="appears in" update="2011-11-10">
<rating votes="6">4.03</rating>
<name>Inari Kami Uke</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2286.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="38530" type="appears in" update="2011-11-10">
<rating votes="6">4.03</rating>
<name>Inari Kami Mike</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2291.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="48691" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-01">
<rating votes="5">5.70</rating>
<name>Cheng-Long Liu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Upper First Class exorcist from Taiwan branch. Comes to Japan to help True Cross Academy change a new barrier. From an elite family and has high exorcism skills.</description>
<picture>93870.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="280" picture="170840.jpg">Kiuchi Hidenobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48692" type="main character in" update="2014-06-25">
<rating votes="9">5.87</rating>
<name>Usamaro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93871.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68236" type="appears in" update="2017-04-23">
<rating votes="8">7.43</rating>
<name>Shima Juuzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shima Juuzou is the second son of the Shima family. As the second son, he has more responsibilities than his younger brothers. He is also an Upper Second Class Exorcist.
Juuzou is first introduced while fighting http://anidb.net/ch85283 [Houjou Mamushi] over their families, and although at first he is advising his younger brother http://anidb.net/ch68237 [Kinzou] not to get into a fight with her, he subsequently gets quite worked up about it, resulting in a physical confrontation. However, he seems to be more level headed and responsible than Kinzou, and less laid back than http://anidb.net/ch25818 [Renzou].
He is serious when it comes to his duties, and has showed concern about his childhood friend Mamushi, as well as taking care of his father. He has a lighthearted side and gets on well with his two youngest brothers.
Source: Ao no Exorcist Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>201478.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68237" type="appears in" update="2017-04-05">
<rating votes="5">3.82</rating>
<name>Shima Kinzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198916.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68238" type="appears in" update="2014-06-25">
<rating votes="3">3.12</rating>
<name>Usamaro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>157258.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="142331" update="2013-07-04">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>90</length>
<airdate>2012-12-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145602" update="2012-11-22">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">30s Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147446" update="2013-02-13">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">予告編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV2 (1m40s)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yokokuhen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147447" update="2013-02-13">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">公開直前PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV1 (1m)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koukai Chokuzen PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147448" update="2013-02-13">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">特報</title>
<title xml:lang="en">30s Trailer 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokuhou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170166" update="2015-07-21">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2012-04-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">特別映像</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Movie Special</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokubetsu Eizou</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
