<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8728" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2012-04-03</startdate>
<enddate>2012-06-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Zetman</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ZETMAN</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Zetman</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">ZETMAN</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="7902" approval="4" total="10">Deadman Wonderland</anime>
<anime id="44" approval="3" total="5">Amon Devilman Mokushiroku</anime>
<anime id="3185" approval="2" total="2">Kyoushoku Soukou Guyver (2005)</anime>
<anime id="8184" approval="1" total="2">Towa no Quon</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="5">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="538802">this series has an interesting concept but fails miserably in deliviering the plot to the audience. storytelling is at times very confusing and makes it hard to get emotionally connected to the characters. only for fans!

[edit: typo]</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="97419">Honestly there is nothing more to say other than it is based on the Manga from Masakazu Katsura. the sad part is that it differs from it after the 1st episode. hence, you`re better off reading the full manga. 

still worth the watch i would say since its just 13 eps.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="541020">very hard to tell this one but i give it a try.  interesting plot though it is very hard to follow through the first 3-4 episodes. after that the series really takes up steam and is imho pretty enjoyable with nice action scenes and strong characters, just give it a try</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="178698">High Quality anime with very catching story. It doesn`t drags out, goes straight to the point. Very emotional.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="309568">Liked the small details of the hidden connections. I think it could have been better if it was longer and more history.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://zetman.jp/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="917" type="Animation Work">TMS Entertainment</name>
<name id="5852" type="Character Design">Takaya Hirotoshi</name>
<name id="3688" type="Series Composition">Tomioka Atsuhiro</name>
<name id="866" type="Original Work">Katsura Masakazu</name>
<name id="1966" type="Direction">Nabeshima Osamu</name>
<name id="30388" type="Music">Sasano Megumi</name>
<name id="29146" type="Music">Gabriele Roberto</name>
<name id="30387" type="Music">Yanaura Yuu</name>
<name id="13715" type="Music">Sasamoto Yasushi</name>
<name id="30386" type="Music">Suble</name>
<name id="5852" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takaya Hirotoshi</name>
<name id="6572" type="Chief Animation Direction">Suzuki Tsutomu</name>
<name id="3520" type="Chief Animation Direction">Iwasa Yuuko</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a manga by http://anidb.net/cr866 [Katsura Masakazu], serialised in http://anidb.net/cr32180 [Weekly Young Jump].
http://anidb.net/ch37863 [Jin] is a strange kid with an angel mark on his hand. He lives a poor but peaceful life with his grandfather, along with the other destitute and abandoned vagabonds near the river. One day, his peaceful life changes when a strange monster, a so-called Player appears, chopping off heads and killing everyone in sight.
Note: The first two episodes received an early screening on Friday, March 30, 2012 at Toho Cinemas Roppongi Hills in Tokyo. Regular television broadcast started on April 3, 2012.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1526">4.04</permanent>
<temporary count="1537">6.28</temporary>
<review count="3">4.77</review>
</ratings>
<picture>79729.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13736</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11837</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://zetman.jp/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.vizanime.com/zetman</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Zetman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ZETMAN</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2484</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>341111</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14424</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2830" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>furo scene</name>
<description>Furo (polite: Ofuro) is Japanese for bath, specifically a type of bath which originated as a short, steep-sided wooden bathtub. Baths of this type are found all over Japan in houses, apartments and traditional Japanese inns (Ryokans).
Furo are part of the Japanese ritual of bathing, not used for washing but for relaxing and warming oneself. Washing is carried out separately outside the furo, and only when completely clean does the bather enter the water. Generally Japanese bathrooms are small, so the bathroom is set up much like a walk-in shower area but containing the ofuro.
The cheapest and shortest way to show naked skin on TV, at least as much as allowed. It usually only takes up few minutes at most and as such it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales while still maintaining a "non-filler" episode.
Compare to the big brothers http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode] and http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160785.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3135" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-16">
<name>hero complex</name>
<description>A hero complex is a state of mind in which an individual believes they need to save or assist others, uphold morals, serve justice, or perform other such supposedly hero-like acts, often at any cost. That is a common trait among vigilantes. Those with a hero complex may feel personally accountable for any failure at those self-assigned duties. Their main concern is performing their supposedly heroic deeds; any questions others might raise about such actions are all secondary concerns at best. Such questions can include, but are not limited to: who is to be saved; what are they to be saved from; why are they being saved; whether or not the other person needs or wants to be saved at all; whether or not others share in the sense of morals and justice being upheld; how people feel about the so-called heroic actions; whether people feel like those actions are being forced down their throats; what negative effects can arise from such actions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3315" parentid="2623" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-28">
<name>superhero</name>
<description>In modern popular fiction, a superhero is a type of costumed heroic character who possesses supernatural or superhuman powers and who is dedicated to fighting crime, protecting the public, and usually battling supervillains. A female superhero is sometimes called a superheroine. Fiction centered on such characters, especially in American comic books since the 1930s, is known as superhero fiction.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3932" parentid="6073" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-05-11">
<name>older female younger male</name>
<description>This tag indicates that this anime has a male and female lead, and the female is older. If the main cast is greater than two people, then the use of this tag would indicate a romantic relationship between those two.
In case of harems it translates to:
a) majority of the girls are older than the guy
b) the lead girl (or her main rival) is older than the guy</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4537" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-15">
<name>time skip</name>
<description>The plot features at least one skip or jump in time.
Example: A skip from the present into the past, or time skips in increments, e.g. every hour there is a time skip by a day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4588" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-20">
<name>fast-paced</name>
<description>Hold onto your hats, this anime`s storyline is relentless.
The characters don`t get time to take a breath as events keep both them and the viewer on a roller coaster ride of revelation and excitement!
Hopefully it all makes sense...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4812" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-07-04">
<name>dark past</name>
<description>Way back when, something horrible happened - like murder, betrayal, rape or cataclysm. It may have happened to a character, or been caused by a character. It may be some powerful evil that was vanquished long ago.
Whatever it was, that past event will echo in the plotline of this story, providing motivation or peril for the protagonists.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5762" parentid="3842" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>violence censoring</name>
<description>Describes TV shows, where parts of the scenes considered as too violent are blackened, blurred, changed to other static screen, or cut out completely.
While TV censoring is normally used to boost the BD/DVD sales, this is done under the mantle of being "for the healthy development of youth" or similar excuses. In the long run, it`s just the same.
Examples: Deadman Wonderland, Fate/Zero, and Mirai Nikki.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5838" parentid="2874" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-26">
<name>fire</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5862" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-08">
<name>melodrama</name>
<description>A melodrama is a dramatic work that exaggerates plot and characters in order to appeal to the emotions, often with strongly stereotyped characters. Language, behaviour, or events which resemble melodramas are also called melodramatic. In scholarly and historical musical contexts melodramas are dramas of the 18th and 19th centuries in which orchestral music or song was used to accompany the action.
Melodrama is a style of drama that has been applied on the stage, in movies and television, and radio formats, from the 18th century to the present. Because of the long timeframe in which the style has existed, it is difficult to derive a precise definition. The term melodrama is most often used pejoratively, to suggest that the work to which the term is applied lacks sophistication or subtlety.
The term originated from the early 19th-century French word mélodrame, which is derived from Greek melos, music, and French drame, drama (from Late Latin drāma, which in turn derives from Greek drān, to do, perform).
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5865" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>manly tears</name>
<description>Somewhere down the line, it became the "norm" that boys don`t cry. The scenario does not matter; shedding tears is the ultimate no-no in terms of what you can and cannot do as a man (at least in the West, anyway). But there comes a time when a man`s emotions do get the better of him, and they pour forth - as prerequisite an impassioned speech may or may not be present - by cascading down his cheeks. These are what we like to call "manly tears". Extremely powerful. Not limited but often used in hot-blooded / super robot shows. Examples include Yuusha Ou GaoGaiGar, Getter Robo and Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann.
The opposite of manly tears are "girly tears".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5882" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>secret identity</name>
<description>The (usually main) protagonist has a secret identity that he or she desperately tries to keep secret.
This can lead to all sorts of amusing misunderstandings, thus is used as comedy element in some anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6073" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-11-23">
<name>age difference romance</name>
<description>A romance between individuals of significantly different ages is featured. Depending on how big the age gap is and on the society featured, that may be considered taboo.
While the terms "lolicon" and "shotacon", often used in relation to anime and its fandom, are limited to a physical or erotic attraction to sexually precocious girls or boys respectively, this tag expands into platonic romances and other age ranges.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="37863" type="main character in" update="2011-12-16">
<rating votes="14">7.69</rating>
<name>Kanzaki Jin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A mysterious young man bearing a circular lump on the back of his left hand, Jin was a result of the Z.E.T. Project by the Amagi Corporation to create the perfect being to fight and destroy the escaped Players. He was however released by Gorou Kanzaki, who wanted nothing more for Jin than to grow up as a normal human. Jin is able to transform a creature known as "ZET", a mutant possessing superhuman abilities, but often mistaken for another Player. The transformation is slow, though it may be accelerated due to extreme rage and conditions.</description>
<picture>78577.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37864" type="main character in" update="2012-01-10">
<rating votes="5">5.42</rating>
<name>ZET</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79735.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="37865" type="main character in" update="2011-12-16">
<rating votes="13">1.52</rating>
<name>Amagi Kouga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Konoha`s elder brother, and grandson of Mitsugai Amagi. Both academically and sports-inclined, especially soccer. Due to his attraction to an anime `Ginga Choujin Alphasz`, Kouga has developed a strong sense of justice since young. Urged by his encounter with Jin during a fire accident (caused by a Player) to become a hero of justice. He had been depending on a trio of researchers since middle school for gadgets which could assist him in his escapades. He initiates the Alphasz Project with the Trio, who created a high-performance combat body suit resembling Kouga`s childhood hero, complete with high-tech weaponry and gadgets, to combat his grandfather`s creations. Very protective of his family, especially his sister, Konoha.</description>
<picture>78576.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="255" picture="40713.jpg">Miyano Mamoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39551" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-10">
<rating votes="11">5.08</rating>
<name>Amagi Konoha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl who has known Jin since they were children and harbors feelings for him. As daughter to Amagi Corp`s president (Kouga`s sister), she is unaware of the fact that Jin is Zet. They originally met when she and her mother were secretly giving out food to the homeless. Since then, due to many complicated events, they are now relatively close friends.</description>
<picture>79741.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40244" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-10">
<rating votes="8">7.03</rating>
<name>Kawakami Akemi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79733.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42" picture="155105.jpg">Hayamizu Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40245" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-10">
<rating votes="2">1.08</rating>
<name>Hayami</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79730.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="191" picture="17006.jpg">Suzumura Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40246" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-10">
<rating votes="3">5.19</rating>
<name>Hashimoto Mayu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79731.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40247" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-10">
<rating votes="3">1.12</rating>
<name>Haitani Seiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79732.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40248" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-10">
<rating votes="10">6.82</rating>
<name>Tanaka Hanako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79734.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="101" picture="16709.jpg">Ise Mariya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40326" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-10">
<rating votes="1">6.95</rating>
<name>Kanzaki Gorou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79736.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3125" picture="24097.jpg">Mitsuo Senda</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40327" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-10">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Amagi Mitsugai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79737.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1986" picture="1919.gif">Iizuka Shouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40328" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-10">
<rating votes="2">1.33</rating>
<name>Amagi Seizou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79738.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="418" picture="17270.jpg">Hirose Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40329" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-10">
<name>Soujinin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79739.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40330" type="main character in" update="2012-01-10">
<rating votes="2">1.90</rating>
<name>Alphas</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79740.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="255" picture="40713.jpg">Miyano Mamoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40332" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-03">
<rating votes="1">8.21</rating>
<name>Sayama-keibu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85127.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="464" picture="24725.jpg">Sugou Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40333" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-25">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Kabe Mamoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2361" picture="228618.jpg">Kusumi Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40334" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-10">
<name>Sugita-hakase</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2224" picture="21768.jpg">Itou Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40335" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-10">
<rating votes="2">4.79</rating>
<name>Amagi Youko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43183" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-04">
<rating votes="2">4.15</rating>
<name>Kanzaki Jin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85163.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43184" type="appears in" update="2012-04-04">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Amagi Kouga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85164.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1442" picture="18829.jpg">Kaida Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43185" type="appears in" update="2012-04-03">
<name>Kurofuku A</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85131.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2258" picture="21881.jpg">Uchida Yuuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43186" type="appears in" update="2012-04-03">
<name>Kurofuku B</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85132.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2231" picture="235895.jpg">Kusunoki Taiten</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43187" type="appears in" update="2012-04-03">
<name>Chameleon Evol</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85133.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="195" picture="17009.jpg">Sakamaki Mitsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43188" type="appears in" update="2012-04-03">
<name>Otoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85134.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2501" picture="191381.jpg">Yoshikai Kiyohito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43189" type="appears in" update="2012-04-03">
<name>Onna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85135.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20569" picture="186287.jpg">Takahashi Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43431" type="appears in" update="2012-04-10">
<name>Fire Evol</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85721.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3155" picture="24137.jpg">Ono Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="136843" update="2012-02-04">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode T1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137457" update="2012-04-05">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-03-30</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">未熟な感情</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Untaught Emotions</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mijuku na Kanjou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138432" update="2012-04-05">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-03-30</airdate>
<rating votes="9">3.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">紅蓮の中で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In the Fire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Guren no Naka de</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138433" update="2012-04-12">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">2.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138434" update="2012-04-03">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-04-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138483" update="2012-04-05">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-05-08</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人質</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hostage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitojichi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138484" update="2012-04-05">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-05-01</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アルファス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Alphas</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Alphas</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138485" update="2012-04-05">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">疫病神</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ill Fortune</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yakubyougami</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138486" update="2012-04-05">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">涙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tears</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Namida</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139568" update="2012-05-11">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">赤い杭</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Red Stake</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akai Kui</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139569" update="2012-05-11">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-06-12</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">操り人形</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Puppet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ayatsuri Ningyou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139570" update="2012-05-11">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-06-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">パーティー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Party</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Party</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139571" update="2012-05-11">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-05-29</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">形見の行方</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Whereabouts of the Pendant</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Katami no Yukue</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139572" update="2012-05-11">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-05-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">普通の家族</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Normal Family</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futsuu no Kazoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139573" update="2012-05-11">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-05-15</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暴きの輪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ring of Exposure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Abaki no Wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="140271" update="2012-06-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-06-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">葬列</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Funeral Procession</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Souretsu</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
