<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8733" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>1996-07-01</startdate>
<enddate>1996-08-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Musekinin Kanchou Tylor: Chijou yori Eien ni</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">無責任艦長タイラー 地上より永遠に</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The Irresponsible Captain Tylor: From Here to Eternity</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">무책임함장 테일러 OVA: 지상에서 영원으로</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="13224" type="Sequel">Musekinin Galaxy Tylor</anime>
<anime id="8732" type="Prequel">Musekinin Kanchou Tylor (1995)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.vap.co.jp/tylor/</url>
<creators>
<name id="730" type="Animation Work">Studio Deen</name>
<name id="5503" type="Character Design">Kawanami Masaaki</name>
<name id="1015" type="Original Work">Yoshioka Hitoshi</name>
<name id="1646" type="Direction">Yoshinaga Naoyuki</name>
<name id="5503" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kawanami Masaaki</name>
</creators>
<description>Some time has elapsed since http://anidb.net/ch7034 [Tylor] and the http://anidb.net/ch7063 [Soyokaze] lead the UPSF forces to victory. The Raalgon war has cooled to a point where it can probably no longer considered to be one: in fact, many of the Soyokaze crew had been temporarily reassigned. http://anidb.net/ch7032 [Azalyn] had taken time away from her duties as Empress. Although generally placid, some areas of the galaxy are certainly not: the Raalgon cabinet is in turmoil. It also seems to some that the UPSF is being pushed towards full scale war with the Raalgon Empire. If there`s a solution to this it won`t come from Tylor, but perhaps from someone who has learned Tylor`s lesson. It`s likely that no one can solve this before the carnage starts though, and even if they did that no one would listen. As the Tylor series comes to an end with this volume, things are looking very grim! Still, if there`s anyone who can save the day...</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="323">6.57</permanent>
<temporary count="326">7.06</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>235280.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>87</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1168</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.vap.co.jp/tylor/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>The_Irresponsible_Captain_Tylor</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>無責任艦長タイラー_(アニメ)#OVA.E3.82.B7.E3.83.AA.E3.83.BC.E3.82.BA</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3147</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>235776</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1576</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7032" type="appears in" update="2011-11-16">
<rating votes="63">7.57</rating>
<name>Azalyn D`el Kran Rykun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The 16-year-old empress of the Holy Raalgon Empire. Azalyn is a child, forced into the unenviable situation of having to assume power of the empire once her parents are murdered. Prompted by her advisors, she gives the command to attack the UPSF (assuming that they were behind the assassination plot). Having not had a chance to be a child, Azalyn must now be strong for the entire empire, and it`s a task that she is afraid of taking, but even more afraid of failing.</description>
<picture>29556.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="167" picture="16972.jpg">Kasahara Hiroko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7033" type="appears in" update="2011-11-16">
<rating votes="57">6.69</rating>
<name>Yuriko Star</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lt. Commander Yuriko Star is another by-the-book officer. Yuriko joined the UPSF to give her life structure and attepts to obey the rules in almost every situation. However, she, unlike http://anidb.net/ch7036 [Yamamoto], has no problem telling http://anidb.net/ch7034 [Tylor] that he has done something wrong and will even resort to slapping him when he gets too far out of line. Yuriko also tries to downplay her gender, making herself a soldier first, and then a woman. This is a sore subject for her when someone comments about Tylor`s obvious attraction to her looks, pointing out that she has never used her appearance to get ahead; an equally sore point for her is her budding attraction to him. Yuriko is one of the most rational and level-headed officers on the http://anidb.net/ch7063 [Soyokaze]. While she is senior to Yamamoto, her speciality as an intelligence officer places her outside the chain of command.</description>
<picture>29565.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2054" picture="186267.jpg">Amano Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7034" type="appears in" update="2012-05-23">
<rating votes="104">9.02</rating>
<name>Justy Ueki Tylor</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Justy Ueki Tylor joins the United Planets Space Force hoping for an easy ride through life but with the devil`s luck becomes a hero. He is soon promoted Lieutenant Commander and Captain of http://anidb.net/ch7063 [Soyokaze]. Tylor is a irresponsible laid back captain that can always find his way out of trouble unscathed. Tylor normally allows his crew to "bend" the rules such as letting the surgeon drink while on duty. Throughout the ranks it is argued that Tylor is either the most brilliant military mind or just a lucky bafoon.</description>
<picture>29553.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="342" picture="17179.jpg">Tsujitani Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7035" type="appears in" update="2011-11-16">
<rating votes="43">6.55</rating>
<name>Kyon-Hwa Kim</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kim works on the bridge as the http://anidb.net/ch7063 [Soyokaze]`s communications officer. It is rumored that Kim was a fashion model prior to joining the military. She still enjoys dressing up and her urges to break out of the strict UPSF dress code cause problems between her and http://anidb.net/ch7033 [Yuriko Star]. Her hobbies include shopping and modern dance. She likes to read a women`s magazine called "Enen" in her free time, but is absolutely professional where her job is concerned.
She is cool-headed in a crisis and extremely skilled as a communications officer. She says at one point that she transfered onto the Soyokaze in order to find direction in her life, and there`s the strong possibility she did it after breaking up with a man.</description>
<picture>29561.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7036" type="appears in" update="2011-11-16">
<rating votes="31">7.62</rating>
<name>Makoto Yamamoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lieutenant Makoto Yamamoto is another very strait-laced, by-the-books military man. Yamamoto is the first officer on the http://anidb.net/ch7063 [Soyokaze] and tried mightily to interject an air of professionalism to the outfit. Constantly enraged by http://anidb.net/ch7034 [Tylor]`s lack of discipline and his loose command of the troops, Yamamoto spends much of his free time in the medic`s office taking tranquilizers and making use of the neuro-cleanser. Yamamoto sees Tylor for what he is, a bumbling fool, but is torn between the unwritten soldier`s code of supporting and obeying your superior officer, and telling the UPSF brass what is REALLY going on. He is always on the lookout for a chance to get some form of command, hoping to get a ship of his own one day.</description>
<picture>29563.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27" picture="26123.jpg">Hayami Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7037" type="appears in" update="2011-11-16">
<rating votes="28">7.88</rating>
<name>Hidezaburo Kitaguchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dr. Kitaguchi maintains the understaffed and under-stocked sick bay of the http://anidb.net/ch7063 [Soyokaze]. A great lover of alcohol in all its form, he even uses it to anesthetize and sterilize his patients. While only 33 years old, Kitaguchi claims to have a 30-year drinking habit and proclaims that he performs better in surgery when he`s liquored up.
With the arrival of http://anidb.net/ch7039 [Harumi], he becomes the envy of the entire male crew. He and http://anidb.net/ch7034 [Tylor] are drinking buddies, and he is one of the few crew members to gain a deep understanding of Tylor`s true nature early on. He claims the reason he became a doctor was because "it`s better than being a patient."</description>
<picture>29559.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3241" picture="24745.jpg">Yanami Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7038" type="appears in" update="2011-11-16">
<rating votes="19">6.02</rating>
<name>Harold Katori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Katori is the spiritual pilot/navigator the http://anidb.net/ch7063 [Soyokaze]. A great lover of Japanese green tea - if he has a cup, he can be counted on to perform the most difficult maneuvers (like steering through an asteroid belt) without breaking a sweat.
While he appears to be a Westerner, he is actually of Japanese descent. Possessed of a self-confidence that borders on arrogance, he claims that the ship is as "safe as a cradle" when he`s at the helm. His hobbies include various types of meditation, including Zen meditation.</description>
<picture>29562.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="387" picture="17233.jpg">Narita Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7039" type="appears in" update="2011-11-16">
<rating votes="31">8.23</rating>
<name>Harumi Nakagawa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Assigned to the http://anidb.net/ch7063 [Soyokaze] as the http://anidb.net/ch7037 [Doctor]`s assistant, Harumi has every man on the ship falling all over her - especially the Marines. But she`s only after one man: http://anidb.net/ch7034 [Tylor]! Unknow to most of the crew, Harumi is actually an android Raalgon spy. She was sent to the UPSF by http://anidb.net/ch7044 [Ru Baraba Dom] and http://anidb.net/ch38778 [Shia Has] to kill Tylor. Instead, she succumbs to Tylor`s charm and ends up falling in love with him!</description>
<picture>29555.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="489" picture="43165.jpg">Okamoto Maya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7040" type="appears in" update="2011-11-16">
<rating votes="20">5.58</rating>
<name>Yumi Hanner</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The remarkable http://anidb.net/ch7041 [Emi] and Yumi Hanner are young girls who first meet http://anidb.net/ch7033 [Tylor] while they are taking care of their father, Admiral http://anidb.net/ch38780 [Robert J. Hanner] (retired). After they are taken hostage, Emi and Yumi are rescued by Tylor and fall in love with him. They join the http://anidb.net/ch7063 [Soyokaze]`s crew when Tylor is reassigned as its captain.
Desired to pilot ships, they persuade http://anidb.net/ch7042 [Kojirou] to train them (against his will of course) and discover that they have a natural piloting ability. Emi and Yumi`s close quarters with Kojirou provide them with endless amusement since he is deathly afraid of females.
Identical twins, the only way to tell them apart is by their pony tails (Yumi`s is on the left side of her head, while Emi`s is on her right) and their voices (Yumi`s is higher pitched than Emi`s). They were also childhood friends of http://anidb.net/ch7033 [Yuriko Star].</description>
<picture>29567.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="70" picture="171604.jpg">Kanai Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7041" type="appears in" update="2011-11-16">
<rating votes="21">5.31</rating>
<name>Emi Hanner</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The remarkable Emi and http://anidb.net/ch7040 [Yumi] Hanner are young girls who first meet http://anidb.net/ch7033 [Tylor] while they are taking care of their father, Admiral http://anidb.net/ch38780 [Robert J. Hanner] (retired). After they are taken hostage, Emi and Yumi are rescued by Tylor and fall in love with him. They join the http://anidb.net/ch7063 [Soyokaze]`s crew when Tylor is reassigned as its captain.
Desired to pilot ships, they persuade http://anidb.net/ch7042 [Kojirou] to train them (against his will of course) and discover that they have a natural piloting ability. Emi and Yumi`s close quarters with Kojirou provide them with endless amusement since he is deathly afraid of females.
Identical twins, the only way to tell them apart is by their pony tails (Yumi`s is on the left side of her head, while Emi`s is on her right) and their voices (Yumi`s is higher pitched than Emi`s). They were also childhood friends of http://anidb.net/ch7033 [Yuriko Star].</description>
<picture>29564.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="70" picture="171604.jpg">Kanai Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7042" type="appears in" update="2011-11-16">
<rating votes="14">5.32</rating>
<name>Kojirou Sakai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The supremely self-confident pilot of the Ranpu-class fighter assigned to the http://anidb.net/ch7063 [Soyokaze]. Known alternately as "The Samurai of Space" and "The Shoot-Down King," Kojirou graduated with honors from flight training. While he hasn`t logged that many hours of flight time, he shows deadly skill against the Raalgon forces.
Possessing an actual phobia of women, he seems to regard the Hanner sisters as a special case, no doubt owing to their own natural piloting skill. He keeps a small mascot doll the twins made for him in the cockpit of his fighter. He also gets along very poorly with the Marines.</description>
<picture>29560.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="554" picture="244340.jpg">Iwata Mitsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7043" type="appears in" update="2011-11-16">
<rating votes="12">7.59</rating>
<name>Karl Bjorn Andresen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Andressen is the pilot of the Dropship, the troop transport which carries the Marines into combat. Nicknamed "Eric the Red," he seems to be the most mature person aboard the http://anidb.net/ch7063 [Soyokaze].</description>
<picture>29554.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3394" picture="24430.jpg">Shibamoto Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7044" type="appears in" update="2011-11-16">
<rating votes="15">7.02</rating>
<name>Ru Baraba Dom</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ru Baraba Dom is the commander of the Raalgon cruiser Doroume, 66th Detached Fleet. As the war progresses, http://anidb.net/ch7032 [Azalyn] comes to trust his intelligent advice. Unlike many of his fellow colleagues, Dom respects and admires http://anidb.net/ch7034 [Tylor] for his fighting and tactical abilities. Both Tylor and Dom recognize that wars can only be won when no one fights.
He is loyal to the young empress and stands firmly in Lonawer`s camp to find a way to end the war honorably and with a minimum of bloodshed.</description>
<picture>29557.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="384" picture="17230.jpg">Seki Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7050" type="appears in" update="2011-11-16">
<rating votes="6">1.47</rating>
<name>Naku Ra Wang</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chief Advisor to the Holy Raalgon Empress, Wang craves to be more than just the Premier. He places the blame of the Emperor`s death on the UPSF and craftily convinces Empress http://anidb.net/ch7032 [Azalyn] to declare war with them. Meanwhile, Wang continues to manipulate the Empire`s opinion against the Empress to force her to bend to his will. Hungry for the power of the throne, he makes several attempts on Azalyn`s life.</description>
<picture>29558.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="385" picture="215702.jpg">Tsukada Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7051" type="appears in" update="2011-11-16">
<rating votes="11">5.12</rating>
<name>Mickey Cryburn</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cryburn is the commander of the Marine contingent on board. His Hammer combat suit is painted pink and he seems to be best friends with http://anidb.net/ch7043 [Andressen].</description>
<picture>29566.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42809" picture="223789.jpg">Nakata Kazuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7063" type="appears in" update="2011-11-16">
<rating votes="13">7.81</rating>
<name>Soyokaze</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>While its design is old, this destroyer is a hardy veteran of many battles. It`s equipped with long-range laser cannons and photon torpedos as well as phaser banks for point defense.</description>
<picture>29568.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7067" type="appears in" update="2009-06-22">
<rating votes="6">4.36</rating>
<name>Yamada</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29682.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7068" type="appears in" update="2009-07-28">
<rating votes="10">4.98</rating>
<name>Bunta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29676.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7069" type="appears in" update="2009-07-28">
<rating votes="8">4.29</rating>
<name>Charly</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29677.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7070" type="appears in" update="2009-07-28">
<rating votes="7">4.30</rating>
<name>Emperor</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29678.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7071" type="appears in" update="2009-07-28">
<rating votes="7">5.81</rating>
<name>Angel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29675.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7075" type="appears in" update="2009-06-21">
<rating votes="9">5.86</rating>
<name>Jason</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29679.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="38776" type="appears in" update="2011-11-16">
<rating votes="4">6.41</rating>
<name>Yutta Do Lonawer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Imperial Minister of Defense, he directly commands the 27th galactic frontier division. http://anidb.net/ch7044 [Dom]`s direct superior, he has shepherded the young captain through the Imperial Forces and acts as a father figure for him.
While strongly suspicious of http://anidb.net/ch7050 [Wang]`s motives for starting the war with the United Planets, he lacks the political strenght to directly oppose him. Fiercely loyal to the empress, he does all he can to protect her from the machinations of her ambitious prime minister. However, this patriotism will not let him directly question the war in public, putting him in a very tenuous position within the Imperial Court.</description>
<picture>77202.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9290">Nishio Toku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38778" type="appears in" update="2011-11-16">
<rating votes="12">8.38</rating>
<name>Shia Has</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Captain of the large destroyer Galguran, Shia Has carries approximately the same rank as http://anidb.net/ch7044 [Ru Baraba Dom], but is under his direct command as part of his fleet. She is more aggressive and forceful than Dom. She is harshly critical of the http://anidb.net/ch7063 [Soyokaze]`s crew and falls to see http://anidb.net/ch7034 [Tylor] in the same light as Dom.</description>
<picture>77201.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3936" picture="245652.jpg">Mita Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91086" type="appears in" update="2017-08-22">
<rating votes="4">4.13</rating>
<name>Sesshuu Mifune</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206523.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39" picture="16629.jpg">Mugihito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91087" type="appears in" update="2017-08-22">
<rating votes="4">4.13</rating>
<name>Susumu Fuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206524.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="436" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1996-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 1</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Vers l’éternité (partie 1)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="437" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>1996-08-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Vers l’éternité (partie 2)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
