<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8735" restricted="false">
<type>Other</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-08-01</startdate>
<enddate>2011-08-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Pikachu no Summer Bridge Story</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pokemon: Movie 14 Short</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pikachu`s Summer Bridge Story</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ピカチュウのサマー・ブリッジ・ストーリー</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7891" type="Parent Story">Pocket Monsters: Best Wishes!</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="727" type="Animation Work">OLM</name>
<name id="27525" type="Character Design">Matsumiya Toshinobu</name>
<name id="27526" type="Character Design">Matsushima Kenji</name>
<name id="2841" type="Work">Shogakukan-Shueisha Productions</name>
<name id="5780" type="Original Plan">Tajiri Satoshi</name>
<name id="10185" type="Original Plan">Masuda Jun`ichi</name>
<name id="10181" type="Original Plan">Sugimori Ken</name>
<name id="4235" type="Direction">Yuyama Kunihiko</name>
<name id="7914" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yamada Shun`ya</name>
<name id="2822" type="Music">Tada Akifumi</name>
<name id="6897" type="Music">Tanaka Hirokazu</name>
<name id="5660" type="Music">Miyazaki Shinji</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch8091 [Satoshi`s Pikachu] and friends visit a town with a huge draw bridge, but problems arise when they come across Satoshi`s http://anidb.net/ch27203 [Mijumaru] and http://anidb.net/ch27206 [Pokabu], who have eaten the fruits that wild Gothimu and Darumakka had collected. They head off to collect fruits from the forest across the bridge, but then Nyarth appears and tries to steal the fruits. On top of that, the bridge is raised, blocking their passage. What will Pikachu do? The fight for the fruits begins!!
Source: bulbapedia.bulbagarden.net
Note: Originally shown on All Nippon Airways (ANA) flights starting from 01.08.2011 to 29.08.2011.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="64">3.50</permanent>
<temporary count="66">5.19</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>143973.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15660</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11853</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1846" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>kodomo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word kodomo refers to a children`s audience roughly for the ages 12 and younger. In Japanese, the word means simply "child", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1938" type="main character in" update="2013-02-13">
<rating votes="420">5.46</rating>
<name>Nyarth (Rocket-dan)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Meowth is a very unique Pokémon as it has many of the characteristics of a human. It walks on two feet, talks and is as smart as any human. Meowth is currently a member of Team Rocket and he travels around with Jessie and James trying to capture Pikachu and other rare Pokémon for Giovanni.
Meowth generally finishes his sentences with "Nyaa (ニャー)" which is the equivalent of "meow" in English. This helps people remember that despite his ability to talk like a human, he still has cat character traits.
Meowth is also known for coming up with his many schemes to try to capture Pikachu. While Jessie and James always agree with Meowth and think his plans are brilliant, they are generally foiled by Ash and his friends.
Long Con to Access Raimon City Pokémon Center
Meowth schemed with Jessie, James and Doctor Zager to figure out a way for them to infiltrate the Raimon City Pokémon Center where high-leveled Pokémon are stored in a vault that is protected by a security machine scan system that would only open if Nurse Joy (Isshu) or Nurse Joy`s Audino were scanned. Meowth pretended to be no longer part of Team Rocket making up a story that his made an error while executing a certain operation and when headquarters hear of his mistake, they told him he was fired.
Ash, Iris and Cilan believed him and allowed Meowth to travel with him. Pikachu though didn`t trust Meowth even though Meowth proved on numerous occasion that it should be trusted. Meowth`s plan was put into action when they arrived at the Raimon City Pokémon Center and as soon as Nurse Joy`s Audino was scanned to open the door, Meowth turned on Pikachu and the other and captured all the Pokémon in the vault. The long con had been a success and Meowth met up with Jessie and James below the Pokémon Center. Unfortunately, they weren`t able to get away as Ash and his friends realized that Meowth had just been conning them and they were able to stop Team Rocket.</description>
<picture>56344.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3832" picture="170554.jpg">Inuyama Inuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8091" type="main character in" update="2017-10-30">
<rating votes="989">3.91</rating>
<name>Pikachu (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Beginning
On the morning that Ash was to start his Pokémon journey, he woke up late and by the time he reached Professor Samual Oak`s laboratory, all of the beginner Pokémon were already taken. However, Professor Samual Oak did have one Pokémon left, a wild Pikachu. At first, Pikachu did not like Ash and would refuse to enter his PokéBall. He would often laugh at Ash`s failures and refused to listen to him. However, after Ash proved his loyalty to Pikachu by protecting him from a flock of Spearow, and thus began to earn Pikachu`s trust and respect. The two have since become best friends and Pikachu never leaves Ash`s side.
Since the day Team Rocket first encountered Pikachu, it has been their sole goal to capture it. Day after day, their plan to capture Pikachu has been thwarted mainly due to Pikachu`s amazingly powerful Thunderbolt that keeps on blasting them off.
On numerous occasions, Pikachu has made it evident that he is happy being a Pikachu and has no desire to evolve into a more powerful Raichu. It has proven time and time again that it is a powerful and worthy opponent to any Pokémon that dares to battle it.
Gym Battle against Burgh`s Leavanny
Pikachu was then sent out to battle Burgh`s Leavanny. Burgh`s Leavanny managed to tie up Pikachu with String Shot but unlike Ash`s Swadloon who was able to break free, Pikachu ended up getting hit with a couple of Leaf Storm attacks and a Hyper Beam before it rolled into another of Burgh`s Leavanny`s Leaf Storm attacks to break the string off its body so it could attack. Freed from the String Shot, Burgh`s Leavanny tried to tie it up again but Pikachu managed to avoid it with its speed and then knocked Burgh`s Leavanny out with a combination of Iron Tail and Electro Ball.
Gym Battle against Elesa
Elesa`s Emolga knocked out Ash`s Snivy and was then matched up with Pikachu. Pikachu made quick work of Elesa`s Emolga and knocked it out with one attack, its Iron Tail.
Elesa`s Tynamo was the last Pokémon that she used in her gym battle against Ash. It was matched up against Pikachu who had just defeated her Emonga. Pikachu had a hard time defending against the fast Tackle attack that Elesa`s Tynamo kept hitting it with but Pikachu used its Thunderbolt to create a large dust cloud leaving only a small corridor for Pikachu to focus on it and so Elesa`s Tynamo couldn`t maneuver out of the way. Pikachu one hit K.O`d Elesa`s Tynamo with a Iron Tail. The loss gave Ash the overall victory.
Battle against Alder`s Bouffalant
Ash challenged Alder to a battle and he accepted though he had been walking all night and was actually quite tired. Alder sent out his Buffron to battle Pikachu but just as the battle started, Alder fell asleep standing up and didn`t give any orders to his Buffron. Alder`s Bouffalant stood still as Pikachu began hitting it with attack after attack until it Alder`s Bouffalant finally got mad at Alder and charged at him and set him flying into a tree. After that, Alder`s Bouffalant no longer wished to battle and Alder conceded the battle.
Gym Battle against Skyla
In Skyla air battle simulation, Ash`s Tranquill was matched up against Skyla`s Unfezant and since her Pokémon was the highest evolved form, she determined that her Pokémon would be the winner in that match-up. In the actual gym battle, Ash`s Tranquill was up against Skyla`s Unfezant which was the match-up just after Ash`s Tranquill had defeated Skyla`s Swoobat. Skyla`s Unfezant proved to be stronger and faster than Ash`s Tranquill, so Ash recalled it and set out Pikachu. Pikachu had a definite advantage over Skyla`s Unfezant with its electric attacks and it quickly knocked it out with its Electro Ball attack.
Ash Just after Pikachu ended up knocking out Skyla`s Unfezant, Skyla`s Swanna was sent out to battle against it. Skyla had been watching her grandpa`s battle videos and noticed that he used the move Aqua Ring to defend against Electric attacks. She used that same defense against Pikachu which nullified its Electric attacks. It`s Iron Tail also couldn`t hit it so high in the air. Ash then noticed the rings in the air and Pikachu jumped up on them and managed to hit Skyla`s Swanna but not directly. Pikachu was now up in the air though and Skyla`s Swanna had the advantage there and it quickly knocked Pikachu out with a powerful Brave Bird attack.
Battle Against Trip`s Serperior at the Isshu League
Pikachu participated in the Isshu League in the preliminary match where it is was matched up against Trip`s Serperior. Cilan noted that Trip`s Serperior speed and its attack power had leveled up quite a bit too since the last time they saw it. The match was pretty one sided for a long time as Pikachu wasn`t able to counter its speed and ended up getting wrapped up. After using Iron Tail on the ground to get loose, Pikachu used a combination attack of Iron Tail and Electro Ball to one hit KO Trip`s Serperior. As a result, Trip was eliminated from the Isshu League and Ash advanced to the next round.</description>
<picture>88041.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7" picture="186500.jpg">Ootani Ikue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27188" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Darumakka</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Darumaka is a Fire-type Pokémon introduced in Generation V.
It evolves into Darmanitan starting at level 35.
In Galar, Darumaka has an Ice-type regional form. It evolves into Galarian Darmanitan when exposed to an Ice Stone.
Darumaka is a round, red Pokémon with an orange face and yellow curly eyebrows. It has three yellow ovals on its abdomen and a curvy yellow line on its back. Its paws are orange and have three digits each. It has very warm droppings, which ancient people put in their clothes to keep themselves warm.
When the flame inside its body burns, Darumaka is very active. It cannot calm down in this state, and thus becomes uncontrollable. As the flame shrinks, it falls asleep. It can tuck in its arms and legs when it rests; during that time, it slightly sways. While it is sleeping, it cannot be tipped over no matter how much it is pushed or pulled, like a tumbler doll, which it resembles in this state. It prefers to live in a desert environment.
Galarian Darumaka has a thicker coat than normal Darumaka, several turquoise ice crystals as its eyebrows and on its chest, and has blue hands and face with white snowy fur. Unlike its normal form, Galarian Darumaka has a timid frown instead of a mischievous smile.
Seismic shift in the Galar region long ago caused the warm climate to cool, and Darumaka in this region have adapted to this cooling. The fire that burned within their bodies went out, leaving an organ that produces cold air instead. The colder Darumaka gets, the more energetic it becomes. They can focus their internal energy to breathe out cold air in the form of snow, which they use to make snowballs for ammo in playful snowball fights with each other. Galarian Darumaka enjoys eating Berries produced by Snover. This leads it to prey on Snover often being driven off by Abomasnow.</description>
<picture>68412.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27193" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Chillarmy</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Minccino, known as the Chinchilla Pokémon, brush each other with their tails as a greeting. They never fail to groom their tails clean.
Game Informer`s Jeff Marchiafava praised it, calling it cute, and stating its move "Tail Slap" is the "most adorable way you can get beat up".</description>
<picture>243497.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="551" picture="228658.jpg">Nishimura Chinami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27194" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Swanna</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Swanna, known as the White Bird Pokémon, is a swan-like Pokémon. With a long yellow bill, it administers sharp, powerful pecks. It whips its long neck to deliver forceful repeated strikes. Swanna start dancing at night, and dance around the leader of the flock.
In the games, Swanna can be found flying around Marvelous Bridge. In the anime, a flock of Swanna appeared in In The Shadow of Zekrom!. A Swanna later appeared under the ownership of Officer Jenny. In the Pokémon Master Black &amp; White manga, a Pokémon Ranger used one with his Zebstrika in a double battle against Monta.</description>
<picture>243506.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27197" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Reshiram</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Reshiram is the Vast White Pokémon (White Yang Pokémon in Japan), and is the mascot for Pokémon Black. It resembles a white wyvern, with wing-shaped arms and claws. Its tail resembles a rocket engine or afterburner. The fire that burns from Reshiram`s tail is capable of incinerating everything.
It (as well as its English name) was revealed on May 28, 2010, on both the official Japanese and English Pokémon websites, alongside its counterpart Zekrom. Both Reshiram and Zekrom appeared as floats in the 2010 Macy`s Thanksgiving Day Parade.
At the climax of Pokémon Black, the player must capture Reshiram and use it to defeat N`s Zekrom, while in Pokémon White the roles of the two dragons are reversed.
Reshiram debuted in the anime as one of the featured Pokémon in the film Pokémon the Movie: Black - Victini and Reshiram. In Pokemon Black and White Version, its wings, tail, and head glows red.
In the Reshiram movie, Reshiram befriends Ash. In the Zekrom movie, Reshiram befriends Damon.</description>
<picture>243561.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27199" type="appears in" update="2013-02-13">
<name>Kibago (Iris)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Iris`s Axew was first seen appearing out of Iris`s large hairdo, much to the surprise of Ash and Pikachu. Ash helped rescue Axew from Team Rocket when they captured it just after Iris met Ash.
Axew is Iris`s main Pokémon and it doesn`t seem to like to travel in its monster ball. It seems to prefer traveling on Iris`s shoulders and in her hair.
Mastering Dragon Rage
Iris had been practicing Dragon Rage with her Kibago for quite a while and every time the attack was used it was unsuccessful and created a crater in the ground where the attack was used and injured everyone in the area. After being captured by Team Rocket along with Crimgan, Iris`s Axew managed to master Dragon Rage which was powerful enough to crash their flying transport mecha. In the battle encounter with Team Rocket that occurred after the crash, Iris`s Axew showed everyone that it had finally mastered the move by launching a successful attack at Team Rocket but they managed to escape before it hit them.
Don Battles Against Luke`s Golett
Iris`s Axew and Luke`s Golett were matched up in the semi-final round of the Don Battles in Raimon Town. Luke`s Golett dominated most of the battle and just as Iris`s Axew was about to be defeated, it learned the move Outrage. Outrage was able to do significant damage to Luke`s Golett and it knocked it out which eliminated Luke from the tournament.
Battle against Cynthia`s Garchomp / Learning Giga Impact
Iris asked to battle Cynthia`s Garchomp with her Kibago as she was working on becoming a Dragon Master. Even before it the started, the battled seemed like Cynthia`s Garchomp would win. Iris`s Axew could not do any damage to Cynthia`s Garchomp until it finally concentrated for a few moments and learned Giga Impact. While Giga Impact was able to do some damage to Cynthia`s Garchomp, it quickly overpowered Iris`s Axew until Cynthia decided to end the match before a finishing blow.</description>
<picture>63840.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21823" picture="131326.jpg">Tsuda Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27201" type="appears in" update="2018-11-11">
<name>Koromori (Musashi)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jessie`s Koromori was caught in the Isshu region. It was first revealed in a battle against Satoshi and his Mamepato. It was able to defeat Satoshi`s Mamepato during that first battle.</description>
<picture>63842.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2364" picture="151724.jpg">Furushima Kiyotaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27203" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-13">
<name>Mijumaru (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ash first encountered Mijumaru at Professor Juniper laboratory as it was one of the Pokémon that Trip was to choose from. Ash called it cute when he first saw it which caused Mijumaru to blush a bit. After being shocked that it wasn`t chosen by Trip, it followed Ash and Pikachu as they started their journey in the Isshu region.
It rescued Pikachu and Iris`s Axew from Rocket Gang. Ash thanked it but quickly left it behind in the forest so that he could treat Pikachu. It continued following Ash until one day it met up again and tried to explain that it wanted to join Ash on his journey. Ash tried to capture it with one of his Poké balls but then realized it already had a Poké ball and that this Mijumaru must have been the same one that he met at Professor Juniper lab. He contacted Professor Juniper and she agreed to let him have the Mijumaru and transferred its Poké ball to him. By the time it had been transferred over, it had disappeared again.
Ash met up with Mijumaru once again when they were resting in the sands at Dan`s hotel. After protecting Ash from being scalded from a hot water geyser, Ash quickly recalled it into the Poké ball before it got scalded itself. Since then Ash`s Oshawott has had the tendency to come out of its Poké ball whenever it feels like despite what the current situation is.
Gym Battles against Lenora`s Watchog
During the first gym battle against Ash`s Oshawott, Lenora`s Watchog used Mean Look so Ash`s Oshawott couldn`t be switched out. Since Ash`s Oshawott wasn`t expecting to battle Lenora`s Watchog at that time, it was at a disadvantage and it was in a bad mood. After Ash`s Oshawott lost its shell during the battle, Lenora`s Watchog was able to use its Thunderbolt effectively to knock Ash`s Oshawott out of the match.
During the rematch battle against Lenora`s Watchog, Ash`s Oshawott had learned Aqua Jet during the time between the two battle and but its accuracy make it easy for Lenora`s Watchog to avoid it. Though through sheer luck, Ash`s Oshawott Aqua Jet managed to hit Lenora`s Watchog and both ended up getting knocked out at the same time as Lenora`s Watchog used Thunderbolt just before it got hit.
Three-on-Three Battle Against Trip`s Timburr
Ash`s Oshawott was paired up against Trip`s Timburr but the beginning of the battle didn`t go to well for Ash as Ash`s Oshawott had its eyes closed during Aqua Jet and completely missed hitting Trip`s Timburr. After a short break in the battle, the two finished up with their final attacks. Ash`s Oshawott`s Razor Shell proved to be stronger than Trip`s Timburr`s DynamicPunch and Ash`s Oshawott defeated Trip`s Timburr despite its initial problems with Aqua Jet`s accuracy.
Mastering Aqua Jet
While training in Don George`s pool for the battle against Lenora, Ash`s Oshawott learned Aqua Jet. It`s aim proved to be quite off but through sheer luck it was able to use Aqua Jet to knock out both Lenora`s Watchog and Stephan`s Blitzle. It wasn`t until Trip noticed by taking some pictures during his three-on-three battle with Ash that Ash`s Oshawott had its eyes closed during Aqua Jet. Ash vowed to help his Oshawott practice to keep its eyes open underwater so that its Aqua Jet`s targeting would be accurate.
While enroute to Raimon City, Ash, Iris and Cilan`s Pokémon all got poisoned and the only thing that could cure them was a waterweed plant found in a nearby lake. Ash`s Oshawott was training with Ash at the time and didn`t get poisoned and since it was a Water Pokémon, it was best suited for the job. Unfortunately Ash`s Oshawott still didn`t like to open its eyes underwater until it was forced to defend itself against a school of Tympole who were protecting their lake from trespassers. Ash`s Oshawott opened its eyes underwater to defend itself and it started to get comfortable doing so. Ash`s Oshawott was later forced to battle Palpitoad because it came out of the water to protect its lake. During the battle, Ash`s Oshawott managed to master its Aqua Jet as it was able to remember the battle against the Tympole school and how having its eyes opened underwater was quite effective and that proved to be the decisive factor in the battle as Palpitoad was knocked out and Ash caught it.
Battle against Bel`s Father`s Hihidaruma
Ash challenged Bianca`s Father to a Pokémon battle to allow Bianca to continue to travel. He agreed but changed the challenge to force Ash to return home to Pallet Town if he lost the battle. Ash`s Oshawott came out of its ball as it wanted to battle against Bianca`s Father`s Darmanitan and Ash thought that it would be okay because it had a type advantage being a water Pokémon. Even though Bianca`s Father`s Darmanitan only used Fire type moves throughout the battle, it proved to be too strong for Ash`s Oshawott. Ash`s Oshawott did manage to land an Aqua Jet. Bianca`s Father commented though that his Red Flash Hihidaruma gets more fired up the more resistance it faces and shortly after it knocked Ash`s Oshawott out. Despite loosing the battle, Bianca`s Father changed his mind because the battle with Ash and his Mijumaru made him remember the joy of traveling.
Battle Against Pod`s Baoppu
Initially, Ash was going to battle Chili`s Pansear with his Pikachu, but Ash`s Oshawott popped out and wanted to battle it instead. Ash agreed and despite the type disadvantage in this battle, Chili just got more fired up. Chili`s Pansear managed to cover its weakness with power and momentum and taking Cilan`s advice into account, it used Flame Charge to increase its speed to become useful when dodging Ash`s Oshawott moves. Chili`s Pansear managed to endure Ash`s Oshawott super effective moves just long enough for it to use its newly learned SolarBeam attack which Ash`s Oshawott was unable to dodge and it was knocked out. Chili`s Pansear won the battle despite the type disadvantage.
Battle Against Clay`s Krokorok
Clay`s Krokorok was the first Pokémon Clay used to battle against Ash during his gym battle. Clay`s Krokorok was paired up against Ash`s Oshawott as Pikachu initially wanted to battle it but Ash realized that an Electric type against a Ground type would be a bad idea.
At the beginning of the battle, Clay`s Krokorok had the upper hand as its Sandstorm managed to get sand in Ash`s Oshawott`s eyes and it also made it harder for Ash`s Oshawott to accurately attack. Clay`s Krokorok managed to hit Ash`s Oshawott with a Bite and a Stone Edge attack but it wasn`t enough to knock it out. Ash`s Oshawott used Water Gun to clear up the Sandstorm and then it began its counterattack. Clay`s Krokorok was repetitively hit with multiple attacks from Ash`s Oshawott including a super effective Aqua Jet and Razor Shell combo that ended up being too much for it and it was knocked out.
Battle Against Clay`s Palpitoad
Ash decided to keep his Oshawott out to battle against Clay`s Palpitoad and right away it became evident that Clay`s Palpitoad was the stronger Pokémon as its Hydro Pump ended up being more powerful than Ash`s Oshawott Water Gun. Clay`s Palpitoad followed up with a Sludge Bomb that knocked Ash`s Oshawott`s scallsword out of its hand and just as it was retrieving it, it got hit by Clay`s Palpitoad Rock Smash`s and was knocked out.
Ash`s Oshawott and Dawn`s Piplup Rivalry
Ash`s Oshawott and Dawn`s Piplup both fell in love with Meloetta and the two of them began a rivalry to win the affection of Meloetta. Ash`s Oshawott would often come out of its PokéBall when it could tell that Dawn`s Piplup was trying to take advantage of a situation. Even though the two of them often argued, they found a common ground and became friends after Meloetta left.</description>
<picture>63844.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="304" picture="17139.jpg">Fukuen Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27206" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-10-27">
<name>Pokabu (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ash`s Pokabu was first seen by Don George at his Battle Club when it original trainer came to battle. Pokabu lost to a Shikijika during the battle and its trainer tied it to a pole and left it. The Pokabu ended up getting the string tied around its snout making it impossible for it to eat.
Ash saw Pokabu on the security camera video and thought it was an Umbreon because it was all dirty. When Ash finally spotted Pokabu, he cornered it in an alley and tried to be friendly with it. Ash noticed the rope tied around its snout and loosened it. Pokabu then helped rescue Pikachu from Team Rocket.
Iris wanted to get Pokabu but it wanted to be caught by Ash instead. Realizing that Pokabu wanted to travel with him, Ash captured Pokabu just outside the Battle Club in Karakusa Town.</description>
<picture>63847.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2413" picture="22272.jpg">Mizuta Wasabi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27209" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-13">
<name>Yanappu (Dent)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cilan`s Pansage was first revealed in the Sanyo Gym when Ash was shown the three gym leaders Pokémon and he looked it up in his PokéDex. Yanappu is Cilan`s main Pokémon and is relied on quite often to help Cilan out with his various tasks.
Yanappu battled against Ash`s Oshawott during his gym battle. Cilan`s Pansage showed its speed by being able to dodge most of Mijumaru Water Gun attacks.
Battle Against Pod`s Baoppu
Chili wanted to see the results of Cilan`s studying and he challenged him to a battle. Chili thought that it would be an easy battle as they had the super effective type advantage but as the battle progressed Chili didn`t like the fact that Cilan`s Pansage kept avoiding all of Chili`s Pansear fire attacks and Chili told Cilan that running away all the time doesn`t make a battle. Cilan though told him that running away is a perfectly fine way to battle. Chili got more angry during the battle and after loosing he blamed his Baoppu for the loss as it missed its Fire Blast at the most crucial moment. Chili`s Pansear ran away in anger as it was mad it was getting blamed for the loss and Cilan then blamed Chili for the loss in the battle which only fueled Chili`s anger and he ran off as well.
Battle against Skyla
Skyla`s Unfezant was matched up against Cilan`s Pansage in Skyla`s air battle and she believed that her Unfezant would be victorious. In the actual gym battle, Skyla`s Swoobat was matched up against Cilan`s Pansage. It proved to be very fast in the air and easily dodged all of Cilan`s Pansage`s attacks. It only used two attacks against Cilan`s Pansage: a Air Cutter and a Gust attack before it knocked it out and gave Skyla the victory in the first round.
Tag Battle against Soran`s Warrgle and Riiku`s Mogurew
Cilan`s Pansage had a tag battle with Ash`s Unfezant against Soran`s Warrgle and Riiku`s Mogurew while Ash and his friends were on their way to Higaki City where the Isshu League was to be held. Soran`s Warrgle and Riiku`s Mogurew used special move combinations which proved to be effective in the tag battle against Ash and Cilan until they also decided to use their own combination of moves which ended up overpowering Soran`s Warrgle and Riiku`s Mogurew and they lost the tag battle.</description>
<picture>63851.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5979" picture="30602.jpg">Fujimura Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27216" type="appears in" update="2013-02-13">
<name>Tsutarja (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>While on route to Shippo City, Ash encountered a resilient Tsutarja. Tsutarja started eating the cakes Dent made. Realizing that it was a strong and powerful Pokémon, he decided to try to capture it right away but it didn`t get captured in the monster ball. Ash then instructed Pikachu to attack Tsutarja but Ash ended up having to protect Pikachu from Tsutarja`s powerful vine whips as it was exposed to Attract which made it dizzy.
Ash`s Oshawott and Ash`s Tepig were both sent out to battle Tsutarja as well but it used Attract against them which proved quite effective due to the gender differences. Ash finally instructed his Mamepato to battle as it wasn`t affected by Attract. After a fierce battle between Tsutarja and Mamepato, Tsutarja was weakened enough and Ash captured it successfully.
Don George Tournament
Georgia faced Ash in the second round of the Don George tournament in Raimon Town. Georgia`s Pawniard faced Ash`s Snivy and at the beginning of the battle it looked like it was going to easily win but Ash`s Snivy was able to avoid getting hit by Guillotine. From that point on, Ash`s Snivy took control of the match and was able to defeat Georgia`s Pawniard which advanced Ash on to the next round in the tournament.
Gym Battle Against Elesa`s Emolga
After Elesa`s Emolga defeated Ash`s Palpitoad, Ash`s Snivy was sent out to battle against Elesa`s Emolga but Ash didn`t really have a battle strategy anymore since his Palpitoad had been defeated and he forgot that Emolga was also a Flying type. Elesa`s Emolga combination of Acrobatics and Aerial Ace was just too hard for Ash`s Snivy to defend against as the type advantage hampered it. Elesa`s Emolga knocked out Ash`s Snivy fairly easily.
Battle against Katharine`s Gothita
Katharine`s Gothita convinced Ash`s Scraggy to come with it outside to get something to eat. They ended up getting in trouble with a Garbodor and Katharine`s Deerling to use its Aromatherapy to calm down the raging Garbodor after Ash`s Snivy had followed them to see what they were up to. Katharine`s Gothita did not like the fact that Ash`s Snivy had been looking up on them and it decided it wanted to battle it.
Katharine`s Gothita was quite mad at Ash`s Snivy but it didn`t stand a chance against it in battle. Ash`s Snivy barely broke a sweat as it was able to counter and avoid all of Katharine`s Gothita`s attacks before it knocked it out with its Leaf Storm. Still upset, Katharine`s Gothita ran off into the distance.
Battle against Clay`s Palpitoad
After knocking out Ash`s Oshawott, Ash`s Snivy was sent out to replace it as Ash picked it because it was strong against both Ground and Water. Ash`s Snivy used Attract right at the beginning of their battle which prove to be an unexpected yet effective technique as Clay`s Palpitoad was unable to attack after the effects of Attract took hold of it. Ash`s Snivy pummeled Clay`s Palpitoad with effective Grass type attacks until it was knocked out.
Battle against Clay`s Excadrill
Ash kept his Snivy out to battle against Clay`s Excadrill but that matchup didn`t last long as Clay`s Excadrill was able to defend against all of Ash`s Snivy`s attacks. Ash`s Snivy was quickly knocked out with a strong Horn Drill.</description>
<picture>63859.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27276" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Munna</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Munna is known as the Dream Eater Pokémon. It resembles a tapir. It can smoke out what looks like a reflection after eating the dreams of people and Pokémon. It evolves into Musharna when exposed to a Moon Stone.
Game Informer`s Jeff Marchiafava stated "the fact that it can eat my dreams makes it one Pokémon that I would want as an ally rather than an enemy."</description>
<picture>243449.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27278" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Mogurew</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Drilbur, known as the Mole Pokémon, burrows underground at more than 50 km/h. Its running speed above ground rivals automobiles. It evolves in Excadrill. By crossing both its claws it makes itself rotate at high speeds and progresses underground at a great speed.
Game Informer`s Jeff Marchiafava criticized its design, stating "I just don`t feel very intimidated when I look at Drilbur."</description>
<picture>243460.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11087" picture="39958.jpg">Satou Kensuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27387" type="appears in" update="2020-01-07">
<name>Basslao</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Basculin, known as the Hostile Pokémon, is a green and black colored fish. It has two forms which main difference is a colored stripe and the player encounters one form more commonly depending on the game version; red-striped Basculin are more common in Black, while the blue-striped variety is more common in White.
Game Informer`s Jeff Marchiafava praised its categorization as the "Hostile Pokémon", stating "Now here`s a category I can get behind". They criticized its abilities for contradicting each other.</description>
<picture>64390.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27396" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Gothimu</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gothita, known as the Fixation Pokémon, is a human-like baby Pokémon with purple skin, and black and white clothes. It has three bows, and a small tuft of hair. Their bows increase their psychic abilities. Gothita closely observe both Trainers and Pokémon, looking at something that only they can see.
They are a version exclusive Pokémon and are only obtainable in Pokémon Black version.</description>
<picture>243499.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1665" picture="19756.jpg">Takahashi Chiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27451" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Vulgina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mandibuzz, known as the Bone Vulture Pokémon, are a female only species that resembles turkey vultures. They decorate themselves with bones; one sits in their hair, while another hangs around their waist. While soaring in the sky, Mandibuzz strike weakened Pokémon, and grab weakened prey with their talons. They haul them to their nest made of bones.
They are version exclusive, and only appear in Pokémon Black version.</description>
<picture>243550.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30494" type="appears in" update="2018-11-11">
<name>Deathmas (Kojirou)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>After finishing a conversation with Giovanni`s secretary, Yamask appeared and was sniffing a tin of Pokémon food that was in Team Rocket`s briefcase. Lighthearted as usual, James quickly offed the Yamask some food which it quickly ate. Fascinated by the Yamask, James asked it if it wished to travel with him which it agreed and captured itself into James` Poké Ball.</description>
<picture>68621.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="70" picture="171604.jpg">Kanai Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="134187" update="2018-10-23">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-08-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
