<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8744" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>16</episodecount>
<startdate>2006-12-23</startdate>
<enddate>2006-12-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Tokyo Loop</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">トーキョー・ループ</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">TOKYO LOOP</title>
</titles>
<creators>
<name id="11207" type="Direction">Kuri Youji</name>
<name id="11205" type="Direction">Furukawa Taku</name>
<name id="25815" type="Direction">Wada Atsushi</name>
<name id="5753" type="Direction">Yamamura Kouji</name>
<name id="37779" type="Direction">Ooyama Kei</name>
<name id="20083" type="Music">Yamamoto Seiichi</name>
<name id="30899" type="Direction">Aihara Nobuhiro</name>
<name id="43399" type="Direction">Tanaami Keiichi</name>
<name id="43790" type="Direction">Shimao Maho</name>
<name id="57892" type="Direction">Murata Tomoyasu</name>
</creators>
<description>Tokyo Strut (Sato Masahiko, Ueta Mio)
Tokyo Trip (Tanaami Keiichi)
Fishing Vine (Seike Mika)
Yuki-chan (Oyama Kei)
Dog &amp; Bone (Shiriagari Kotobuki)
Public Convenience (Tabaimo)
TOKYO (Uda Atsuko)
Black Fish (Aihara Nobuhiro)
Unbalance (Ito Takashi)
Tokyo Girl (Shimao Maho)
Manipulated Man (Wada Atsushi)
Nuance (Murata Tomoyasu)
Hashimoto (Furukawa Taku)
Funkorogashi (Kuri Yoji)
Fig (http://anidb.net/cr5753 [Yamamura Kouji])
12 O`Clock (Iwai Toshio)
Tokyo`s centre for experimental and art cinema, Image Forum, under the guidance of program director Takashi Sawa and coordinator Koyo Yamashita, has a knack for putting together some clever screening packages together for the Image Forum Festival every year. Many of these packages, such as http://anidb.net/a7972 [Thinking and Drawing], make their way into international festivals, and in some cases even onto DVD. Such is the case with the 2006 omnibus Tokyo Loop featuring the work of both established artists like Yoji Kuri, Taku Furukawa, Keiichi Tanaami, Nobuhiro Aihara, as well as exciting younger artists such as Kei Oyama, Mika Seike, Tabaimo, and Tomoyasu Murata.
Tokyo Loop came out of Image Forum`s desire to do something to celebrate the hundredth anniversary of Stuart Blackton`s animation "Humorous Phases of Funny Faces" (1906), considered by many the first publicly screened animated film. Sawa and Yamashita commandeered the help of Furukawa who contributed to the project with a film of his own and helped recruit other independent animation and experimental artists.
The 16 artists were asked to contribute a short film inspired by the city of Tokyo. The films would also be linked by the participation of Seiichi Yamamoto, a well-known musician from Osaka`s underground music scene who composed the score. Yamamoto corresponded with the artists during the production process. He composed the music in advance based upon the sketches and storyboards provided by each animator, then revised them to fit the final edit of the film.
Source: http://nishikataeiga.blogspot.com/2009/09/tokyo-loop.html</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="65">2.93</permanent>
<temporary count="65">4.22</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>74579.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4761</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>326366</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16658</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4542" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-04-25">
<name>no dialogue</name>
<description>The anime either has no spoken dialogue or no dialogue at all.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4664" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-18">
<name>short movie</name>
<description>Typically used when an OVA only has one part and is less than the usual 20 to 25 minutes in length.
So instead of calling it a `short episode`, the `short movie` tag is more appropriate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5529" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-05">
<name>black and white</name>
<description>Some or all of this anime is in black and white, typical of older anime made before ~1960. Some modern anime may intentionally shift to black and white for certain scenes or episodes as an artistic effect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5939" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-09">
<name>CAST MISSING</name>
<description>Important characters are missing, either in-part or entirely. This includes basic entry info (name, gender, picture), appear episode range, seiyuu and/or tags.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5980" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-24">
<name>live-action imagery</name>
<description>This anime incorporates still images and/or video footage of real-world objects and locations into the animation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6399" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-25">
<name>episodic</name>
<description>An episodic anime consists of many successive short arcs that are generally 1-2 episodes in length, with strong plot continuity within each arc but generally little continuity from one arc to the next. For long shows (well upwards of 50 episodes), the episode count constraint is less tight; for example, a show with close to 250 episodes would also be considered episodic if it consisted of a majority of arcs of up to 3 or maybe 4 episodes and possibly also very few slightly longer arcs.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="134369" update="2013-02-17">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2006-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゆきちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yuki-chan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuki-chan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134370" update="2013-02-17">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2006-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アンバランス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unbalance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unbalance</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134371" update="2013-02-17">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2006-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トーキョー・トリップ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tokyo Trip</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokyo Trip</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134372" update="2013-02-16">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2006-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">TOKYO STRUT</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tokyo Strut</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokyo Strut</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134373" update="2013-02-16">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2006-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">tokyo girl</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tokyo Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokyo Girl</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134374" update="2013-02-16">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2006-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">&amp;lt;blink&amp;gt;トウキョウ&amp;lt;/blink&amp;gt;</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tokyo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">&amp;lt;blink&amp;gt;Tokyo&amp;lt;/blink&amp;gt;</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134375" update="2013-02-15">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2006-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">公衆便女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Public Convenience</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koushuubenjo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134376" update="2013-02-15">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2006-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ニュアンス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nuance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nuance</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134377" update="2013-02-15">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2006-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">声が出てきた人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Manipulated Man</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koe ga Detekita Hito</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134378" update="2013-02-15">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2006-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はしもと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hashimoto</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hashimoto</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134379" update="2013-02-15">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2006-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フンコロガシ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Funkorogashi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Funkorogashi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134380" update="2013-02-14">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2006-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">釣り草</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fishing Vine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsurigusa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134381" update="2014-11-13">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2006-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Fig(無花果)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fig</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fig (Ichijiku)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134382" update="2013-02-14">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2006-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">イヌトホネ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dog &amp; Bone</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inu to Hone</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134383" update="2013-02-09">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2006-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Black Fish</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134384" update="2013-02-09">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2006-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">12 O`Clock</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
