<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="876" restricted="true">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>4</episodecount>
<startdate>1992-10-01</startdate>
<enddate>1993-08-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Choujin Densetsu Urotsukidouji: Mirai Hen</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Return of the Overfiend</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Urotsukidoji III - Return of the Overfiend Collection</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">초신전설 우로츠키 동자 미래편</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Urotsukidōji: Powrót Superdemona</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Urotsukidoji 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Urotsukidouji 3</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">超神伝説うろつき童子 未来篇</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Urotsukidoji III: Return of the Overfiend</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Urotsukidōji III - Le retour du démon</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Уроцукидодзи: Тайна сверхдемона</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Urotsukidoji III: Legend of Overfiend</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="877" type="Sequel">Choujin Densetsu Urotsukidouji: Inferno Road</anime>
<anime id="874" type="Prequel">Shin Choujin Densetsu Urotsukidouji Mataiden</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="1229" type="Original Work">Maeda Toshio</name>
<name id="4483" type="Music">Amano Masamichi</name>
<name id="5493" type="Direction">Takayama Hideki</name>
</creators>
<description>Twenty-five years ago, the world was annihilated. With the coming of the Overfiend, God of all Gods, the human, demon, and beast realms collapsed together in chaos. With the promise that he would be born in 100 years to re-create his failed world, the Overfiend settled back to sleep within his mother`s womb.
But something has gone terribly wrong...
Now the Overfiend is born prematurely and awaits the coming of his natural the enemy, the Lord of Chaos. His only hope for survival are Amano Jyaku and his sister Megumi. But destiny has moved in ways that even the Overfiend could never predict, as a new race of half-breed demon beasts has evolved.
As Amano travels to the kingdom of Azuma to investigate the appearance of the Lord of Chaos, he is swept up in the world-conquering schemes of Caesar, Azuma`s dictator.
Against the backdrop of a demon beast slave revolt and the return of the diabolical Munhihausen, only Amano and the demon beast Buju can save the world from another fiery destruction. With the fate of the earth and its inhabitants hanging in the balance, all wait to see what the coming of the Lord of Chaos will bring...</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="223">3.17</permanent>
<temporary count="228">5.44</temporary>
<review count="1">6.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>80331.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13133</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2343</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723</identifier>
<identifier>wgloyb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>162161</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2615" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-25">
<name>18 restricted</name>
<description>This isn`t really an "audience".
While some anime might feature sexual content they still might not be considered pornography. This category is meant only for when the content is clearly *not* intended for minors. The distinction is made by whether the content is sold only to adults.</description>
<picurl>67867.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5939" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-09">
<name>CAST MISSING</name>
<description>Important characters are missing, either in-part or entirely. This includes basic entry info (name, gender, picture), appear episode range, seiyuu and/or tags.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="9097" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>1992-10-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真·超神の誕生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Birth of the True Overfiend</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shin Choujin no Tanjou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9098" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>55</length>
<airdate>1993-01-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シーザーズ·パレスの謎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mystery of Caesar`s Palace</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Caesar`s Palace no Nazo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9099" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1993-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シーザーズ·パレスの崩壊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Collapse of Caesar`s Palace</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Caesar`s Palace no Houkai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9100" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>1993-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">未知への旅立ち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Journey to an Unknown World</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Michi e no Tabidachi</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
