<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8775" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-12-14</startdate>
<enddate>2012-01-17</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Major: World Series</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">メジャーWorld Series</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8161" type="Sequel">Major: Message</anime>
<anime id="7236" type="Prequel">Major (2010)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1"/>
<url>http://mv.avex.jp/major/dvd.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="1163" type="Animation Work">SynergySP</name>
<name id="1649" type="Character Design">Oonuki Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="1573" type="Music">Nakagawa Koutarou</name>
<name id="2841" type="Work">Shogakukan-Shueisha Productions</name>
<name id="4412" type="Original Work">Mitsuda Takuya</name>
<name id="7764" type="Direction">Fukushima Toshinori</name>
<name id="1649" type="Chief Animation Direction">Oonuki Ken`ichi</name>
</creators>
<description>"Truly the last" original video anime project of Mitsuda Takuya`s Major baseball manga. The OVA project adapted the thus-far-unanimated World Series arc and the story`s illusive final matchup, while the new book lets fans see the last pitch in the manga. The project gives us the return of the "Golden Battery" in America.
Note: While originally released together with the manga books, both episodes also received a stand-alone release on 05.10.2012.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="516">8.27</permanent>
<temporary count="517">7.91</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>78187.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13860</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11917</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://mv.avex.jp/major/dvd.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>343673</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14267</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="28" parentid="2881" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-16">
<name>baseball</name>
<description>Baseball is like a complicated version of Rounders. It involves hitting a ball with a stick, then running around several bases placed in the form of a diamond on a field. Big in the US, and also in Japan.</description>
<picurl>29801.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1253" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-12-08">
<name>ambitious</name>
<description>having a strong desire for success or achievement; wanting power, money, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2378" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-02">
<name>hard-working</name>
<description>Describes someone, who is constantly, regularly, or habitually active or occupied.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2384" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-22">
<name>prodigy</name>
<description>Character is very good at everything he/she does.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2812" parentid="2832" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>United States</name>
<description>The United States of America (commonly referred to as the United States, the U.S., the USA, or America) is a federal constitutional republic comprising fifty states and a federal district. The country is situated mostly in central North America, where its forty-eight contiguous states and Washington, D.C., the capital district, lie between the Pacific and Atlantic Oceans, bordered by Canada to the north and Mexico to the south. The state of Alaska is in the north-west of the continent, with Canada to the east and Russia to the west across the Bering Strait. The state of Hawaii is an archipelago in the mid-Pacific. The country also possesses several territories in the Caribbean and Pacific.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>45504.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2832" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Americas</name>
<description>The Americas, also collectively called America, encompass the totality of the continents of North America and South America. Together they make up most of Earth`s western hemisphere and comprise the New World.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192247.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3831" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-13">
<name>training</name>
<description>Training is extensive, serious practising a person undergoes in order to develop skills and abilities, such as handling weapons, playing instruments, playing sports, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4198" parentid="5604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-14">
<name>hard work and guts</name>
<description>One of the character`s motto in the anime. Because there is nothing that cannot be achieved by hard work and guts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5805" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-06-11">
<name>post-credits scene</name>
<description>A little bit of the story is found after the credit titles. A little bonus for those patient enough!
This applies regardless of if the credits play over an ED sequence, or over the "regular episode" that continues to air into the credits.
A sequence at the end of an episode, showing what will happen in the next episode, is NOT a post-credits scene; that is a preview.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2065" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-10">
<rating votes="19">5.81</rating>
<name>Honda Gorou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16885.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3794" picture="38865.jpg">Kumai Motoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2067" type="main character in" update="2010-03-08">
<rating votes="242">8.03</rating>
<name>Shigeno Gorou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The story`s main character, Goro Honda is a young talented baseball player. His love of the game stems from his father who played for the Yokohama Marine Stars. Wanting nothing more than to follow in his father`s footsteps, he strives to become a professional ball player. Thriving on the challenge of the mound, he puts everything into the competition. He makes friends easily, as people are drawn to his personality and his excitement of the game. After Momoko and Hideki married his name was changed to Goro Shigeno. He initially pitched right handed, but blew out his shoulder in senior little league. In junior high school and high school, he pitches left, but continues to bat right. While he never made it to Koshien, his excellent match against the Kaido High School earned him the attention of many professional baseball team`s scouts. However, he went to America and joined a Triple A team, the Memphis Bats. During the Baseball World Cup, he replaced the injured pitcher Noro, and played as an excellent closer. He used to only use the pitch gyroballs ("rising fastball"), though beginning with the Baseball World Cup, he has successfully added gyrofork ("forkball") to his repertoire.</description>
<picture>16889.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="143" picture="23260.jpg">Morikubo Shoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2072" type="main character in" update="2009-01-09">
<rating votes="99">8.32</rating>
<name>Shigeno Momoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16898.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="140" picture="170306.jpg">Noda Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2074" type="main character in" update="2009-01-09">
<rating votes="44">2.91</rating>
<name>Satou Toshiya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16901.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="138" picture="23200.jpg">Morita Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2077" type="main character in" update="2009-01-10">
<rating votes="34">6.46</rating>
<name>Shigeno Hideki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2380.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="144" picture="16904.jpg">Sakuya Shunsuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2107" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-10">
<rating votes="49">9.07</rating>
<name>Joe Gibson</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16938.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="156" picture="227713.jpg">Ochiai Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9632" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-19">
<rating votes="1">7.25</rating>
<name>Satou Miho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2336.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13071" type="main character in" update="2014-04-09">
<rating votes="17">3.25</rating>
<name>Shimizu Taiga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Brother to Kaoru Shimizu. First seen back in Season 1 where he asked his sister if baseball was fun? Returned again in Season 3 as a new member of Seishuu Baseball Team where he played as a shortstop. With his excellent skill and speed, he helped Goro in challenging Kaido. Besides that, he also helped to take over the mound when Goro was injured by Egashira during their practice game with Kaido. Later on he became the captain of the Seishuu Baseball Team to challenge Kaido once again with his new teammates.</description>
<picture>153313.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13087" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-08">
<rating votes="9">7.99</rating>
<name>Mayumura Ken</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Introduced in season 2, he is initially asked to teach Goro a lesson by Kaido`s recruiter for rejecting Kaido during a middle school game between Kaido Unified, and East Mifune. This beating makes him the instant rival of Goro, even though he admires him for his confidence and straight forward attitude. His personality is very direct and to the point, often times coming off as cold. He appears to be in complete control of his emotions at all times, including when facing established and more experienced players. His pre-game ritual of sitting in a bathroom stall while listening to music is seen by others as getting him in the right frame of mind to pitch, but in actuality he does it because he is anxious and helps him focus his anxiety. His goals are to achieve all possible individual achievements in Japanese Baseball before moving onto the Majors.</description>
<picture>38915.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="68" picture="16675.jpg">Yasumura Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14043" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-27">
<rating votes="6">8.74</rating>
<name>Sanders</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>82311.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="67" picture="25195.jpg">Ishii Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15306" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-25">
<rating votes="14">4.37</rating>
<name>Joe Gibson Junior</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The son of Joe Gibson, Junior is of the same age as Goro. When Junior`s parents divorced because his mother could not stand life in Japan, whereas Gibson wanted to remain in Japan pitching until he had found out how to make up for killing Honda, Junior stayed with his father in Japan. When his mother and sister died in a traffic accident in America, Junior became resentful towards his father and the deceased Honda. His motivation to play baseball was fueled by the desire to defeat his father. He is an extremely talented batter, being able to bat both left and right as a switch hitter. He played for the AAA Oklahoma Falcons, the MLB team Texas Raiders, as well as the USA Team during the Baseball World Cup. He typically fields the third base.</description>
<picture>43631.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25881" type="main character in" update="2018-08-27">
<rating votes="5">8.44</rating>
<name>Shigeno Kaoru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222863.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="137" picture="214428.jpg">Sasamoto Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44104" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-09">
<rating votes="4">8.54</rating>
<name>Jeff Keane</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jeff Keane is a catcher who is recruited into the "Memphis Bats" during the Minor League season. He is known as a golden rookie due to his success and potential. His baseball style is reliant on player stats and exploiting their weaknesses.
At first, he doesn`t get along with his team members due to his anti social personality and overtaking Sander`s position as catcher, especially with Goro. However, as the team gets used to him, they start to appreciate his ability to play baseball as he increases the amount of games they win. As soon as he realizes that Goro is a clutch pitcher, he starts to rely on his ability to pitch better when the situation is more intense.</description>
<picture>153332.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44105" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-17">
<name>Kellogg</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154034.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17816" picture="47549.jpg">Katou Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44106" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-17">
<name>Dunston</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154035.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1683" picture="223030.jpg">Kanemitsu Nobuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44107" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-17">
<name>Butler</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154036.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2135" picture="66343.jpg">Nakakuni Takurou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44108" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-09">
<name>Mike Murdoch</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153331.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3161" picture="69050.jpg">Yamanoi Jin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44109" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-20">
<name>Roy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154316.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44110" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-09">
<name>Richard Watts</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153330.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2016" picture="240331.jpg">Yanaka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44111" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-17">
<name>Saotome Taizou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154037.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44112" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<name>Shimizu Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154318.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="264" picture="228626.jpg">Ogata Mitsuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44113" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-05-01">
<name>Mayumura Shizuka</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44116" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<name>Toshiya no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154315.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="295" picture="25758.jpg">Shinohara Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44117" type="appears in" update="2014-04-19">
<name>Toshiya no Sofu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154309.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4690" picture="246059.jpg">Itou Kazuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44118" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<name>Shimizu Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154317.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3954" picture="173079.jpg">Motoi Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="135219" update="2012-09-02">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135220" update="2012-09-02">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-01-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
