<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="88" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>1999-10-05</startdate>
<enddate>2000-04-04</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Koutetsu Tenshi Kurumi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">KTK</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">SAK1</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">SAK</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">kurumi tv</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Kurumi</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">鋼鉄天使くるみ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Steel Angel Kurumi</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Kurumi, l`ange d`acier</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Steel Angel Kurumi</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1182" type="Sequel">Koutetsu Tenshi Kurumi Encore</anime>
<anime id="89" type="Alternative Setting">Koutetsu Tenshi Kurumi 2-shiki</anime>
<anime id="38" type="Alternative Setting">Koutetsu Tenshi Kurumi Zero</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="109" approval="16" total="18">Mahoromatic: Automatic Maiden</anime>
<anime id="526" approval="4" total="4">Bannou Bunka Nekomusume (1998)</anime>
<anime id="344" approval="2" total="2">Saber Marionette J</anime>
<anime id="4529" approval="1" total="4">Mamoru-kun ni Megami no Shukufuku o!</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20110808221434/http://www.ponycanyon.co.jp/pc-moe/kurumi/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="727" type="Animation Work">OLM</name>
<name id="2256" type="Character Design">Chiba Yuriko</name>
<name id="3760" type="Series Composition">Arakawa Naruhisa</name>
<name id="6517" type="Original Work">Kaishaku</name>
<name id="3840" type="Direction">Takahashi Naohito</name>
<name id="2256" type="Chief Animation Direction">Chiba Yuriko</name>
<name id="3174" type="Music">Sahashi Toshihiko</name>
</creators>
<description>In the Taishou Roman period, a Steel Angel is an android that has an Angel Heart created by powerful magic. In other words a Steel Angel is a creature of both science and magic.
http://anidb.net/ch4792 [Kurumi] is the first Steel Angel, and she is awakened when http://anidb.net/ch4791 [Nakahito] kisses her. Nakahito is the second child of Onmyoudou Shuke (a house of a Japanese Yin and Yang spiritual leader). Kurumi has so much affection for him that she calls him "my master", and only follows his orders. Now, Nakahito, a boy with a gentle heart, and Kurumi, an android with an Angel Heart and incredible power, join forces. And when the second Steel Angel http://anidb.net/ch4793 [Saki], the third Steel Angel http://anidb.net/ch4794 [Karinka] appear, things really start to mix up...
Note: Taishou is the Japanese historical period dating from July 30 1912 to December 25 1926.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1116">4.71</permanent>
<temporary count="1126">6.82</temporary>
<review count="3">6.83</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221935.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>326</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>554</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>528</identifier>
<identifier>pmoweo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20110808221434/http://www.ponycanyon.co.jp/pc-moe/kurumi/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Steel_Angel_Kurumi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>鋼鉄天使くるみ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>307</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>90290</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3210</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6914</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1894" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-04">
<name>shota</name>
<description>Shotacon, sometimes shortened to shota, is a Japanese slang portmanteau of the phrase Shoutarou complex and describes an attraction to young boys, or an individual with such an attraction. Outside Japan, the term is less common and most often refers to a genre of manga and anime wherein pre-pubescent or pubescent male characters are depicted in a suggestive or erotic manner.
In a general sense, this is the same as http://anidb.net/t2566 [loli], just replace young girls with young boys.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>35399.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2072" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>maid</name>
<description>A maid is a female employed in domestic service. They usually wear uniforms. Since their nature is to be obedient and serve their goshujin-sama (master), they are one of the most desired types of women in Japan, a dream of every Japanese man, particularly http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku]. Often seen in so-called Maid Cafes in Akihabara, where male customers can for a little time enjoy the feeling of being served by a woman. The male gender opposite is the butler.</description>
<picurl>4954.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2346" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-14">
<name>angel</name>
<description>An angel is a supernatural being, said to be the messenger of God. They are often depicted as human beings with a pair of white feathered wings and sometimes with a halo.
In contrast, a fallen angel who has turned evil will be depicted with black wings.</description>
<picurl>35521.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3898" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-11">
<name>science and magic coexist</name>
<description>In this anime science and magic do not exclude each other. Magic here is actually very advanced, artefact- and/or ritual-based science.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5742" parentid="2641" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-19">
<name>Taishou period</name>
<description>A period in the history of Japan dating from July 30, 1912 to December 25, 1926, coinciding with the reign of the Emperor Taishou.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6494" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>half-length episodes</name>
<description>Half-length episodes are regular episodes that are somewhat shorter than the standard length. This includes episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length; shows with episodes up to and including 10 minutes are http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes] instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="4791" type="main character in" update="2009-03-11">
<rating votes="6">1.00</rating>
<name>Kagura Nakahito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The primary male protagonist for the show, Nakahito unwittingly becomes the master of Steel Angel Kurumi when he accidentally awakens her with a kiss. Hesitant and unsure of himself, he teaches Kurumi as much as he can while slowly falling in love with the hyperactive girl.</description>
<picture>20940.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4792" type="main character in" update="2009-03-11">
<rating votes="24">6.10</rating>
<name>Kurumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Steel Angel built by Dr. Ayanokouji and equipped with a Mark II Heart, she is awakened by Nakahito`s kiss in the first episode and immediately becomes possessive of him while simultaneously pledging her love and service to him. The main female lead and an incredibly wild individual, she is overwhelmingly manic when it comes to Nakahito (whom she calls "Master"). Whenever her antics become too much, one word from her master will make her stop (usually). Very protective of her master and her sisters, she will stop at nothing to ensure their safety. She is impossibly strong and rather handily defeats all her opponents due to her Mark II Heart.</description>
<picture>20938.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="348" picture="17186.jpg">Enomoto Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4793" type="main character in" update="2009-03-11">
<rating votes="18">6.65</rating>
<name>Saki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Another Steel Angel built by Dr. Ayanokouji, Saki was activated by Dr. Amagi with Dr. Brandow`s help, and given orders to destroy Kurumi and seize her Mark II Heart. Amagi and the General decide to use the largest of the seized Angel Hearts to give Saki as much power as possible.</description>
<picture>20939.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4794" type="main character in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="8">4.16</rating>
<name>Karinka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The third Steel Angel built on the design by Dr Ayanakouji, she was activated by the Academy to destroy Kurumi. She is very strong due to being installed with two Angel Hearts instead of one (however this also means she is exempted from following the orders of Dr. Walski, her creator). She is very temperamental, devious, and has occasionally shown traits of sadism (shown explicitly during the time she held Saki hostage). She later joins Nakahito and the group, originally to figure out Kurumi`s power, but she eventually develops a crush on Nakahito.</description>
<picture>21016.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="634" picture="18161.jpg">Kurata Masayo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55605" type="appears in" update="2014-04-08">
<rating votes="1">5.02</rating>
<name>Koganei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153155.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="158" picture="38198.jpg">Neya Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66366" type="appears in" update="2014-04-08">
<name>Ayanokouji Hakase</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The scientist who built the three Steel Angels. He came to the area where Nakahito lives to find a mystic to activate Kurumi. He has connections to the mysterious Academy.</description>
<picture>153154.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3136" picture="24121.jpg">Suzuoki Hirotaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66367" type="appears in" update="2014-04-08">
<rating votes="8">5.94</rating>
<name>Amagi Hakase</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153156.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="588" picture="41015.jpg">Orikasa Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66369" type="appears in" update="2014-04-08">
<rating votes="2">2.55</rating>
<name>Kaga</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaga is the unofficial leader and spokesman of the Steel Angels working for the Academy. She is sent, along with Kaori and Tsunami, to destroy Kurumi and retrieve the Mark II Angel Heart. Kaga has a set of boomerang-like weapons that she can throw with deadly accuracy. She believes that Kurumi and her Mark II Heart are dangerous and should not be allowed to continue functioning.
There is evidence that Kaga is not truly a bad person, since she instructs Nakahito to stay back during her fight with Kurumi so he won`t get hurt.</description>
<picture>153157.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16799" picture="186162.jpg">Tezuka Chiharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66370" type="appears in" update="2014-04-08">
<rating votes="2">3.80</rating>
<name>Kaori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the three Steel Angels sent by the Academy to destroy Kurumi. Kaori first shows up in disguise, posing as a physician so she can get data on Kurumi`s Mark II Heart. In battle, she uses a scythe-like weapon.</description>
<picture>153158.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="319" picture="228606.jpg">Okamura Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66371" type="appears in" update="2014-04-08">
<name>Shougun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The commander of the Japanese Army. The General seeks to recapture Dr. Ayanokoji so he can help them produce new secret weapons. When this fails, he relieves Dr. Amagi so that she can go searching for Dr. Ayanokoji`s lab. He also sends the spies Kagonei and Kichijoji to follow and protect the doctor and the others. The General also apparently has a preference for younger girls, such as Saki and Karinka.
The General`s personality is stereotypical of a soldier: rigid, efficient, and orderly. However, he admits to having not always been that way.</description>
<picture>153159.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2366" picture="203225.jpg">Ooki Tamio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66372" type="appears in" update="2014-04-08">
<rating votes="2">2.55</rating>
<name>Tsunami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the three Steel Angels who are sent by the Academy to destroy Kurumi. She delays the group on their way to Izumo by placing a large boulder on the railroad tracks, which was so heavy, only Kurumi and Saki can move it. In battle, she uses a whip as a weapon.</description>
<picture>153160.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66373" type="appears in" update="2014-04-08">
<rating votes="1">5.02</rating>
<name>Kichijouji</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kichijouji is one of two spies the General sends to tail Dr. Amagi and the others as they make their way to Izumo. She is a more serious pesronality than her partner, Koganei, with whom she often quarrels. Because of her spy training, she is able make a deadly weapon of a simple playing card. She also apparently has an attraction to Dr. Amagi.</description>
<picture>153161.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="563" picture="73156.jpg">Kawakami Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="1940" update="2018-02-19">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>1999-12-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">迎えに来たんだ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Triple Threat</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je viens vous chercher</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mukae ni Kitanda</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1941" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>1999-11-02</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妹ができたですぅ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Warm Saki</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">J`ai une petite sœur !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Imouto ga Dekita Desuu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1942" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2000-02-29</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">突入! アカデミー基地</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Storming The Base</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Incursion à l`Academie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Totsunyuu! Academy Kichi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1943" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>1999-10-26</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">嫌いにならないでです!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Hate Me</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ne me haïssez pas !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kirai ni Naranaide Desu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1944" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2000-02-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そんなのうそだ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lies</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ce ne sont que des mensonges !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sonna no Uso Da!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1945" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2000-04-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">KissからはじまるMiracle</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kiss</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Est-ce la fin ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiss kara Hajimaru Miracle</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1946" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>1999-10-19</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新たなる天使・サキ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cold Saki</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Saki, nouvel Ange d`acier</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aratanaru Tenshi Saki!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1947" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2000-02-15</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">出雲に着いたですぅ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mikhail</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Nous voilà à Izumo !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Izumo no Tsuita Desuu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1948" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2000-03-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">罪と罰</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crime And Punishment</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Crimes et châtiments</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsumi to Batsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1949" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>1999-10-12</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ご主人様は一人ですぅ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A One-Master Kinda Gal</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Maître est mon seul maître</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Goshujin-sama wa Hitori Desuu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1950" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2000-02-08</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">仲人最大の危機!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Our Lips Are Sealed</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La plus grave crise de Nakahito !?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nakahito Saidai no Kiki!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1951" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2000-03-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カオスエンゼル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hell`s Angel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`ange du chaos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chaos Angel</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1952" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>1999-10-05</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">くるみ大地に立つですぅ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Activation</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Kurumi entre en scène</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kurumi Daichi ni Tatsu Desuu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1953" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2000-02-01</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">わかったよお姉ちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dark Wings</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">J`ai compris grande sœur !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakatta yo Onee-chan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1954" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2000-03-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天使が消えた日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">When Angels Die</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le jour où l`ange s`est éteint</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenshi ga Kieta Hi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1955" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2000-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">諦めないもん!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Not Fair</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je n`abandonnerai pas !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akiramenai mon!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1956" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2000-03-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">究極の超鋼鉄天使</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Avenging Angel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Super Ange d`Acier</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyuukyoku no Chou Koutetsu Tenshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1957" update="2018-02-19">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>1999-12-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふたりで花火ですぅ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fireworks</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Des feux d`artifice tous les deux !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari de Hanabi Desuu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1958" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2000-01-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">また妹ができたですぅ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Second Sister</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">J`ai une nouvelle petite sœur !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mata Imouto ga Dekita Desuu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1959" update="2018-02-19">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>1999-11-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天城礼子二十三歳?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tsunami</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Reiko Amagi, 23 ans ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Amagi Reiko Nijuusansai?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1960" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2000-01-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カリンカだよ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Karinka</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">C`est Karinka !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Karinka Da yo!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1961" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>1999-11-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そこはダメですぅ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Playing Doctor</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ah non, pas là !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soko wa Dame Desuu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1962" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2000-01-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そうだ! 八つ橋を...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cinnamon Cookies</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Oui ! Des yatsuhashi !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sou Da! Yatsuhashi o...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1963" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>1999-11-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛姉妹</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love Shack</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sœurs d`amour</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai Shimai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14738" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Text Intro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84309" update="2007-10-12">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121078" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
