<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8808" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-03-31</startdate>
<enddate>2013-06-16</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Date a Live</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Рандеву с жизнью</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Среща на живо</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">デート・ア・ライブ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Date a Live</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">约会大作战</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9734" type="Sequel">Date a Live: Date to Date</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="7568" approval="48" total="73">Kami nomi zo Shiru Sekai</anime>
<anime id="3408" approval="6" total="16">Shakugan no Shana</anime>
<anime id="9905" approval="2" total="11">Aoki Hagane no Arpeggio: Ars Nova</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="508247">HAREM! It can be very absurd at times but if you can suspend belief (to a great extent) and like harems you can enjoy it , the music deserves a special mention .</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="421763">I wasn`t really expecting anything from this one, given the "premise" as described. But surprises do occur, and I found the overall plot and few of the characters to be quite likable.

Thus recommend for those, who do not explicitly hate "harem" animes, and want them with a little more "something" - like, a decent plot, for example. Also, the soundtrack is noteworthy.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="387237">Probably not a good idea to take the other recommendations listed to heart. They were all completely off for me. This anime is definitely in my top ten, if not top five, but time will have to tell!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://date-a-live-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="2995" type="Animation Work">AIC Plus+</name>
<name id="128" type="Character Design">Ishino Satoshi</name>
<name id="4637" type="Series Composition">Shirane Hideki</name>
<name id="1539" type="Direction">Motonaga Keitarou</name>
<name id="23325" type="Music">Sakabe Gou</name>
<name id="34043" type="Original Work">Tachibana Koushi</name>
<name id="10780" type="Effects Direction">Sawada Jouji</name>
<name id="11842" type="Chief Animation Direction">Furukawa Hideki</name>
<name id="128" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ishino Satoshi</name>
<name id="2382" type="Chief Animation Direction">Morishima Noriko</name>
<name id="16338" type="Chief Animation Direction">Watanabe Motoko</name>
<name id="34043" type="Original Plan">Tachibana Koushi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the light novel series written by http://anidb.net/cr34043 [Tachibana Koushi] and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr34044 [Tsunako].
"30 years ago a large Spacequake[i] occurred in Eurasia. 150 million people died and human life and infrastructure was laid to waste.
Spacequakes: A destructive phenomenon of unknown origin. Like the name says, it is a void which destroys everything in and around it. An unexplainable disaster. It has been thirty years after the apocalyptic Spacequake, in the six months that followed smaller scale Spacequakes occurred all over the planet. Japan, the place where I live, also faces similar occurrences. It is known as the [/i]South Kanto Void Zone. Twenty five years had passed without anything happening. But suddenly, five years ago, it started again, around the Tenguushi City area. This phenomenon increased by the day, and these occurrences seem to be centred around Japan." — Itsuka Shidou
As another Spacequake is about to hit the town, http://anidb.net/ch47638 [Itsuka Shidou] and his class run for the shelters. Then he remembers how insistent his sister http://anidb.net/ch47639 [Kotori] was about their meal at a family restaurant. He rushes back out into the open, when locating her GPS signal at said restaurant, frantically rushing to save her. When a Spacequake hits nearby, Shidou discovers a non-human girl, a Spirit named http://anidb.net/ch47641 [Yatogami Tooka], at the epicentre of the quake. Tooka asks him if he is also here to kill her. Still confused, several girls in combat suits, the Anti-Spirits Team (AST), among them his genius of a classmate http://anidb.net/ch49435 [Tobiichi Origami], attack Tooka. Shidou loses consciousness, awakening in sickbay, on board the Fraxinus, a floating ship located 15,000 metres above Tenguushi City.
The commander of this ship and the ongoing operation is none other than Shidou`s sister Kotori! As she explains, when the Spirits drop down to Earth, this usually ends in a Spacequake occurrence. There are only two ways to stop a Spirit: one is to go on the offensive and kill it (rarely succeeds), the other, of all things, is to go on a date with the Spirit girl... and that will be Shidou`s responsibility!
— written by foo2
Note: The series had a stream on Niconico prior to airing on TV channels.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="3180">4.63</permanent>
<temporary count="3203">6.63</temporary>
<review count="4">4.49</review>
</ratings>
<picture>129405.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14953</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15583</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5175</identifier>
<identifier>hdtarq</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://date-a-live-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Date_A_Live</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>デート・ア・ライブ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2910</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>343805</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15829</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>date-a-live</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="859" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-04-22">
<name>hand puppet</name>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1136" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-18">
<name>transfer student</name>
<description>A transfer student is a student who changes from one institution or course to another at the same level. Their arrival, when not at the beginning of the school year, tends to cause a stir.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1446" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-15">
<name>energetic</name>
<description>An energetic character, often also called a genki character, shows great, often excessive levels of activity or vitality, and seems to always be doing everything extra fast. Genki characters are often slightly, or sometimes very, eccentric, and are filled with confidence and determination, regardless of whether they are competent or not; in fact, they often have little to no actual competence at whatever they generally do. Although genki characters are usually played exclusively for comedy effect, sometimes they may slow down for a serious or introspective moment. The most common genki character archetype is the genki schoolgirl, who will often be late to school and run with a toast in her mouth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2396" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-08">
<name>swimsuit</name>
<description>A swimsuit is one of several kinds of garments designed to be worn by people engaging in water-based activities or sports or during certain activities under sunlight. Most kinds of swimsuit reveal a large portion of the body surface area, but exceptions exist. The more revealing kinds may also be worn as undergarment in sports that require wetsuits, or when there is a need to display the body, as in the case of beauty pageants or bodybuilding contests.
There is a very wide range of styles of modern swimsuits, which vary in relation to body coverage and materials. The choice of style of swimsuit is dependent on current fashions, community standards of modesty, and plain personal preference. Swimsuits for men usually expose the chest, while those for women do not usually do so; however, many women prefer to engage in water or sun activities with their torso uncovered, in a practice commonly described as toplessness or topfreedom. Since the early twentieth century a naturist movement has developed in western countries that seeks a return to non-sexual nakedness when swimming and during other appropriate activities; in some places around the world, nude beaches have been set aside for people who choose to engage in normal beach activities in the nude, and such beaches may or may not enforce nudity onto their goers.
In anime, it is common for at least one episode to feature the characters in swimsuits, usually as an excuse for gratuitous fanservice; when that happens, the episode is usually labeled a pool or beach episode, after the place the characters went to. Swimsuits, and in particular one-piece swimsuits, are a very common fetish in Japan; while the reason for that is uncertain, a common folk explanation is the fact that boys throughout their entire adolescence are commonly exposed to their female classmates wearing them, in what might be called an experiment in sexual discovery waiting to happen.</description>
<picurl>149786.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2467" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-22">
<name>sword</name>
<description>A sword is a long, edged piece of metal, used as a cutting, thrusting, and clubbing weapon in many civilizations throughout the world. Before firearms became commonplace, and fast enough to render other weapons pointless in the battlefield, they were the main kind of weapon for war and duels alike. A sword fundamentally consists of a blade and a hilt, typically with one or two edges for striking and cutting, and a point for thrusting. That aside, however, they may come in all sorts of designs: the medieval European swords used to be big, heavy weapons that did not actually cut but instead broke the enemy`s bones under their armor; conversely, the Chinese jian sword (called "ken" in Japanese) attempted to exploit the armor`s joints and perforate the enemy`s flesh in those places, but was useless against the armor itself, and did not take the strikes, preferring to redirect them, to this day being considered a highly "circular" weapon and associated to taijiquan; on the other hand, the Japanese katana was a balanced all-purposes weapon that could be used even in an axe-like way, but which a master swordsman could use in many other, more elaborate manners.</description>
<picurl>127113.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2781" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>first kiss</name>
<description>The first kiss plays a role in this anime. Especially for the female cast this can be quite an important moment, so that stealing ones first kiss is serious for them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2784" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>sudden girlfriend appearance</name>
<description>Sudden Girlfriend Appearance anime involve a sudden change in the main character`s life where (s)he suddenly gets confronted with an individual (s)he`s sexually attracted to, the two of them inevitably becoming a couple.</description>
<picurl>210066.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2829" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-21">
<name>shower scene</name>
<description>The anime contains a shower scene, obligatory for ecchi anime. The person under the shower will most likely be female — providing "fanservice".</description>
<picurl>208635.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2830" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>furo scene</name>
<description>Furo (polite: Ofuro) is Japanese for bath, specifically a type of bath which originated as a short, steep-sided wooden bathtub. Baths of this type are found all over Japan in houses, apartments and traditional Japanese inns (Ryokans).
Furo are part of the Japanese ritual of bathing, not used for washing but for relaxing and warming oneself. Washing is carried out separately outside the furo, and only when completely clean does the bather enter the water. Generally Japanese bathrooms are small, so the bathroom is set up much like a walk-in shower area but containing the ofuro.
The cheapest and shortest way to show naked skin on TV, at least as much as allowed. It usually only takes up few minutes at most and as such it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales while still maintaining a "non-filler" episode.
Compare to the big brothers http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode] and http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160785.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3101" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-22">
<name>lottery wheel</name>
<description>One of the protagonists plays the lottery wheel in some shopping mall and — as fate will have it — wins a prize, e.g. a visit to the local hot springs or water park. Thus adding an unexpected plot twist to the story (and some ecchi potential).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3277" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-28">
<name>bendy lasers</name>
<description>Lasers — of all things — bend at strange angles, are profusely in effect in this anime. Usually seen in a space setting, as part of a weapon system on spaceships.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3444" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>hot springs visit</name>
<description>An onsen is a term for hot springs in the Japanese language, though the term is often used to describe the bathing facilities and inns around the hot springs. Often the cast of a show somehow ends up going to an onsen because of various reasons, such as winning a lottery ticket. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters nude and raise the DVD sales.
Another cheap variant is the http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160784.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3702" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-12">
<name>swimsuit shopping</name>
<description>To provide additional, potentially ecchi moments, the usually female character(s) go shopping for a new, often quite revealing, swimsuit — as preparation for an upcoming pool or beach episode.</description>
<picurl>166999.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4389" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>amusement park visit</name>
<description>Plot device: All or part of the cast visit an amusement park. 
Added to show the characters in a more leisurely environment (i.e. other than school or at home). Often used in school settings to "develop" and "further" the relations between the male and female leads in this anime. Can also set the stage for comedic misunderstandings, or private moments with possibly ecchi undertones. 
Furthermore, it gives the anime creators a chance to show off their characters in non-uniforms (e.g. school uniforms). Also see "pool episode".</description>
<picurl>160897.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4481" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>protection complex</name>
<description>A character has a protection complex if the character is overly protective of other characters, beyond what would be considered a "normal" or "expected" duty of care.
The magnitude of overprotection can vary. It can be as low as constantly nagging someone to "stay safe". It can be as extreme as the protector making it their mission in life to protect the other character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4496" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-02">
<name>public aquarium</name>
<description>A public aquarium is the aquatic counterpart of a zoo, housing living aquatic species for viewing. Most public aquariums feature tanks larger than those kept by home aquarists, as well as smaller tanks. Since the first public aquariums were built in the mid-19th century, they have become popular and their numbers have increased. Most modern accredited aquariums stress conservation issues and educating the public.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>167001.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4564" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-06-01">
<name>spirits</name>
<description>Spirits will appear throughout this anime. These will often be depicted as small orbs of glowing light, or transparent images of the deceased.
Not to be mistaken with "I see dead people", these spirits will usually appear at the location of their departure when the characters have gotten close to the truth surrounding their death. Or as plot element, when a spirit will often stay close to a character as a sort of "Guardian Angel". Although they are never actually seen, their presence is sometimes felt.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5805" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-06-11">
<name>post-credits scene</name>
<description>A little bit of the story is found after the credit titles. A little bonus for those patient enough!
This applies regardless of if the credits play over an ED sequence, or over the "regular episode" that continues to air into the credits.
A sequence at the end of an episode, showing what will happen in the next episode, is NOT a post-credits scene; that is a preview.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6039" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-18">
<name>piggyback ride</name>
<description>One of the protagonists (usually male) gives another character (usually female) a ride on the back. Can be interpreted as a sign of closeness or endearment in a romance setting.
Reasons: The female character is exhausted from previous running, or has a fit of anaemia, or hurt herself and no longer can walk.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6046" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>pool episode</name>
<description>An episode playing at the pool, mostly in school, sometimes outside of it when the cast does not have a chance for a beach episode.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version of the http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode].
Other variants are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160904.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6137" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-09">
<name>catchphrase</name>
<description>A catchphrase is a sound, word or phrase commonly used by a person. That may be simply out of habit, or in an attempt to deliver some form of image, like that of cuteness. In fiction, characters often use catchphrases as a way to deliver specific personality traits. Examples include Otohime Mutsumi`s "ara ara" in Love Hina, Yang Wenli`s "yare yare" in Legend of the Galactic Heroes, Misuzu`s "gao" in AIR, Sakura`s "hoe" in Card Captor Sakura, Suiseiseki`s "desu" in Rozen Maiden, and Ayu`s "uguu" in Kanon (as well as several other characters in the same show).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="47638" type="main character in" update="2014-11-22">
<rating votes="99">3.10</rating>
<name>Itsuka Shidou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The protagonist of the story, he possesses a strange power that allows him to seal the powers of a Spirit in his body with a kiss; however, the seal will only work if the Spirit holds enough trust or affection toward him to allow it. This ability to seal and contain 99% of a spirit`s power might have been given to him by Phantom soon after it turned Kotori into the spirit Efreet. After sealing a Spirit`s powers, there will be an invisible link connecting him and the Spirit, through which a portion of the sealed power will flow back to the Spirit if said Spirit`s mental state becomes unstable, and back to Shidou once the Spirit`s mental state restabilizes. So the more angry/distraught/unhappy a spirit is the more power she takes back temporarily while conversely the happier/content/joyful a spirit the more her power level doesn`t rise from the minimum level of 1%.
Abandoned by his birth mother, he lives with his foster sister Kotori. He was in despair for a time after being abandoned and subsequently adopted, which made him sensitive to similar feelings from others and wanting to bring them out of it, fuelling his desire to save the Spirits. His real younger sister is Takamiya Mana.</description>
<picture>152551.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10776" picture="77627.jpg">Shimazaki Nobunaga</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47639" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-23">
<rating votes="157">6.50</rating>
<name>Itsuka Kotori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152554.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47640" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-21">
<rating votes="108">6.96</rating>
<name>Himekawa Yoshino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152556.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5886" picture="30429.jpg">Nomizu Iori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47641" type="main character in" update="2014-04-21">
<rating votes="91">6.65</rating>
<name>Yatogami Tooka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152553.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47642" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-05">
<rating votes="431">8.49</rating>
<name>Tokisaki Kurumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152557.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="359" picture="65537.jpg">Sanada Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47643" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-30">
<rating votes="91">6.45</rating>
<name>Murasame Reine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152558.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="424" picture="224027.jpg">Endou Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47644" type="main character in" update="2014-03-31">
<rating votes="242">6.89</rating>
<name>Tobiichi Origami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152555.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9512" picture="35180.jpg">Togashi Misuzu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48985" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-23">
<rating votes="35">5.05</rating>
<name>Okamine Tamae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44566.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24067" picture="67787.jpg">Sadohara Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48986" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-03-31">
<rating votes="55">4.61</rating>
<name>Takamiya Mana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152559.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27341" picture="74876.jpg">Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49257" type="main character in" update="2014-04-21">
<rating votes="172">6.38</rating>
<name>Yatogami Tooka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152552.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49435" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-21">
<rating votes="71">6.92</rating>
<name>Tobiichi Origami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44235.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9512" picture="35180.jpg">Togashi Misuzu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51321" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-23">
<rating votes="24">2.74</rating>
<name>Tonomachi Hiroto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138938.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2002" picture="21307.jpg">Katsu Anri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51322" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-11">
<rating votes="39">5.31</rating>
<name>Kannazuki Kyouhei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kyouhei is the vice commander of Fraxinus, thus he usually comes in contact with Shido, and is regularly featured with the other crew members of Fraxinus as assistants on Shido`s mission to save the Spirits. Kyouhei is a nice man with elegant manners; however he is kind of an idiot, and seems to be unreliable given his rank and position. Obsessed with Kotori, he always thinks of perverted ideas that includes Kotori in it, and often gets punished as a result. Also, he usually shows masochistic qualities when receiving punishment from Kotori, however in some other cases he also shown that "M" qualities as well. Nevertheless, sometimes he can be serious when needed to on certain situations, though usually those are on rare occasions when Kotori is not around to command.
Source: Date A Live Wikia</description>
<picture>136232.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55100" type="appears in" update="2016-09-29">
<rating votes="9">4.08</rating>
<name>Nakatsugawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191995.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36764" picture="135413.jpg">Gorgeous</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55101" type="appears in" update="2013-06-23">
<rating votes="26">4.77</rating>
<name>Yamabuki Ai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138937.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27065" picture="87901.jpg">Murai Risako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55102" type="appears in" update="2013-06-23">
<rating votes="4">4.12</rating>
<name>Kawagoe</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138939.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2888" picture="200816.jpg">Inoue Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55103" type="appears in" update="2013-06-23">
<rating votes="14">5.03</rating>
<name>Kusakabe Ryouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138944.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1439" picture="223493.jpg">Takahashi Ao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55104" type="appears in" update="2013-06-23">
<rating votes="19">4.05</rating>
<name>Shiizaki Hinako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138943.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1511" picture="173601.jpg">Akesaka Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55105" type="appears in" update="2013-06-23">
<rating votes="39">6.19</rating>
<name>Fujibakama Mii</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138935.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23589" picture="127456.jpg">Tsukimiya Midori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55106" type="appears in" update="2013-06-23">
<rating votes="28">4.65</rating>
<name>Hazakura Mai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138936.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27068" picture="73524.jpg">Tsumita Kayoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55107" type="appears in" update="2013-06-23">
<rating votes="7">4.07</rating>
<name>Mikimoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138942.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3186" picture="171957.jpg">Tone Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55108" type="appears in" update="2013-06-23">
<rating votes="11">3.65</rating>
<name>Minowa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138941.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36765" picture="135414.jpg">Usami Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55783" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-05">
<rating votes="159">8.67</rating>
<name>Tokisaki Kurumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136616.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="359" picture="65537.jpg">Sanada Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55784" type="appears in" update="2013-05-12">
<name>Joukan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3965" picture="25836.jpg">Souya Shigenori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55785" type="appears in" update="2015-02-25">
<name>Ryouko no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="32217" picture="86168.jpg">Kamenaka Rieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56480" type="appears in" update="2013-06-01">
<rating votes="30">7.32</rating>
<name>Itsuka Kotori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>137496.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56999" type="appears in" update="2013-06-09">
<name>Suzuki</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="32034" picture="85884.jpg">Mizuno Takao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57419" type="appears in" update="2019-11-06">
<rating votes="3">9.65</rating>
<name>Ratatosk Kikan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>240793.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="57420" type="appears in" update="2013-06-23">
<name>Anti-Spirit Team</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="147856" update="2013-03-02">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-03-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">PV【第2弾】"五河琴里編"</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">PV Dai 2 Dan "Itsuka Kotori Hen"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147857" update="2013-03-02">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-02-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">PV【第1弾】"夜刀神十香編"</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">PV Dai 1 Dan "Yatogami Tooka Hen"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147858" update="2013-03-02">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-12-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アニメPV ver1.2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV ver1.2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anime PV Ver 1.2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148575" update="2013-03-23">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-03-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">PV【第3弾】"鳶一折紙編"</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">PV Dai 3 Dan "Tobiichi Origami"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148601" update="2018-05-10">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-12</airdate>
<rating votes="18">6.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">来訪者達</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Visitors</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Besucher</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Raihousha-tachi</title>
<summary>A young AST joins Origami and the others in the fight against the Spirits. Meanwhile, another transfer student appears at Shido`s school.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>767157</identifier>
<identifier>date-a-live</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148602" update="2018-05-10">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-05</airdate>
<rating votes="18">6.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋する温泉</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Romantic Hot Springs</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Quelle der Liebe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi Suru Onsen</title>
<summary>Shido and the Spirits decide to visit Tengu City Hot Springs, but they run into some trouble on the way.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>767153</identifier>
<identifier>date-a-live</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148603" update="2018-05-10">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="19">6.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">凍て付く大地</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Frozen Ground</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Gefrorener Boden</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itetsuku Daichi</title>
<summary>Shido goes to Origami`s apartment to look for Hermit`s puppet, Yoshinon, who was lost during the last fight, and Tohka talks with Reine about her feelings for Shido.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>767149</identifier>
<identifier>date-a-live</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148604" update="2018-05-10">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-04-21</airdate>
<rating votes="19">6.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">不機嫌な雨</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sullen Rain</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Trauriger Regen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukigen na Ame</title>
<summary>Shido encounters the mysterious "Hermit" one rainy day, and Tohka and Origami fight over Shido at school.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>767145</identifier>
<identifier>date-a-live</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148605" update="2018-05-10">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="20">6.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">空分かつ剣(つるぎ)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">For the Sky and the Sword</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das den Himmel zerteilende Schwert</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sora Wakatsu Tsurugi</title>
<summary>With the support of Ratatoskr, Shido goes on a date with Tohka as Origami watches from afar.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>767141</identifier>
<identifier>date-a-live</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148606" update="2019-06-26">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="20">6.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">再接近遭遇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Another Close Encounter</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Zweite Begegnung</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saisekkin Souguu</title>
<summary>Shido practices making women fall in love with him and has another encounter with the Spirit "Princess".
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>767137</identifier>
<identifier>date-a-live</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148607" update="2019-06-26">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-31</airdate>
<rating votes="23">5.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">四月一〇日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">April 1x</title>
<title xml:lang="de">10. April</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shigatsu Tooka</title>
<summary>Shido Itsuka is an ordinary high school student living with his little sister in Tengu City, a city that is often disrupted by "spatial quakes". During a spatial quake at the beginning of the school year, he meets a beautiful and mysterious "Spirit".
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>767135</identifier>
<identifier>date-a-live</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148984" update="2013-07-06">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-03-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148985" update="2013-04-14">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-04-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="149639" update="2013-10-04">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-04-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="149748" update="2013-10-07">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-04-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150367" update="2018-05-10">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-16</airdate>
<rating votes="17">6.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">譲れないもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">That Which Cannot Be Forgiven</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Keine Komprosmisse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuzurenai Mono</title>
<summary>Shido and Kotori enjoy their date at the amusement park until they are interrupted by Origami.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>767177</identifier>
<identifier>date-a-live</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150368" update="2018-05-10">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-09</airdate>
<rating votes="18">6.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カウントダウン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Countdown</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Countdown</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Countdown</title>
<summary>To get ready for his date with Kotori, Shido goes swimsuit shopping with Tohka and Yoshino. Meanwhile, Origami finds out more about Ifrit.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>767173</identifier>
<identifier>date-a-live</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150369" update="2018-05-10">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-02</airdate>
<rating votes="18">7.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">炎の精霊(イフリート)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Flame Spirit (Ifrit)</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Geist der Flammen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ifrit</title>
<summary>Shido learns the truth about his and Kotori`s powers, and Origami reveals more details about her past.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>767171</identifier>
<identifier>date-a-live</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150370" update="2019-06-26">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="18">7.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狂乱の悪夢</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Frenzied Nightmare</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Endloser Alptraum</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyouran no Akumu</title>
<summary>Shido and the others face off against "Nightmare", and they receive some unexpected help.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>767165</identifier>
<identifier>date-a-live</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150371" update="2018-05-10">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-19</airdate>
<rating votes="19">6.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">三重狂騒曲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Triple Capriccio</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Dreifacher Wahnsinn</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sanjuu Kyousoukyoku</title>
<summary>Shido takes Tohka, Kurumi, and Origami out on dates on the same day. Will he be found out?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>767161</identifier>
<identifier>date-a-live</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150418" update="2013-10-07">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-05-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150419" update="2013-10-07">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-04-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154714" update="2013-12-27">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-06-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154715" update="2013-10-07">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-05-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154716" update="2013-10-07">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-04-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156907" update="2013-12-27">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-11-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 6</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
