<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8834" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2012-04-13</startdate>
<enddate>2012-06-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shining Hearts: Shiawase no Pan</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">シャイニング・ハーツ ~幸せのパン~</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Shiny Bread</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Shining Hearts: Bread of Happiness</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">Shining Hearts -幸せのパン-</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Shining Hearts</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">光明之心-幸福的面包</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5084" type="Same Setting">Shining Tears X Wind</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="7280" approval="22" total="30">Shukufuku no Campanella</anime>
<anime id="10241" approval="15" total="17">Escha &amp; Logy no Atelier: Tasogare no Sora no Renkinjutsushi</anime>
<anime id="13912" approval="2" total="2">Bermuda Triangle: Colorful Pastorale</anime>
<anime id="11544" approval="1" total="4">Manaria Friends</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="622725">Its not simple to make a fantasy series based on a bakery, but on my opinion this is a slighty success, either not good nor bad, for fans</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://shining-world.jp/hearts/info/#anime</url>
<creators>
<name id="1178" type="Original Work">Sega</name>
<name id="721" type="Animation Work">Production I.G</name>
<name id="11238" type="Character Design">Matsumoto Keita</name>
<name id="4797" type="Direction">Kawasaki Itsurou</name>
<name id="13979" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yahiro Yuuko</name>
<name id="28302" type="Music">Kikuta Hiroki</name>
<name id="4797" type="Series Composition">Kawasaki Itsurou</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch39650 [Rick] lives on the island of Windaria, inhabited by various races such as elves and beast-people. Amnesiac, he is rescued by http://anidb.net/ch39648 [Airy], http://anidb.net/ch39647 [Amil], and http://anidb.net/ch39649 [Neris], and starts to work at their bakery. But when the red moon rises and the deathly wind blows, they are all overwhelmed by a series of strange events.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="778">2.71</permanent>
<temporary count="784">5.55</temporary>
<review count="1">5.83</review>
</ratings>
<picture>227089.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13866</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12367</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>15769</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>15505</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5081</identifier>
<identifier>zdypfa</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://shining-world.jp/heartsTV/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://shining-world.jp/hearts/info/#anime</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.production-ig.co.jp/works/shining-hearts</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Shining_Hearts:_Shiawase_no_Pan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>シャイニング・ハーツ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2503</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>342138</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14465</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="34">
<externalentity>
<url>https://ch.nicovideo.jp/hearts</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1403" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-10">
<name>nun</name>
<description>A nun is a member of a religious community of women, typically one living under vows of poverty, chastity, and obedience. She may have decided to dedicate her life to serving all other living beings, or she might be an ascetic who voluntarily chose to leave mainstream society and live her life in prayer and contemplation in a monastery or convent. The term "nun" is applicable to Catholics (eastern and western traditions), Orthodox Christians, Anglicans, Lutherans, Jains, Buddhists, Taoists, Hindus and some other religious traditions.
Source: Wiktionary</description>
<picurl>165755.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1609" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-03-01">
<name>elf</name>
<description>The origin of Elves (Norse; álfar(elves), álfr(elf)) can be found in ancient Norse mythology, in which, elves are described as divine, or near-divine, race of humanoids (Vættir), likened to the Æsir. In common description they are described as sage and immortal beings occupying the threshold between humans and the gods. In some cases humans that were beloved by the gods became elves within their lives. Ancient Elves are delineated into a pair of similar but distinct races; Light Elves (Ljósálfar) and Dark Elves (Svartálfar), each originating from separate homes within the nine worlds of Yggdrasil. Within the Poetic Edda the differences are commonly ascribed as:
"There is one place there that is called the Elf Home (Álfheimr which is the elven city). People live there that are named the light elves (Ljósálfar). But the dark elves (Dökkálfar) live below in earth, in caves and the dark forest and they are unlike them in appearance - and more unlike them in reality. The Light Elves are brighter than the sun in appearance, but the Dark Elves are blacker than pitch." (Snorri, Gylfaginning 17, Prose Edda)</description>
<picurl>63489.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1835" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-17">
<name>animal sidekick</name>
<description>Every mahou shoujo anime needs them, the cute little critters that are supposed to help the protagonists but in reality are nothing but useless bystanders most often abused for gags. Kids love them but they can also often turn into an annoyance.</description>
<picurl>227760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2346" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-14">
<name>angel</name>
<description>An angel is a supernatural being, said to be the messenger of God. They are often depicted as human beings with a pair of white feathered wings and sometimes with a halo.
In contrast, a fallen angel who has turned evil will be depicted with black wings.</description>
<picurl>35521.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2631" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-11">
<name>island</name>
<description>Part of this anime takes place on an island, a small landmass that is surrounded by the sea. Generally, an island setting involves interaction with "island" elements. Such elements could include (but is not limited towards): riding on a boat, fishing, foraging/hunting, beach scene, "peaceful island life", being "shipwrecked", island fever, lamenting isolation from the mainland, etc.
An island or isle is any piece of sub-continental land that is surrounded by water. Very small islands such as emergent land features on atolls can be called islets, cays or keys. An island in a river or lake may be called an eyot (also ait), or holm. A grouping of geographically or geologically related islands is called an archipelago.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2795" parentid="1973" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>baking</name>
<description>The art of making bread, cakes, pastries, pies, tarts, quiches, cookies and similar food in the oven.
Mmmm.... smells nice.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2801" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>RPG</name>
<description>Any anime that is based on a role-playing game aka RPG. A role-playing video game is a video game which includes elements of non-electronic role-playing games. The player assumes control of one or several fictional characters (a party) who have joined forces in order to perform quests and overcome a great number of challenges and enemies, usually monsters inspired by fantasy, and, to a lesser extent, science fiction and classic mythology. During the course of the game the characters, or avatars, which are generally defined by quantized characteristics, evolve and improve in that their various attributes increase, as well as by gaining more powerful artefacts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3908" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-02">
<name>lap pillow</name>
<description>As a sign of closeness the usually male character is encouraged to rest his weary head on the female’s lap.</description>
<picurl>167007.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4116" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-13">
<name>eternal blush</name>
<description>It is no ordinary blush it is a blush that does not disappear.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5884" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-22">
<name>slow-paced</name>
<description>The story — including its characters and events — develop slowly.
May contain a weak continuity of plot and/or character development. 
Or may be a story telling device to increase the "sense of foreboding" in an anime with thriller or horror setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="39647" type="main character in" update="2012-04-12">
<rating votes="10">5.24</rating>
<name>Amil Manaflare</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78498.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39648" type="main character in" update="2012-04-12">
<rating votes="10">6.15</rating>
<name>Airy Ardet</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78497.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4007" picture="25937.jpg">Mikami Shiori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39649" type="main character in" update="2012-04-12">
<rating votes="11">6.33</rating>
<name>Neris Filiam</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78499.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="539" picture="228668.jpg">Aizawa Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39650" type="main character in" update="2012-04-12">
<rating votes="4">6.40</rating>
<name>Rick Elwood</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78500.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39656" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-02">
<rating votes="8">7.62</rating>
<name>Kaguya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaguya is a mysterious girl who was washed ashore the island of Wyndaria one day after a great storm. She has lost her memories and along with them, her emotions.</description>
<picture>78517.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39657" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-14">
<rating votes="9">8.16</rating>
<name>Rouna Murasame</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rouna is Rufina`s maid, and also a cook. She is an expert with blades and she keeps a good store underneath her dress and in her bag.</description>
<picture>78518.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="346" picture="17184.jpg">Hirohashi Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39658" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-02">
<rating votes="7">6.93</rating>
<name>Rufina Wyndaria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rufina Wyndaria is the princess of Wyndaria. She is kind and gentle, and due to her interest in tea and herbs, she is found often in the palace garden. She takes a great interest in Rick and his friends.</description>
<picture>78519.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39659" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-14">
<rating votes="9">7.67</rating>
<name>Melty de Granite</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Melty de Granite is a witch who resides in a mansion separate from the village. Because she is not too fond of people and hates the sun she avoids going out.</description>
<picture>78520.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39660" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-14">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Sorbe</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78521.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="553" picture="170553.jpg">Kaneda Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39662" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-14">
<rating votes="11">8.49</rating>
<name>Lin Xiao-Mei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lin Xiao-Mei is a fickle black cat pirate. She normally runs an antique shop, but she is also a thief who refers to herself as Black Tail.</description>
<picture>78523.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41225" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-28">
<rating votes="3">1.65</rating>
<name>Alvin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>86685.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41226" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-15">
<rating votes="6">6.17</rating>
<name>Queen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>89623.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4929" picture="41385.jpg">Kitta Izumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41227" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-07">
<rating votes="3">4.88</rating>
<name>Dylan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>89152.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="259" picture="17082.jpg">Nakai Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41228" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-05-07">
<rating votes="3">4.17</rating>
<name>Hank</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87374.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2279" picture="23207.jpg">Satou Masaharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41229" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-12">
<rating votes="3">5.17</rating>
<name>Madera</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85808.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3271" picture="171421.jpg">Emori Hiroko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41230" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-02">
<rating votes="2">2.40</rating>
<name>Lagnus Wyndaria</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88879.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41231" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-12">
<rating votes="8">5.95</rating>
<name>Lana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85809.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="346" picture="17184.jpg">Hirohashi Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43971" type="appears in" update="2012-04-28">
<rating votes="2">6.16</rating>
<name>Sammy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>86684.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2416" picture="180631.jpg">Fujitou Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45697" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-07">
<rating votes="6">5.59</rating>
<name>Flora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>89150.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="142" picture="68482.jpg">Ooura Fuyuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45698" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-07">
<name>Ron</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>89151.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3064" picture="24692.jpg">Asou Tomohisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45857" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-13">
<name>Shuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>89459.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="142" picture="68482.jpg">Ooura Fuyuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45934" type="appears in" update="2012-06-15">
<name>Shinpu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>89606.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28672" picture="84423.jpg">Arai Souta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45935" type="appears in" update="2012-06-15">
<name>Monban</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>89607.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32192" picture="86110.jpg">Sasajima Mitsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45936" type="appears in" update="2012-06-15">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Iria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>89612.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12323" picture="171959.jpg">Takayama Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45937" type="appears in" update="2012-06-15">
<name>Jean</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>89615.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29979" picture="223317.jpg">Oosaka Ryouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45938" type="appears in" update="2012-06-15">
<name>Vance</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>89614.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6942" picture="41078.jpg">Takaoka Binbin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45939" type="appears in" update="2012-06-15">
<name>Sylph</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>89608.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45940" type="appears in" update="2012-06-15">
<name>Onnanoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>89609.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="425" picture="17296.jpg">Fukuhara Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45941" type="appears in" update="2012-06-15">
<name>Josei Kyaku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>89610.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="35883" picture="132002.jpg">Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45942" type="appears in" update="2012-06-15">
<name>Shoutaichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>89613.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17523" picture="223264.jpg">Yamamoto Kanehira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45943" type="appears in" update="2012-06-15">
<name>Otoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>89618.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17523" picture="223264.jpg">Yamamoto Kanehira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45944" type="appears in" update="2012-06-15">
<name>Obaasan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>89619.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6932" picture="223628.jpg">Katakai Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45945" type="appears in" update="2012-06-15">
<name>Ani</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>89620.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="35883" picture="132002.jpg">Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45946" type="appears in" update="2012-06-15">
<name>Onnanoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>89621.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10410" picture="223211.jpg">Izawa Shiori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47214" type="appears in" update="2012-07-24">
<name>Igyou no Kaizoku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="137268" update="2012-03-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-04-13</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ル・クールへようこそ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to Le Coeur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Le Coeur e Youkoso</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138051" update="2012-03-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-05-04</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">機械人形</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Automaton</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikai Ningyou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138052" update="2012-03-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-04-27</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">灯火管制</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mandatory Blackout</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toukakansei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138053" update="2012-03-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="7">3.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">嵐の日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Day of the Storm</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arashi no Hi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138847" update="2012-04-12">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-04-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138848" update="2012-04-12">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-04-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139196" update="2012-04-27">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-06-01</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">漂流人[さすらいびと]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Drifters</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sasuraibito</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139197" update="2012-04-27">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それぞれのココロ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Differing Hearts</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sorezore no Kokoro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139198" update="2012-04-27">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-05-18</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">王子からの依頼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Request from the Prince</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ouji kara no Irai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139199" update="2012-04-27">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-05-11</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">とろけるような</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Like Something That Melts</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Torokeru You na</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139547" update="2012-05-11">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-06-08</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">怪盗再び</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Thief Returns</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaitou Futatabi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139548" update="2012-05-11">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-06-15</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">異世界からの使者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Messenger from Another World</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Isekai kara no Shisha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="140050" update="2012-06-23">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-06-30</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幸せのパン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bread of Happiness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiawase no Pan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="140051" update="2012-06-08">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-06-22</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Decisive Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="141362" update="2012-08-04">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-08-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">"心がとどいた" ピクチャードラマ ネリス編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Kokoro ga Todoita" Picture Drama: Neris Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="141363" update="2014-11-21">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-08-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オマケ劇場 ル・クール業務日誌その2 ダイエット</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omake Gekijou: Le Coeur Gyoumu Nisshi Sono 2 - Diet</title>
</episode>
<episode id="141364" update="2014-11-21">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-07-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">"心がとどいた" ピクチャードラマ アミル編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Kokoro ga Todoita" Picture Drama: Amil Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="141365" update="2012-08-04">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-07-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オマケ劇場 ル・クール業務日誌その1 海水浴</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omake Gekijou: Le Coeur Gyoumu Nisshi Sono 1 - Kaisuiyoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144820" update="2012-10-19">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-12-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">"心がとどいた" ピクチャードラマ カグヤ編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 12</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Kokoro ga Todoita" Picture Drama: Kaguya Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144821" update="2012-10-19">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-12-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オマケ劇場 ル・クール業務日誌その6 みんなありがとう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 11</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omake Gekijou: Le Coeur Gyoumu Nisshi Sono 6 - Minna Arigatou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144822" update="2012-10-19">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-11-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">"心がとどいた" ピクチャードラマ ローナ編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 10</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Kokoro ga Todoita" Picture Drama: Rouna Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144823" update="2012-10-19">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-11-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オマケ劇場 ル・クール業務日誌その5 おおそうじ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 9</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omake Gekijou: Le Coeur Gyoumu Nisshi Sono 5 - Oosouji</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144824" update="2012-10-19">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-10-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">"心がとどいた" ピクチャードラマ シャオメイ編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 8</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Kokoro ga Todoita" Picture Drama: Xiao-Mei Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144825" update="2012-10-19">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-10-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オマケ劇場 ル・クール業務日誌その4 ざんげの日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 7</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omake Gekijou: Le Coeur Gyoumu Nisshi Sono 4 - Zange no Hi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144826" update="2012-10-19">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-09-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">"心がとどいた" ピクチャードラマ エアリィ編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Kokoro ga Todoita" Picture Drama: Airy Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144827" update="2012-10-19">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-09-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オマケ劇場 ル・クール業務日誌その3 まぜまぜまぜまぜ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omake Gekijou: Le Coeur Gyoumu Nisshi Sono 3 - Maze Maze Maze Maze</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
