<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8836" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>25</episodecount>
<startdate>2012-10-06</startdate>
<enddate>2013-03-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Bakuman. (2012)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Bakuman S3</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">爆漫王3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">bakuman3</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">バクマン. (2012)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Bakuman. (2012)</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Бакуман (2012)</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">食梦者。3</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8150" type="Prequel">Bakuman. (2011)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="9">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="45669">Probably the best season so far! Really great anime. You really feel what the main characters feel and you want them to succeed so bad!
Ashirogi vs Nizuma Eiji competition is fantastic.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="535802">One of the best anime out there along with the two previous seasons.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="730868">I felt this was a bit weaker than Bakuman 2. In any case, if you`ve watched the first two, you`re going to have to watch this one.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="591695">Season 3 really is the climax. Characters develops further with more twists in the plot. Great watch. It`s one of those shows that you know it is going to be a happy ending, but watching the progress towards this goal really is the gem of bakuman.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="455302">Awesome finale! best season ever! even though i say that, both previous seasons have been superb which actually led to this awesome season 3. The intense tension in the concluding 4-5 episodes was so perfect. Amazing journey leading to  fullfillment of the characters dreams. Well done! 
Of course, a must see anime!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="301941">Awesome, enough said.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="194756">Awesome throughout, with an amazing climax. Each season surpasses my expectations</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www9.nhk.or.jp/anime/bakuman/3rd/</url>
<creators>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="1790" type="Series Composition">Yoshida Reiko</name>
<name id="654" type="Direction">Kasai Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="11137" type="Direction">Akitaya Noriaki</name>
<name id="9749" type="Chief Animation Direction">Komori Atsushi</name>
<name id="2932" type="Chief Animation Direction">Shitaya Tomoyuki</name>
<name id="2841" type="Work">Shogakukan-Shueisha Productions</name>
<name id="1050" type="Work">NHK</name>
<name id="1234" type="Work">NHK Enterprises</name>
<name id="2932" type="Character Design">Shitaya Tomoyuki</name>
<name id="10808" type="Music">Audio Highs</name>
<name id="1499" type="Original Work">Obata Takeshi</name>
<name id="1498" type="Original Work">Ooba Tsugumi</name>
<name id="11736" type="Chief Animation Direction">Matsuura Mai</name>
<name id="11871" type="Chief Animation Direction">Haneda Kouji</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a shounen manga by http://anidb.net/cr1498 [Ooba Tsugumi] and http://anidb.net/cr1499 [Obata Takeshi] serialised in http://anidb.net/cr5372 [Weekly Shounen Jump].
http://anidb.net/ch16785 [Mashiro Moritaka] and http://anidb.net/ch16787 [Takagi Akito] have come a long way since they started making manga in middle school, but trials still await them as they head towards their goal of getting an anime adaption for one of their manga. As they continue to grow as artists and as people, they will be faced with new friends, new rivals, and new hurdles to overcome.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2236">8.74</permanent>
<temporary count="2247">8.28</temporary>
<review count="1">4.83</review>
</ratings>
<picture>126361.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13867</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12365</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>15711</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>23361</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5206</identifier>
<identifier>prsulz</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www9.nhk.or.jp/anime/bakuman/3rd/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2741</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>343757</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15334</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1298" parentid="2883" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-02">
<name>drawing</name>
<description>The art or technique of representing an object or outlining a figure, plan, or sketch by means of lines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2378" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-02">
<name>hard-working</name>
<description>Describes someone, who is constantly, regularly, or habitually active or occupied.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2403" parentid="3971" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-16">
<name>seiyuu</name>
<description>In Japanese, the term seiyuu denotes a voice actor, or someone that provides voice-overs or narration in radio, television, or films, as well as character actors for animated works and video games. Conventionally, the term "seiyuu" is used among English-speaking fans to denote a Japanese actor, whereas "voice actor" is the norm when referring to their counterparts in other languages, and particularly in English voice-overs of anime.</description>
<picurl>41870.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2779" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>multiple couples</name>
<description>More than one couple is developed in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2978" parentid="5604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-28">
<name>aim for the top</name>
<description>This can be a positive or negative plot device. A character may strive to become the best in an altruistic way (e.g. best healer, most widely learned master), or it can be quite banal and primitive (e.g. challenged delinquents wanting to be the strongest fighters).
Alas in fighting anime the latter usually prevails.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3149" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-15">
<name>journalism</name>
<description>Journalism is the work and distribution of reports on the interaction of events, facts, ideas, and people that are the "news of the day" and that informs society to at least some degree. The word applies to the occupation (professional or not), the methods of gathering information, and the organizing literary styles. Journalistic media include: print, television, radio, Internet and, in the past, newsreels.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3170" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-10">
<name>occupation and career</name>
<description>The kind of anime which shows the career of a character, usually from the beginning.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3395" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-18">
<name>promise</name>
<description>A dramatically-made promise that serves as foreshadowing. The promise will eventually be called in and action will be required.
Whether they succeed, fail or refuse to keep their promise depends almost entirely on the idealism-level of the story. Other factors, such as whether they were told what they had to do, or if it was a Leonine Contract, may come into play. Even Releasing from the Promise is usually a scene of high drama.
Source: TVTropes</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3444" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>hot springs visit</name>
<description>An onsen is a term for hot springs in the Japanese language, though the term is often used to describe the bathing facilities and inns around the hot springs. Often the cast of a show somehow ends up going to an onsen because of various reasons, such as winning a lottery ticket. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters nude and raise the DVD sales.
Another cheap variant is the http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160784.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3589" parentid="4251" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-04">
<name>multiple protagonists - TO BE MOVED TO PARENT OR DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is to be moved into its parent tag http://anidb.net/t4251 [ensemble cast], or removed entirely. If the tagged entry meets the updated definition of ensemble cast, tag ensemble cast and delete multiple protagonist. If it does not meet the ensemble cast definition, delete this tag and take no further action.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3971" parentid="3170" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-07-04">
<name>entertainment industry</name>
<description>The show depicts how the entertainment industry works and how the main protagonists strive to cope with the sudden change to fame. At times this can be a very ugly sight indeed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4198" parentid="5604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-14">
<name>hard work and guts</name>
<description>One of the character`s motto in the anime. Because there is nothing that cannot be achieved by hard work and guts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4344" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-26">
<name>motivational anime</name>
<description>The anime motivates doing something which is shown in the show (for example club activity, sports, choosing a job, a hobby etc).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4480" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>happy ending</name>
<description>And they lived "happily ever after"... *sniff*.
All issues in the anime have been resolved, the love polygons sorted out, the conflicts resolved, the guy gets the girl (or the other way around), and everyone else lives on blissfully.
(Not very realistic, but then again this is anime.)</description>
<picurl>222185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5213" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-04">
<name>the effects of time and distance on human relationships</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5863" parentid="2798" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-06">
<name>Weekly Shounen Jump</name>
<description>The Weekly Shounen Jump is a Japanese manga magazine released on a weekly basis. Its main target audience consists of young males and it features several manga titles. The magazine was created by http://anidb.net/cr780 [Shueisha] in July, 1968, and was originally only called Shounen Jump, because it was not published every week at the time. A number of very famous shounen manga were or are published in it, such as http://anidb.net/a386 [Hokuto no Ken], http://anidb.net/a231 [Dragon Ball], http://anidb.net/a942 [City Hunter], http://anidb.net/a826 [Saint Seiya], http://anidb.net/a590 [Slam Dunk], http://anidb.net/a312 [Yuu Yuu Hakushou], http://anidb.net/a69 [One Piece], http://anidb.net/a239 [Naruto], http://anidb.net/a2369 [Bleach], http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], http://anidb.net/a3468 [Gintama], to name a few of the most well-known.</description>
<picurl>66685.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="226" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-07-05">
<rating votes="1440">6.74</rating>
<name>Uzumaki Naruto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60771.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="474" type="cameo appearance in" update="2019-03-01">
<rating votes="4175">8.53</rating>
<name>Monkey D. Luffy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Monkey D. Luffy is a fictional character and the main protagonist in the anime and manga series http://anidb.net/a69 [One Piece] created by http://anidb.net/cr4013 [Oda Eiichiro]. He is a boy whose body is made of rubber after he ate a http://anidb.net/t2518 [devil`s fruit] and acquired the accursed ability.
In the anime and manga, Luffy is captain of the http://anidb.net/ch1954 [Straw Hat Pirates], a group of pirates he assembles himself as he quests to find the "One Piece" and become the King of the Pirates. His primary motivation throughout the series is to reach the goal with all of his comrades, a task he pursues no matter what stands in his way. While he is goofy and reckless, he gets quite serious when anyone is in serious danger, notably his crew, whom he considers his friends. Luffy has additionally appeared in all of the featured movies in the series and other media relating to the series, including several video games and specials.
His blood type is F in XFS blood group system used in his world. It is equivalent to B in ABO blood group system.</description>
<picture>77294.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2069" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-05-11">
<rating votes="1320">6.46</rating>
<name>Kurosaki Ichigo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kurosaki Ichigo was raised by his father together with his two sisters after the traumatic experience of losing his mother. One day, minding his own business, he meets Rukia, the Shinigami, who needs his help. While protecting his family they find out about his supernatural abilities and thus a still-living - substitute - Shinigami is born....</description>
<picture>136529.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="16784" type="main character in" update="2017-08-10">
<rating votes="159">5.98</rating>
<name>Azuki Miho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Azuki Miho is http://anidb.net/ch16785 [Mashiro]`s former classmate and fiancée. She aspires to become a voice actress and shows promise in the field. She promises to marry Mashiro after they achieve their dreams. However, they must not see each other until then. Since this promise, Azuki has picked up a voicing role, and is gaining growing popularity, not because of her skills, but for her looks. At one point Azuki`s agent urged her to bring out a photo book, in effect becoming a gravure idol. With Mashiro`s support, however, she turned down the offer and persevered in her voice acting. Her mother is the woman Mashiro`s uncle fell in love with. She and Mashiro often communicate through text and sometimes through phone calls, but rarely meet.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>65266.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16785" type="main character in" update="2017-08-10">
<rating votes="118">5.46</rating>
<name>Mashiro Moritaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mashiro Moritaka is one of the main protagonists of the series. He follows in the footsteps of his late, manga artist uncle, who loved a classmate from afar, but never got the chance to tell her so and later died from overwork. He is fond of his classmate http://anidb.net/ch16784 [Azuki Miho], who wishes to become a voice actress. To avoid becoming like his uncle, Mashiro accidentally proposes to Miho. She accepts, stating she will marry him after they achieve their dreams on the condition that they must not see each other until then. Mashiro then decides to team up with another classmate, a talented writer named http://anidb.net/ch16787 [Takagi Akito], and try to get published and have an anime adaption of the series. The two work under the pen name http://anidb.net/ch20022 [Ashirogi Muto]. He is a talented artist, but is highly dissatisfied with his drawings.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>65261.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="545" picture="188506.jpg">Abe Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16787" type="main character in" update="2017-08-10">
<rating votes="104">8.25</rating>
<name>Takagi Akito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takagi Akito is the second main protagonist. He starts out as one of http://anidb.net/ch16785 [Mashiro Moritaka]`s classmate and after discovering Mashiro`s talent in drawing in school, he proposed that they try to publish a manga together. Although Mashiro originally refuses, the two begin to work together after he takes Mashiro to http://anidb.net/ch16784 [Azuki]`s house and Azuki and Mashiro decide to get married after their dreams come true. He eventually dates and becomes married to Azuki`s best friend http://anidb.net/ch16786 [Miyoshi Kaya]. Takagi is a writer and writes the storylines for the pair`s manga. The two started working under the pen name http://anidb.net/ch20022 [Ashirogi Muto]. Takagi specializes in unorthodox story lines.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>65262.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19967" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-16">
<rating votes="45">1.65</rating>
<name>Nakai Takurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67669.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="78" picture="16686.jpg">Shimura Tomoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19968" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-16">
<rating votes="18">7.90</rating>
<name>Sasaki Hisashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sasaki Hisashi is the Executive Editor at Weekly Shounen Jump. He has the final word most of the time when it comes to manga.</description>
<picture>59320.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19969" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-16">
<rating votes="57">5.04</rating>
<name>Iwase Aiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A former classmate of Moritaka and Akito during junior high school. She at first has a crush on Akito but is rejected because she disapproves of writing manga. She later reappears as a student at To-Oh University along with Aoki Kou. She writes her first novel while in University, but since she sees Akito as a rival, she decides to write a manga for Shounen Jump to prove her superiority. Her editor is originally Akira, who works with Akito and Moritaka beforehand, but after Akira returns as Akito and Moritaka`s editor, her new editor becomes Miura Gorou, which angers her because she had feelings for Hattori. Her writing and plot are praised as very well made and she is the writer of Natural.</description>
<picture>56278.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19970" type="appears in" update="2014-11-06">
<rating votes="18">5.40</rating>
<name>Mashiro Nobuhiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mashiro Nobuhiro aka Kawaguchi Tarou (川口たろう) is the late uncle of Moritaka and also a mangaka. He is scruffy looking man, with his hair held in a loose ponytail, and a bit of stubble. He wears round glasses and often holds a cigarette. He is rather uncaring of his appearance, often being seen in a t-shirt and shorts while in his studio. When he was younger, his hair was short and smothed out and he had yet to grow faical hair or wear glasses.
He`s the reason Moritaka know so much about manga. His love interest is Miyuki, Miho`s mother, but was too late to confess with her. At high school, he`s best friend of Miyoshi father, Yosshi. His first manga is a gag manga named Superhero Legend (he wasn`t a good artist; despite getting good grades in art class, his skills were subpar compared to most professional manga artists). Nobuhiro was also especially determined, and refused to let failure dissuade him. Even after learning that Miyuki had gotten married, he continued writing out of the belief that she was still watching him progress, and she did, in fact, she glanced at Shounen Jump to read his manga. After being told that his contract had been canceled, he told Sasaki that he saw it as an opportunity to start over as a newbie, and submitted finished drafts until five days before his death. Nobuhiro believes in three rules for mangakas who are not geniuses; 1) conceit 2) hardwork 3) luck. He was still remembered by the editors long after his passing. Later, Moritaka and Takagi use his workplace as their workplace. He`s a hard-working man, and his death acctually is by overworking because he wanted to get published again, not by suicide. His death is also a matter to dissuade Moritaka to become a mangaka, but later Moritaka can go through it.</description>
<picture>55780.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="373" picture="191382.jpg">Hamada Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19971" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-08-04">
<rating votes="129">7.94</rating>
<name>Niizuma Eiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Niizuma Eiji is a 16-year-old high school student hailed as a genius by many people. He wins the Tezuka Award for his manga Large bander, after which http://anidb.net/ch16785 [Mashiro Moritaka] and http://anidb.net/ch16787 [Takagi Akito] declare him their rival. Although Mashiro and Takagi view him as a rival, he is very friendly upon meeting them and states he is a fan of theirs. He moves to Tokyo to work on the serialization of his manga Crow on the condition he is able to cancel one series in the Weekly Shounen Jump after becoming the magazine`s most popular author. The head editor has described the difference between Mashiro and Takagi to Niizuma is love of manga, indeed, Niizuma seems to have been obsessed with and drawing manga since he was 6, and makes loud sound effects with his mouth while drawing. Niizuma tends to act conceited because he is hailed as a genius; however, after working on Crow for quite a long time, he is more humble, even claiming to not be good enough of a Mangaka to be judging other people`s work when asked by his editor to judge for the treasure magazine. He works under the direction of the Weekly Shounen Jump editor http://anidb.net/ch19973 [Hattori Yuujirou] and works with two assistants, http://anidb.net/ch19975 [Fukuda Shinta] and http://anidb.net/ch19967 [Nakai Takurou].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>65264.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19972" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-16">
<rating votes="68">8.40</rating>
<name>Hattori Akira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hattori Akira begins as Akito Takagi`s and Moritaka Mashiro`s editor. He helps them with their pen name and eventually gets them serialized for Detective Trap. Once it becomes serialized, however, Akira loses them to Miura Gorou due to conflicting responsibilities, and soon becomes Iwase Aiko`s editor. After The Perfect Crime Club is serialized, Akira returns as Ashirogi Mutou`s editor, leading Gorou to edit Aiko`s work. He comes up with the idea of having Eiji and Aiko collaborate on Natural in order to inspire Moritaka and Akito to work harder.</description>
<picture>58761.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3186" picture="171957.jpg">Tone Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19973" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-16">
<rating votes="29">4.06</rating>
<name>Hattori Yuujirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67670.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="214" picture="238138.jpg">Nojima Hirofumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19974" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-16">
<rating votes="20">4.77</rating>
<name>Heishi Yoshihisa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69905.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="60" picture="171602.jpg">Kawada Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19975" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-16">
<rating votes="74">6.87</rating>
<name>Fukuda Shinta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fukuda Shinta and http://anidb.net/ch16785 [Mashiro Moritaka] first met when Mashiro decided to become an assistant for http://anidb.net/ch19971 [Niizuma Eiji]. Fukuda had already won an honorable mention when he tried for the Tezuka Award and also got seventh place in the same issue of Akamaru Jump in which http://anidb.net/ch20022 [Ashirogi Muto]`s Money and Intelligence ran and got third place. Fukuda then became friends with Mashiro and also competed with Ashirogi in the Golden Future cup with his original manga, Kiyoshi Knight. Fukuda then got serialized somewhat time after Ashirogi and is now an aspiring rival to Ashirogi, Eiji, and http://anidb.net/ch19967 [Nakai]. Among these three, he is considered to have the worst drawings, though they apparently match his stories. His drawings often border on grotesque. He can be extremely conceited and competitive at times, yet helps out his rivals, who are also his friends.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>67667.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19976" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-08-02">
<rating votes="111">7.66</rating>
<name>Aoki Kou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aoki Kou (real name, Aoki Yuriko (青木 優梨子)) is an aspiring female mangaka that only recently began to work in the shonen genre, previously having worked exclusively as a shoujo manga author. Aoki is a beautiful woman a couple of years older than http://anidb.net/ch16785 [Mashiro] and http://anidb.net/ch16787 [Takagi], which her editor believes will help her sales. She is distrustful of men, as she draws a number of suitors interested in her appearance, including her assistant http://anidb.net/ch19967 [Nakai Takurou], whose advances she rejects a number of times. Because shoujo art styles do not match well with Jump, she initially needs help from assistants and artists in order to be published. She is initially paired with Nakai for her first series, Hideout Door. After Hideout Door is cancelled, Aoki resolves to return to shoujo, although she is later convinced to stay on working for Shonen Jump. She is now working on the serialized series The Time of Green Leaves, which is an ecchi series, although she now does her own drawings with assistance on the ecchi portions from http://anidb.net/ch19975 [Fukuda Shinta].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>65259.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19977" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-16">
<rating votes="98">8.12</rating>
<name>Hiramaru Kazuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiramaru Kazuya is a new mangaka who, one day, picked up Shounen Jump for the first time in his life, and decided to quit his job to draw manga. His series is called Otters 11 and became serialized around the same time as http://anidb.net/ch16785 [Mashiro] and http://anidb.net/ch16787 [Takagi]. He can be overwhelmed easily and finds it hard to deal with the stress of writing a manga. He frequently shows up at the other mangaka`s studios to hide, but is always soon found out by his editor. He complains about his job a lot and wonders aloud why he ever decided to do it in the first place, but consistently ranks high with the readers in the questionnaires. Due to this, he has been called as a manga genius possibly on the level of http://anidb.net/ch19971 [Niizuma Eiji], especially considering he has barely read any manga.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>69909.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="138" picture="23200.jpg">Morita Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22049" type="appears in" update="2016-08-05">
<rating votes="40">7.01</rating>
<name>Azuki Miyuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Azuki Miyuki is mother of Miho and Mina.  She also the love interest of Kaya`s father, Yosshi and Moritaka uncle, Nobuhiro. Although she reject Yosshi because she love Nobuhiro, but later she decided to married someone else because she grew tired of waiting for Nobuhiro said to her "I love You". She looks very young despite her ages; she also bears a strong resemblance to her oldest daughter, Miho, especially when she was younger, looking almost exactly like Miho. At first, she feared Moritaka and Miho would go down the same path at her and Mobuhiro, but has been proven wrong. After learning of Mashiro and Takagi`s plan to be successful mangakas, she encourages them to go through with their dream. Despite being kind and caring, she does have a negative trait of being too nosey about Miho and Moritaka`s love life. Miyuki is good at keeping secrets unless she feels no need to keep them, but she will give hints about the secret, such as warning Miho not to go down the same path in love as she did with Nobuhiro.
</description>
<picture>57119.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22050" type="appears in" update="2011-04-16">
<rating votes="9">4.38</rating>
<name>Mashiro Kayoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>56277.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="690" picture="187038.jpg">Higa Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23354" type="appears in" update="2016-10-14">
<rating votes="9">5.48</rating>
<name>Mashiro Fumio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is Masahiro and Nobuhiro father; Moritaka grandfather. He`s the one who gave Moritaka the key to Nobuhiro`s workplace and Nobuhiro diary.</description>
<picture>57121.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="694" picture="52187.jpg">Choo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23503" type="appears in" update="2016-10-14">
<rating votes="17">4.54</rating>
<name>Azuki Mina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miho`s younger sister</description>
<picture>58002.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="430" picture="246278.jpg">Hidaka Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24900" type="appears in" update="2011-04-16">
<rating votes="20">3.91</rating>
<name>Aida Souichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>58763.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="310" picture="17147.jpg">Kazama Yuuto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31208" type="appears in" update="2011-04-15">
<rating votes="4">3.66</rating>
<name>Yahagi Fuku-Henshuuchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69904.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="688" picture="18295.jpg">Tanaka Kan</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31209" type="appears in" update="2011-04-15">
<rating votes="4">3.66</rating>
<name>Nakano Hiroyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69906.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3801" picture="171533.jpg">Sakamaki Manabu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31210" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-15">
<rating votes="26">7.76</rating>
<name>Yoshida Kouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69907.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31212" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-15">
<rating votes="23">2.71</rating>
<name>Miura Gorou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69910.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="262" picture="62656.jpg">Kirii Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37350" type="appears in" update="2011-10-04">
<rating votes="4">5.12</rating>
<name>Ogawa Nato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63922.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16987" picture="86303.jpg">Shimoyama Yoshimitsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37351" type="appears in" update="2011-10-04">
<rating votes="5">7.11</rating>
<name>Katou Natsumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63923.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="593" picture="17990.jpg">Honda Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37352" type="appears in" update="2011-10-04">
<rating votes="6">2.87</rating>
<name>Takahama Shouyou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63924.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18131" picture="223909.jpg">Shimowada Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37353" type="appears in" update="2011-10-04">
<rating votes="2">4.13</rating>
<name>Torishima</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63926.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="601" picture="165793.jpg">Nakamura Hidetoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50035" type="appears in" update="2012-10-23">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Uketsuke Jou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>127148.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33525" picture="91481.jpg">Hashi Afumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50036" type="appears in" update="2013-02-19">
<rating votes="3">4.31</rating>
<name>Orihara Ichiriki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132342.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1692" picture="224934.jpg">Okitsu Kazuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50037" type="appears in" update="2013-02-19">
<rating votes="3">3.49</rating>
<name>Moriya Shuuichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132344.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="195" picture="17009.jpg">Sakamaki Mitsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50038" type="appears in" update="2013-02-18">
<rating votes="3">4.31</rating>
<name>Shiratori Shun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132340.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12623" picture="151646.jpg">Iguchi Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50039" type="main character in" update="2012-10-23">
<rating votes="27">7.85</rating>
<name>Takagi Kaya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>127149.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="89" picture="148709.jpg">Yahagi Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50040" type="appears in" update="2013-04-26">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Josei Assistant</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60292.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="18198" picture="228672.jpg">Akasaki Chinatsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50041" type="appears in" update="2013-02-19">
<name>Yamahisa Masakazu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132346.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3801" picture="171533.jpg">Sakamaki Manabu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50765" type="appears in" update="2013-04-26">
<rating votes="2">4.41</rating>
<name>Prince Eight Shachou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60293.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="5040" picture="88977.jpg">Kawahara Yoshihisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50766" type="appears in" update="2013-04-26">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Shiratori no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60296.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1901" picture="186579.jpg">Kobayashi Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50767" type="appears in" update="2013-04-26">
<name>Shiratori Hitomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60294.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="23686" picture="224554.jpg">Uchiyama Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50768" type="appears in" update="2013-04-26">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Shiratori no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60295.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="6082" picture="222919.jpg">Hirano Toshitaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50769" type="appears in" update="2013-02-19">
<rating votes="1">4.70</rating>
<name>Yasuoka Hiromi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132341.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5040" picture="88977.jpg">Kawahara Yoshihisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51238" type="appears in" update="2013-02-19">
<rating votes="2">4.41</rating>
<name>Kosugi Tatsurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132343.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51239" type="appears in" update="2013-04-28">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Kim Songyu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60338.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1692" picture="224934.jpg">Okitsu Kazuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51240" type="appears in" update="2013-02-19">
<rating votes="3">3.58</rating>
<name>Nanamine Tooru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132345.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1680" picture="132752.jpg">Tachibana Shinnosuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51241" type="appears in" update="2013-04-26">
<rating votes="2">4.13</rating>
<name>Nakaji Seijirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60299.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="5040" picture="88977.jpg">Kawahara Yoshihisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51242" type="appears in" update="2013-04-26">
<name>Saeki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60298.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51243" type="appears in" update="2013-04-26">
<name>Takahashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60297.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="20249" picture="186289.jpg">Matsuoka Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51896" type="appears in" update="2013-04-28">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Oonishi Kouhei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60339.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1406" picture="18432.jpg">Suzuki Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51897" type="appears in" update="2013-04-27">
<name>Kanchan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60313.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="60" picture="171602.jpg">Kawada Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51898" type="appears in" update="2013-04-27">
<name>Sugi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60309.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3801" picture="171533.jpg">Sakamaki Manabu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51899" type="appears in" update="2013-04-28">
<name>Emo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60311.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="5040" picture="88977.jpg">Kawahara Yoshihisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51900" type="appears in" update="2013-04-27">
<name>Right</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60312.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="195" picture="17009.jpg">Sakamaki Mitsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51901" type="appears in" update="2013-04-27">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Nakai Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60304.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3368" picture="132584.jpg">Kujira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51902" type="appears in" update="2013-04-27">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Boss</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60307.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="310" picture="17147.jpg">Kazama Yuuto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51903" type="appears in" update="2013-04-27">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Nobuo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60310.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51904" type="appears in" update="2013-04-27">
<name>Yamashita</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60308.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1683" picture="223030.jpg">Kanemitsu Nobuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51905" type="appears in" update="2013-04-27">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Naoi Ichiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60306.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="20274" picture="52888.jpg">Nakajima Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51906" type="appears in" update="2013-04-27">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Michimoto Makoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60322.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52588" type="appears in" update="2013-04-27">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Nonaka Shinobu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60325.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="195" picture="17009.jpg">Sakamaki Mitsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52589" type="appears in" update="2013-04-27">
<rating votes="2">5.19</rating>
<name>Annojou Mai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60323.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53650" type="appears in" update="2013-03-10">
<rating votes="3">2.42</rating>
<name>Kitami Ririka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133450.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2228" picture="21776.jpg">Gibu Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53651" type="appears in" update="2013-04-27">
<name>Tanabe Futoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60326.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="18360" picture="48491.jpg">Yamazaki Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53653" type="appears in" update="2013-03-10">
<name>Uchida Taiju</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="5040" picture="88977.jpg">Kawahara Yoshihisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53654" type="appears in" update="2013-04-27">
<rating votes="2">4.41</rating>
<name>Oobayashi Hajime</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60330.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="30012" picture="130105.jpg">Odagaki Yuuta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53655" type="appears in" update="2013-04-27">
<rating votes="2">4.41</rating>
<name>Ehara Masaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60328.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="467" picture="38026.jpg">Ebara Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53656" type="appears in" update="2013-04-27">
<name>Tamiya Mamoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60331.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2356" picture="22132.jpg">Yamaguchi Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53662" type="appears in" update="2013-03-10">
<name>Manager</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2356" picture="22132.jpg">Yamaguchi Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53663" type="appears in" update="2013-03-10">
<name>Naka Keiko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="34426" picture="128153.jpg">Suzaki Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53664" type="appears in" update="2013-04-27">
<rating votes="2">5.84</rating>
<name>Nanba Kana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60332.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53665" type="appears in" update="2013-04-27">
<rating votes="2">4.41</rating>
<name>Konaka Manabu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60329.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="5040" picture="88977.jpg">Kawahara Yoshihisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53666" type="appears in" update="2013-03-10">
<name>Yamazaki Saya</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="36264" picture="223629.jpg">Kitahara China</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53667" type="appears in" update="2013-03-10">
<name>Arishima Aki</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="32609" picture="87647.jpg">Sudou Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53668" type="appears in" update="2013-03-10">
<name>Kitani Mai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="20274" picture="52888.jpg">Nakajima Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55404" type="appears in" update="2013-04-27">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Josei Assistant</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60302.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="28304" picture="51542.jpg">Tanaka Satowa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55405" type="appears in" update="2013-04-27">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Dansei Assistant</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60303.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="18360" picture="48491.jpg">Yamazaki Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55409" type="appears in" update="2013-04-27">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Akechi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60314.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3712" picture="240126.jpg">Tamura Mutsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55410" type="appears in" update="2013-04-27">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Rokuzuka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60319.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="20383" picture="186909.jpg">Makiguchi Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55411" type="appears in" update="2013-04-27">
<name>Tokunaga Minoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60324.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="690" picture="187038.jpg">Higa Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55414" type="appears in" update="2013-04-27">
<rating votes="2">4.41</rating>
<name>Announcer</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60327.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55417" type="appears in" update="2013-04-27">
<rating votes="2">5.74</rating>
<name>Gouda Takami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60333.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3304" picture="186561.jpg">Hirano Fumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55418" type="appears in" update="2013-04-27">
<name>Tanaka Mika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60334.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2345" picture="22115.jpg">Oogame Asuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55419" type="appears in" update="2013-04-27">
<rating votes="2">5.84</rating>
<name>Ootsuki Nana-kan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60335.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1918" picture="225099.jpg">Sakurai Harumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55420" type="appears in" update="2013-04-27">
<rating votes="2">4.41</rating>
<name>Dansei Announcer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60336.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="30012" picture="130105.jpg">Odagaki Yuuta</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="144605" update="2013-01-28">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">余裕と落とし穴</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Leeway and Trap</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yoyuu to Otoshiana</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144606" update="2013-01-28">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラストと暗号</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending and Code</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Last to Angou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144607" update="2013-01-28">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">毎晩と融合</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Every Night and Collaboration</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maiban to Yuugou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144608" update="2013-01-28">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">意地と決断</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stubbornness and Decision</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iji to Ketsudan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144640" update="2013-01-12">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-10-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144641" update="2012-10-07">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-10-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144954" update="2012-10-25">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-11-24</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狙いと評価</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Aims and Evaluation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nerai to Hyouka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144955" update="2012-10-25">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-11-17</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">記念撮影と教室</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Photoshoot and Classroom</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kinen Satsuei to Kyoushitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144956" update="2012-10-25">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-11-10</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">パンチと1人立ち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Punch and Striking Out</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Punch to Hitoridachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144957" update="2012-10-25">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ステップとウォッチ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Step Up and Watch</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Step to Watch</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145786" update="2012-12-03">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-12-29</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">模倣と無意識</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Copycat and Unconscious</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mohou to Muishiki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145787" update="2013-01-28">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">熱血と完敗</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hot-Blooded and Total Defeat</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nekketsu to Kanpai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145788" update="2012-12-03">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">焦慮と逆転</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Anxiety and Turn Back</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shouryo to Gyakuten</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145789" update="2013-01-28">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-12-08</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">考察と挑発</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Consideration and Provocation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kousatsu to Chouhatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145790" update="2012-12-03">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-12-01</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">自信と覚悟</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Confidence and Preparation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jishin to Kakugo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146548" update="2013-01-28">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-05</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">連続と阻止</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Consecutive and Prevention</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Renzoku to Soshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146549" update="2013-01-05">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-02</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">週刊と月刊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Weekly and Monthly</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuukan to Gekkan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146550" update="2015-08-07">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-26</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゾンビと悪魔</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Zombie and Demon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zombie to Akuma</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146551" update="2015-08-07">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-19</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最終話とコメント</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Final Chapter and Comment</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saishuuwa to Comment</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146552" update="2013-01-05">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-12</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">巻頭とセンター</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Front Color and Centre Color</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kantou to Centre</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146601" update="2016-08-23">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-01-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146602" update="2013-01-12">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-01-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147340" update="2013-02-10">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-09</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">間延びと一気</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dragging On and Top Speed</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Manobi to Ikki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147423" update="2013-02-12">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-09</airdate>
<rating votes="7">9.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マイクと台本</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Microphone and Script</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mic to Daihon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147424" update="2013-09-27">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-02</airdate>
<rating votes="6">9.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">訂正と宣言</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Correction and Declaration</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Teisei to Sengen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147425" update="2013-02-12">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-23</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">温泉と意思確認</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hot Spring and Choices</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onsen to Ishi Kakunin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147426" update="2013-09-27">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-16</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">息継ぎとパーティー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Breather and Party</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikitsugi to Party</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147979" update="2013-03-07">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-30</airdate>
<rating votes="7">9.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢と現実</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dreams and Reality</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume to Genjitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147980" update="2013-03-07">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-16</airdate>
<rating votes="5">9.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あり方と終わり方</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Way and the End</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arikata to Owarikata</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157510" update="2014-01-19">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アニメ 『REVERSI』 PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anime "REVERSI" PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157511" update="2014-01-19">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-06-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラッコ11号最終回</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rakko 11-gou Saishuukai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170017" update="2015-07-19">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">デラマン. 第2弾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Deraman. 2</title>
<summary>Shows many of the mangakas` works. Main cast members also talk about which "Bakuman." works they would like to see animated.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="170018" recap="true" update="2015-07-19">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-09-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">デラマン.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Deraman.</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
