<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8864" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>11</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-04-11</startdate>
<enddate>2014-06-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ryuugajou Nanana no Maizoukin (2014)</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">류가죠 나나나의 매장금 (2014)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Ryuugajou Nanana no Maizoukin (TV)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">龍ヶ嬢七々々の埋蔵金(2014)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Nanana`s Buried Treasure</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Nanana`s Buried Treasure</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">龙娘七七七埋藏的宝藏</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="10602" type="Other">Ryuugajou Nanana no Maizoukin</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="10480" approval="12" total="16">Rokujouma no Shinryakusha!?</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="340905">really enjoyed the story.
nice character and design as well..
but dissappoint in the end...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="570341">Each episode is well done and interesting to watch, but overall story and character-building are definitely the weakest part, to the point where I still didn`t remember most of the names by ep11. While I can appreciate that last scene is there just for the viewer to put pieces together on one of the mysteries left unsolved, series ends so abruptly that creators are clearly betting on second season.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="324108">One of my favorites. Great story and characters, beautiful animation, a solid all around anime. For some reason it reminds me of The Goonies (probably the treasure hunting &amp; puzzles).</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.nanana.tv/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1303" type="Work">A-1 Pictures</name>
<name id="3020" type="Music">Monaca</name>
<name id="14377" type="Music">Hoashi Keigo</name>
<name id="2886" type="Direction">Kamei Kanta</name>
<name id="7716" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sakazaki Tadashi</name>
<name id="8138" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kawakami Tetsuya</name>
<name id="741" type="Work">Fuji TV</name>
<name id="802" type="Work">Movic</name>
<name id="13476" type="Work">Biglobe</name>
<name id="805" type="Work">Dentsu</name>
<name id="762" type="Work">Aniplex</name>
<name id="38970" type="Work">Kadokawa</name>
<name id="1303" type="Animation Work">A-1 Pictures</name>
<name id="44905" type="Work">Kyouraku Sangyou Holdings</name>
<name id="8138" type="Character Design">Kawakami Tetsuya</name>
<name id="1557" type="Series Composition">Kurata Hideyuki</name>
<name id="38900" type="Original Work">Ootorino Kazuma</name>
</creators>
<description>"I am going to build a place where young people can challenge themselves to reach their dreams!" — Ryuugajou Nanana
The seven genius students, known as the http://anidb.net/ch66815 [Great 7], launched a project to construct an artificial island called Nanae Island to realize their leader http://anidb.net/ch62276 [Ryuugajou Nanana]`s vision.
Twelve years later, with a total population of 100,000, and with as much as 80% of those inhabitants being students, Nanae Island has prospered as a special student zone. One of the island`s latest residents is http://anidb.net/ch62888 [Yama Juugo], a high school student who has just transferred to the island, after being disowned by his father. One day, Juugo finds in his apartment the earth-bound spirit of the late Ryuugajou Nanana, who was murdered 10 years ago! Juugo`s plan of living alone is suddenly thwarted by this strange room-mate...
Source: AniplexUSA</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1737">4.98</permanent>
<temporary count="1745">6.64</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>149800.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15759</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>25117</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>21561</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.nanana.tv/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ryūgajō_Nanana_no_Maizōkin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>龍ヶ嬢七々々の埋蔵金</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3335</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>347855</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16997</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>nananas-buried-treasure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="618" parentid="2565" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>trap</name>
<description>A trap is a plot device where a male character is mistaken for a female, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the male (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the male, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the male character as a female; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through his behaviour, and/or language. A male character misinterpreted by others as female, without action from the male (explicitly feminine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t1637 [reverse trap].
Note: the tag image is from http://anidb.net/a10475 [Himegoto].</description>
<picurl>161537.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2072" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>maid</name>
<description>A maid is a female employed in domestic service. They usually wear uniforms. Since their nature is to be obedient and serve their goshujin-sama (master), they are one of the most desired types of women in Japan, a dream of every Japanese man, particularly http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku]. Often seen in so-called Maid Cafes in Akihabara, where male customers can for a little time enjoy the feeling of being served by a woman. The male gender opposite is the butler.</description>
<picurl>4954.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2535" parentid="1152" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-18">
<name>ghost</name>
<description>In traditional belief, a ghost is the soul or spirit of a deceased person or animal that can appear, in visible form or other manifestation, to the living. Descriptions of the apparition of ghosts vary widely: The mode of manifestation can range from an invisible presence to translucent or wispy shapes, to realistic, life-like visions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3865" parentid="6153" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>noitaminA</name>
<description>noitaminA (ノイタミナ) – Animation written backwards – is a Fuji Television programming block, devoted to anime, broadcast each Thursday night from 00:45 to 1:15. It was launched with the intention of expanding the target audience beyond the typical young male demographic.
The timeslot was expanded from half an hour to a full hour in 2010, and now airs Thursday nights from 00:45 to 1:45.
noitaminA aired its first non-anime series in 2010, with the premiere of the live-action adaptation of Moyashimon. On April 15, 2010, Fuji TV and FUNimation announced an agreement that allows FUNimation to simulcast series from the noitaminA block in North America within an hour of their airing in Japan.</description>
<picurl>36897.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3896" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-23">
<name>bloodless wounds</name>
<description>No matter what weapon is used in what way to attack, hurt or kill somebody, there won`t be blood. You may see ripped clothes and smoke coming from the deadly wounds, but that`s it.
So if you have an aversion towards the red liquid but still love some action going on - this is the anime for you!</description>
<picurl>39189.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4052" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-23">
<name>treasure hunting</name>
<description>A significant part of the anime centres on the protagonists` search for some obscure artefact or other treasure, an epic adventure and wild goose chase for something unusual and quite valuable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5773" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-14">
<name>secret organisation</name>
<description>A secret organisation or secret society is an organisation whose activities and inner functioning are concealed from non-members. The society may or may not attempt to conceal its existence itself. Examples of historical and existing secret societies include Freemasonry, the Knights Templar, the Rosicrucians, Skull and Bones, the Thule Society, and the Illuminati.</description>
<picurl>192876.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5916" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-26">
<name>product placement</name>
<description>Otherwise known as a "plug" or "writing commercials right into a show". The practice of prominently displaying or talking about a recognizable product in a program, in exchange for some consideration from the manufacturer, usually monetary. (Source: TV Tropes)
Particularly notorious example, Pizza Hut for the involvement with Code Geass, Darker than Black and other series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6021" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>gender bender</name>
<description>Term used to refer to a person who takes on the role of their opposite gender. This often only reaches to the extent of cross-dressing (involving physical appearance and clothing only), but in rarer cases, involves a total gender swap (which seems to be more common in anime) - where the willing or unwilling victim receives a body opposite of their original gender (either permanently or temporarily), with all natural parts per their new body fully (or just all-out amply) included.
Example of cross-dressing gender bender: "Maria+Holic"
Examples of body-swap gender bender: "Kashimashi: Girl meets Girl", "Birdy the Mighty Decode"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6078" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-23">
<name>gotta catch them all</name>
<description>A typical plot or sub-plot for many shows. Either the cast or somebody else, that being often the main antagonist, embarks on a quest to collect things, shiny things. Things that are said to grant simple wishes or even do miracles like bringing people back to life, destroying the whole world, galaxy, universe and in rare cases turning the hero into the greatest Pokemon Master. Those things can be weapons, lost technology, magical artefacts, pieces of a giant magical artefact and in some cases even people or little critters.
The point is, there`s stuff to collect!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6083" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>master-servant relationship</name>
<description>To some genres, this would suggest a genuine pairing where one person exists to serve another person, such as in some action/dramas where the pair becomes united by destiny as partners — fighting or battles between different pairs/partners will usually be a dominant part of the story.
In other genres, this suggests a relationship where one person may be occupied as or even forcefully treated as a servant or slave to the other who designates themself the master — these services usually apply anywhere from tsundere/romantic-comedies to ecchi or to the more extreme in hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="62276" type="main character in" update="2013-12-12">
<rating votes="46">5.64</rating>
<name>Ryuugajou Nanana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147077.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38109" picture="155778.jpg">Tanabe Rui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62888" type="main character in" update="2014-04-11">
<rating votes="29">5.88</rating>
<name>Yama Juugo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149796.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3155" picture="24137.jpg">Ono Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63823" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-07">
<rating votes="58">7.06</rating>
<name>Ikkyuu Tensai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149798.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63824" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-17">
<rating votes="25">3.36</rating>
<name>Hoshino Daruku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149797.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63825" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-07">
<rating votes="20">1.98</rating>
<name>Yuiga Isshin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149799.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1692" picture="224934.jpg">Okitsu Kazuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="64814" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-21">
<rating votes="36">7.36</rating>
<name>Fugi Yukihime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150582.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="64815" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-21">
<rating votes="7">4.04</rating>
<name>Tsurezure Kagetora</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150581.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5978" picture="170983.jpg">Hayashi Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="64816" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-21">
<rating votes="14">2.88</rating>
<name>Todomatsu Shuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150583.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="64817" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-21">
<rating votes="28">5.23</rating>
<name>Maboro Shiki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150584.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23686" picture="224554.jpg">Uchiyama Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="64818" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-21">
<rating votes="23">2.40</rating>
<name>Ibara Yuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150580.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37089" picture="228978.jpg">Suzuki Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65262" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-27">
<rating votes="13">5.68</rating>
<name>Yoshino Saki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150860.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20806" picture="182700.jpg">Kuno Misaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65263" type="appears in" update="2014-02-27">
<rating votes="5">4.80</rating>
<name>Yumeji Yurika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150861.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65264" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-27">
<rating votes="7">4.52</rating>
<name>Tsujimi Tetsunoshin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150859.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3709" picture="84359.jpg">Hosoya Yoshimasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65265" type="appears in" update="2014-02-27">
<rating votes="3">5.41</rating>
<name>Kurosu Sansa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150858.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1918" picture="225099.jpg">Sakurai Harumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66498" type="appears in" update="2014-04-10">
<rating votes="4">4.50</rating>
<name>Maboro Shiki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>10609.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="66499" type="appears in" update="2014-04-10">
<rating votes="4">5.62</rating>
<name>Kurosu Sansa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153452.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="66517" type="appears in" update="2014-06-06">
<rating votes="2">5.07</rating>
<name>Konjou Kasumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Konjou Kasumi is Nanana`s friend who wrote Nanana`s Manual. She founded and was the first president of Adventure Club.</description>
<picture>156383.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66815" type="appears in" update="2014-06-13">
<name>Great 7</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Members:
* http://anidb.net/ch62276 [Ryuugajou Nanana] - head of Great 7, who proposed the Nanae Islands project
* Ikkaku Shunjuu - adminstrator of the islands
* Mutsumi Koma - master architect, built many buildings on Nanae Islands
* http://anidb.net/ch64817 [Maboro Shiki] - landlady of the Happy House apartment
* Futaba Saito
* http://anidb.net/ch65265 [Kurosu Sansa] - leader of the Three Skulls
* Kakyou Uzuki</description>
</character>
<character id="66816" type="appears in" update="2014-04-19">
<name>Bouken-bu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="67138" type="appears in" update="2014-05-03">
<name>Juugo no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67410" type="appears in" update="2014-05-12">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Sanada Hajiki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155513.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38670" picture="185856.jpg">Kobayashi Yuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67482" type="appears in" update="2014-05-15">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Kisaragi Shizuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155629.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39944" picture="155630.jpg">Mayama Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67483" type="appears in" update="2014-05-15">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Misaki Kamome</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A worker at the hot spring inn.
It`s in fact a disguise of phantom thief Hundred Faces Todomatsu Shuu.</description>
<picture>155628.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32020" picture="127735.jpg">Murakawa Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67484" type="appears in" update="2014-05-15">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Hino Yumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A worker at hot spring inn.</description>
<picture>155627.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32035" picture="151695.jpg">Muranaka Tomo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67590" type="appears in" update="2014-05-23">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Juugo (Youshouki)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Young Juugo.</description>
<picture>155885.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36907" picture="135730.jpg">Kino Futaba</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67591" type="appears in" update="2014-05-23">
<rating votes="3">6.49</rating>
<name>Yukihime (Youshouki)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Young Yukihime.</description>
<picture>155884.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67764" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-08-02">
<rating votes="11">2.77</rating>
<name>Ikusaba Hiiyo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159011.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67765" type="appears in" update="2014-06-02">
<rating votes="2">5.07</rating>
<name>Suruga Aya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156183.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32939" picture="237666.jpg">Kakuma Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67830" type="appears in" update="2014-06-06">
<rating votes="2">5.07</rating>
<name>Fuwa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156384.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34407" picture="202909.jpg">Suwa Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="159197" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-11</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勘当されて島流し</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Disowned and Exiled</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Déshérité et exilé</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kandousarete Shimanagashi</title>
<summary>Yama Juugo is a high school boy who has moved to Nanae Island, also known as the Special Student Zone, after being kicked out of the house by his father. He has chosen to begin his solo life in room 202 of the Happy House, a one-room apartment plus kitchen with separate bath and toilet, including furniture, appliances, and extras for 5,000 yen per month. But when he enters the room, he sees a girl relaxing inside, watching TV...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653293</identifier>
<identifier>nananas-buried-treasure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159198" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-02</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢とか野望とか否定とか憧れとか</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dreams and Ambitions and Denial and Attraction</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rêves, ambitions, refus, admiration</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume toka Yabou toka Hitei toka Akogare toka</title>
<summary>After Juugo and Tensai escape from the Rising Building, Juugo receives an email from Tensai saying that Isshin plans to sell the Wizard`s Cane to Ikkaku Shunjuu.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653299</identifier>
<identifier>nananas-buried-treasure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159199" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地上1000mの《遺跡》</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ruins 1,000 Meters Above Ground</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Des ruines à 1 000 m de haut</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chijou 1000m no Iseki</title>
<summary>After clearing the ruins in the classroom, Juugo, Tensai, and Daruku become members of the Adventure Club. At club president Yuiga Isshin`s request, Juugo undergoes a trial administered by Nanana to get her to share the location of the next treasure. This complete, the Adventure Club sets off to the Rising Building. As they search for the ruins, Tensai quickly finds a certain door...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653297</identifier>
<identifier>nananas-buried-treasure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159200" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-18</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">七重島第三高等部・冒険部</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Nanae Island Third High School Adventure Club</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Lycée 3 de Nanaejima - Club d`aventures</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanae-jima Dai San Koutoubu Boukenbu</title>
<summary>Juugo picks up a jewel that fell from the sky as he was on his way home from the convenience store. It turns out to be one of Nanana`s Collection: the The Eye of Yuguthos. Juugo is shocked that Nanana`s Collection really exists. Meanwhile, the master detective Ikkyuu Tensai and her assistant, Hoshino Daruku, pay a visit to room 202 of the Happy House in search of the stolen jewel.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653295</identifier>
<identifier>nananas-buried-treasure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159202" update="2014-04-10">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-04-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159203" update="2014-04-10">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-04-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159473" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-30</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">奇妙な来訪者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Strange Visitor</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un étrange visiteur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimyou na Raihousha</title>
<summary>At the start of class one day, a first year student comes to see Tensai. After speaking with her, Tensai returns in a bad mood and walks out of the class. The same day, one of the people Juugo met in the Tsukuyomi District, Tetsu, transfers into Third High School.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653307</identifier>
<identifier>nananas-buried-treasure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159474" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-23</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪党のお悩み相談</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Counseling for Bad Guys</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Hotline du cœur pour un méchant</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akutou no Onayamisoudan</title>
<summary>Juugo has been cowering in fear in a corner of his room while Nanana has been on the rampage. Finally the delivery he`s been waiting for arrives, and he presents Nanana with its contents, special thick pudding from the hot springs town, along with an apology for selling off her video games to pay his utility bill. But there was something else hidden in the package...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653305</identifier>
<identifier>nananas-buried-treasure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159475" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-16</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いざ, 温泉街へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the Hot Springs Town</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">En route pour les sources chaudes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iza, Onsenmachi e</title>
<summary>The Adventure Club has come to a hot springs town. In the hallway of their inn, Juugo sees Yukihime with a friend of hers, but she ignores him. That evening, Isshin shows everyone the layout of the nearby house that he has brought them to explore, and Tensai pinpoints the room that the ruins are in.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653303</identifier>
<identifier>nananas-buried-treasure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159476" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-09</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミッション・インポッシブル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mission Impossible</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mission impossible</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mission Impossible</title>
<summary>The Adventure Club is back in action. Isshin proposes that they plan an overnight trip to a hot springs town on the west side of the island, where he suspects they`ll find the next ruins.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653301</identifier>
<identifier>nananas-buried-treasure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160160" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-20</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">八真重護が決める覚悟</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Resolve of Yama Juugo</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La détermination de Yama Jugo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yama Juugo ga Kimeru Kakugo</title>
<summary>Isshin`s plan has rendered Ikusaba`s "Shadowfins" useless, and victory is right before the Adventure Club`s eyes... but then Ikusaba unleashes the power of his other Nanana`s Collection treasure, leaving Juugo in serious trouble. Then Tensai steps in, telling Ikusaba she`s figured out his power and offering him a proposal.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653313</identifier>
<identifier>nananas-buried-treasure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160161" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-13</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">対決</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Showdown</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Confrontation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiketsu</title>
<summary>Hoping to clear the ruins in Southred Mall before Ikusaba, the Adventure Club follows Nanana`s hints to find the entrance to the ruins. But the entrance is too visible to passers-by, so they agree to come back that night to conquer it. Back at the Happy House, Nanana asks Juugo several questions, but Juugo is too anxious about Ikusaba to talk.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653311</identifier>
<identifier>nananas-buried-treasure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160162" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-06</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦場緋夜と吉野咲希についての考察</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Study of Ikusaba Hiiyo and Yoshino Saki</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Étude sur Ikusaba Hiyo et Yoshino Saki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikusaba Hiiyo to Yoshino Saki ni Tsuite no Kousatsu</title>
<summary>Tensai and Daruku have not been seen since meeting with Suruga Aya. Though he`s worried about them, Juugo goes out to have fun at Southred Mall with Yumeji, Tetsu, and Yun. Ikusaba Hiiyo has been watching them strengthen their friendships and follows them, while Tsurezure Kagetora follows him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653309</identifier>
<identifier>nananas-buried-treasure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162736" update="2014-09-23">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2014-06-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">SDキャラショートムービー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">SD Character Short Movie 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">SD Chara Short Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162863" update="2015-04-21">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2014-09-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">SDキャラショートムービー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">SD Character Short Movie 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">SD Chara Short Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162864" update="2015-04-21">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2014-08-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">SDキャラショートムービー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">SD Character Short Movie 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">SD Chara Short Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162865" update="2015-04-21">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2014-07-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">SDキャラショートムービー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">SD Character Short Movie 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">SD Chara Short Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168081" update="2015-04-21">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2014-11-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">SDキャラショートムービー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">SD Character Short Movie 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">SD Chara Short Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168082" update="2015-04-21">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2014-10-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">SDキャラショートムービー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">SD Character Short Movie 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">SD Chara Short Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
