<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8886" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2012-07-08</startdate>
<enddate>2012-09-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kyoukaisen-jou no Horizon II</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Horizon on the Middle of Nowhere 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Kyoukai Senjou no Horizon S2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Horizon 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Horizon II</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">horizon2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">境界線上のホライゾン II</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Horizon in the Middle of Nowhere II</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">境界线上的地平线 第二季</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8323" type="Prequel">Kyoukaisen-jou no Horizon</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="12">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="489594">I really enjoyed watching the first season and the second one is far better. I understood what this anime was all about from the start. I know some people find it hard to understand, but it`s alright. Understanding the anime or not. You will still like this anime. Tori might be the guy of the "impossibles", but when he gets serious I got to say. He is right on the point and it makes sense. I REALLY RECOMMEND this anime. I give it a 4.9/5</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="539006">I like it but most of the time I don`t know what`s going.
Perhaps that`s why I find it intriguing...LOL</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="296685">It`s still as baffling as ever. Good though.

Despite the confusion.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="432603">Great story with epic characters, if you love ss1 then this is something you must see. A little bit confuse and different to original novel but overall the studio still adapts it into great anime.
Can`t wait til ss3 (if they plans to make it)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="473211">For me it`s even better than the S1 cause things just got real and new characters are really nice add to the cast. But if you disliked S1 don`t even bother to watch it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="303237">way better then first season  ,still it could be even better if it was polished more</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="361286">Pretty good anime if you understood first season. It`s not retarded, it`s just little complex and everything makes sense.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="556522">it`s one of those anime that you can say "what the hek? i dont understand a thing!" but try to watch it and look up some facts. its one awesome anime. it has a very vast universe about it. and production did the best they could to make such story fit to a twelve season anime. (i read some sources that the first vol. of this has more than a thousand pages simply for introduction ONLY). haven`t tried reading it because there are no translations yet.... it has a simple story. but it`s really one great anime!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="260717">http://kyoukaisen.tumblr.com/neta1

USE THIS. Everything starts to make just a little more sense. This anime is already amazing, with great animation and music, but understanding the smaller nuances really brings things to life.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="127475">In a sentence: Very, very enjoyable even without knowing what`s going on.

Appears to me as an underrated anime due to its complexity and depth (and, to some, excessive fanservice - not for me). However, watching the anime without any additional material (blogs, novel, explanation on characters) would only let you enjoy the art and superficial story.

There`s a lot going on that doesn`t hinder you to enjoy the anime if you don`t know them, but if your excuse for not enjoying the anime is not knowing what is going on, then you better look for additional materials.

This is the first anime which I watched from beginning to end enjoying it immensely without knowing what`s going on. Then I rewatched it after researching more of the backstory and it adds to the fun.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="516857">another compliment for the creator, Tenzou Clothunit is this season main character, S3 posibility is high, many new character, and a quick glimpse about the leader of another faction, can`t wait to see what kinda fate waiting for Musashi</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="116115">This is a very good show, with fantastic characters, epic moments and an intriguing story, but should be watched after understanding the background. The LN it`s based on is a huge work of many books but there are excellent intros in anime blogs that will introduce you to that world and its rules (for instance, google "horizon stilts"). Absolutely read them, you will enjoy the show on a whole new level and even the most insignificant detail and character will find their right place. I was confused at the beginning, but but after I was introduced to the Horizon universe, I had to re-watch everything from season 1 and at the end, I was astonished by how well everything is orchestrated. Truly a masterpiece.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://genesis-horizon.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="9890" type="Chief Animation Direction">Fujii Tomoyuki</name>
<name id="726" type="Animation Work">Sunrise</name>
<name id="14275" type="Character Design">Aikei Yukiko</name>
<name id="11678" type="Character Design">Suzuki Kanta</name>
<name id="9890" type="Character Design">Fujii Tomoyuki</name>
<name id="14204" type="Character Design">Nishizawa Shin`ya</name>
<name id="3405" type="Series Composition">Urahata Tatsuhiko</name>
<name id="24066" type="Original Work">Kawakami Minoru</name>
<name id="5371" type="Direction">Ono Manabu</name>
<name id="10106" type="Music">Katou Tatsuya</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a light novel series written by http://anidb.net/cr24066 [Kawakami Minoru] and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr28785 [Satoyasu].
After claiming sovereignty over the Japanese prefecture Mikawa, the flying city-ship http://anidb.net/ch38183 [Musashi] seeks refuge by retreating to England. While initial talks with the reluctant ruler of England seem promising, sudden chaos ensues as the Musashi finds itself in the middle of a re-enactment of the 1588 AD invasion of England by the Spanish Armada. Now the students of the Ariadust Academy must use their unique abilities to gain allies while simultaneously defending the resurrected heir to the Mikawa throne, http://anidb.net/ch30906 [Horizon], against the various world superpowers which are now their enemies.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1149">5.93</permanent>
<temporary count="1158">7.11</temporary>
<review count="2">6.58</review>
</ratings>
<picture>84886.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14205</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12487</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5127</identifier>
<identifier>xzvjoc</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://genesis-horizon.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Horizon_in_the_Middle_of_Nowhere</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>境界線上のホライゾン</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2605</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>343094</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15033</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=E5n4QKT3Sno</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=4aMUcWI5MqQ</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=KMrfO2Pup64</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=NLJsfD8ImdY</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=SSCDxAyggrg</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=-pgJ4xgJtuw</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=4tDnFFYg2Xw</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=JcNEQXGiryU</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>horizon-in-the-middle-of-nowhere</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="904" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-18">
<name>eccentric</name>
<description>Because normal people are no fun.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1609" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-03-01">
<name>elf</name>
<description>The origin of Elves (Norse; álfar(elves), álfr(elf)) can be found in ancient Norse mythology, in which, elves are described as divine, or near-divine, race of humanoids (Vættir), likened to the Æsir. In common description they are described as sage and immortal beings occupying the threshold between humans and the gods. In some cases humans that were beloved by the gods became elves within their lives. Ancient Elves are delineated into a pair of similar but distinct races; Light Elves (Ljósálfar) and Dark Elves (Svartálfar), each originating from separate homes within the nine worlds of Yggdrasil. Within the Poetic Edda the differences are commonly ascribed as:
"There is one place there that is called the Elf Home (Álfheimr which is the elven city). People live there that are named the light elves (Ljósálfar). But the dark elves (Dökkálfar) live below in earth, in caves and the dark forest and they are unlike them in appearance - and more unlike them in reality. The Light Elves are brighter than the sun in appearance, but the Dark Elves are blacker than pitch." (Snorri, Gylfaginning 17, Prose Edda)</description>
<picurl>63489.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2346" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-14">
<name>angel</name>
<description>An angel is a supernatural being, said to be the messenger of God. They are often depicted as human beings with a pair of white feathered wings and sometimes with a halo.
In contrast, a fallen angel who has turned evil will be depicted with black wings.</description>
<picurl>35521.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2535" parentid="1152" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-18">
<name>ghost</name>
<description>In traditional belief, a ghost is the soul or spirit of a deceased person or animal that can appear, in visible form or other manifestation, to the living. Descriptions of the apparition of ghosts vary widely: The mode of manifestation can range from an invisible presence to translucent or wispy shapes, to realistic, life-like visions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2572" parentid="2282" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-09">
<name>ninja</name>
<description>A ninja was a covert agent or mercenary of feudal Japan specializing in unorthodox arts of war.
The functions of the ninja included espionage, sabotage, infiltration, and assassination, as well as open combat in certain situations.
The ninja, using covert methods of waging war, were contrasted with the samurai, who had strict rules about honor and combat.</description>
<picurl>244347.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2730" parentid="2848" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>exhibitionism</name>
<description>Exhibitionism is the act of exposing in a public or semi-public context the parts of one`s body that are not normally exposed. That may be done to prompt sexual arousal, but many forms of exhibitionism actually mean to create humour or disparagement through shock value or mockery. The idea of exhibitionism is closely tied to the notions of decency and modesty in dressing, and as such is highly dependent on one`s own cultural background. Certain forms of exhibitionism may be considered indecent exposure, and thus in many jurisdictions they may lead to civil or criminal charges. While both deal with the lack of clothing and may in certain cases overlap, exhibitionism is very different from and not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t2304 [nudism].</description>
<picurl>162657.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2867" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>politics</name>
<description>From commies to fat capitalist pigs, all the stuff done by the "guys with the power", mainly evil tactics for gaining more power over the masses.
Watching this title may remind you why CNN is boring.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3252" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>history is written by the victors</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3635" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-01-01">
<name>sea battles</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3843" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>saving the world</name>
<description>While villains love to take over the world or cause the end of the world as we know it, the heroes are most likely motivated by the polar opposite, saving the world. A fairly simple plot/motivation related to for great justice and what not, this trope is pretty broad and very common for many stories not focused on character interaction only.
Source: TV Trope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3876" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>folklore</name>
<description>Folklore, or simply Lore, are the traditions of a culture, subculture, or group, in the form of legends, music, proverbs, jokes, popular beliefs, fairy tales, stories, tall tales and customs. In usage, there is a continuum between folklore and mythology.
Folklore is generally divided into four areas of study: physical artifacts, transmissible entities and stories, culture and technologies, and behaviors and rituals.
[From Wikipedia]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3898" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-11">
<name>science and magic coexist</name>
<description>In this anime science and magic do not exclude each other. Magic here is actually very advanced, artefact- and/or ritual-based science.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3953" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-06">
<name>in medias res</name>
<description>In medias res, also medias in res (Latin for "into the midst of affairs (lit. into mid-affairs)"), refers to a literary and artistic technique where the narrative starts in the middle of the story instead of from its beginning. It is generally a plot-driven concept rather than a character-driven one; though characters are commonly used to provide the backstory. The characters, setting, and conflict are often introduced through a series of flashbacks or through characters relating past events to each other.
Probably originating from an oral tradition, the technique is a convention of epic poetry, one of the earliest and most prominent examples in Western literature being Homer`s Odyssey and Iliad. Virgil`s Aeneid began the tradition in literature of imitating Homer, continued in Torquato Tasso`s Jerusalem Delivered, John Milton`s Paradise Lost and "Inferno" from Dante`s Divine Comedy. George Lucas`s Star Wars saga was told using in medias res.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4048" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>Japanese mythology</name>
<description>Japanese mythology is a system of beliefs that embraces Shinto and Buddhist traditions as well as agriculture-based folk religion. The Shinto pantheon alone consists of an uncountable number of kami (Japanese for "gods" or "spirits").
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4461" parentid="6234" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-21">
<name>seven deadly sins</name>
<description>The seven deadly sins, also known as the capital vices or cardinal sins, is a grouping and classification of vices of Christian origin. Behaviors or habits are classified under this category if they directly give birth to other immoralities. According to the standard list, they are pride, greed, lust, envy, gluttony, wrath, and sloth, which are also contrary to the seven virtues. These sins are often thought to be abuses or excessive versions of one`s natural faculties or passions (for example, gluttony abuses one`s desire to eat).
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>205317.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5485" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-28">
<name>penis jokes</name>
<description>A penis or other phallic object is used as a device to elicit laughter from the viewer. This also includes indirect references to such objects provided the intent is clearly the same.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5850" parentid="2869" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-13">
<name>absurdly powerful student council</name>
<description>A student council is a student-managed body inside a school which engages in administrative affairs, usually usually working in a partnership with management, staff and parents, for the benefit of the whole school environment. In real life, a student council holds no actual power; however, in many anime/manga, they have an insane amount of power, which usually allows them to overrule nearly everyone else (the school board, the mayor, the prime minster, you name it). In those cases, that device is explored as a major source of slapstick comedy.</description>
<picurl>70561.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6021" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>gender bender</name>
<description>Term used to refer to a person who takes on the role of their opposite gender. This often only reaches to the extent of cross-dressing (involving physical appearance and clothing only), but in rarer cases, involves a total gender swap (which seems to be more common in anime) - where the willing or unwilling victim receives a body opposite of their original gender (either permanently or temporarily), with all natural parts per their new body fully (or just all-out amply) included.
Example of cross-dressing gender bender: "Maria+Holic"
Examples of body-swap gender bender: "Kashimashi: Girl meets Girl", "Birdy the Mighty Decode"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6028" parentid="2876" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-10-12">
<name>Shintoism</name>
<description>Shintoism presents a blessed being or creature that governs over areas of terrain, general space of existence, or an individual object (be it alive or inanimate). Everything has its own "spiritual essence".
Defined as the earliest Japanese thoughts of an unified religion, the word Shinto comes from the Chinese hanzi "神道", combining two kanji: "shin" (神), meaning gods or spirits; and "tō" (道), meaning a philosophical path or study.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6029" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-04-08">
<name>mundane made awesome</name>
<description>Sometimes normal just doesn`t cut it. Eating: you put food in your mouth and chew. Playing sports: you throw a ball around. You need to make it awesome, no matter how mundane it is.
Let`s throw in some gripping orchestral music, lighting changes, different camera angles, something! Don`t write like a man, write like an evil overlord! Exaggerate your expressions and gestures, speak with excessive intonation, and if all else fails, throw in some close-ups, slow motion, and ominous Latin chanting! With practice, even you can turn something like eating chips into an epic battle of light and dark, blinding the viewer with sheer awesomeness.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>149443.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6234" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>motifs</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="30906" type="main character in" update="2011-12-25">
<rating votes="40">6.41</rating>
<name>Horizon Ariadust</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A cybernetic doll that works at the Blue Thunder bakery. She strongly resembles a girl killed ten years age.
Later it had discovered that she is the Armor of Deadly Sins. Because both of her masters were died, she was ordered to suicide. Students of Musashi try to prevent this From happening so they start a war</description>
<picture>73039.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="245" picture="46862.jpg">Chihara Minori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30907" type="main character in" update="2012-01-04">
<rating votes="43">5.95</rating>
<name>Aoi Toori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tori is the Head of Musashi Ariadust Academy`s Supreme Federation and President of the student council. His athletics and grades are average, and he`s both self and publicly recognized as an incompetent leader. However, because he doesn`t know the meaning of being depressed and has an incredibly cheerful attitude, he`s very respected nonetheless. He knows a lot of strip jokes, and often plays the fool.</description>
<picture>73040.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32120" type="main character in" update="2011-12-25">
<rating votes="59">7.32</rating>
<name>Neit Mitotsudaira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nate Mitotsudaira is a knight of Hexagone Française and successor of the Mitotsudaira Clan. Half-human, half-wolf. Although she cannot transform into a wolf form, she possesses the form`s great strength. She uses her special weapon, her silver chains, to great effect.
Because of her chivalrous nature and strong sense of duty, Nate feels very protective of the land on the Musashi, which technically falls within her family`s domain.
She is against the idea of saving horizon. But after being defeated by a silly method of using Mukai Suzu as a bait, she joins the team.
Source: kyoukaisen.tumblr.com</description>
<picture>73037.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32121" type="main character in" update="2011-12-25">
<rating votes="33">6.74</rating>
<name>Honda Masazumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The vice president of the student council. She`s very serious, skilled in debate, and aiming to become a politician. In the past she underwent gender reassignment surgery in order to succeed the family name, but certain circumstances forced her to stop the process part way. Her lack of breasts is a result of the surgery, but Tori treats her as a girl with a tiny chest.</description>
<picture>73034.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32122" type="main character in" update="2011-12-25">
<rating votes="50">7.32</rating>
<name>Asama Tomo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Shinto priestess of the Sengen Shrine and a childhood friend of Tori and Kimi. She uses the bow and arrow as her weapon and can shoot with high precision with the aid of Konoha, her artificial left eye.</description>
<picture>73036.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32123" type="main character in" update="2012-01-04">
<rating votes="70">7.83</rating>
<name>Aoi Kimi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Toori`s older sister. Both she and Toori were born on the same year, so they are of the same grade level. Bad with ghosts. Is a follower in the god of eroticism and dance. Dislikes her name, "Kimi" for some reason, so she changes it habitually. Though she calls Toori a foolish little brother, she also has another side that cares for him.
She was the person who tried to take Toori back to normal life after Horizon`s Death. Its said that she only cried for Toori and so she never complains about any other pain, since she believes they are not comparable to that time earlier.
Source: kyoukaisen.tumblr.com</description>
<picture>73035.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33174" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="33">6.49</rating>
<name>Adele Barrufet</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65300.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3622" picture="214935.jpg">Oohashi Ayuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33175" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-01">
<rating votes="11">4.52</rating>
<name>Kiyonari Urukiaga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65255.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="371" picture="166173.jpg">Kuroda Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33176" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-25">
<rating votes="16">6.97</rating>
<name>Shirojiro Bertoni</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Works as one of the youngest merchants in the Musashi Business Administration, and is contracted to the god of commerce. Makes decisions using profitability as his basis. In other words - a miser. He is The Partner of Heidi and only she can convince her to do something he is not interested about by saying "its about money"</description>
<picture>1697.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33177" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-25">
<rating votes="7">5.16</rating>
<name>Toussaint Neshinbara</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Toussaint Neshinbara has a very dry personality that penetrates even the thickest atmosphere of tomfoolery, yet is also fond of history, an aspiring novelist, and a romanticist. Is in charge of strategics planning and command during wartime.</description>
<picture>1694.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3712" picture="240126.jpg">Tamura Mutsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33178" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="6">4.52</rating>
<name>Noriki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1702.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="99" picture="139554.jpg">Hirakawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33179" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-25">
<rating votes="24">6.44</rating>
<name>Heidi Oogezavalour</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Heidi Augesvarer is Shirojiro Bertoni`s partner, both in business and in personal life. Although she constantly has a smile on, she is as much of a miser as Shirojiro is. She is always accompanied by her Maus named Erimaki.
Source: kyoukaisen.tumblr.com</description>
<picture>1699.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33180" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-25">
<rating votes="35">6.66</rating>
<name>Marga Naruze</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A black-haired, 6-winged white magic user. Also affiliated with the manga club. Her personality is rather rebellious, but she always puts Margot above all else.</description>
<picture>65280.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22170" picture="226837.jpg">Nitta Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33181" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-25">
<rating votes="35">6.80</rating>
<name>Margot Night</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A blonde, 6-winged black magic user, as well as Naruze`s lover. Always smiling. Freely uses her abilities in flight, characteristic of magicians. Pursues a career in the transportation industry.
Source: kyoukaisen.tumblr.com</description>
<picture>65256.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33183" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-25">
<rating votes="30">8.29</rating>
<name>Mukai Suzu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Suzu Mukai is a blind girl who acts as a "stopper" for the intense cast surrounding her. Highly perceptive, and is able to detect phenomena that escape most people`s attention.
She was the Childhood Friend of Toori and Horizon and it seems that she has feelings for Toori.</description>
<picture>1700.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33184" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-01">
<rating votes="15">3.21</rating>
<name>Azuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1944.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="330" picture="171543.jpg">Morinaga Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33185" type="main character in" update="2011-12-25">
<rating votes="16">6.23</rating>
<name>Tenzou Crossunite</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A highly talented ninja, excelling in Ninjutsu and intelligence. Though very nice in character, he is also quite the pervert, openly declaring his love for blonde-haired, big-breasted women.</description>
<picture>65251.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33186" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="24">6.24</rating>
<name>Naomasa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65283.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="453" picture="45925.jpg">Shindou Kei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35274" type="appears in" update="2011-12-25">
<rating votes="8">2.41</rating>
<name>Innocentius</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Innocentius is the representative of K.P.A.Italia, and Pope-President of the top school, K.P.A. Scuola; holds a lot of influence around the whole world. Owner of the Armor of Deadly Sins, Steisos Porneia (Lust). Highly ambitious; intends to expand his power and influence under the pretext of recreating history.</description>
<picture>1969.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35553" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-25">
<rating votes="30">7.24</rating>
<name>Oriotorai Makiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Makiko Oriotorai Class 3-Plum`s homeroom teacher. Self-centered in both speech and action, but is a very personable teacher who always thinks of her students. Has incredible physical power, to the point where she is called a "Real Amazon". Loves alcohol.
Source: kyoukaisen.tumblr.com</description>
<picture>1689.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="208" picture="20458.jpg">Shiraishi Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35554" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-25">
<rating votes="11">6.36</rating>
<name>Miriam Poke</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Confined to a wheelchair; thus, conducts studies at home. Has a strong character, is very tactless, and will say anything that comes to her mind. However, she has very gentle eyes.</description>
<picture>1946.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1676" picture="144276.jpg">Matayoshi Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35555" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="3">4.48</rating>
<name>Yoshinao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1952.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="231" picture="23486.jpg">Madono Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35556" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="8">5.81</rating>
<name>Sanyou Mitsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1949.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="550" picture="151677.jpg">Shimizu Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35557" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="4">1.68</rating>
<name>Itou Kenji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1710.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2145" picture="82117.jpg">Miyashita Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35558" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="2">3.04</rating>
<name>Ohiroshiki Ginji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65313.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="434" picture="41082.jpg">Shiraishi Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35559" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-20">
<rating votes="49">6.49</rating>
<name>Honda Futayo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Futayo Honda is a student of Mikawa, and is Masazumi Honda`s second cousin. She is Tadakatsu Honda`s daughter, one of the Four Divine Matsudaira Kings, and is the head of the Mikawa Security Force. Because she has only ever received combat training from Tadakatsu, she is incredibly clueless about the world.
She starts a battle with Musashi students against the idea to save Horizon, but was defeated by Aoi Kimi. Kimi convinces her that she has to serve Horizon since she is the princess of her land, so then she joins the Musahi Team.</description>
<picture>1967.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35560" type="appears in" update="2011-12-25">
<rating votes="18">7.17</rating>
<name>"Musashi"</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Musashi is an automaton managing the vessel of the same name where Toori Aoi and the others reside. She is the captain of each and every one of the eight ships making up the Musashi. Possesses a characteristic sharp tongue.</description>
<picture>1950.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35561" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="7">4.60</rating>
<name>Tachibana Muneshige</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1971.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35562" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="30">6.78</rating>
<name>Tachibana Gin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1976.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1798" picture="20493.jpg">Kotobuki Minako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35563" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="3">7.11</rating>
<name>Sakai Tadatsugu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65335.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2231" picture="235895.jpg">Kusunoki Taiten</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36601" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="2">2.69</rating>
<name>Galileo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1970.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="267" picture="25729.jpg">Koyama Tsuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36605" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="7">7.07</rating>
<name>Blue Thunder Tenshu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1957.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="36606" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="3">3.84</rating>
<name>Nenji</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54117.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="99" picture="139554.jpg">Hirakawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36607" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="3">3.28</rating>
<name>Hassan Furubushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1690.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36611" type="appears in" update="2011-09-10">
<name>Seitokai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="36614" type="appears in" update="2011-11-02">
<rating votes="3">5.14</rating>
<name>Jizurisuzaku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>1984.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="38178" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="3">2.80</rating>
<name>Konishi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1956.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="436" picture="90853.jpg">Kobushi Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38179" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="2">6.21</rating>
<name>Kuromo no Kemono</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1980.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="330" picture="171543.jpg">Morinaga Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38183" type="appears in" update="2011-12-03">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Jun Bahamut Kyuu Koukuu Toshi Kan - Musashi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>An airship city. There are two ships in the middle, flanked by 3 ships on each side, for a total of 8 ships, over 7 kilometers in length overall.</description>
<picture>1988.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="38274" type="appears in" update="2011-11-02">
<rating votes="2">6.73</rating>
<name>Yuurei (?) no Shoujo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76122.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="550" picture="151677.jpg">Shimizu Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38275" type="appears in" update="2011-11-02">
<name>Musashi Ariadust Gakuin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="38277" type="appears in" update="2011-12-03">
<name>Musashi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The only independent territory in the Far East, and where the main characters reside; an airship city.</description>
</character>
<character id="38330" type="appears in" update="2011-12-04">
<name>Seiren</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>An organization established by the world`s superpowers, responsible for smooth conduction of history recreation. An abbreviation of "Seifu Renmei".
Source: genesis-horizon.wikia.com</description>
</character>
<character id="38332" type="appears in" update="2011-11-03">
<rating votes="5">7.87</rating>
<name>Hanami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2061.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38336" type="appears in" update="2011-12-03">
<name>Tres Espana</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The territory of Shimoseki, currently under provisional rule, under the warlords Ootomo and Ouchi, as well as Spain.</description>
</character>
<character id="39230" type="appears in" update="2011-12-03">
<rating votes="14">5.74</rating>
<name>"Shinagawa"</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2743.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39232" type="appears in" update="2011-12-03">
<name>Kyokutou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The stage of the story, and the only inhabitable area on the earth. Formerly called the Divine States, it was renamed to the Far East as a result of a certain disturbance. It is currently divided into territories under provisional rule by each superpower.</description>
</character>
<character id="39236" type="appears in" update="2011-12-03">
<rating votes="2">6.09</rating>
<name>Souchou Rengou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The organization within the Musashi Ariadust Gakuin that deals with military affairs.</description>
</character>
<character id="39261" type="appears in" update="2011-12-03">
<name>Shinshuu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="39263" type="appears in" update="2011-12-03">
<name>Juusou Shinshuu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="43067" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-15">
<rating votes="4">2.20</rating>
<name>Diego Velazquez</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91008.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43068" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-15">
<rating votes="11">6.76</rating>
<name>Elizabeth</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90989.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43069" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-15">
<name>Felipe Segundo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>5457.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2605" picture="22592.jpg">Shiratori Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43425" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-15">
<rating votes="22">5.35</rating>
<name>Juana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91009.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43426" type="appears in" update="2012-07-15">
<rating votes="4">5.40</rating>
<name>Flores Valdes</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>5462.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="81" picture="41282.jpg">Sanpei Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43427" type="appears in" update="2012-07-15">
<rating votes="2">3.04</rating>
<name>Pedero Valdes</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>5464.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="5040" picture="88977.jpg">Kawahara Yoshihisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43428" type="appears in" update="2012-07-15">
<rating votes="2">3.04</rating>
<name>Hironaka Takakane</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91010.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43429" type="appears in" update="2012-07-15">
<rating votes="4">4.77</rating>
<name>Era Yosae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>5458.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43430" type="appears in" update="2012-07-15">
<rating votes="2">3.04</rating>
<name>Achiyuki Byakko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>91011.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="44702" type="appears in" update="2012-05-13">
<name>William Cecil</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87748.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="328" picture="17164.jpg">Kuwatani Natsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44703" type="appears in" update="2012-05-13">
<name>Robert Dudley</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87749.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4008" picture="65413.png">Yamada Miho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44704" type="appears in" update="2012-05-13">
<name>Ben Jonson</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87750.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="183" picture="16992.jpg">Onosaka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44705" type="appears in" update="2012-05-13">
<name>Nicholas Bacon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87762.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="81" picture="41282.jpg">Sanpei Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44706" type="appears in" update="2012-05-13">
<name>Charles Howard</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87751.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="387" picture="17233.jpg">Narita Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44707" type="appears in" update="2012-05-13">
<rating votes="4">5.90</rating>
<name>Thomas Shakespeare</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87753.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="476" picture="23579.jpg">Saitou Momoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44708" type="appears in" update="2012-05-13">
<rating votes="1">6.41</rating>
<name>Francis Drake</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87754.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10750" picture="186166.jpg">Takeuchi Ryouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44709" type="appears in" update="2012-05-13">
<name>John Hawkins</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87755.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="375" picture="17221.jpg">Chiba Susumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44710" type="appears in" update="2012-05-13">
<rating votes="3">5.41</rating>
<name>Thomas Cavendish</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87756.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44711" type="appears in" update="2012-05-13">
<rating votes="3">6.53</rating>
<name>Grace O`Malley</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87757.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44712" type="appears in" update="2012-05-13">
<rating votes="2">9.13</rating>
<name>Christopher Hutton</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87758.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44713" type="appears in" update="2012-05-13">
<rating votes="4">7.51</rating>
<name>F. Walsingham</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87759.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="328" picture="17164.jpg">Kuwatani Natsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44714" type="appears in" update="2012-05-13">
<rating votes="1">6.41</rating>
<name>Walter Raleigh</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87760.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44715" type="appears in" update="2012-05-13">
<name>Milton</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87763.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5040" picture="88977.jpg">Kawahara Yoshihisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44716" type="appears in" update="2012-05-13">
<name>Kobold</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87764.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44717" type="appears in" update="2013-08-30">
<rating votes="2">6.17</rating>
<name>Kizuari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87765.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47852" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-30">
<rating votes="17">6.57</rating>
<name>Mary Stuart</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142132.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48284" type="appears in" update="2012-08-28">
<name>Eikoku Taichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93151.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2672" picture="188511.jpg">Endou Daichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48285" type="appears in" update="2012-08-28">
<name>Eikoku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="48286" type="appears in" update="2012-08-29">
<rating votes="2">8.56</rating>
<name>Mishina Hiro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93152.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48287" type="appears in" update="2017-11-12">
<name>Maeda Toshiie</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93153.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="303" picture="166016.jpg">Toyonaga Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48288" type="appears in" update="2012-08-29">
<name>Matsu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93154.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1798" picture="20493.jpg">Kotobuki Minako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48303" type="appears in" update="2012-08-30">
<rating votes="5">6.98</rating>
<name>"Asakusa"</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93197.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48407" type="appears in" update="2012-09-03">
<name>Hachidairyuuoh</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Hachidairyuuoh (八大竜王, Eight Great Dragon Kings/Lords) is the traditional term used for the eight wielders of the Logismoi Óplo (Mortal Sin Armaments).</description>
</character>
<character id="48409" type="appears in" update="2012-09-03">
<name>San Lorenzo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="49505" type="appears in" update="2012-09-30">
<rating votes="6">6.86</rating>
<name>"Musashino"</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50086.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49506" type="appears in" update="2012-09-30">
<name>Taizou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="5040" picture="88977.jpg">Kawahara Yoshihisa</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="136471" update="2012-01-18">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">第2期特報</title>
<title xml:lang="en">2nd Season News Flash</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138297" update="2012-03-31">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-03-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">第2期第1弾PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="140360" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">劇場の支配者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ruler of the Theatre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekijou no Shihaisha</title>
<summary>Musashi prepares for the upcoming school event as Tres España makes their appearance.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>606797</identifier>
<identifier>horizon-in-the-middle-of-nowhere</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="140361" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">土上の下り者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Those Descending to the Surface</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dojou no Kudari Mono</title>
<summary>Musashi ‘s Shirojiro Bertoni is negotiating with England’s Charles Howard over the upcoming joint school event; A vicious back and forth between two skilled treasurers as the residents watch.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>606795</identifier>
<identifier>horizon-in-the-middle-of-nowhere</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="140362" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">舞台上の宣告者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Herald on the Stage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Butai-jou no Senkokusha</title>
<summary>With the cargo ship crashed into England soil, the fighting has been put on hold until a treaty can be reached.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>606793</identifier>
<identifier>horizon-in-the-middle-of-nowhere</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="140363" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">朱の場の部員達</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Members of the Vermillion Grounds</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shunoba no Buintachi</title>
<summary>Tori is still naked and the battle continues with the battle against the Tres Espana and Europe!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>606791</identifier>
<identifier>horizon-in-the-middle-of-nowhere</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="140383" update="2012-06-25">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-06-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">番宣スポット放送前Ver.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pre-Broadcast CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="140885" update="2012-07-10">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="141040" update="2016-09-17">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-07-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="141309" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-08-05</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">猟場の人道主義者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hunting Ground`s Humanitarians</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryouba no Jindou Shugisha</title>
<summary>The “exhibition” fights have started against Musashi and England, while Horizon and Tori discuss terms of 
their date.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>606799</identifier>
<identifier>horizon-in-the-middle-of-nowhere</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="141310" update="2016-09-17">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-07-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="141487" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-08-12</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">広場の男女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Man and Woman in the Plaza</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hiroba no Danjo</title>
<summary>The fights are coming to an end and their a few members of Musashi are missing.  To make thing worse, Bloody Double Mary has decided to make her appearance.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>606801</identifier>
<identifier>horizon-in-the-middle-of-nowhere</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="141586" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-08-19</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">広間の語り部</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Storyteller in the Hall</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hiroma no Kataribe</title>
<summary>The fighting has ended, but the battle of politics is beginning. Musashi has a few 
tricks up their sleeves but an unannounced party may ruin everything.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>606803</identifier>
<identifier>horizon-in-the-middle-of-nowhere</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="142200" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">高所の決定者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Decision Maker on High</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kousho no Ketteisha</title>
<summary>With all the acronymed groups butting in, Musashi is forced to think quick before the newcomer brings their house of cards crashing in.  If accepted, the new plan will offer them a chance to see behind the curtain and into the apocalypse.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>606805</identifier>
<identifier>horizon-in-the-middle-of-nowhere</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="142320" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">居場所の刃傷持ち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Where the One Scarred by Swords Belongs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ibasho no Ninjoumochi</title>
<summary>The battle is heating up with the Gods of War and the baseball team pressing Musashi. With the help of non-combative students, Musashi plans to turn the war around.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>606813</identifier>
<identifier>horizon-in-the-middle-of-nowhere</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="142321" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">花畑の合格者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Successful Candidate in the Flower Garden</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hanabatake no Goukakusha</title>
<summary>As Tenzo battles the Fairy Queen for his Mary’s life, the Inadequate HQ must overcome Spain’s barrage attack or they will lose the war.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>606811</identifier>
<identifier>horizon-in-the-middle-of-nowhere</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="142322" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-09-09</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">劇場の咆哮者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Howler at the Theatre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekijou no Houkousha</title>
<summary>Two writers clash over Shakespeare work as the students work together for Tenzo to make it to 
his date.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>606809</identifier>
<identifier>horizon-in-the-middle-of-nowhere</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="142323" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-09-02</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夜空の別離者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">One Parting Under the Night Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yozora no Betsurisha</title>
<summary>Even though Musashi agreed to be a mercenary for England in the upcoming war, plans are derailed by a letter of resignation from Tenzo Clothunit.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>606807</identifier>
<identifier>horizon-in-the-middle-of-nowhere</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="143975" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-09-30</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">境渡りの欲深き者達</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Greedy Ones Who Cross Borders</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakaiwatari no Yokufukaki Mono-tachi</title>
<summary>Spain and Musashi are going for broke with Spain gaining the upper hand. But when 
England relinquishes its Armor of Deadly Sins, Musashi finally gains the upper hand.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>606815</identifier>
<identifier>horizon-in-the-middle-of-nowhere</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="144343" update="2016-09-16">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-09-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145796" update="2013-05-01">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2012-09-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">極東なるほど講座其の2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sensei`s Lesson 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyokutou Naruhodo Kouza Sono 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146188" update="2013-05-01">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2012-09-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">極東なるほど講座其の3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sensei`s Lesson 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyokutou Naruhodo Kouza Sono 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146195" update="2012-12-27">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>2012-12-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">生勉強会V</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 7</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nama Benkyou Kai V</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146196" update="2012-12-27">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2012-11-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アニメコンテンツエキスポ 2012トークショー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anime Content Expo 2012 Talk Show</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146197" update="2012-12-27">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2012-10-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">生勉強会IV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nama Benkyou Kai IV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146198" update="2012-12-27">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2012-09-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">武蔵アリアダスト教導院学園祭</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Musashi Aria Dust Kyoudou in Gakuen Sai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146199" update="2012-12-27">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2012-09-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">第02話 予告</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai 02 wa Yokoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147271" update="2013-11-05">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2012-09-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">極東なるほど講座其の4</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sensei`s Lesson 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyokutou Naruhodo Kouza Sono 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147272" update="2013-02-07">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>2013-01-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">オールナイト上映会2 さぁ, みなさんご一緒に!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 8</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">All-night Joueikai 2: Saa, Mina-san Goissho ni!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148143" update="2013-03-13">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2013-03-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">オールナイト上映会3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 13</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">All-night Jouei Kai 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148144" update="2013-03-13">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2013-03-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">電撃文庫 秋の祭典2012 スペシャルトークショー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 12</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dengeki Bunko Aki no Saiten 2012 Special Talk Show</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148145" update="2013-03-13">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>2013-02-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">キャラホビ2012トークショー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 11</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Charahobby 2012 Talk Show</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148146" update="2013-03-13">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>2013-02-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">生勉強会VI</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 10</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nama Benkyou Kai VI</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150198" update="2016-09-16">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-07-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150199" update="2016-09-16">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-09-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150200" update="2016-09-16">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-09-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150205" update="2013-04-29">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-09-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150279" update="2013-05-01">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">第2弾PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150280" update="2016-09-16">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブルーレイ発売予告CM第2弾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">BD CM 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150281" update="2016-09-16">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブルーレイ発売予告CM</title>
<title xml:lang="en">BD CM 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227610" update="2020-03-26">
<epno type="2">S14</epno>
<length>12</length>
<airdate>2018-12-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">境界線上のホライゾンXXI-PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kyoukai Senjou no Horizon XXI-PV</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
