<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8888" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2012-07-05</startdate>
<enddate>2012-09-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Binbougami ga!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Нищебог же!</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Ах ти ж злидня!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">貧乏神が!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Good Luck Girl!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">贫乏神来了!</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="3468" approval="20" total="40">Gintama</anime>
<anime id="8719" approval="6" total="16">Haiyore! Nyaruko-san</anime>
<anime id="9466" approval="5" total="20">Hataraku Maou-sama!</anime>
<anime id="117" approval="5" total="20">Furi Kuri</anime>
<anime id="4777" approval="1" total="8">Lucky Star</anime>
<anime id="4381" approval="1" total="5">Muteki Kanban Musume</anime>
<anime id="291" approval="1" total="5">Hanada Shounen-shi</anime>
<anime id="323" approval="1" total="4">Pita Ten</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="8">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="63783">Extremely funny Anime. That`s definitely thumbs up, for this one!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="553242">I`ve really been enjoying it so far. Very Funny.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="296685">Who`d have thought that a comedy series could actually be really funny.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="408027">this is recommended for those people who loves parodies.. its got lots of them and so funny..</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="572074">If you like comedy, slapstick, and parody, you shouldn`t miss this one. I felt a couple of the episodes weren`t as funny as the rest, but that isn`t saying much as the rest were absolutely hilarious. On the whole, a great watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="51210">For couple months, I did not watch an anime with this quality. Only problem is that it didnt have an ending. You need to wait for another fun series to come...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="116870">Amazing. Definetly a must see for comedy fans.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.binbogamiga.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="32810" type="Music">Hamauzu Masashi</name>
<name id="19259" type="Character Design">Tanabe Kenji</name>
<name id="11572" type="Chief Animation Direction">Suzuki Yukie</name>
<name id="7168" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nishimura Satoshi</name>
<name id="3439" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ishikawa Tetsuya</name>
<name id="726" type="Animation Work">Sunrise</name>
<name id="11572" type="Chief Animation Direction">Suzuki Yukie</name>
<name id="19259" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tanabe Kenji</name>
<name id="30393" type="Original Work">Sukeno Yoshiaki</name>
<name id="19607" type="Series Composition">Shimoyama Kento</name>
<name id="20103" type="Chief Direction">Kawamura Tomoyuki</name>
<name id="24337" type="Direction">Fujita Youichi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the manga by http://anidb.net/cr30393 [Sukeno Yoshiaki], serialised in http://anidb.net/cr31875 [Jump Square] since July 2008.
http://anidb.net/ch44065 [Sakura Ichiko] leads a blissful life due to her bountiful store of happiness energy — gained by sapping that energy from other people. To restore the balance, the Binbougami (Poverty God) http://anidb.net/ch44066 [Binbada Momiji] attempts to eliminate her.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2730">6.83</permanent>
<temporary count="2737">7.47</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>238115.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14191</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13535</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5139</identifier>
<identifier>lioncr</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/binbogamiga/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.binbogamiga.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Binbō-gami_ga!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>貧乏神が!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2589</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>342971</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15027</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>窮神</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="204" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-06-19">
<name>violent</name>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1482" parentid="2751" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-08">
<name>wrestling</name>
<description>Wrestling is a fight between two people without weapons, in which each person tries to beat their opponent. Wrestlers use clinching, holding, locking, and leverage. It resembles ritual fighting as it avoids things that will likely lead to serious injury. It is similar to military hand-to-hand combat or self-defence systems.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1662" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-22">
<name>weaponized paper fan</name>
<description>Harisen (ハリセン meaning "slapping fan" in Japanese) is a giant paper fan, usually made in a closed fashion, It is used in Japanese comedy shows as a form of physical comedy (this is what is usually seen in anime when a character smacks another on the head with a paper fan).</description>
<picurl>47539.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1835" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-17">
<name>animal sidekick</name>
<description>Every mahou shoujo anime needs them, the cute little critters that are supposed to help the protagonists but in reality are nothing but useless bystanders most often abused for gags. Kids love them but they can also often turn into an annoyance.</description>
<picurl>227760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1999" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-29">
<name>tomboy</name>
<description>A girl who acts and dresses like a boy and enjoys rough, noisy activities traditionally associated with boys.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2491" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-09-09">
<name>nurse</name>
<description>For hentai shows, it`s enough if a http://anidb.net/t884 [nurse costume] is worn without the female character actually working as a nurse.
For ecchi shows, the nurse profession must play a big enough part in the overall setting.
Almost completely exclusive to hentai animations.</description>
<picurl>160445.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2751" parentid="2881" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-27">
<name>combat</name>
<description>Combat involves a violent conflict with the goal to establish dominance over an opponent.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2752" parentid="2881" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tennis</name>
<description>Tennis is yet another sport involving hitting a ball. Were it not for the copious amounts of grass involved in certain varieties, it seems hard to imagine that people would pay it any attention at all.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2830" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>furo scene</name>
<description>Furo (polite: Ofuro) is Japanese for bath, specifically a type of bath which originated as a short, steep-sided wooden bathtub. Baths of this type are found all over Japan in houses, apartments and traditional Japanese inns (Ryokans).
Furo are part of the Japanese ritual of bathing, not used for washing but for relaxing and warming oneself. Washing is carried out separately outside the furo, and only when completely clean does the bather enter the water. Generally Japanese bathrooms are small, so the bathroom is set up much like a walk-in shower area but containing the ofuro.
The cheapest and shortest way to show naked skin on TV, at least as much as allowed. It usually only takes up few minutes at most and as such it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales while still maintaining a "non-filler" episode.
Compare to the big brothers http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode] and http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160785.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2894" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>female student</name>
<description>Pretty much exclusive to hentai shows only unless an ecchi show has implied sex and/or a strong indicator of nudity. A character is considered a student if she goes to school, doesn`t matter if it`s high school, college or homeschooling, but she should be of appropriate age for a student; a housewife going to college should not get this category.</description>
<picurl>210611.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2901" parentid="2729" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-09">
<name>bondage</name>
<description>Bondage is the use of restraints for the sexual pleasure of the parties involved. It may be used in its own right, as in the case of rope bondage and breast bondage, or as part of sexual activity or BDSM activity. When a person is sexually aroused by bondage, it may be considered a paraphilia, known as vincilagnia (from Latin vincio, to bind or fetter with chains, and lagneia, lust).
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42021.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2909" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>karaoke</name>
<description>Obligatory national pastime for students in any anime with school setting. Amateur singing to subtitled music videos.
The word itself is a compound of the Japanese words for "empty orchestra".</description>
<picurl>160894.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4290" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>bath house visit</name>
<description>A sentou is a type of Japanese communal bath house where customers pay for entrance. Some Japanese find social importance in going to public baths, out of the theory that physical intimacy brings emotional intimacy, which is termed skinship in Japanese. Traditionally it is gender-segregated — men usually bathe only with men, and women with women. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales.
See also http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode], http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160783.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4951" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2018-03-22">
<name>age change</name>
<description>Because who wouldn`t like to be young/old again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5459" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>poverty</name>
<description>It refers to the condition of not having the means to afford basic human needs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5518" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-03">
<name>flat chest jokes</name>
<description>Jokes about the (supposedly or actually) flat chest of a character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5805" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-06-11">
<name>post-credits scene</name>
<description>A little bit of the story is found after the credit titles. A little bonus for those patient enough!
This applies regardless of if the credits play over an ED sequence, or over the "regular episode" that continues to air into the credits.
A sequence at the end of an episode, showing what will happen in the next episode, is NOT a post-credits scene; that is a preview.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5824" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-23">
<name>god is a girl</name>
<description>In storylines where many or all gods are portrayed as goddesses (female gods), "The God of all Gods", or the Number-One-God so to speak, is also female.
In other instances, such may just refer to a girl with god-like powers.</description>
<picurl>215285.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7220" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="78">7.03</rating>
<name>Urameshi Yuusuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Urameshi Yuusuke is known to be a stereotypical bad seed; having a spotty attendance record, doing poorly in class, and picking fights with many other students. He also smokes cigarettes and drinks alcohol in the manga.
He dies after saving a small child from being struck by a car, which is something the guardians of the afterlife did not predict. Koenma allows Botan to becoming Yuusuke`s guide for the Ordeal that he must undergo in order to be brought back to life, as well as help show him that he is actually a good person. He is then forced to become a Spirit Detective who protects the human race from demons.</description>
<picture>2120.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="7812" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-04-12">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Medama-oyaji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Medama-oyaji is Kitarou`s father. Once a fully-formed adult ghost, he perished of a disease, only to be reborn out of his decayed body as an anthropomorphic version of his own eyeball. He looks small and fragile, but has a strong spirit and a great love for his son. He is also extremely knowledgeable about ghosts and monsters. He enjoys staying clean, and is often seen bathing in a small bowl. He has a great love for sake.</description>
<picture>26843.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="11363" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="80">6.90</rating>
<name>Neko Musume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Neko Musume is a normally-quiet youkai girl, who transforms into a frightening cat monster with fangs and feline eyes when she is angry or hungry for fish. Predictably, she does not get along well with Nezumi Otoko. She seems to harbor a slight crush on Kitaro, who sees her only as a friend. She bears some resemblance to the bakeneko of Japanese folklore.
Neko-Musume first appears in the story Neko-Musume and Nezumi-Otoko (Weekly Shounen Magazine version), however another cat-girl named Neko (寝子) appears in the earlier stories The Vampire Tree and the Neko-Musume and A Walk to Hell (Rental version).</description>
<picture>33849.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="44065" type="main character in" update="2016-08-12">
<rating votes="66">6.50</rating>
<name>Sakura Ichiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ichiko is a super lucky girl who actually possesses an attractive figure, bright mind, and perfect health. She`s never had to work hard for anything, and she`s a self-centered egoist, but she`s also a bit of a lonely person.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>87628.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44066" type="main character in" update="2013-08-16">
<rating votes="71">8.37</rating>
<name>Momiji</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Momiji is a god of poverty who posses http://anidb.net/ch44065 [Ichiko] in order to preserve the balance between fortune and misfortune. Her flat chest also troubles her. She makes use of various poverty tools in order to steal energy from Ichiko, but all the expenses come from her own pocket.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>87627.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23686" picture="224554.jpg">Uchiyama Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45542" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-25">
<rating votes="21">5.46</rating>
<name>Tsuwabuki Keita</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch44065 [Ichiko]`s classmate. Keita is the main provider for a family of four siblings in his parents` absence. He works many part-time jobs.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>90080.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2588" picture="153507.jpg">Uchiyama Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45543" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-06">
<rating votes="16">3.88</rating>
<name>Inugami Momoo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Momoo is a dog god summoned by http://anidb.net/ch44066 [Momiji]. He`s very masochistic and capable of transforming into a chihuahua.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>90083.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45544" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-25">
<rating votes="15">3.41</rating>
<name>Bobby</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bobby is a monk traveling to exorcise evil spirits. Although he can sense the supernatural, he`s also quite a pervert.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>90085.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5040" picture="88977.jpg">Kawahara Yoshihisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45568" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-12">
<rating votes="11">4.80</rating>
<name>Kumagai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88955.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="45569" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-25">
<rating votes="38">7.15</rating>
<name>Rindou Ranmaru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl who transferred into http://anidb.net/ch44065 [Ichiko]`s class. She`s a manly woman and a hot-blooded, stalwart karate girl.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>90081.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46287" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-25">
<rating votes="6">4.24</rating>
<name>Suwano Kikunoshin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90087.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2340" picture="151335.jpg">Naka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46288" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-16">
<rating votes="14">6.91</rating>
<name>Yamabuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90086.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46686" type="appears in" update="2012-08-02">
<rating votes="10">5.66</rating>
<name>Adenokouji Nadeshiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91856.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33251" picture="204767.jpg">Kanda Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46692" type="appears in" update="2013-08-16">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Tange Akane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92742.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15586" picture="222826.jpg">Harashima Kozue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46836" type="appears in" update="2012-07-13">
<name>Ishi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90872.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23680" picture="65778.jpg">Kuratomi Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46837" type="appears in" update="2012-07-13">
<name>Yamada Eiji</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="31807" picture="85618.jpg">Sakurai Tsubasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46838" type="appears in" update="2012-07-13">
<name>Kanja</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90871.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30393" picture="90653.jpg">Sukeno Yoshiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46839" type="appears in" update="2012-07-13">
<rating votes="1">6.80</rating>
<name>Tannin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90877.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23683" picture="65780.jpg">Gotou Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46840" type="appears in" update="2012-07-13">
<name>Suzuki Manabu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="33471" picture="90873.jpg">Yanagisawa Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46841" type="appears in" update="2012-10-24">
<name>Nagasawa Ai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="34233" picture="146257.jpg">Nagata Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46842" type="appears in" update="2012-07-13">
<name>Nakamura Rie</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="33510" picture="91423.jpg">Yoshii Ayami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46843" type="appears in" update="2012-07-13">
<name>Watanabe Tomoharu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="23680" picture="65778.jpg">Kuratomi Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46844" type="appears in" update="2012-07-13">
<name>Ishida Hayato</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="31807" picture="85618.jpg">Sakurai Tsubasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46845" type="appears in" update="2012-07-13">
<name>Kagaku Kyoushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90878.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33471" picture="90873.jpg">Yanagisawa Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46846" type="appears in" update="2012-07-13">
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<name>Endou Mai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90879.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33511" picture="185820.jpg">Akina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47209" type="appears in" update="2012-07-24">
<rating votes="1">6.80</rating>
<name>Tsuwabuki Ryuuta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91442.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1735" picture="31933.jpg">Shimoda Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47210" type="appears in" update="2012-07-24">
<rating votes="6">7.23</rating>
<name>Tsuwabuki Rika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91441.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1528" picture="223648.jpg">Kawaragi Shiho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47211" type="appears in" update="2012-07-24">
<rating votes="3">6.78</rating>
<name>Tsuwabuki Mika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91440.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33510" picture="91423.jpg">Yoshii Ayami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47212" type="appears in" update="2013-08-16">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Tsuwabuki Sorata</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91443.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33511" picture="185820.jpg">Akina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47213" type="appears in" update="2012-07-24">
<name>Chuushyajou no Otoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91439.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23680" picture="65778.jpg">Kuratomi Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47428" type="appears in" update="2012-07-30">
<name>Gomi Shobunba no Shokuin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91739.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23680" picture="65778.jpg">Kuratomi Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47429" type="appears in" update="2012-07-30">
<name>Mansion no Kanrinin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91738.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23683" picture="65780.jpg">Gotou Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47517" type="appears in" update="2012-08-04">
<rating votes="7">4.94</rating>
<name>Michiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She`s http://anidb.net/ch44065 [Sakura Ichiko] who shrank due to one of Momoji`s traps.</description>
<picture>91923.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47611" type="appears in" update="2013-08-16">
<name>Mizunoe Urashimako</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92120.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3155" picture="24137.jpg">Ono Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47834" type="appears in" update="2013-08-16">
<name>Rindou Genjuurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92579.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47930" type="appears in" update="2012-08-21">
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<name>Josei Ten`in</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92739.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34259">Mori Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47931" type="appears in" update="2012-08-21">
<name>Keikan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92741.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23680" picture="65778.jpg">Kuratomi Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47932" type="appears in" update="2012-08-21">
<name>Bus no Untenshu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92738.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23680" picture="65778.jpg">Kuratomi Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47933" type="appears in" update="2012-08-21">
<name>Kakashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92740.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31807" picture="85618.jpg">Sakurai Tsubasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48108" type="appears in" update="2013-08-16">
<name>Minowa Kurumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132387.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48201" type="appears in" update="2012-08-27">
<name>Yuusuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93047.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33511" picture="185820.jpg">Akina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48299" type="appears in" update="2012-08-30">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Adenokouji Shion</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93191.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48300" type="appears in" update="2012-08-30">
<name>Gorihara Ryuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93192.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48301" type="appears in" update="2013-08-16">
<rating votes="4">5.65</rating>
<name>Kuroyuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93193.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="208" picture="20458.jpg">Shiraishi Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48393" type="appears in" update="2012-09-03">
<name>Gorihara no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93390.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="26648" picture="73162.jpg">Takeda Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48394" type="appears in" update="2012-09-03">
<name>Taiiku no Sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93389.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33898" picture="93331.jpg">Manmosu Nishio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48736" type="appears in" update="2016-08-12">
<name>Tama-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93901.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34259">Mori Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48737" type="appears in" update="2012-09-11">
<rating votes="2">8.42</rating>
<name>Ibuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93903.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48739" type="appears in" update="2012-09-11">
<name>Tama-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93902.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34259">Mori Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49438" type="appears in" update="2012-09-29">
<name>Driver</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46162.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30393" picture="90653.jpg">Sukeno Yoshiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73473" type="appears in" update="2015-02-25">
<name>Momiji</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>169436.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="140470" update="2012-07-27">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-07-26</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">「縮んど~るやな~いか!」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">He Shrank, Didn`t He?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Chijindooru Yanaai ka!"</title>
<summary>Momiji ends up summoning the masochistic dog god, Momou Inugami, and has him transform into a puppy so he can get close to Ichiko and attempt to steal her fortune. However, Momou finds that getting the fortune off of Ichiko isn`t as easy as it looks. As Momou observes Ichiko`s behaviour, she notices her personality is different when reading letters from Suwano. That night, as Momou activates a Misfortune Item to spread misfortune, the box containing Suwano`s letters falls from the top of the desk, and is thrown away by the cleaners the next day. When Ichiko learns of this, she goes to the trash dump and spends the entire night searching for the box, much to Momou`s surprise. Against his better judgement, Momou finds the box for Ichiko. As Momou deduces that Ichiko may not be such a bad person after all, his cover is blown when he reverts to human form, prompting a swift punishment from Ichiko.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="140471" update="2012-07-22">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-07-19</airdate>
<rating votes="7">9.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">「お前に命令されるのはなんか腹立つ!!!」 「なんかって何!!?」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Taking Orders from You Kinda Ticks Me Off!!! What Do You Mean, Kinda?!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Omae ni Meirei Sareru no wa Nanka Haradatsu!!!" "Nankatte Nani!!?"</title>
<summary>Figuring she needs a boyfriend, Ichiko takes an interest in her sleepy classmate, Keita Tsuwabuki. Upon finding and returning his ID card, Ichiko is invited by Keita to have dinner with his siblings, who are quite poor as their parents had left them. Keita soon takes a strong dislike to Ichiko when she rejects his ideal that being together is more important than money. The next day, Ichiko tries to make up with Keita`s brother Ryūta by buying him a super rare trading card. However, he ends up dropping the card down a sewer and gets trapped in there whilst attempting to retrieve it just as a typhoon starts to settle in. As Ichiko is told by Keita how he doesn`t want to be in anyone`s debt, Momiji makes her aware of the danger Ryūta is in, prompting her to go and save him. As Ryūta gets swept into the river, Ichiko dives in after him, using a device given to her by Momiji to use her fortune to rescue him. Afterwards, Keita and Ryūta give their thanks to Ichiko, who feels a warmth in her heart.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="140472" update="2012-07-13">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-07-12</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">「これぞまさに『神と少女の戦いが今, 始まる――』って感じネ♥」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This, Indeed, Has the "The Battle Between God and Girl Now Begins" Feel To It</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Kore zo Masa ni `Kami to Shoujo no Tatakai ga Ima, Hajimaru...` tte Kanji ne"</title>
<summary>In order to get closer to Ichiko, Momiji transfers into her class, much to Ichiko`s displeasure. As Momiji continues to bother her, Ichiko meets Bobby, a perverted travelling priest with the ability to detect fortune energy, giving her an item called the Soumin Shourai, allowing her to manifest her good fortune into various creatures. Momoji responds by manifesting her own monsters out of her misfortune, but they turn out to be useless and she is soundly beaten.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="140473" update="2012-07-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-07-05</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">「神は神でも貧乏神じゃなくて貧乳神の間違いじゃないの?」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Are You Sure You Haven`t Confused Being a God of Flat-Brokeness with Being a God of Flat-Chestedness?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Kami wa Kami demo Binbougami ja Nakute Hinnyuugami no Machigai ja Nai no?"</title>
<summary>A God of Poverty named Momiji is sent down to earth to greet a spoiled high-school girl named Ichiko Sakura, who has had good fortune all her life. Momiji explains that Ichiko has an abnormally high level of good fortune, and is also sucking up fortune from those near her. Momoji attempts to take some of Ichiko`s fortune and make her a normal girl, but Ichiko manages to fight her off. The nexy day, however, Ichiko`s butler, Suwano, has a heart attack and is left in a critical condition as a result of Ichiko taking his fortune over the years he served her. Ichiko agrees to let Momiji suck some good fortune out of her, but then she runs off with it and releases it at the hospital, saving Suwano`s life. Afterwards, Ichiko decides to sack Suwano from his position so he can live his own life without being at risk. A week later, Ichiko`s fortune levels soon return, as does Momiji.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="140740" update="2012-07-05">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-07-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="140741" update="2012-07-05">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-07-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="141124" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-08-23</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">「名前で呼んで」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Call Me By My Name</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Namae de Yonde"</title>
<summary>Ranmaru is invited to a welcoming party by the other girls, but when she tries to invite Ichiko along, she refuses. Despite Ranmaru`s attempts at friendship. Ichiko keeps pushing her away. What is it that prevents Ichiko from making friends with others?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="141125" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-08-16</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">「いわゆる男として育てられちゃったパターン?」 / 「今日のことは一生忘れねーよ!!」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Is This That So-Called Boy-Raised-As-a-Girl Pattern?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Iwayuru Otoko to Shite Sodaterarechatta Pattern?" / "Kyou no Koto wa Isshou Wasurenee yo!!"</title>
<summary>When mistaken for a shoplifter, Ichiko shifts suspicion onto the nearby karate freak Ranmaru Rindo to get away. Soon after, Ranmaru transfers in to Ichiko`s class, and vows to get back at her. Is Ranmaru`s karate a match for Ichiko`s happiness energy?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="141126" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-08-09</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">「目を開けろおおおおっ!!!!」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Open Your Eye-es!!!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Me o Akerooooo!!!!"</title>
<summary>After seeing Tsuwabuki`s brothers and sisters in tears over his absence, Ichiko sets out to find him with the help of Momo`o. Seeing how happy theTsuwabuki home life is, Ichiko grows troubled at the realization that something is missing in her own life.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="141127" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-08-02</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">「どっちが貧乳なのかな~? ん? ん!? ん!!?」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Which One of Us Is Flat-Chested, Again? Hm? Hm?! Hm!!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Docchi ga Hinnyuu na no ka naa? N? N!? N!!?"</title>
<summary>When Ichiko opens a treasure box that turns her back into a child, she is powerless against Momiji, and runs away. She meets up with Mika Tsuwabuki, and talks her way into hiding out with Mika`s family until she can find a way to return herself to normal.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="141611" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">「いつか名前で呼んで」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sometime, Call Me By My Name</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Itsuka Namae de Yonde"</title>
<summary>Momiji surprises everyone by acting differently, and even draws her male classmates` attention away from Ichiko. Momiji claims that when a poverty god bathes in the human realm, they lose their poverty god powers. Ichiko, however, believes otherwise.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="141612" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-09-13</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">「...誰!?」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">...Who Are You?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"...Dare!?"</title>
<summary>When Momiji has a guest over that befouls the bathtub, Ichiko must look for other facilities. She resigns herself to going to a bathhouse, where she and Ranmaru meet Tsuwabuki and his siblings. Bobby and Momo`o also arrive for some good clean, dirty fun
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="141613" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-09-06</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">「カボチャ嫌いの子供にカボチャを食べさすためこっそりシチューに混ぜておくみたいなもんですよ」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Like Secretly Mixing Pumpkin into a Stew in Order to Feed It to a Child Who Hates Pumpkin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Kabochagirai no Kodomo ni Kabocha o Tabesasu Tame Kossori Stew ni Mazete Oku Mitai na Mon Desu yo"</title>
<summary>Ichiko takes in a pet kitten that was left outside her apartment. She meets Ibuki, a bathroom god, who also delivers a warning to her about hoarding happiness energy. When Momiji kidnaps the kitten, Ichiko must square off with her to get her pet back.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="141614" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-08-30</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">「えっ!!! 今さらっと言ったね!?」 / 「2分でこうなるワケねーだろ!!!!」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">"Eh?! You Said, `After All This`?!" &amp; "There`s No Way That Happens After Just Two Minutes!!!!"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"E!!! Ima Saratto Itta ne!?" / "2-fun de Kou Naru Wake Nee Daro!!!!"</title>
<summary>The high school boys and the girls are forced to play mixed doubles tennis in gym class, and Ichiko and Momiji square off against each other. Ichiko decides to learn to cook for herself, with surprising results. Momiji challenges Ichiko to a cook-off.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="143823" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-09-27</airdate>
<rating votes="6">9.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">「それもう答え出てるだろ」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You Already Have the Answer to That</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Sore Mou Kotae Deteru Daro"</title>
<summary>Ichiko saves Momiji from being returned to her original self, and together with Ranmaru, the three of them run away from Momo`o and Kumagai. Their flight causes Ichiko to rexamine her relationship with Momiji, and come to terms with what she wants.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="147689" update="2013-02-24">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-09-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147690" update="2013-02-24">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-09-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
