<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="890" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2004-03-06</startdate>
<enddate>2004-03-06</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Innocence</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">イノセンス</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Ghost in the shell 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Ghost in the Shell - Innocence</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Дух в стальной плоти: невинность</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Призрак в доспехах: Невинность</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Duch w pancerzu II: Niewinność</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Ghost in the Shell: Niewinność</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="synonym">Fantasma do Futuro 2: Inocente</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Kabuktaki Hayalet 2: Masumiyet</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Призрак в черупка 2 : Невинност</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Koukaku Kidoutai: INNOCENCE</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Дух в оболонці: Невинність</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="synonym">معصومیت</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">GitS2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">GitS INNOCENCE</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">Innocence</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Ghost in the Shell 2: Innocence</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Ghost in the Shell 2 - Innocence</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Ghost in the Shell 2 - Innocence</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Ghost in the Shell 2 - L`attacco dei cyborg</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Ghost in the Shell 2: Innocence</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Призрак в доспехах 2: Невинность</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">공각기동대 2 이노센트</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Ghost in the Shell 2: Innocence</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Cidade Assombrada - Inocência</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Ghost in the Shell 2: Innocence</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="official">Dvasia šarvuose 2: Nekaltybė</title>
<title xml:lang="et" type="official">Hing anumas 2: Süütus</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">攻壳机动队2 无罪</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="61" type="Prequel">Ghost in the Shell</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9127" approval="26" total="44">Psycho-Pass</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="11">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="17776">Stunning visuals marred by a hideously convoluted, pretentious and shallow plot that lacks any real sense or impact. Recommended for `completeness`.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="323466">Shallow plot with a lot of mistakes, but.... Absolutely stunning animation</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="118349">GitS:Innocence is more twisted, darker and philosophical of the 1st movie so, it isn`t an easy watch for everyone... that said, I think that if you`re a fan of Shirow Masamune`s works, you definitely cannot miss to watch this one, if nothing else for understanding where Kusanagi Motoko went! Highly recommended.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="97536">It`s prettier than the first one but lacks its eerieness. Also the quotes, while appealing to my intellectual snobbery, tend to be a little tedious and pretentious. 
However, the animation is truly beautiful, the story sufficiently creepy and the music rather lovely. Perhaps not as strong as the prequel or even the series but not a bad watch at all.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="368986">it`s buitiufull......
story .. whatever..
but some scenes are just biuuutiifull</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="523721">Not quite as good as the prequel, but still a cyberpunk masterpiece. Superb visuals, story is kinda metaphysical and open to interpretations. Definitely must see.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20070423062143/http://www.innocence-movie.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="871" type="Original Work">Shirou Masamune</name>
<name id="1946" type="Music">Kawai Kenji</name>
<name id="131" type="Direction">Oshii Mamoru</name>
<name id="4500" type="Character Design">Okiura Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="721" type="Work">Production I.G</name>
</creators>
<description>Following the events of the first Ghost in the Shell movie, Major Motoko Kusanagi has since left her physical body and is now a "ghost" living in the network. This leaves Batou as the top officer at Section 9, the special task force assigned to matters of human/machine relations.
Batou`s latest assignment is to investigate the recent string of suicide-murders perpetrated by a certain brand of "gynoids" — androids designed to look like women. Together with officer Togusa (one of the last few people who hasn`t had his body fitted with cybernetic parts), Batou tracks down the cause of the wayward gynoids — all the while pondering and discussing the hazy realms where machines become dangerously close to human, and humans become dangerously close to machines.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="7451">7.00</permanent>
<temporary count="7494">7.82</temporary>
<review count="7">8.25</review>
</ratings>
<picture>157742.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2081</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>468</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1384</identifier>
<identifier>pogqib</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20070423062143/http://www.innocence-movie.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.productionig.com/contents/works_sp/01_/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ghost_in_the_Shell_2:_Innocence</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>イノセンス</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>603</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>240800</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>이노센스_(2004년_일본_영화)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>攻殼機動隊2_INNOCENCE</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B01MR4QVN7</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1528" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-12">
<name>artificial intelligence</name>
<description>Artificial intelligence (AI) is the intelligence of machines and the branch of computer science that aims to create it. AI textbooks define the field as "the study and design of intelligent agents" where an intelligent agent is a system that perceives its environment and takes actions that maximize its chances of success. John McCarthy, who coined the term in 1956, defines it as "the science and engineering of making intelligent machines."
The field was founded on the claim that a central property of humans, intelligence—the sapience of Homo sapiens—can be so precisely described that it can be simulated by a machine. This raises philosophical issues about the nature of the mind and the ethics of creating artificial beings, issues which have been addressed by myth, fiction and philosophy since antiquity. Artificial intelligence has been the subject of optimism, but has also suffered setbacks and, today, has become an essential part of the technology industry, providing the heavy lifting for many of the most difficult problems in computer science.
AI research is highly technical and specialized, and deeply divided into subfields that often fail to communicate with each other. Subfields have grown up around particular institutions, the work of individual researchers, the solution of specific problems, longstanding differences of opinion about how AI should be done and the application of widely differing tools. The central problems of AI include such traits as reasoning, knowledge, planning, learning, communication, perception and the ability to move and manipulate objects. General intelligence (or "strong AI") is still among the field`s long term goals.</description>
<picurl>71305.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2180" parentid="2636" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-24">
<name>cyborg</name>
<description>A cyborg is a cybernetic organism (i.e. an organism that has both artificial and natural systems). The term was coined in 1960 when Manfred Clynes and Nathan Kline used it in an article about the advantages of self-regulating human-machine systems in outer space. D. S. Halacy`s Cyborg: Evolution of the Superman in 1965 featured an introduction which spoke of a "new frontier" that was "not merely space, but more profoundly the relationship between `inner space` to `outer space` -a bridge...between mind and matter." The cyborg is often seen today merely as an organism that has enhanced abilities due to technology, but this perhaps oversimplifies the category of feedback.
Fictional cyborgs are portrayed as a synthesis of organic and synthetic parts, and frequently pose the question of difference between human and machine as one concerned with morality, free will, and empathy. Fictional cyborgs may be represented as visibly mechanical (e.g. the Cybermen in the Doctor Who franchise or The Borg from Star Trek); or as almost indistinguishable from humans (e.g. the "Human" Cylons from the re-imagining of Battlestar Galactica). The 1970s television series The Six Million Dollar Man featured one of the most famous fictional cyborgs. Cyborgs in fiction often play up a human contempt for over-dependence on technology, particularly when used for war, and when used in ways that seem to threaten free will. Cyborgs are also often portrayed with physical or mental abilities far exceeding a human counterpart (military forms may have inbuilt weapons, among other things).
Real (as opposed to fictional) cyborgs are more frequently people who use cybernetic technology to repair or overcome the physical and mental constraints of their bodies. While cyborgs are commonly thought of as mammals, they can be any kind of organism.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42022.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2839" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>virtual world</name>
<description>A virtual world is a place where the character interacts with a computer (or some other device)-simulated environment, be it real or imagined. The condition for a virtual reality to exist is the existence of an originating "real" (source/anchor) world for the character. In some cases, a virtual reality where characters can get harmed physically is depicted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2852" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>thriller</name>
<description>The thriller is a genre of fiction in which tough, resourceful, but essentially ordinary heroes are pitted against villains determined to destroy them, their country, or the stability of the free world. The hero of a typical thriller faces danger alone or in the company of a small band of companions. The protagonist may be a law enforcement agent, a journalist, or a soldier, but typically he or she is cut off from the resources of "their" organization. More often the hero is an ordinary citizen drawn into danger and intrigue by circumstances beyond their control.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214683.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2861" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>cyberpunk</name>
<description>Cyberpunk focuses on computers or information technology, usually coupled with some degree of breakdown in social order. The plot often centres on a conflict among hackers, artificial intelligences, and mega corporations, tending to be set within a near-future dystopian Earth.</description>
<picurl>211264.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3964" parentid="6254" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-26">
<name>cyberterrorism</name>
<description>With the development of computer and Internet technology a new form of terrorism has emerged, the cyberterrorism, which is the manipulation of a target`s computers and information, particularly via the Internet, to cause physical, real-world harm or severe disruption of infrastructure. It finds often use in science fiction stories.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4196" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-01-23">
<name>fate worse than death</name>
<description>If you think death is the worst that can ever happen to someone, you had better think again: at least one character in this show is sure to end up in such a terrible way that many people would likely have preferred death if they had the choice. The fate of such characters is normally not for the faint of heart, and the audience is expected to at least sympathise with the poor character`s fate, and at times even be horrified at the shocking turn of events that led to their demise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4280" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-02">
<name>surreal</name>
<description>Refers to things or occurrences that are generally bizarre or dreamlike, with the relentless capability of replacing reality through the eyes of the beholder. Surrealism is boundless, limited only by thought itself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4417" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>existentialism</name>
<description>Most commonly defines the rejection of a god and any transcendent will that dictates how humans should live. It rejects any "created" meaning of life and the world, stating a leap of faith is required to live an authentic life. In this existentialism, belief in a god is often considered a form of Bad Faith.
In length, the Absurd contains ideas that there is no meaning in the world beyond what meaning it`s given. Meaninglessness also encompasses amorality or "unfairness" of the world. This contrasts with "karmic" ways of thinking in which "bad things don`t happen to good people"; there is no such thing as a good person or a bad thing; what happens happens, and it may just as well happen to a good person as to a bad person. This contrasts daily experience where most things appear meaningful, and where good people receive a "reward" for goodness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4612" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep?</name>
<description>The title of Philip K. Dick`s SF novel (movie: Blade Runner). 
The phrase implies a set of existential questions: Do artificial beings (e.g. Replicants, Bioroids, or other AI constructs) dream, feel, or have a soul? If memories can be implanted, what makes real memories real? By contrast — what makes humans human? What is reality? 
These are central themes e.g. in all of the Ghost in the Shell and Appleseed series / movies.</description>
<picurl>210067.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5793" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-13">
<name>Asimov`s Three Laws of Robotics</name>
<description>The SF author Isaac Asimov developed (1942) a set of laws he used to govern the behaviour of robots:
1. A robot may not injure a human being or, through inaction, allow a human being to come to harm.
2. A robot must obey any orders given to it by human beings, except where such orders would conflict with the First Law.
3. A robot must protect its own existence as long as such protection does not conflict with the First or Second Law.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5884" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-22">
<name>slow-paced</name>
<description>The story — including its characters and events — develop slowly.
May contain a weak continuity of plot and/or character development. 
Or may be a story telling device to increase the "sense of foreboding" in an anime with thriller or horror setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6254" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-23">
<name>terrorism</name>
<description>Terrorism is, in the broadest sense, the use of intentionally indiscriminate violence as a means to create terror among masses of people; or fear to achieve a religious or political aim. It is used in this regard primarily to refer to violence during peacetime or in war against non-combatants (mostly civilians and neutral military personnel). Some definitions now include acts of unlawful violence and war.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10657.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1584" type="main character in" update="2011-08-10">
<rating votes="739">8.78</rating>
<name>Batou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Batou is a main male character in the Ghost in the Shell series, the second best melee fighter in http://anidb.net/ch1590 [Section 9], and is the second in command under Major http://anidb.net/ch1582 [Kusanagi Motoko].
Batou had seemingly hated anyone who tries to make Section 9 fixing the mess of another organization, such as the AI hijacking of the Jigabachi choppers in the SAC series. In addition, he jokes around with a hint of irony being mentioned.</description>
<picture>43025.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1588" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-12-18">
<rating votes="338">7.89</rating>
<name>Aramaki Daisuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aramaki Daisuke is a strict chief, and is referred to by others in http://anidb.net/ch1590 [Section 9] as the "old ape" (most likely because in the original manga he was drawn with a face that appeared to be half monkey, half man). Even so, he is fiercely loyal to the members of Section 9, and often puts his own career on the line to ensure the survival of the rest of his team.</description>
<picture>129602.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2366" picture="203225.jpg">Ooki Tamio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1590" type="appears in" update="2010-05-09">
<rating votes="195">8.66</rating>
<name>Kouan Kyuuka</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Public Security Section 9 was established as a search and rescue organization. Officially billed as an international organization, it is actually a counter-terrorist network and anti-crime unit operating in the Japanese National Public Safety Commission. Its operatives are allowed to act with or without government consent as they are almost unknown to the public eye. In particular, Section 9 and its members are among the best cyber warfare operatives in the country, and as a result usually end up involved in case relating to the internet, such as hacking and cyber terrorism.</description>
<picture>16128.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1592" type="main character in" update="2010-05-08">
<rating votes="426">8.03</rating>
<name>Togusa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Togusa is 27 years old, married and has a young daughter, although it depends on the incarnation; in the S.A.C. universe, he also has a son. Togusa`s personality varies somewhat between the manga, movies, and series. In the manga he tends to be very emotional and plagued with feelings of failure; in the films he is savvier but still aware of his inexperience, and in the Stand Alone Complex his personality is a combination of the two. He also tends to be the most emotional and temperamental, getting so outraged at one criminal committing murder right under his nose in an episode of http://anidb.net/a1176 [Ghost in the Shell: S.A.C. 2nd GIG] he seriously wounded the man and ends up on trial. He seems very friendly with http://anidb.net/ch1584 [Batou] and he was arguably the one who cracked the Laughing Man case.</description>
<picture>16131.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="380" picture="158572.jpg">Yamadera Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1597" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-01-09">
<rating votes="256">6.90</rating>
<name>Ishikawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ishikawa formerly served with http://anidb.net/ch1582 [Kusanagi] and http://anidb.net/ch1584 [Batou] in South America when they were with the Ground Self-Defense Forces in the Japanese UN contingent. He was one of the earliest members recruited to be in http://anidb.net/ch1590 [Section 9] and seems to know the Major and her dislikes quite well. He is shown as being in charge of a pachinko parlor called Parlor Ishikawa, and on occasion uses the cyberbrains of the old men who play there to complete particularly heavy data gathering, though it seems the men suffer no ill effects or are even aware of their situation. Ishikawa is the most seemingly laid-back member of the unit.</description>
<picture>129603.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="415" picture="241624.jpg">Nakano Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51511" type="appears in" update="2013-03-30">
<name>Azuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134466.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3185" picture="171529.jpg">Terasoma Masaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51512" type="appears in" update="2012-12-20">
<name>Gaya</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51513" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-12-20">
<name>Kim</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129713.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4038" picture="25985.jpg">Takenaka Naoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51514" type="appears in" update="2012-12-20">
<name>Koga</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="323" picture="211661.jpg">Hirata Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51515" type="appears in" update="2012-12-20">
<name>Togusa no Musume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Togusa`s daughter.</description>
<picture>129709.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34771" picture="129973.jpg">Yamauchi Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51516" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-12-20">
<name>Hallaway</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129712.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="571" picture="172734.jpg">Sakakibara Yoshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51517" type="appears in" update="2012-12-20">
<name>Suichuu Cyborg</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129710.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32" picture="16618.jpg">Tachiki Fumihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51518" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-12-20">
<name>Nazo no Shoujo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rescued girl by Batou on the ship.</description>
<picture>129711.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="429" picture="17306.jpg">Mutou Sumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51519" type="appears in" update="2012-12-20">
<name>Kanshiki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Forensics manager.</description>
<picture>129708.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="710" picture="228657.jpg">Hori Katsunosuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51520" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-12-20">
<name>Type 2052 "Hadaly"</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129714.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="429" picture="17306.jpg">Mutou Sumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51521" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-12-20">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Kusanagi Motoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kusanagi and Batou are reunited in the middle of a firefight in the ship when she downloads a part of her consciousness into an empty gynoid.</description>
<picture>129715.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="222" picture="19786.jpg">Tanaka Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51537" type="appears in" update="2015-02-09">
<name>Gabriel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gabriel is the dog of which Batou takes care. He is Basset Hound breed.
The dog Gabriel, looking one more time like the only real being, makes a key appearance, like in many of Oshii`s movies.
A scene of Batou feeding his dog is echoing Ash in Avalon (2001) and Oshii Mamoru in his real life, as the director himself admits: "Batou is a reflection of my own thoughts and feelings. Innocence is a kind of autobiographical film in that way."
He also explained the reason why all his films feature a basset hound-his faithful companion in real life.
"This body you see before you is an empty shell. The dog represents my body. Humans can be free only if they free themselves from their body. When I am playing around with my dog, I forget that I am a human being and it`s only then that I feel free."
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>129762.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="9579" update="2005-08-22">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo-trailer / Teaser-trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12945" update="2005-08-22">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>6</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Special Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13460" update="2005-08-22">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">5.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Teaser-Trailer 2 (Promotion DVD)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17629" update="2013-07-07">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>100</length>
<airdate>2004-03-06</airdate>
<rating votes="20">8.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20163" update="2008-01-22">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video Anthology - Incubation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Innocence no Jokei - Incubation</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20164" update="2005-08-22">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>6</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video Anthology - Civilization - River of Crystals</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Innocence no Jokei - Civilization - River of Crystals</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20165" update="2005-08-22">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video Anthology - Abyss - Attack the Wakabayashi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Innocence no Jokei - Abyss - Attack the Wakabayashi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20166" update="2005-08-22">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video Anthology - Confusion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Innocence no Jokei - Confusion</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20168" update="2005-08-22">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video Anthology - Sabbath - The Doll House I</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Innocence no Jokei - Sabbath - The Doll House I</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20169" update="2005-08-22">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>10</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video Anthology - Rumble</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Innocence no Jokei - Rumble</title>
</episode>
<episode id="20170" update="2005-08-22">
<epno type="4">T10</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video Anthology - Pathos - Follow Me</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Innocence no Jokei - Pathos - Follow Me</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24240" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>55</length>
<airdate>2004-03-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24241" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2004-03-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24382" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>2004-03-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24385" update="2005-09-05">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2004-03-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24386" update="2005-09-05">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>2004-03-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 3 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24758" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>50</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Special making of TV Guide</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51595" update="2008-01-22">
<epno type="4">T11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">9.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video Anthology - Dog Box</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Innocence no Jokei - Dog Box</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51596" update="2008-01-22">
<epno type="4">T12</epno>
<length>4</length>
<rating votes="1">9.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video Anthology - Follow Me (Instrumental)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Innocence no Jokei - Follow Me (Instrumental)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
