<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="891" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>51</episodecount>
<startdate>1995-04-05</startdate>
<enddate>1996-03-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ai Tenshi Densetsu Wedding Peach</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Legend of the Angel of Love, Wedding Peach</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Love Angel Legend Wedding Peach</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Легенда об ангеле любви: Свадебный Персик</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">wp</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">愛天使伝説 ウェディングピーチ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Wedding Peach</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Wedding Peach</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">사랑의 천사 웨딩피치</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">ตำนานเทพธิดาแห่งรัก เวดดิ้งพีช</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="892" type="Sequel">Ai Tenshi Densetsu Wedding Peach DX</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="235" approval="33" total="34">Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon</anime>
<anime id="161" approval="13" total="15">Tokyo Mew Mew</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20060325195426/http://www.advfilms.com/titles/weddingpeach/</url>
<creators>
<name id="2119" type="Original Work">Tomita Sukehiro</name>
<name id="4073" type="Music">Hasegawa Tomoki</name>
<name id="743" type="Animation Work">KSS</name>
<name id="19574" type="Original Work">Yazawa Nao</name>
<name id="4148" type="Character Design">Tadano Kazuko</name>
<name id="4235" type="Direction">Yuyama Kunihiko</name>
<name id="6017" type="Music">Kouzu Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="51960" type="Original Work">Tenyu</name>
</creators>
<description>Love is on the run as the deliciously wicked Lady Raindevila conspires to rid the world of romance and love! However, armed with a mysterious ruby ring left by her mother, the unsuspecting Momoko finds herself caught in the middle of this cosmic battle. She`s cute, she`s sassy, and she`s full of love! But will it be enough?</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="423">3.58</permanent>
<temporary count="433">5.99</temporary>
<review count="4">7.12</review>
</ratings>
<picture>10185.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1066</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>26189</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>1533</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>27</identifier>
<identifier>wkqmbv</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20060325195426/http://www.advfilms.com/titles/weddingpeach/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Wedding_Peach</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ウェディングピーチ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2133</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88985</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1816" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-09">
<name>uniform -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>The "uniform" tag is to be split and removed. Please help by tagging the character with the appropriate kind of uniform (e.g. school uniform, maid dress, etc) and removing this tag from them, and by not adding this tag to any further characters. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2779" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>multiple couples</name>
<description>More than one couple is developed in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3159" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-11-27">
<name>emotions awaken superpowers</name>
<description>During an extreme emotional state — rage, love, hate, angst, sadness, compassion — something inside the character will "click" that will increase greatly his/her power or a new superpower awakes, that surpasses anything achieved by him/her until then.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4480" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>happy ending</name>
<description>And they lived "happily ever after"... *sniff*.
All issues in the anime have been resolved, the love polygons sorted out, the conflicts resolved, the guy gets the girl (or the other way around), and everyone else lives on blissfully.
(Not very realistic, but then again this is anime.)</description>
<picurl>222185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5882" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>secret identity</name>
<description>The (usually main) protagonist has a secret identity that he or she desperately tries to keep secret.
This can lead to all sorts of amusing misunderstandings, thus is used as comedy element in some anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="11721" type="main character in" update="2009-09-14">
<rating votes="10">6.24</rating>
<name>Hanasaki Momoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is a bright and cheerful girl, and her clumsiness never ceases to amuse people. She lives with her father, who is a professional wedding photographer. She was told that her mother left when Momoko was only two...
Like her father, Momoko is also a photographer. She loves working on the school newspaper along with her two best friends, Yuri and Hinagiku, and especially enjoys reporting and taking pictures of the ever so popular soccer team of Saint Flower Garden School. It also helped that her two love interests are on that team: Yanagiba Kazuya, the star player and Fuuma Yousuke, the goalie.</description>
<picture>35466.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="206" picture="228617.jpg">Hikami Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11722" type="main character in" update="2019-10-01">
<rating votes="6">6.60</rating>
<name>Tanima Yuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Soft-spoken and elegant Tanima Yuri is the exact contrast of Hinagiku. She is very polite and very feminine, and one can seldom see her lose her temper. Yuri is quick to catch onto anything, which makes her a great and understanding friend. She lives with her father and mother, who is a fashion designer.
As one of the reporters of the school newspaper, Yuri takes great pride in her job. She loves reporting and watching the popular soccer team of Saint Flower Garden School, where she attends. Just like Momoko and Hinagiku, Yuri also has her eyes set on Yanagiba Kazuya, the captain and star player of that team. But she later also fell in love with Limone, the angel who always appeared to help the Ai Tenshi.</description>
<picture>238974.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16" picture="16592.jpg">Nogami Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11723" type="main character in" update="2009-09-14">
<rating votes="8">6.47</rating>
<name>Tamano Hinagiku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tamano Hinagiku is the tomboy of the team. She is blunt, outgoing, athletic and can appear to be rude to people who just met her. Hinagiku`s courage often gets her into trouble, and she enjoys endlessly teasing her friends. Even so, underneath all that strength, there is really a sensitive and understanding girl. Hinagiku lives in a family of four: herself, her younger brother, her father and her mother who is a tomboy just like Hinagiku.
Hinagiku works for the school newspaper, with no real definite position. She often switches around with Yuri. Besides that, she also practices Judo, and is excellent at it too. She has her heart set on Yanagiba Kazuya, the star player of the Saint Flower Garden soccer team. But of course, there is also Takuruu, who has been Hinagiku`s close friend since childhood...</description>
<picture>35468.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="164" picture="16962.jpg">Miyamura Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11724" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-09-14">
<rating votes="10">5.02</rating>
<name>Scarlet O`Hara</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Stubborn and fiery redhead Scarlet O`Hara is also the last Ai Tenshi. She is aloof, strong minded, ambitious and despised akuma with a passion until she met Momoko-tachi. Scarlet appeared not to have a family; she lives in a fancy and expensive boarding school.
Even when she`s with Momoko-tachi, Scarlet really stands out with her maturity. She has few friends, and doesn`t seem to be interested in anything particular. It was revealed later that her desire for independence came from past experience.</description>
<picture>35470.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="362" picture="74735.jpg">Imai Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11725" type="main character in" update="2009-09-14">
<rating votes="3">8.07</rating>
<name>Fuuma Yousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The replacement goalie of the famous Saint Flower Garden School`s soccer team. He is very good friends with Yanagiba Kazuya, the captain of the team.
Yousuke enjoys teasing Momoko endlessly, whom he affectionately calls Momo-P (P is a suffix often added to the name of your lover or close friend), and Momoko often gets very mad and annoyed. Even so, it is apparent that they like each other alot.</description>
<picture>35477.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3002" picture="17154.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11726" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-02-18">
<rating votes="3">3.25</rating>
<name>Amano Takurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The smartest boy in the class, Takuruu once had a major crush on Momoko. He went out of his way to get her attention and her "kiss" (which he still didn`t get), and even ended up making a deal with the devil Igunisu.
Takuruu has been Hinagiku`s close friend since childhood, but later he moved away.
Even so, they remained pretty close. Despite the huge gap of differences between him and Hinagiku, Takuruu ended up falling in love with his childhood friend anyways.</description>
<picture>35480.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11727" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-20">
<rating votes="3">4.99</rating>
<name>Yanagiba Kazuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The famous star player and captain of the Saint Flower Garden School`s soccer team, Yanagiba not only has the skill, but the looks as well.
All those combined with his sophisticated and polite personality makes him popular with all the girls in the school, but Yanagiba doesn`t even seem to notice.</description>
<picture>35490.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11728" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-09-14">
<rating votes="4">4.93</rating>
<name>Jamapii</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jamapi was once the pet of akuma general Pluie. He was swayed by Wedding Peach`s love waves, and turned good and became the companion of Ai Tenshi. Jamapi acts as the informat of the Ai Tenshi, telling them whenever there is an akuma, the akuma`s name, and what it does (for Jamapi did live in the akuma world). He had two other tukaima companions, whom Wedding Peach also helped turned good.</description>
<picture>35494.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6928" picture="211675.jpg">Matsumoto Miwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11729" type="appears in" update="2019-11-28">
<rating votes="6">5.38</rating>
<name>Hanasaki Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hanasaki Sakura is the mother of Momoko. Sakura is not her real name (Celeste is), it was given to her by Shouichirou when he found her unconscious at the beach. This lovely and understanding mother later appeared to Momoko as Celeste and told her the whole story.</description>
<picture>241591.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4770" picture="76766.jpg">Suzuka Chiharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12408" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-20">
<rating votes="2">8.42</rating>
<name>Limone</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Limone (which means lemon in Italian) is a powerful angel sent by Aphrodite to watch over Momoko and the other Love Angels, granting them assistance whenever he is able.
To remain close to them, he takes the form of Yanagiba, a popular upperclassman at the school and captain of the soccer team, but when turning into Yanagiba, he has no memory of the Love Angels or that he is one himself until later in the season.
In the Angel World, he and Angel Lily had a very close relationship.</description>
<picture>37462.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50459" type="appears in" update="2012-11-09">
<name>Noise</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>127847.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30056" picture="20193.jpg">Honda Chieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106962" type="main character in" update="2019-11-12">
<name>Wedding Peach</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is tasked with fighting devils intent on destroying the Love Wave. She uses St. Mirror to transform into Wedding Peach and shoot attack, and can also summon the rod from the ruby ring to make the stronger love attack. She holds the ruby ring "St. Something Old" from her mother (who is the goddess`s sister in Angel World), which is the one of four wedding relics from Angel World and responsible for the inheritance of love.</description>
<picture>241158.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="206" picture="228617.jpg">Hikami Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106998" type="main character in" update="2019-11-14">
<name>Angel Lily</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She uses Saint Lipliner to transform into Angel Lily and makes ribbon to attack, and can also summon the rod to make the stars attack. She holds the sapphire earrings "St. Something Blue" which is the relic of pure love.</description>
<picture>241222.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16" picture="16592.jpg">Nogami Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107000" type="main character in" update="2019-11-14">
<name>Angel Daisy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She uses Saint Pendule (the watch) to transform into Angel Daisy and shoot attack, and can also summon the fan rod to make the wind attack. She holds the locket pendant "Saint Something Borrowed" which is the relic of friendship.</description>
<picture>241224.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="164" picture="16962.jpg">Miyamura Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107008" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-15">
<name>Aphrodite</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Goddess of love and beauty and ruler of the angel world. She is unable to leave the angel world and must rely on Limone and the Love Angels to ward off the devils. She is the sister of Angel Celeste, Momoko`s mother, and considered Momoko`s aunt respectively. In Wedding Peach DX, it is revealed after defeating Raindevila that Aphrodite erased the Love Angels, Limone’s, Yousuke’s, and Takuro’s memories of anything to do with angels and devils in order for them to live normal lives again. She then makes the Love Angel`s memories known again because due to the revolting devils, with the exception of Limone.</description>
<picture>241256.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2184" picture="49347.jpg">Hyoudou Mako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107009" type="appears in" update="2019-11-15">
<name>Potamos</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The fourth of Raindevila`s henchmen to appear in the story. She comes to help Igneous and has a crush on him, but later in the series kills him for turning soft by the love angels and falls for Yousuke. Potamos is later turned good by Wedding Peach and becomes an ordinary school girl. She becomes a love angel in the second special.</description>
<picture>241258.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107014" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-16">
<name>Angel Salvia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The fourth Love Angel to appear in the series, Salvia is now a pure angel, she assumes the name of Scarlet O`Hara while in the human world. She holds the tiara "Saint Something New" which is the relic of new love.</description>
<picture>241288.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="362" picture="74735.jpg">Imai Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107015" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-16">
<name>Raindevila</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The leader of the devil world (her name is French for "Queen Devil"). Her greatest desire is to destroy all love and subjugate the angel world. In the anime, it is revealed that years ago she ventured into the Angel World and fell in love with an angel at first sight, who later became another angel`s husband. With that event, they both unknowingly banished Reine Devila from the Angel World. Ever since, Reine Devila has wanted to kill all those who love.</description>
<picture>241290.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="542" picture="60897.jpg">Doi Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107161" type="appears in" update="2019-11-27">
<name>Aquelda</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241563.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1509" picture="19311.jpg">Fukami Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107162" type="appears in" update="2019-11-27">
<name>Blitz</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241564.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="491" picture="38232.jpg">Yokoyama Chisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107163" type="appears in" update="2019-11-27">
<name>Cloud</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241565.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="158" picture="38198.jpg">Neya Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107174" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-28">
<name>Igneous</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Igneous is the third of Raindevila`s primary henchmen to appear in the story. He is a fire demon from the tribe of Hima. He is a sneaky and manipulative demon who doesn`t like to get his hands dirty and usually has his minions fight for him before he goes in for the kill. He makes a pact with Takurou and takes residence in his heart and controls his body. He starts to like peace and quiet and actually sees Takuro as a friend, though he doesn`t admit saying he is a member of the fire demon tribe. He is later killed by Potamos. Before he dies he goes to Takuro and releases him from his contract. He then tells Takuro that he actually started to become fond of him. As he passes he looks at the moon and admits that it is beautiful.</description>
<picture>241589.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107175" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-28">
<name>Sandra</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sandra is the second of Raindevila’s primary henchmen to appear in the story, but only in the anime. He sends out the three devils Blitz, Noise, and Cloud to find the Saint Something Four. As the episodes progress, one by one they are purified, including Sandra’s side devil Donna. In episode 22, Sandra locates and kidnaps Jama-P to lure out the Love Angels, which ultimately backfires and gets him purified by the love wave.</description>
<picture>241590.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107176" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-28">
<name>Pluie</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The first of Raindevila`s primary henchmen to appear in the story. He enacts various schemes to both destroy love and lure out the Love Angels, but eventually is sucked into the vortex of destruction as punishment for countless defeats by Raindevila (in the anime). He is destroyed by the angels in the manga. In the anime, before his demise, he appears to have hints of feelings for Aquelda, protecting her before she was killed, and reaching out to save her when she was caught in the Angel`s love wave.</description>
<picture>241593.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="283" picture="17113.jpg">Yao Kazuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107471" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-14">
<name>Viento</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Viento, as he is came to be known in the Demon World, is the heir to the Rafaal Tribe, and holds the power to destroy the Love Angels and what is left of the Angel World. Reine Devila aims to capture him for this very reason, but with Wedding Peach`s help, he is able to break free from the evil within him, and through the love they share, they are able to purify the world of all demons, even Reine Devila herself. As requested by Wedding Peach, Yousuke`s demonic powers get sealed by Aphrodite, and he restarts his relationship with Momoko as a normal human. In the manga, they marry ten years later along with their friends.</description>
<picture>242110.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3002" picture="17154.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108782" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-03-20">
<name>Donna</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245145.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7" picture="186500.jpg">Ootani Ikue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108783" type="appears in" update="2020-03-20">
<name>Celeste</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Celeste is the sister and guardian of Aphrodite. While fighting against devils with Angels Lily, Daisy and Salvia, she was knocked down to earth, losing her memory. She begins to use the name Sakura. On Earth she falls in love with Hanasaki Shouichirou, a young photographer. They have a child together, named Momoko. Three years later, Limone finds Celeste and restores her memory. Celeste says goodbye to her family and leaves. She vanishes, leaving behind her ring, which is part of the Saint Something Four, the Something Old. She then returns to the angel world to protect it and falls into a deep sleep.
Celeste returns after waking from the energies of the Saint Something Four to tell Momoko of her past. She is given permission by Aphrodite to spend one day on Earth. However, she uses up more energy saving Momoko from a brainwashed Viento, and again falls to sleep. In the final episode after defeating Raindevila, she awakes and returns to a normal family life in the OVA. In Wedding Peach DX, Celeste is aware of Momoko’s former identity as a Love Angel. In episode 4 of the OVA, Celeste helps Momoko and the others help get back into their bodies after being switch by the devil Dr. Belphegor.</description>
<picture>245146.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4770" picture="76766.jpg">Suzuka Chiharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108836" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-03-24">
<name>Iwamoto Gouzaburou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245262.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108837" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-03-24">
<name>Petra</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245263.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108838" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-03-24">
<name>Kawanami Hiromi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245264.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108839" type="appears in" update="2020-03-24">
<name>Nocturne</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245265.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1823" picture="20708.jpg">Adachi Shinobu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="9286" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-11-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">四人目の愛天使</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fourth Love Angel</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der vierte Liebesengel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yonin Me no Aitenshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9287" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-10-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ウソ! 柳葉さまに恋人?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">No way! Yanagiba-sempai`s girlfriend?</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wer mit Wem</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uso! Yanagiba-sama ni Koibito?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9288" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-04-19</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ねらわれた花嫁</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The targeted bride</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Hochzeitsfeier mit Hindernissen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nerawareta Hanayome</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9289" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-03-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛すれどせつなく</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Loving, but It`s Painful</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kampf der Dämonen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai Suredo Setsunaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9290" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-05-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">パジャ魔と眠り姫</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pajama and Sleeping Princess</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der schlafende Engel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pajama to Nemuri Hime</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9291" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-12-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">一人ぼっちの愛天使</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Love Angel`s Loneliness</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kein Team mit Salvia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitoribocchi no Aitenshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9292" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-01-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゆりのく・ち・び・る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yuri`s L-I-P-S</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kiiro`s Opfer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuri no Kuchibiru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9293" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-11-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">マフラーに愛を込めて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Scarf With My Love</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein Schal der Liebe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Muffler ni Ai o Komete</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9294" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-12-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">お別れの熱いキス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Kiss of Parting</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Unerwiderte Liebe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Owakare no Atsui Kiss</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9295" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-04-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あっぱれ! お色直し</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Splendid! A change of clothes</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Verwandlung</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Appare! Oironaoshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9296" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-08-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ねらわれたじゃ魔ピー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Targeted Jamapi</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Jamapi wird entführt</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nerawareta Jamapi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9297" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-04-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エンジェルリリィ誕生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Angel Lily is born</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Lily, der Engel der Reinheit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Angel Lily Tanjou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9298" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-09-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪魔のキスは甘くない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Devil`s Kiss is not Sweet</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Seelenraub</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akuma no Kiss wa Amakunai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9299" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-08-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">海辺のペンダント</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Pendant of the Beach</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Geborgt wie das Leben</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Umibe no Pendant</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9300" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-01-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋愛ごっこ大スキー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ski Trip`s Love Games</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Armreif der Liebe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ren`ai Gokko Dai Ski</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9301" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-03-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">2人だけの夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Our Night Together</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Wahrheit über Satania</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari Dake no Yoru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9302" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-10-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハロウィンな魔女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Halloween Witch</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Schwere Bürde für Takuro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Halloween na Majo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9303" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-03-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">離れない心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inseparable Hearts</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kiiro kehrt zurück</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hanarenai Kokoro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9304" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-05-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">3人目の愛天使</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The third angel of love</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Daisy, der Engel der Wahrheit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">3 Nin Me no Aitenshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9305" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-10-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋する少女は最強よ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Girl in Love is the Strongest!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kuppelei</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi Suru Shoujo wa Saikyo yo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9306" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-11-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦場に咲いた恋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Love in the Battlefield</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Eifersucht schlägt Purzelbäume</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senjou ni Saita Koi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9307" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-01-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛が吸われちゃう!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Love will be Sucked Out!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Pettler gibt nicht auf</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai ga Suwarechau!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9308" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-02-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">帰ってきたママ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mama Comes Back!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Aphrodites Schwester</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaette Kita Mama</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9309" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-11-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋のあやつり人形</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Puppet of Love</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Marionetten - Theater</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi no Ayatsuri Ningyou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9310" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-02-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">じゃ魔ピーの初恋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jamapi`s First Love</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Liebe siegt</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jamapi no Hatsukoi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9311" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-05-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">食べすぎにご用心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Be Sure to Eat Properly</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der hohe Preis der Schönheit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tabesugi ni Goyoujin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9312" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-08-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛天使, 夏休みも戦うわ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love Angels, Fighting During Summer Vacation!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Alt wie die Welt</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aitenshi, Natsuyasumi mo Tatakau wa!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9313" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-08-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">真夏の夜(よ)の神秘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Summer Night`s Mystery</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Blau wie die Treu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Manatsu no Yoru no Shinpi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9314" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-02-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">よみがえれ, 愛の記憶</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Remember! Love Memories</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Vento vs. Yosuke</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yomigaere! Ai no Kioku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9315" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-04-05</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">祝! 愛天使誕生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Celebrate! The Birth of the Love Angel</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein Engel erwacht</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuku! Ai Tenshi Tanjou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9316" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-09-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">初(ファースト)キスが奪われる!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My "First Kiss" Will Be Stolen!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein mieser Trick</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">First Kiss ga Ubawareru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9317" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-06-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">勝負! 悪魔のPK戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fight! A Devil`s "PK" match</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der blaue Anhänger</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoubu! Akuma no PK Sen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9318" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-08-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピアノよ響け星空に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Echo of the Piano in a Starry Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Pianistin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Piano yo Hibike Hoshizora ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9319" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-12-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">先生は悪魔?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Is the Teacher a Devil?</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Aufstand der Schüler</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sensei wa Akuma?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9320" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-05-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">奪われたサムシングフォー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stolen Something Four</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die „Zauberhaften Vier"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ubawareta Something Four</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9321" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-09-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドキドキ学園祭</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Exciting School Festival</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Schulfest</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dokidoki Gakuensai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9322" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-07-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪魔族の誇り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Pride of the Devils</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Kraft der Liebe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akumazoku no Hokori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9323" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-10-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">グッバイ悪魔さま</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Good-Bye, Devil-lord!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Pakt</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Goodbye Akuma-sama</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9324" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-01-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">レインデビラの真実</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reine Devila`s Story</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Krieger Raphaels</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rain Devila no Shinjitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9325" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-09-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">いつわりの結婚式</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A False Bride</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wie der Tag so neu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itsuwari no Kekkonshiki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9326" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-07-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">奪われた愛の指輪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stolen Ring of Love</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Momoko geht baden</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ubawareta Ai no Yubiwa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9327" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-07-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">潜入! 悪魔の森</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stealth! Devil`s Forest</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Böses Blut</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sennyuu! Akuma no Mori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9328" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-11-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">乱入! 恋のライバル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Intrusion! A Rival in Love</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Rivalin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rannyuu! Koi no Rival</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9329" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">美人悪魔の恋占い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Beautiful Devil Fortune-teller</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Aquelda</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bijin Akuma no Koi Uranai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9330" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-02-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">私の恋人は悪魔</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Boyfriend is a Devil</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Scarlett setzt Zeichen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi no Koibito wa Akuma</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9331" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-06-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">時をかけるひなぎく</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hinagiku`s Journey Through Time</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die gestohlene Zeit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toki o Kakeru Hinagiku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9332" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-06-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">お見事! 友情お色直し</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Congratulations! Oyonashi in Friendship</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Freundschaft in Gefahr</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omigoto! Yuujou Oironaoshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9333" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-05-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">じゃ魔ピーの逆襲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jamapi`s return</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Jamapi schlägt zurück</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jamapi no Gyakushuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9334" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-12-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">サルビアの涙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Tears of Salvia</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kampf dem Schneemann</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Salvia no Namida</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9335" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-03-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラスト・ウェディング</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Last Wedding</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Hochzeitsglocken</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Last Wedding</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9336" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-07-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">聖花園学園の秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Flower Garden Academy`s Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Blitz und Donner</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sei-Hanazono Gakuen no Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27000" update="2012-05-01">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1995-04-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27001" update="2012-05-01">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1995-04-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46876" update="2012-05-01">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1995-10-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46877" update="2012-05-01">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1995-10-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49574" update="2020-03-13">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>1995-12-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ごめんね ようすけ の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sorry, Yousuke</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gomenne Yousuke no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85172" update="2009-11-27">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">合体! ウェディングロボ!! の巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Combine! Wedding Robo!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gattai! Wedding Robo!! no Kan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85173" update="2020-03-13">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>1996-05-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛天使戦隊 最後の戦い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Love Angel Task Force`s Final Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai Tenshi Sentai Saigo no Tatakai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111785" update="2009-11-30">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>6</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video: Virgin Love</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111786" update="2009-11-30">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">名場面集 Wedding Wars</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Video Compilation: Wedding Wars</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meibamen Shuu Wedding Wars</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120205" update="2012-05-01">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1996-03-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
