<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8910" restricted="false">
<type>Other</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-10-23</startdate>
<enddate>2010-10-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Nurarihyon no Mago: Gekitou Dai Futsal Taikai! Nuragumi W Cup!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Nurarihyon no Mago: Jump Super Anime Tour Special</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ぬらりひょんの孫 ~激闘 大フットサル大会!奴良組Wカップ!!~</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7404" type="Parent Story">Nurarihyon no Mago</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="730" type="Animation Work">Studio Deen</name>
<name id="3918" type="Character Design">Oka Mariko</name>
<name id="20100" type="Original Work">Shiibashi Hiroshi</name>
<name id="2241" type="Direction">Nishimura Junji</name>
<name id="5259" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sakurai Masaaki</name>
<name id="3918" type="Chief Animation Direction">Oka Mariko</name>
<name id="1393" type="Music">Tanaka Kouhei</name>
</creators>
<description>The Nura clan have its own football W-Cup.
Note: This was an exclusively produced animation, which was screened at the Jump Super Anime Tour 2010 events, together with other currently serialised Shounen Jump titles. It was later included as a bonus on the Blu-ray Box 1, released on June 24, 2011.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="230">3.26</permanent>
<temporary count="234">5.65</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221676.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10886</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ぬらりひょんの孫#.E3.82.B8.E3.83.A3.E3.83.B3.E3.83.97.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1.E7.89.88</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="997" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>association football</name>
<description>Football is a sport that involves kicking a ball in order to score a goal, while the other team tries to stop you by kicking the ball in the other direction to score a goal of their own. In the United States, this sport is known as soccer; the inappropriately titled "American" football (which in fact is played with the egg-shaped "ball" being carried around) is some kind of rugby for babies.</description>
<picurl>40031.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="15458" type="main character in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="50">4.69</rating>
<name>Nura Rikuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rikuo is the title character and main protagonist of the series, an average 12-year old boy who inherited 1/4 of his grandfather`s youkai blood. In times of impending danger his youkai blood awakens and he switches into his night form to become the Master of the youkai (the master of all spirits). His youkai form is confident, strong and inspires "Fear" amongst his allies leading many to join him. Rikuo is destined to take over as the Third Master of youkai from his grandfather, though the main conflict for the first portion of the series lies in his rejection of the idea. As a child, Rikuo respected and looked up to youkai, playing pranks on members of the Nura house and often declaring he would become more youkai-like and take over as the Third. However, after a discussion at school, he came to realize the evil nature of youkai deeds and decided to set himself firmly on the path of living a strictly human life. Since then, he has attempted to become more like a normal human by doing all sorts of good deeds. Even though he appreciates all that his youkai underlings do for him, he is nevertheless desperate to prevent his school friends from learning of his connection to youkai. After being tested by Gyuuki he decides to take the position of Young Head and saves both humans and youkai.</description>
<picture>47591.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15460" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-20">
<rating votes="132">8.44</rating>
<name>Yukionna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yukionna is Rikuo`s trusted attendant and part of Rikuo`s new "Hyakki Yakou" who follows him to school disguised as Tsurara Oikawa, a normal schoolgirl. She is affectionate towards Rikuo and even gets jealous when other girls pay him attention. This is also reinforced by the fact that other characters express how bad a situation would be come if Tsurara were to see what other female characters did to Rikuo. She also admires Rikuo`s youkai form, because she finds him very reliable and magnificent. She is overprotective of Rikuo when he is his "day" or human form and expresses great concern for his well being, which is the reason why she is always around him at school (which causes misunderstandings and concern on Kana`s part). She also acts as a cook and, though her food is delicious, most of the time it is chilled or cold.
She also has a fear of Yura as she is an onmyouji and a rivalry with Kana (going so far as to nearly freeze her), however she protects as her death would sadden Rikuo. She is in Kyoto protecting the Investigation group along with Aotabou. Later, she rejoins Rikuo but is kidnapped by Tsuchigumo.</description>
<picture>47590.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17492" type="main character in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="78">7.93</rating>
<name>Nura Rikuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>His night (youkai) form is confident, strong and inspires "Fear" amongst his allies leading many to join him. He decides to leave the human side of things to his "Day" form and handle the youkai-side of things. After losing to his grandfather, he is taken to the youkai village to train and finally learns what type of demon he is and how to gain his Fear abilities. He has departed for Kyoto to face Hagoromo Gitsune to save Yura and avenge his father. He is currently undergoing a 3-day training with Gyuuki to surpass "Himself" after losing to Tsuchigumo. He seems to get stronger when his "Day" and "Night" blood mix. But now it seems as though night Rikuo and day Rikuo are one being and are not a split personality. His primary weapon is the Spirit Blade Nenekirimaru, which was designed to only harm youkai.</description>
<picture>47585.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17495" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="22">6.17</rating>
<name>Zen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Poisonous bird Youkai who was a childhood friend of Rikuo, he was disappointed the Rikuo had become so soft. His species has short lifespan and as a result he has become very weak, but he specializes in making medicine. After being betrayed and nearly killed he was rescued by "Night" Rikuo, he continues to support Rikuo and is the first to exchange Sakazuki and tells him to form a new "Hyakki Yakou".He was on board of Takarabune and poured his medicine on Kubinashi and Itaku to stop their battle. Rikuo later punch him.</description>
<picture>47588.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19463" type="main character in" update="2010-10-16">
<rating votes="39">7.20</rating>
<name>Gyuuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The kanji for his name means `bull.` According to legend, he was once a human who died searching for his mother. His resentment led him to become a youkai after his death. He is a high-ranked subordinate of the Nura group. He was in charge of a conspiracy against Rikuo using Kyuuso. It was revealed this coup was a means of a test, to see if Rikuo could handle being what he was and told Rikuo to abandon his human side as that would only get him killed. In response to Rikuo`s aim for being the third he works even harder now.He fought the Tengu of Mount Kurama 400 years ago. He appeared in Kyoto by the order of Nurarihyon to help Rikuo.</description>
<picture>54299.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19465" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-16">
<rating votes="36">6.23</rating>
<name>Kubinashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A "No-neck" Youkai and one of Rikuo`s demon guardians. He fights using thread that entangle you the more you struggle, made from Kejourou`s personality and Jorougumo`s restriants. Part of Rikuo`s new "Hyakki Yakou" he is traveling to Kyoto. He used to go by the name `Joushuu No Gentsatsushi Kubinashi` (Lit. String Assassin of Hitachi Province) and is strong enough to restrain Toono youkai easily using his "Black string" technique. He seems to be a gizoku (honorable thief) before he joined the Nura clan. He goes back to his murderous way in Kyoto and is confronted by Ibaraki Douji. He was almost killed by Ibaraki Douji until he was saved by Kappa and Yura.</description>
<picture>54301.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19466" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-10">
<rating votes="35">6.38</rating>
<name>Aotabou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The degenerate priest who wears the iron blue robe and the physically strongest Youkai in the Nura household. He used to be a monk who killed many warriors. He has fists that can crush rock and palms that can fit a person`s head. He was enlightened by a holy man. He wishes to protect children after being enlightened. The holy man once stated that it is up to him whether to become human again or a raging god, he almost became human but he killed the people who were torturing the children he wishes to protect while crying. He is often seen with Kurotabou and the two are known as the assault officers of the Nura House. He has a skull necklace that when removed greatly increases his strength. He is also the leader of a biker gang called the Blood Night Hyakki Yakou. Part of Rikuo`s new "Hyakki Yakou" he is in Kyoto along with Yuki Onna. He fought and managed to kill Shoukera.</description>
<picture>54302.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19468" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-16">
<rating votes="41">7.06</rating>
<name>Kurotabou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Assassin and Destruction Monk &amp; Master of the hidden blade, he is often seen with Aotabou and the two are known as the assault officers of the Nura House. In his human form he dresses like a businessman, and he also saved Torii from her curse as repayment for helping him. Part of Rikuo`s new "Hyakki Yakou", he is traveling to Kyoto. He is currently fighting Ibaraki Douji with Ryuuji and Mamiru.</description>
<picture>54303.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19471" type="appears in" update="2011-04-13">
<rating votes="25">7.94</rating>
<name>Kappa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Kappa Youkai in the Nura clan whose domain is the fear of water and one of Rikuo`s demon guardians, he loves cucumbers. He fights extremely well near water and fights in a ninja suit. As part of Rikuo`s new "Hyakki Yakou", he is traveling to Kyoto. He appears to save Kubinashi and Kejourou.</description>
<picture>54284.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="19472" type="appears in" update="2010-10-16">
<rating votes="40">7.85</rating>
<name>Kejourou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A demon who uses her hair to fight, she serves as one of Rikuo`s Guardians. After Rikuo got beat at the first seal in Kyoto and went to recover and train she got the Hyakki Yako to keep motivated by asking them if they want to disappoint Rikuo when he got back. She appears to be Kubinashi`s lover, of sorts, having, in the past, offered her life to save his. She is also closest to Kubinashi out of all the Youkai in the series ad is once known as Kino. Her fear is Midaregami.</description>
<picture>54286.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="19475" type="appears in" update="2010-10-16">
<rating votes="20">8.10</rating>
<name>Nura Wakana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rikuo`s mother. Though she herself is human, she seems to have no problem living in a home full of youkai.</description>
<picture>55507.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="20086" type="appears in" update="2010-10-16">
<rating votes="20">4.28</rating>
<name>Nattou-Kozou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the demons who lives in Nura`s house. His head is a nattou and he consequently smells like nattou.</description>
<picture>54285.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="20578" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-01">
<rating votes="18">6.22</rating>
<name>Mezumaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gyuuki clan`s young head assistant. Wears a horse`s skull and his face looks like a girl. Can control human with string but don`t have any other mean to attack so he usually become a support. Now lives in Nura`s house.</description>
<picture>54291.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="381" picture="186189.jpg">Hoshi Souichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20579" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="22">5.13</rating>
<name>Gozumaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gyuuki clan`s young head. Cool and cruel, wield a katana, Tsume, he also able to control human with string but not as good Mezumaru. Now he lives in Nura`s house as candidate for next Gyuuki clan`s next leader, but actually a hostage.</description>
<picture>54290.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20580" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-16">
<rating votes="7">6.77</rating>
<name>Kuroumaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The messy-haired tengu with a gem on his forehead.</description>
<picture>54292.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20581" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-16">
<rating votes="8">6.18</rating>
<name>Tosakamaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The blond tengu with a mohawk.</description>
<picture>54294.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="470" picture="17419.jpg">Irino Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20582" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-16">
<rating votes="11">6.93</rating>
<name>Sasami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The long-haired tengu who wears glasses and the only female of the Sanbagarasu (as revealed in an omake in volume 6). She was disgusted by Mezumaru attacking the women`s baths. She wields a pair of short whips as weapons.</description>
<picture>54293.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34635" type="appears in" update="2012-01-17">
<rating votes="24">7.57</rating>
<name>Hagoromo-Gitsune</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The demon fox who was originally considered the master of spirits, she is the head of the Kyoto youkai. According to Keikan records, Hagorome-Gitsune first appeared during turbulent times, possessed the body of a notable child, and took control of the body to attain adult form. Gathering power by absorbing hatred, envy, anger, despair and large quantities of malice from the center of government, she continued to grow stronger and it is said that the stronger the malice in the world, the stronger she will become. Despite this, she can only live as long as a human lifetime, for when her host body`s life reaches its end, she must hide her "true form" somewhere safe until a suitable candidate for her reincarnation appears. If her "true form" isn`t sealed, then regardless of how many times she is defeated, she will continue to reincarnate into the next generation.
400 years ago, she posed as the legendary courtesan Yodo-dono and fought Nurarihyon at Osaka Castle, but was eventually defeated. In the course of 400 years, her reincarnation was repeatedly prevented due to Nura Rihan`s interferences, until Abe no Seimei and Sanmoto Gorouzaemon successfully plotted his murder by reviving and manipulating Rihan`s ex-wife, the ayakashi Yamabuki Otome. Yamabuki Otome` revived body (which resembled her previous appearance) later became Hagoromo Gitsune`s current host and successfully gave birth to Nue, Abe no Seimei`s reincarnation during the battle in Kyoto. Hagoromo Gitsune was eventually forced out of the host`s body by Rikuo`s Nenekirimaru and Yura`s Hangun. As soon as Nue broke out of his cocoon, he killed and sent Hagoromo Gitsune to hell.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>53015.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37681" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-21">
<rating votes="6">5.60</rating>
<name>Sannokuchi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sannokuchi is a small youkai of the http://anidb.net/ch37514 [Nura Clan]. Because his mouth looks like the number "3," he is named as such. He is often seen in the company of http://anidb.net/ch20086 [Nattou Kozou], http://anidb.net/ch37686 [Toufu Kozou] and http://anidb.net/ch37687 [Ko-oni], and the group frequently play Go or hold miniature banquets.</description>
<picture>216512.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12352" picture="130106.jpg">Hirata Mana</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="131432" update="2012-03-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2010-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
