<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8913" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>6</episodecount>
<startdate>2012-03-17</startdate>
<enddate>2012-04-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ozuma</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Озма</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">オズマ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Ozma</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="725" approval="9" total="13">Uchuu Kaizoku Captain Harlock</anime>
<anime id="683" approval="5" total="6">Queen Emeraldas</anime>
<anime id="3660" approval="2" total="2">Hakugei Densetsu</anime>
<anime id="732" approval="2" total="2">Submarine Super 99</anime>
<anime id="7873" approval="1" total="6">Fractale</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="538802">almost decided to skip this series because of the bad ratings, glad i decided otherwise. the story evolves in a postapocalyptic nausicaä type of setting mixed with fast paced action and some more intense and thoughtful scenes</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="13264" type="Character Design">Fujisaki Kenji</name>
<name id="3634" type="Series Composition">Takegami Junki</name>
<name id="13264" type="Chief Animation Direction">Fujisaki Kenji</name>
<name id="7392" type="Music">Yamashita Kousuke</name>
<name id="17590" type="Direction">Ikezoe Takahiro</name>
<name id="1107" type="Original Work">Matsumoto Reiji</name>
<name id="660" type="Chief Direction">Takahashi Ryousuke</name>
<name id="1107" type="Chief Designer">Matsumoto Reiji</name>
<name id="735" type="Animation Work">Gonzo</name>
<name id="30252" type="Animation Work">LandQ Studio</name>
<name id="43948" type="Work">Planet Entertaiment</name>
<name id="46964" type="Character Design">Nanko Kimimichi</name>
<name id="46964" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nanko Kimimichi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a science-fiction action concept developed by http://anidb.net/cr1107 [Matsumoto Leiji].
"Sometimes the sun is a gentle mother, bringing life to the surface of the Earth. And sometimes a strict father, who brings trials. These trials, which have happened many times since the creation of Earth, have come again. The land is dry, the oceans vanished. And vast seas of sand were born. Most of the life that survives is in danger of extinction, clinging to the thin atmosphere that remains. But some still live on, seeking out a tiny glimpse of hope... in the dry seas of sand." — from the intro
http://anidb.net/ch40653 [Sam Coin] witnesses how a young women named http://anidb.net/ch40654 [Maya] is relentlessly pursued by several Theseus Sand-borne Destroyers when an Ozma, a gigantic sand whale, surfaces cutting them off. Sam only barely saves Maya from being buried by sand, and the Theseus army, believing her to have died in the incident, seems to give up the search...
Sam brings Maya to Port Oase, a still thriving independent town, placed in a rock canyon. Neither http://anidb.net/ch40655 [Mimei] a good friend nor Captain http://anidb.net/ch40656 [Binas] are thrilled by the sudden appearance of mysterious Maya... and when the Theseus army shows up, the chase for the sand pirate ship, Bardanos, with Maya on board is on.
— written by foo2</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="742">3.36</permanent>
<temporary count="747">5.80</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>205932.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13973</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12677</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5053</identifier>
<identifier>thcngs</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ozuma</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>オズマ_(アニメ)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2455</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>341732</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14421</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/3326</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>leiji-matsumotos-ozma</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="509" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-19">
<name>clone</name>
<description>This character is grown from a single somatic cell or cell nucleus and genetically identical to it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="898" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-04-17">
<name>submarine</name>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1700" parentid="2872" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>pirate</name>
<description>Pirates are people who attack ships on the high seas to rob others of their treasure. Well, at least usually. Other people calling themselves pirates are not unheard of, usually focusing on the freedom and romance involved in the piracy-related tropes and cliches. They may or may not be after the One Piece or a spaceship full of diamonds, too, if that`s what they see as treasure. Real-life pirates were extremely common a few centuries ago, and countries even sponsored their own pirates, called "privateers", to attack ships with flags of other countries. Nowadays, however, very few actual pirates still exist, and they rely more on terrorism and guerrilla warfare than anything else, demanding ransom in exchange for hostages instead of openly attacking the enemies with their swords. Another, more modern meaning for the word refers to people who illegally download copyrighted works they are not entitled to have a copy of. Be whichever it may, there are pirates around here. Arr, avast! Thar be pirates in these dark waters, matey!</description>
<picurl>126791.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1783" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>immature</name>
<description>Marked by or indicating a lack of maturity</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2629" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-16">
<name>desert</name>
<description>Setting with vast amounts of sand, merciless high temperatures, and very little water.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2882" parentid="2952" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-17">
<name>dystopia</name>
<description>A dystopia (from Ancient Greek: δυσ-, "bad, ill", and Ancient Greek: τόπος, "place, landscape"; alternatively cacotopia, or anti-utopia) is, in literature, an often futuristic society that has degraded into a repressive and controlled state, often under the guise of being utopian. Dystopian literature has underlying cautionary tones, warning society that if we continue to live how we do, this will be the consequence. A dystopia, thus, is regarded as a sort of negative utopia and is often characterized by an authoritarian or totalitarian form of government. Dystopias usually feature different kinds of repressive social control systems, a lack or total absence of individual freedoms and expressions and constant states of warfare or violence. Dystopias often explore the concept of humans abusing technology and how humans individually and collectively cope with technology that has evolved too quickly such as the car, the flamethrower or the microwave. A dystopian society is also often characterized by widespread poverty and brutal political controls such as a large military-like police.</description>
<picurl>69879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3581" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-23">
<name>tactics</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3625" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-14">
<name>water scarcity</name>
<description>Water scarcity is the lack of sufficient available water resources to meet water needs within a region.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4521" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>lost technology</name>
<description>Any advanced technology or science-related knowledge that was lost for some reason fits the description. This could be technology from a time before a post-apocalyptic cataclysm, knowledge gained a long time ago but forgotten, or the relics of an old alien civilization only recently discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5305" parentid="6234" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-29">
<name>tarot</name>
<description>The tarot is a pack of playing cards, most commonly numbering 78, used from the mid-15th century in various parts of Europe to play a group of card games such as Italian tarocchini and French tarot. From the late 18th century until the present time, the tarot has also found use by mystics and occultists for divination. Tarot cards are used throughout much of Europe to play card games. In English-speaking countries, where these games are largely unplayed, tarot cards are now used primarily for divinatory purposes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>191977.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5862" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-08">
<name>melodrama</name>
<description>A melodrama is a dramatic work that exaggerates plot and characters in order to appeal to the emotions, often with strongly stereotyped characters. Language, behaviour, or events which resemble melodramas are also called melodramatic. In scholarly and historical musical contexts melodramas are dramas of the 18th and 19th centuries in which orchestral music or song was used to accompany the action.
Melodrama is a style of drama that has been applied on the stage, in movies and television, and radio formats, from the 18th century to the present. Because of the long timeframe in which the style has existed, it is difficult to derive a precise definition. The term melodrama is most often used pejoratively, to suggest that the work to which the term is applied lacks sophistication or subtlety.
The term originated from the early 19th-century French word mélodrame, which is derived from Greek melos, music, and French drame, drama (from Late Latin drāma, which in turn derives from Greek drān, to do, perform).
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5876" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-25">
<name>biting</name>
<description>Some people seem to like biting others, especially when irritated. This may also be an aggression or self-defence mechanism. In anime, this will often lead to greatly enlarged mouths being able to bite someone else`s head, commonly for comedic effect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6005" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-10-17">
<name>battle of wits</name>
<description>There is some intellectual battle between the characters. They each might attempt to discern what the other knows and/or could be planning. Then, rather than simply relying on the use of raw power, try to deduce an effective strategy to foil their opponent(s). The battle of wits can be in the center of the intrigue or just a side story.
Examples: Death Note, Code Geass</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6234" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>motifs</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="40653" type="main character in" update="2012-03-08">
<rating votes="5">1.63</rating>
<name>Sam Coin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>80091.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="174" picture="41158.jpg">Kakihara Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40654" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-08">
<rating votes="7">5.18</rating>
<name>Maya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>80092.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40655" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-08">
<rating votes="7">4.25</rating>
<name>Mimei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>80093.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40656" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-08">
<rating votes="7">7.59</rating>
<name>Binas</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>80094.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="222" picture="19786.jpg">Tanaka Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40815" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-05-21">
<rating votes="2">2.57</rating>
<name>Ejiboura Gii</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173684.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2603" picture="22591.jpg">Sakurai Toshiharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40816" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-08">
<rating votes="3">1.50</rating>
<name>Gido Gairaa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>80446.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27" picture="26123.jpg">Hayami Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40817" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-05-14">
<rating votes="2">2.57</rating>
<name>Kun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173401.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2135" picture="66343.jpg">Nakakuni Takurou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40818" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-05-14">
<rating votes="2">1.88</rating>
<name>Danga Shougun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173372.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="371" picture="166173.jpg">Kuroda Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40819" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-05-14">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Tom</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173379.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="403" picture="74821.jpg">Horie Kazuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40820" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-05-14">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Yamu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62859.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="320" picture="66660.jpg">Kobayashi Yumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40821" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-05-14">
<rating votes="3">4.84</rating>
<name>Luna Noguchi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173399.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1827" picture="55501.jpg">Uran Sakiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40822" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-05-14">
<rating votes="1">6.80</rating>
<name>Rokusanda Umai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173376.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="652" picture="18178.jpg">Tatekabe Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40823" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-05-14">
<rating votes="2">3.54</rating>
<name>Bokus Rafu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173378.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12671" picture="74490.jpg">Fujinuma Kento</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42570" type="appears in" update="2015-05-14">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Schultz</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173400.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11034" picture="170736.jpg">Kabuta Yuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42571" type="appears in" update="2015-05-14">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Souryuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173373.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32282" picture="86377.jpg">Igarashi Ryouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42572" type="appears in" update="2015-05-14">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Sophie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173375.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34424" picture="128158.jpg">Yamaguchi Karin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42573" type="appears in" update="2012-03-18">
<name>Varda</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="28873" picture="66030.jpg">Tanaka Masayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42574" type="appears in" update="2015-05-14">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Marie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173374.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32964" picture="89757.jpg">Matsu Kiyoka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75320" type="appears in" update="2015-05-21">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Heidkamp</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173685.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33637" picture="245666.jpg">Yano Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75321" type="appears in" update="2015-05-21">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Mist</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173686.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42928" picture="172058.jpg">Tokutome Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75322" type="appears in" update="2015-05-21">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Dick Coyne</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173687.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27" picture="26123.jpg">Hayami Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75323" type="appears in" update="2015-05-21">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Carla</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173688.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="75324" type="appears in" update="2015-05-21">
<rating votes="1">6.80</rating>
<name>Olga-fukukan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173689.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12666" picture="42833.jpg">Ikuta Yoshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75325" type="appears in" update="2015-05-21">
<rating votes="1">6.80</rating>
<name>Eir</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62871.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="39175" picture="149494.jpg">Uno Chihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="137649" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-04-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新生の日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Day of New Life</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinsei no Hi</title>
<summary>Ozma`s nature is revealed, and it`s time for Maya to make her choice:  begin a new era with the life inside the zone, or allow humanity to remain in control of a dying planet.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>593855</identifier>
<identifier>leiji-matsumotos-ozma</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="137650" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">仮面の男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Masked Man</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kamen no Otoko</title>
<summary>The Bardanos finds itself in Ozma`s nest: a strange cave filled with fresh water and life.  Bainas shoots Gido`s mask, and the face beneath it is that of Sam`s brother.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>593853</identifier>
<identifier>leiji-matsumotos-ozma</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="137651" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地の果てまで</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the Ends of the Earth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chi no Hate made</title>
<summary>As Gido escapes with Maya, Sam sets off in pursuit with Mimay in tow.  But their bike is no match for the Theseus sand cruiser, and Gido escapes.  To catch them, they`ll have to go back under the ground with the Bardanos...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>593851</identifier>
<identifier>leiji-matsumotos-ozma</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="137652" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-03-31</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">千年の迷い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Thousand Years of Doubt</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sennen no Mayoi</title>
<summary>Sam takes Maya to a hidden shelter constructed in the distant past, and filled with ancient technology.  This shelter is the source of the ship`s technology, and the secret of Sam`s plans to hunt the sand whale...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>593849</identifier>
<identifier>leiji-matsumotos-ozma</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="137653" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-03-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">潜航限界</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Underground Voyage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senkou Genkai</title>
<summary>The Sand Pirates have escaped with Maya, and Theseus is in hot pursuit.  The pirates dive under the sand, but are locked down by sand anchors.  The pressure and temperature in the ship are rising, and time is running out...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>593847</identifier>
<identifier>leiji-matsumotos-ozma</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="137654" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-03-17</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">砂のクジラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sand Whale</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suna no Kujira</title>
<summary>It`s a post-apocalyptic future, and the oceans have dried up and the world turned into a single massive desert.  Sam Coyne is out hunting sand whales, when he stumbles across a much bigger prize: a mysterious woman on the run from a fleet of destroyers!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>593845</identifier>
<identifier>leiji-matsumotos-ozma</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138003" update="2012-03-17">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-03-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138004" update="2012-03-17">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-03-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
