<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8914" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2012-07-27</startdate>
<enddate>2012-07-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Code Geass: Hangyaku no Lelouch - Nunnally in Wonderland</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Nunnally in Wonderland</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Code Geass: Lelouch of the Rebellion - Nunnally in Wonderland</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Code Geass: Nunnally in Wonderland</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">코드 기아스: 반역의 를르슈 - 나나리 in 원더랜드</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">コードギアス 反逆のルルーシュ ナナリーinワンダーランド</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">Code Geass 反叛的鲁鲁修 娜娜莉梦游仙境</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4521" type="Alternative Setting">Code Geass: Hangyaku no Lelouch</anime>
<anime id="5373" type="Alternative Setting">Code Geass: Hangyaku no Lelouch R2</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8337" approval="2" total="3">Heart no Kuni no Alice: Wonderful Wonder World</anime>
<anime id="7369" approval="1" total="7">Kuroshitsuji II</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="210496">Clearly for fans only. If you have watched the original code geass, you will probably get a good laugh out of this little spin-off. I know I did.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.geass.jp/nunnally/</url>
<creators>
<name id="11249" type="Direction">Baba Makoto</name>
<name id="1573" type="Music">Nakagawa Koutarou</name>
<name id="1824" type="Music">Kuroishi Hitomi</name>
<name id="665" type="Character Design">Kimura Takahiro</name>
</creators>
<description>In the all-new story, http://anidb.net/ch103 [Lelouch] makes the ultimate use of his Geass power for his little sister http://anidb.net/ch2000 [Nunnally], who loves Alice in Wonderland.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1148">2.80</permanent>
<temporary count="1167">5.40</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>224347.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13974</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12685</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5172</identifier>
<identifier>ggsrbe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.geass.jp/nunnally/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Code_Geass#Anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>コードギアス_反逆のルルーシュ_ナナリーinワンダーランド</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15874</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3457" parentid="6397" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-17">
<name>Alice`s Adventures in Wonderland</name>
<description>Alice`s Adventures in Wonderland (often shortened to Alice in Wonderland,) is an 1865 novel written by English author Charles Lutwidge Dodgson under the pseudonym Lewis Carroll. It tells of a girl named Alice falling through a rabbit hole into a fantasy world populated by peculiar, anthropomorphic creatures. The tale plays with logic, giving the story lasting popularity with adults as well as with children. It is considered to be one of the best examples of the literary nonsense genre. Its narrative course and structure, characters and imagery have been enormously influential in both popular culture and literature, especially in the fantasy genre.
The anime or an episode features important elements of the novel. This could mean that the main character is portrayed as Alice (with another name), accompanied by somebody portraying the white rabbit (possibly as a human). While the world can be a Wonderland, it does not have to be.</description>
<picurl>169452.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4474" parentid="2655" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-04">
<name>self-parody</name>
<description>The anime is a parody of itself. 
I.e. the authors make fun of the genre they are portraying, and take the actions of their characters and story lightly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4606" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>slide show animation</name>
<description>The entire anime or parts of it show sequences of still images. Sometimes used in low budged animations for action scenes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6397" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-02">
<name>tales</name>
<description>Tales are stories told time and again and passed down from generation to generation, and some of those show up in anime not just once or twice, but several times.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="103" type="main character in" update="2012-07-17">
<rating votes="1943">8.60</rating>
<name>Lelouch Lamperouge</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16249.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2000" type="appears in" update="2009-01-07">
<rating votes="187">2.78</rating>
<name>Nunnally Lamperouge</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nunnally was born Nunnally vi Britannia, daughter of the Emperor of Britannia, Charles zi Britannia, and Marianne vi Britannia. She was 87th in line of succession to the Britannia Throne. When her mother was assassinated, Nunnally was paralysed by bullet wounds, and went blind due to psychological trauma of witnessing the brutal murder of her mother. Lelouch believes that she may be able to see again someday. After the confrontation between Lelouch and the Emperor of Britannia about the murder of their mother, both Lelouch and Nunnally were exiled to Japan as political prisoners.</description>
<picture>16784.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41004" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-30">
<rating votes="2">3.96</rating>
<name>Anya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>White Rabbit version of Anya.</description>
<picture>91764.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41005" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-30">
<name>Kanon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Red Queen version of Kanon.</description>
<picture>91754.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="632" picture="18159.jpg">Mito Kouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41006" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-30">
<rating votes="4">6.55</rating>
<name>Kallen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91757.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41007" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-30">
<rating votes="2">5.06</rating>
<name>Cornelia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>White King version of Cornelia.</description>
<picture>91759.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="570" picture="151691.jpg">Minagawa Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41008" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-30">
<rating votes="5">7.08</rating>
<name>Shirley</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91758.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41009" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-30">
<rating votes="1">2.17</rating>
<name>Schneizel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Red King version of Schneizel.</description>
<picture>91763.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="633" picture="33549.jpg">Inoue Norihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41010" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-30">
<name>Gino</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Red Knight version of Gino.</description>
<picture>91761.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="381" picture="186189.jpg">Hoshi Souichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41011" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-30">
<rating votes="3">3.65</rating>
<name>Suzaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>White Knight version of Suzaku.</description>
<picture>91762.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41012" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-30">
<rating votes="4">6.33</rating>
<name>Cecile</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91755.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41013" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-30">
<rating votes="4">2.57</rating>
<name>Nina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91766.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="311" picture="44706.jpg">Chiba Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41014" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-03">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Marianne</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Queen of Hearts version of Marianne.</description>
<picture>91756.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="628" picture="188442.jpg">Dodo Asako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41015" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-30">
<rating votes="5">7.63</rating>
<name>Milly</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91753.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41016" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-30">
<rating votes="4">5.38</rating>
<name>Euphemia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>White Queen version of Euphemia.</description>
<picture>91765.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="186" picture="16999.jpg">Minami Omi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41017" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-30">
<rating votes="1">8.17</rating>
<name>Lloyd</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91760.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2605" picture="22592.jpg">Shiratori Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41018" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-30">
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<name>Rolo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91752.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="326" picture="17162.jpg">Mizushima Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41019" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-30">
<rating votes="3">6.75</rating>
<name>Villetta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91751.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41020" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-30">
<name>Koutei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91750.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2" picture="16471.jpg">Wakamoto Norio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41021" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-30">
<rating votes="12">6.34</rating>
<name>C.C.</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cheshire Cat version of C.C.</description>
<picture>91749.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47434" type="appears in" update="2012-07-30">
<rating votes="5">6.11</rating>
<name>Lelouch</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mad Hatter Lelouch.</description>
<picture>91769.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47435" type="main character in" update="2012-07-30">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Nunnally</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Alice version of Nunnally.</description>
<picture>91770.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47436" type="appears in" update="2012-07-30">
<rating votes="2">5.08</rating>
<name>Nunnally Lamperouge</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91771.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="47437" type="appears in" update="2012-07-30">
<rating votes="6">8.30</rating>
<name>Lelouch Lamperouge</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91772.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="136748" update="2012-02-02">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2012-07-27</airdate>
<rating votes="8">3.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138050" update="2012-03-19">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">1.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
