<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8943" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>51</episodecount>
<startdate>2012-04-03</startdate>
<enddate>2013-03-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Naruto Sugoi Doryoku: Rock Lee no Seishun Full-Power Ninden</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">NARUTO -ナルト- SD ロック・リーの青春フルパワー忍伝</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">NARUTOSD ロック・リーの青春フルパワー忍伝</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Naruto SD - Rock Lee no Seishun Full-Power Ninden</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Naruto SD</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">NARUTO SD[すごいどりょく] ロック・リーの青春フルパワー忍伝</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">NARUTO Spin-Off: Rock Lee &amp; His Ninja Pals</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Naruto Rock Lee</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">火影忍者SD 李洛克的青春全力忍传</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4880" type="Parent Story">Naruto Shippuuden</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="11468" approval="3" total="7">Shingeki! Kyojin Chuugakkou</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="444920">Hilarious.

Most probably disregard this one which is a shame since they`re missing out on a really funny show.

I burst out laughing every time Rock Lee "copies" a jutsu.

A must see for every Naruto fan</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="67909">freakin cute</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/lee/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1695" type="Character Design">Tanaka Chiyuki</name>
<name id="19607" type="Series Composition">Shimoyama Kento</name>
<name id="7019" type="Music">Mutou Seiji</name>
<name id="7026" type="Music">Abe Jun</name>
<name id="2977" type="Original Work">Kishimoto Masashi</name>
<name id="669" type="Direction">Murata Masahiko</name>
<name id="10892" type="Direction">Sessha Gorou</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a manga by Taira Kenji, serialised in Saikyou Jump. A spin-off of http://anidb.net/cr2977 [Kishimoto Masashi]`s popular http://anidb.net/a239 [Naruto] manga.
The story focuses on the strange antics of Team Guy as they work on becoming great ninjas, a job which often requires saving Lee from himself.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="420">2.79</permanent>
<temporary count="439">5.26</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>80946.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13834</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12979</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5152</identifier>
<identifier>gtouuv</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/lee/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ロック・リーの青春フルパワー忍伝</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2513</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>342047</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14459</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B00XVPQASW</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2572" parentid="2282" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-09">
<name>ninja</name>
<description>A ninja was a covert agent or mercenary of feudal Japan specializing in unorthodox arts of war.
The functions of the ninja included espionage, sabotage, infiltration, and assassination, as well as open combat in certain situations.
The ninja, using covert methods of waging war, were contrasted with the samurai, who had strict rules about honor and combat.</description>
<picurl>244347.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3831" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-13">
<name>training</name>
<description>Training is extensive, serious practising a person undergoes in order to develop skills and abilities, such as handling weapons, playing instruments, playing sports, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4474" parentid="2655" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-04">
<name>self-parody</name>
<description>The anime is a parody of itself. 
I.e. the authors make fun of the genre they are portraying, and take the actions of their characters and story lightly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6349" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>multi-segment episodes</name>
<description>Multi-segment episodes are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes], which are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length (up to and including 10 minutes).
Also not to be confused with an OVA or music video with multiple (otherwise unrelated) full-length http://anidb.net/t7241 [bundled episodes] consolidated into a single episode video track.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7213" type="appears in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="361">8.16</rating>
<name>Jiraiya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jiraiya (自来也) is a remarkable ninja and possibly the closest thing to the Hokage that never was, not only trained by the third Hokage but also the trainer of the man who would eventually go on to become the Fourth, as well as a young boy who dreams of one day being the Hokage himself. Since childhood, he has had an eye for the opposite sex and often had conflicts with one of his team, Tsunade, over her figure. Jiraiya was not a model ninja at all and usually ended up as the fall guy, although his master comparing him to Orochimaru, his other team member, didn`t help much.</description>
<picture>54626.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="297" picture="233915.jpg">Ootsuka Houchuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7256" type="appears in" update="2011-05-26">
<rating votes="471">8.04</rating>
<name>Hyuuga Hinata</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hyuuga Hinata is a member of Team 8 who suffers from a lack of self-confidence throughout the series. She is very shy and always reluctant to speak her mind or to do something that might antagonize another character, causing her difficulties whenever she is on a mission. This results in her effective expulsion from her clan even though she is the eldest daughter of the Hyuga clan`s leader and the heiress to the clan. Hinata`s inability to stand up for herself caused her father to disown her at a young age, leaving her in the care of her teacher, Kurenai Yuhi. Masashi Kishimoto had originally intended Hinata to be a regular member of the Hyuga clan but instead made her a ninja. Soon after her introduction, Hinata begins training to become stronger, both to overcome her own weaknesses and to prove her worth to her father. Her efforts begin to prove successful towards the end of Part I, as her father takes a greater interest in her training.
Source: wikipedia.org</description>
<picture>29538.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7719" type="appears in" update="2010-07-04">
<rating votes="504">3.28</rating>
<name>Uchiha Sasuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26580.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="221" picture="17039.jpg">Sugiyama Noriaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8600" type="appears in" update="2012-09-09">
<rating votes="117">7.50</rating>
<name>Tobi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tobi, whose real name is Obito Uchiha, is the leader of Akatsuki who initially acts as a regular member of the group. He first appears as a carefree and a goofy person whose actions often result on him being attacked by his partner, Deidara. After Deidara dies in a suicidal bid to kill Sasuke Uchiha, Tobi starts taking a special interest in Sasuke`s development up to Itachi Uchiha`s death while leading the Akatsuki. He falsely claims to be Madara Uchiha, the leader of the Uchiha clan, and shows a more serious personality.</description>
<picture>54596.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8603" type="appears in" update="2015-01-26">
<rating votes="284">7.59</rating>
<name>Orochimaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Orochimaru is a major antagonist of Naruto series. He is a missing ninja from http://anidb.net/ch8864 [Konohagakure], who is recognised as one of the most powerful ninjas and known as one of the "Legendary Sannin" (Legendary Three Ninja), which was a title that was given to him and his former team mates, http://anidb.net/ch7213 [Jiraiya] and http://anidb.net/ch8606 [Tsunade], by Hanzou during the Second Shinobi World War. His main goals are to capture http://anidb.net/ch7196 [Uchiha Sasuke] as his new body to gain possession of the Sharingan and to destroy Konoha.</description>
<picture>37851.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3368" picture="132584.jpg">Kujira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8606" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="419">6.45</rating>
<name>Tsunade</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsunade, as well as her former teammates http://anidb.net/ch7213 [Jiraiya] and http://anidb.net/ch8603 [Orochimaru], is a former student of the http://anidb.net/ch8865 [Third Hokage]. She is also the granddaughter of the http://anidb.net/ch8859 [First Hokage], and so many characters in the series refer to her with the Japanese honorific "hime" (meaning "princess"). Despite her connections to past Hokage, Tsunade hates the position when she is first introduced. After her brother and boyfriend died in pursuit of their dreams to become Hokage, she lost faith in the title and the concept of dreams. She regains her faith in both after meeting http://anidb.net/ch240 [Naruto Uzumaki], who consistently overcomes any obstacle in his own dreams of being Hokage. As a result, Tsunade accepts the position of Fifth Hokage to protect http://anidb.net/ch8864 [Konohagakure] on behalf of everyone she has loved. Despite the importance of her position, Tsunade tends to avoid her duties, instead leaving them for her assistants. She will fulfil her role to address matters important to the village, and throughout Part II leads Konoha in combating http://anidb.net/ch8599 [Akatsuki]. When Konoha is invaded by http://anidb.net/ch11993 [Pain], she uses up all her energy summoning http://anidb.net/ch17274 [Katsuyu], her slug summon, to protect the villagers, and stays in a coma for a long time causing her to be dismissed as Hokage temporarily. Tsunade possesses a number of traits that set her apart from other characters in the series, such as being a compulsive gambler with terrible luck. On the rare occasions that she hits a winning streak she perceives it as a bad omen, and makes it a point to fortify her defences when it occurs. Additionally, although she is in her fifties, she constantly assumes the appearance of a twenty-year-old woman, retaining only her characteristically large breasts. Despite her odd personality Tsunade is a talented ninja; she has superhuman strength that allows her to reduce buildings to rubble and can heal injuries that most others would consider incurable. Her healing abilities are such that she has devised a method of regeneration for herself, making her all but invincible in battle. At the conclusion of Part I, Tsunade takes http://anidb.net/ch7194 [Haruno Sakura] as an apprentice, teaching her how to use both of her trademark abilities.</description>
<picture>27913.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1813" picture="172159.jpg">Katsuki Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8607" type="appears in" update="2011-09-12">
<rating votes="92">3.92</rating>
<name>Yakushi Kabuto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54628.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="211" picture="17028.jpg">Kanna Nobutoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8613" type="appears in" update="2010-04-28">
<rating votes="50">5.92</rating>
<name>Shizune</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shizune is a http://anidb.net/ch8864 [Konohagakure] ninja introduced in the series as http://anidb.net/ch8606 [Tsunade]`s assistant. She left Konohagakure with Tsunade after the death of her uncle, and over the years, Tsunade taught her medical techniques. Despite her medicinal affinity, many of the attacks she uses in the series are poison-based, including using concealed poisoned needles or emitting toxic gas from her mouth. Shizune is one of the few characters that Tsunade trusts with absolute certainty, as she identifies details that Tsunade tends to overlook. In Part II of the series, Shizune`s concern for details causes her to question Tsunade`s judgment, creating interference with Tsunade`s plans and temporarily straining the relationship between the two.</description>
<picture>28660.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4725" picture="27575.jpg">Nemoto Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17192" type="appears in" update="2010-04-28">
<rating votes="14">6.81</rating>
<name>Tonton</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tonton is http://anidb.net/ch8606 [Tsunade]`s pet pig, often kept in the care of http://anidb.net/ch8613 [Shizune]. She does not speak in any human language, but still manages to get her point across by whining in her own unique tone (a "buhi" or "oink" depending on the language). It seems that Tsunade and Shizune are able to understand what Tonton is trying to say. Tonton`s nose also seems adept at tracking things, such so that http://anidb.net/ch10966 [Pakkun] has some familiarity with her.</description>
<picture>47039.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4725" picture="27575.jpg">Nemoto Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42754" type="main character in" update="2012-03-21">
<rating votes="8">5.32</rating>
<name>Uzumaki Naruto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>84349.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="302" picture="17134.jpg">Takeuchi Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42755" type="main character in" update="2012-03-21">
<rating votes="6">8.10</rating>
<name>Hatake Kakashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>84351.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42756" type="main character in" update="2012-03-21">
<rating votes="5">7.51</rating>
<name>Tenten</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>84352.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42757" type="main character in" update="2012-03-21">
<rating votes="3">8.48</rating>
<name>Might Guy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>84353.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="467" picture="38026.jpg">Ebara Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42758" type="main character in" update="2012-03-21">
<rating votes="4">9.73</rating>
<name>Rock Lee</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>84350.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4757" picture="46951.jpg">Masukawa Youichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42759" type="main character in" update="2012-03-21">
<rating votes="5">9.06</rating>
<name>Hyuuga Neji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>84354.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2090" picture="151718.jpg">Toochika Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42760" type="main character in" update="2012-03-21">
<rating votes="9">2.35</rating>
<name>Haruno Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>84355.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="234" picture="244740.jpg">Nakamura Chie</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="138207" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-04-03</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロック・リーは忍術の使えない忍者です / ロック・リーのライバルはナルトです</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rock Lee Is a Ninja Who Can`t Use Ninjutsu / Rock Lee`s Rival Is Naruto</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rock Lee wa Ninjutsu no Tsukaenai Ninja Desu / Rock Lee no Rival wa Naruto Desu</title>
<summary>Welcome one day in the Hidden Leaf Village, home of Uzumaki Naruto, a young girl is accosted by debt collectors.  Just in the nick of time, she`s rescued by...not Naruto, but the hardest working ninja in the vollage, Rock Lee!  And a ninja...who can`t use ninjutsu!  Whatwill happen to the girl...and Lee?!
Rock Lee is on a mission to procure a special baumkuchen cake, but only 50 are baked each day.  Suddenly, Naruto appears out of nowhere with the same goal!  With only one cake left, can Lee overcome Naruto`s "Sexy Technique?!"
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>595241</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138645" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-06-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">師弟対決! ロック リー vs マイト ガイです / ガイ先生を超えるのです!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Student vs. Master! Rock Lee vs. Might Guy! / I Will Surpass Guy Sensei!</title>
<summary>The ninjas of the Hidden Leaf are being tested on their combat skills, and Team Guy must win a match against their sensei in order to pass.  Neji and Tenten succeed using their special moves, but how will Lee stand up to Guy-sensei`s Morning Peacock?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>600919</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138646" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">忍術禁止の体験学習なのです / サクラさんと相合傘をしたいのです</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The No-Ninjutsu Lifestyle! / I Want to Share an Umbrella with Sakura</title>
<summary>Fed up with their pupils using their ninja skills for the simplest of tasks, Guy and Kakashi set out to teach 
them some appreciation. Lee is training in the train without an umbrella, when he sees Sakura getting soaked as well.  Naruto appears with an umbrella to save the day, and a jealous Lee has to choose between training 
and love.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>595263</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138647" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-06-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">古都といえば, 修学旅行です! / 女子の部屋と書いてお菓子箱です!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Field Trip to the Old Capital! / Girls` Rooms and Candy Boxes</title>
<summary>Lee and Naruto are both vying to be on Sakura`s team for a research trip to the old capitol city.  But when they`re stuck with Neji instead, they settle for tailing her. Evening falls and Lee wants to slip away from the senseis to go hang out with the girls.  He sends Konohamaru in to do some recon,  While the young ninja is caught, he manages to leave behind a single scrap of paper...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>595261</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138648" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-06-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">チームワークこそ青春の証です / 犯人はこの中にいる! です!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Teamwork Symbolizes Youth / The Culprit Is Among Us!</title>
<summary>After seeing Shikamaru and Chouji in action, Lee attempts to strengthen his friendship with Neji and perfect their own combo moves. The Leaf ninja are scheduled to take an IQ test, but on the way to the exam, Lee`s team discovers Guy-sensei collapsed on the ground!  They`ll have to push their brains to the limit to solve this mystery!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>595259</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138649" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-05-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヒナタはネジのいとこなのです / ヒナタの弱点はナルトです</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hinata Is Neji`s Cousin / Hinata`s Weak Point Is Naruto</title>
<summary>Neji`s cousin Hinata is trying to get some training in, but it`s not easy with Lee getting in the way.  And Guy, Kiba, Akamaru, Shino... Hinata`s one weak point is her tendency to faint around her beloved Naruto, so Lee and several others don some familiar orange outfits to help her fix the problem.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>595257</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138650" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-05-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">火影だってハゲるときはハゲるのです / 大蛇丸はとってもしつこい男なのです</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Even Hokages Go Bald / Orochimaru Is Persistent</title>
<summary>Lee`s team is pulling bodyguard duty for the Fifth Hokage Tsunade while she`s off on a gambling binge, and Tenten can only seem to screw up in front of her heroine... Orochimaru summons Manda to swallow Tsunade, Naruto, and even Guy-sensei whole!  Can Lee`s team come up with a plan and rescue them?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>595255</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138651" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-05-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大蛇丸はさそり座B型です! / ラブレターは最大の罠なのです</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Orochimaru Is a B-Type Scorpio / Love Letters Are the Ultimate Trap</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Orochimaru wa Sasoriza B Gata Desu! / Love Letter wa Saidai no Wana na no Desu</title>
<summary>Lee and his team are on guard duty at the front gate, but they`ll have to 
be more vigilant than the TSA to prevent Orochimaru and Kabuto from 
sneaking in! Lee is flummoxed by Guy-sensei`s new "Smooth Operator Fist," 
but not half as much as he is by Orochimaru`s love letter!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>595253</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138652" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-05-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">木ノ葉の里の大運動会です / 騎馬戦は青春の醍醐味なのです</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Leaf Village Sports Meet / Chicken Fights Are Part of the Thrill of Youth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Konoha no Sato no Daiundoukai Desu / Kibasen wa Seishun no Daigomi na no Desu</title>
<summary>The Hidden Leaf Village is holding a sports meet!  Lee is called upon to read the Athlete`s Pledge of Fair Play, but screws up in front of the entire stadium.  Hoping to save face, he swears to outperform everyone at every event.  Will Guy-sensei`s advice of "be confident and you`ll win every time" awaken a well-intentioned demon within Lee?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>595251</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138653" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-05-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">木ノ葉丸に拳法を教えるのです / 健康診断は勝負パンツで挑みます</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m Going to Teach Konohamaru Kempo / I Save My Lucky Undies for Physicals</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Konohamaru no Kenpou o Oshieru no Desu / Kenkoushindan wa Shoubu Pants de Idomimasu</title>
<summary>Konohamaru usually practices ninjutsu with Naruto.  But now he`s sought out Rock Lee to learn better hand-to-hand combat skills.  Lee prepares to teach Konohamaru his best moves, but notices something...odd about him?
Lee and the others are ordered to appear for a routine physical exam. But with all the various personalities from the Hidden Leaf Village converging in one spot, it`s one incident after another.  Will Lee`s group survive their physical?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>595249</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138654" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それでもガイ先生はやってない...です / カカシ先生はガイ先生のライバルです</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Guy Sensei Didn`t... Do It... / Guy Sensei`s Rival Is Kakashi Sensei</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soredemo Guy-sensei wa Yattenai... Desu / Kakashi-sensei wa Guy-sensei no Rival Desu</title>
<summary>Lee`s beloved teacher Guy-sensei is arrested for lewd behavior!  Lee promises to clear his teacher`s name, but Guy claims it`s just another test for his pupil.  Inspector Lee is on the case! / Kakashi-sensei`s secret move leaves Guy utterly defeated, and Lee decides to follow Kakashi-sensei and become as powerful as he is.  The first step?  Copying the Copy Ninja`s appearance.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>595247</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138655" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天才忍者ネジと勝負なのです / テンテンには譲れない戦いがあるのです</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Competition with the Genius Ninja, Neji / Tenten`s Must-Win Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tensai Ninja Neji to Shoubu Na no Desu / Tenten ni wa Yuzurenai Tatakai ga Aru no Desu</title>
<summary>One of Lee`s teammates is Hyuuga Neji, a talented ninja who many refer to as a genius.  So talented in fact, that he took out an enemy boss from the Hidden Grass Village in one strike!  Frustrated, Lee challenges Neji, hoping to prove that with enough hard work, a genius can be defeated!
There`s one thing Tenten can`t stand, and that`s her teammates Lee and Neji not treating her like a woman.  Just as she`s getting mad, they encounter a female bandit and her gand and the two of them attempt tp protect the leader from her underlings.  All Tenten wants is for her teammates to notice that she`s a girl, too!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>595245</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138656" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-04-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋もまた青春の一部なのです / 愛とはふたりで愚かになることです</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love Is a Part of the Springtime of Youth / Love Makes Both Sides Crazy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi mo Mata Seishun no Ichibu na no Desu / Ai to wa Futari de Oroka ni Naru Koto Desu</title>
<summary>Rock Lee has a crush on Haruno Sakura.  He mounts numerous "love offenses" on the target of his affections, but Sakura easily brushes them off.  He recruits Tenten, hoping to show Sakura how cool he can be, but...
Hoping to get closer to Sakura, Lee goes to slip a love letter into her shoebox.  But when he arrives, he sees her happily carrying a love letter envelope from someone else!  Naruto hatches a plan to cheer Lee up by stealing the other letter before Sakura can read it!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>595243</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138820" update="2012-04-11">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-04-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138821" update="2012-04-11">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-04-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="140721" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-07-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">忍者人気を取り戻すのです! / デス!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`ll Restore the Reputation of Ninjas! / Death!</title>
<summary>Fewer children in the Hidden Leaf Village are choosing to become ninjas.  Lee goes to talk to Guy-sensei about the issue, only to overhear his idol say "Ninjutsu is the most important part of being a ninja! On his way to visit a hospitalized Guy-sensei, Lee hears Tsunade say he "doesn`t have much time left."  Can Lee whip up a curry dish that`s spicy enough to save his teacher`s life?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>600921</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="140722" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドキドキ☆プール開きです / ワクワク♡おろちプール園です</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Pool`s Finally Open / The Super Happy Orochi-Pool Park!</title>
<summary>It`s summer in the Leaf Village, but the pool`s empty!  Lee and the gang set out to fill it, but are they playing into Orochimaru`s hands?! Lee wants to take Sakura on a date, so he, Neji and Tenten go to check out the newly-opened "Super Happy Orochi-Pool Park."  And of course, lying in wait is...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>600923</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="140933" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-08-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">我愛羅くんと仲良くなろう. です! / ロック・リーのニセモノ現る! です!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Want to Be Friends with Gaara! / The Rock Lee Impostor Strikes!</title>
<summary>Gaara, Kazekae of the Hidden Sand Village, is coming to visit the Leaf Village.  Thinking Lee might still be mad about his past defeat at Gaara`s hands, Tenten and the others try to find a way to bring them closer. A Rock Lee impostor appears and starts causing trouble in the village.  Lee`s group attempt to catch him using a cross-dressing Neji as bait, but 
then Tenten and Neji impostors show up!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>600933</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="140934" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-08-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏はやっぱり貝パンスタイルです! / スイカップを巡る激闘です!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summer Means Seashell Styles! / Watermelon Wars!</title>
<summary>Team Guy and Team Kakashi head to the beach.  Lee wants to scope out Sakura`s "amazing" new bathing suit, but Guy-sensei makes him train instead.  Can Naruto and Konohamaru help him escape Guy-sensei`s clutches? Lee wants to have fun by splitting watermelons, but Guy-sensei turns it into a training exercise.  It`s a race for survival to get a crack at the perfect target!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>600931</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="140935" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドキッ! 忍者だらけの花火大会です! / ギクッ! テンテンの様子がオカシイです!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Boom! The Shinobi Fireworks Show! / Bang! Tenten`s Acting Weird!</title>
<summary>The Leaf Village is holding a fireworks show, including a contest to see which ninja can make the biggest boom.  Guy-sensei orders Lee to win at any cost! After the fireworks show, Tenten starts acting strange.  Neji and Lee set her up for numerous punchlines, but she just doesn`t seem to want to play the part this week.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>600929</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="140936" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ROAD TO GUYです! / 実録! 木ノ葉の里の妄想映画祭です!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The New Naruto Movie Premiere! / Please Go See the New Naruto Movie!</title>
<summary>Lee and Tenten grab the latest issue of Jump to get the scoop on the new Naruto movie!  But the moment they get it, a bright light blinds them, and when it fades, everyone`s personality is totally different!
The new Naruto movie is almost here, and Tsunade`s worried it`s lacking something to make it must-see.  Tenten overhears the Hokage and works with Lee and Neji to figure out what`s missing.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>600927</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="140937" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">3つ巴の料理ショーです! / ガイ先生を薄くするのです!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Warring Chef Triad! / Time to Tone Down Guy-Sensei!</title>
<summary>Lee and the gang are out camping, but it`s not easy to cook in the great outdoors.  When Shikamaru comes up with a plan to pit the girls against each other in a cook-off, Tenten, Sakura and Ino put their pride as women on the line and charge into battle! This year Guy-sensei is in charge of running morning exercises, but he`s a lot to deal with first thing in the 
morning.  Lee and the team set out to drum up attendence.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>600925</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="142101" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サイ. をプロデュースです! / 綱手さまのハートをGETYOUです!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m Sai`s New Agent! / Win Lady Tsunade`s Heart!</title>
<summary>It`s the Leaf Village culture festival, and Lee is convinced Sai wants to stand out more.  Poor Sai... The “Mr. Leaf Village” contest is just around the corner – Can Lee win a pair of ticket`s to the village`s swankiest restaurant?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>600941</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="142102" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-09-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナルトがリーでリーがナルトで, です! / 九尾くんとお散歩するのが夢です!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Naruto Is Lee, Lee Is Naruto! / I Dream of Taking the Nine-Tails for a Walk!</title>
<summary>Ino catches Naruto and Lee trying to peep on Sakura while she`s in the bath, but when she misfires with her Mind-Body Switch jutsu, Lee and Naruto end up swapping bodies!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>600939</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="142103" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宿題とは期限前日にやるのが基本です! / 3年リー組! ガイ班です!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Always Do Your Homework at the Last Minute! / Class 3-Lee! We Are Team Guy!</title>
<summary>Lee and Naruto seek help from their friends the day before their summer homework is due.  Unfortunately for them, they also seem to have forgotten all the craziness that happened over the summer...
Lee`s team visits the Academy, only to find a class of lazy kids who mock Lee for working so hard.  Can Lee teach them the joys of dilligence?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>600937</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="142104" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">寝苦しい夜は身も凍る怖い話です / 火影様の涙は飾りじゃないのです</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Hot Night for a Chilling Tale / The Hokage Tears Aren`t for Decoration</title>
<summary>It`s a sweltering summer night, but Guy-sensei wants Lee and the boys to cool themselves off without air conditioning.  Can a scary ghost story get the job done?
Lee and Konohamaru set out to solve one of the “Seven Mysteries of the Leaf” - “The Tears of Mount Hokage.”  What is the truth behind the otherworldly tears the 3rd Hokage`s monument sheds in the dark of night?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>600935</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="143910" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">我愛羅くんの胸キュン☆初恋デートです / 大蛇丸からのプレゼントです</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gaara`s First Date! / A Gift from Orochimaru</title>
<summary>When Lee notices the middle character on Gaara`s forehead has changed from “Love” to “Romance,” he`s convinced the Kazekage`s got a crush on someone and sets out to learn their identity.  Lee gets a booby-trapped watch from Orochimaru that will explode if he stops training.  Or if Neji cross-dresses.  Or Tenten overreacts.  How will Lee survive?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>600943</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="144291" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蒼い炎の逃球児・ドッジ☆リーです / ブラック企業の言いなりはコリゴリです</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Green Flame, Dodge Lee! / The Yes-Man Says No!</title>
<summary>Lee`s convinced the upcoming dodgeball tournament is going to be a silly game for kids, until a few choice words from Guy-sensei light a fire in his soul. After a fight with Orochimaru, Kabuto sets out to prove he`s better than his former boss by joining Lee`s group.  Can he pass their tests?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>600945</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="144458" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">まわらないお寿司初体験です! / 友情・努力・勝利は永遠の三原則です!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My First Five-Star Sushi! / Friendship, Effort, and Victory!</title>
<summary>Lady Tsunade hits a lottery jackpot and promises to take Lee and the gang out for five-star sushi, but needs Kakashi and Guy`s help to get out of it when she notices her ticket was off by one number.
Iruka-sensei`s had enough with his disobedient students, so Lee and the gang come to the Academy to put on a show.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610717</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="144680" update="2012-10-08">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144681" update="2012-10-08">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144682" update="2012-10-08">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-07-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144683" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-11-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サクラさんに看病してもらうのです! / ロック・リーに清き一票を! です!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura`s My Nurse! / One Vote for Rock Lee!</title>
<summary>Lee fakes being sick so that Sakura will nurse him, only to find that his rival in love is using the same tactic.
Sasuke won the last popularity contest, while Lee wasn`t even ranked.  Can the show`s main character find a way to steal 1st place?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610727</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="144684" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-10-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">温泉は混浴に限るのです! / 10月27日は大蛇丸の誕生日! でした...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nothing Beats Mixed Bathing! / October 27th WAS Orochimaru`s Birthday...</title>
<summary>Guy-sensei gives the gang a rare break, but will the end up being broken by Orochimaru`s "Orochi Hot Springs" trap?
Orochimaru realizes his birthday, October 27th, came and went without anyone noticing, and he wants Lee to suffer the same anguish.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610725</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="144685" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">秋の忍術安全運動です! / 先輩の芸術はいつでも爆発中です!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Autumn Shinobi Safety Lessons! / Deidara`s Art Is Always a Blast!</title>
<summary>With a lot of ninjas getting injured do to carelessness, Lady Tsunade sets out to teach her charges the importance of safety.
Lady Tsunade puts Lee and the gang in charge of the village Halloween celebration, but Deidara and Tobi are on hand to show them what real terror is all about.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610723</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="144686" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">我愛羅くんを接待するのです! / 秋のダイエット大作戦です!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We`re Here to Welcome Gaara! / The Ultimate Autumn Diet!</title>
<summary>Gaara`s on his way to the Leaf Village again, and Team Guy is scrambling to make sure he feels welcome.
The girls beg Guy to train them, but their reason is not what it seems.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610721</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="144687" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">食欲の秋! マツタケ狩りに行くのです! / リーとネジ, 決別の時です!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hunting for Matsutake Mushrooms! / Lee and Neji Part Ways!</title>
<summary>Naruto, Lee and the others go out hunting for matsutake mushrooms, but there are none to be found after the abnormally hot summer.  Or are there?
Neji`s finally had enough of being forced to cross-dress for Lee`s skits, and turns his back on Lee.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610719</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="145390" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-11-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マイト・ガイ, 愛と髪の日々です! / ナレーションに挑戦するのです!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Might Guy - A Story of Love and Hair / Substitute Narrator!</title>
<summary>When Orochimaru`s poison leaves Guy-sensei completely bald, it`s up to Lee and the gang to find him the right wig. Our beloved narrator comes down with a bad cold, and much to Tenten and Neji`s chagrin, Lee`s his temporary replacement.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610729</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="145530" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一楽の危機を救うのです! / 休みの日も修業です!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Save Ichiraku Ramen! / Vacations Are for Training!</title>
<summary>When Naruto`s favorite ramen stand, Ichiraku, meets hard financial times, Lee tries to help the restaurant revamp its image. Worried about Lee`s feverish training pace, Tenten and Neji try to get their hard working teammate to actually use his vacation time to rest.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610731</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="145692" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クリスマスは恋の最終決戦です! / 大掃除は一年間の後悔と恥を洗い流すことです!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Christmas Is the Last Chance for Love! / Cleanup Is a Chance to Wash Away the Past!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Christmas wa Koi no Saishuu Kessen Desu! / Oosouji wa Ichinenkan no Koukai to Haji o Arainagasu Koto Desu!</title>
<summary>The Hidden Leaf Village holds a big Christmas party, but with so many ninjas competing for one another`s affections, will the Secret Santa turn into a battle for survival? It`s time for the yearly cleanup, and in his zeal to finish quickly and ask Sakura on a date, Lee accidentally throws away something very important…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610741</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="145693" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-12-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暁のアジトに潜入です! / 決死の脱出大作戦です!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Infiltrate Akatsuki`s Hideout! / A Desperate Escape Plan!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akatsuki no Ajito ni Sennyuu Desu! / Kesshi no Dasshutsu Daisakusen Desu!</title>
<summary>Lee`s team stumbles upon Akatsuki`s hidden base, and Deidara is determined to chase them out before the rest of his teammates learn about his history with the hard-working ninja and his pals.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610739</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="145694" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-12-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガイ先生が火影さまなのです! / IQ200はめんどくさいのです</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Guy Sensei is the New Hokage! / IQ: 200, Status: Troublesome</title>
<summary>When Tsunade leaves on a diplomatic mission to a neighboring village, she leaves the only shinobi who wasn`t busy in charge - Guy. Team Guy is assigned to go on patrol with Shikamaru`s team, and the genius ninja hopes to pick the lease troublesome route.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610737</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="145695" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">テンテンvsテマリです! / 大蛇丸の婚活です</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tenten vs. Temari! / Orochimaru`s Search for Love!</title>
<summary>An encounter with the Sand siblings turns ugly when Temari insults Tenten, igniting the Leaf ninja`s desire for a Chuunin Exam rematch. Orochimaru begins to long for a normal life after being barred from entering a family-oriented shopping market.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610735</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="145696" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いきもののお世話は大変なのです / ナルトにほえろ! です</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Caring for Animals is Hard Work / Howl at the Naruto!</title>
<summary>Owing them all many debts of gratitude, Lee tries to bond with the many summoned ninja animals of his comrades. With so many romantic holidays happening in winter, Hinata aims to grow a little closer to Naruto before autumn is over.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610733</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146653" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お正月からメンツをかけた人生すごろくです! / ナルトを見極めるのです!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A New Year`s Escape Clause / Naruto Under Surveillance!</title>
<summary>Lee and the gang catch the adults in a game tournament, and the grand prize is not having to give their pupils a New Year`s gift! Neji decides to observe Naruto and determine once and for all if the orange ninja is worthy of Hinata`s affections.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610743</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146804" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">終わらない悪夢なのです / 未来から来たアライグマカラクリです!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Endless Nightmare / A Creation from the Future!</title>
<summary>Trapped by Orochimaru`s blizzard, Lee and the gang fight to stay warm. Can they stave off sleep and avoid freezing to death?! Out of the First Hokage`s nostril pops Rock Lee, from 30 years in the future!  He`s come back to give his past self a helpful robot, in hopes that he won`t end up a complete loser!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610745</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146944" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">虫愛づるシノ, です / テンテン, 乙女の戦場で炎上です!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shino Loves Insects / Tenten Fights a Maiden`s Battle!</title>
<summary>Shino`s bugs refuse to leave his body because the weather`s too cold, so Lee and his pals help him search for replacements. A maiden`s battle…the floor of a department store sale.  Tenten, Ino, Sakura, and Hinata square off and try to snatch up the best deals!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610747</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147105" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">存在感を消したい17の夜です / トイレ掃除は心も綺麗にするのです!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">17 Nights of Staying Out of Sight / Cleaning the Bathroom Cleanses the Soul</title>
<summary>When the team gets assigned to infiltrade an illegal chakra-trading ring, Lee goes to Sai for advice on how to blend in with the crowd. A nefarious neer-do-well keeps leaving the village bathrooms a filthy disgusting mess, so Tsunade appoints Lee`s team as guards.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610749</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147246" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">撒いた豆は後でスタッフが美味しく頂いたのです! / 狙われた雷影さまです!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Staff Will Eat the Beans Afterwards! / The Raikage Is Under Attack!</title>
<summary>Lee`s team gets to play the ogres for the annual Setsubun festival, but Orochimaru schemes to ruin the fun. When they hear the Raikage is being targeted by criminals Lee and his friends have to team up with Killer Bee to protect the Hidden Cloud!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610751</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147251" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いよいよヤマト隊長が任務に登場です / 木ノ葉・オブ・ザ・デッドです!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yamato Gets a Mission / Leaf Village of the Death!</title>
<summary>Lee, Tenten, and Sai, led by Captain Yamato, embark on a mission to recover a stolen scroll. Orochimaru creates a virus that turns humans into Oro-Zombies, and it`s up to Lee to stop him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610759</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147252" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">犬の友だちは犬なのです / ついにあの忍がやってきたのです!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dogs Need Dog Friends / The Shinobi You`ve Been Waiting For!</title>
<summary>Kiba enlists Hinata and the girls to find Akamaru some canine companions. Lee and his team run into Sasuke on their way back from a mission, and Lee takes it upon himself to bring the rogue ninja back home.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610757</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147253" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">伝説の三忍, 自来也さまです! / いざ, 女湯に突入です!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Legendary Sannin, Jiraiya! / Infiltrate the Women`s Bath!</title>
<summary>Jiraiya trains Lee, Naruto, and Konohamaru.  Tsunade takes Sakura and the girls to the hot springs. Chaos ensues.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610755</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147254" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">熱くて熱い雪像コンテストです! / 男の戦場はバレンタインです!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Fiery Snow Sculpting Contest! / The Battlefield Called Valentine`s Day!</title>
<summary>When the freezing cold leaves Lady Tsunade feeling down, the village organizes a snow sculpting contest to cheer her up. It`s Valentine`s Day, and Lee would give anything for a girl to give him some chocolates.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610753</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147255" update="2013-02-05">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-01-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148135" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ホワイトデー撲滅同盟なのです! / おひな様を片付けるのです!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">White Day, Destroyer of Alliances! / Take Care of the Princess Dolls!</title>
<summary>It`s the day before White Day, and a sinister trio of villains has ruined the village supply of sweets. It`s been quite a few days since the Leaf Doll`s Festival ended, but some prankster keeps putting the dolls back out every night.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610761</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148480" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガイ先生をお世話するのです! / 綱手さまのお見合いです!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Taking Care of Guy Sensei! / Lady Tsunade`s Marriage Interview!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Guy-sensei o Osewasuru no Desu! / Tsunade-sama no Omiai Desu!</title>
<summary>Lee wants be an adult like his sensei, and he gets the chance when Guy turns into a baby after drinking a youth-restoring potion. When Lee overhears Lady Tsunade mutter something about being lonely, he sets her up on an arranged marriage interview…with the Raikage!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>610763</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148617" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最期の戦い / 最後の任務はSランク級です!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Final Battle / Our Final Mission Is S-Ranked!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo no Tatakai / Saigo no Ninmu wa S-Rank-kyuu Desu!</title>
<summary>The final battle against Sasuke is now. Lady Tsunade tasks Lee`s team with an S-Ranked mission: Prepare a cherry blossom viewing party.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>615511</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="149635" update="2013-04-14">
<epno type="5">P1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ep1 Parody</title>
</episode>
<episode id="182136" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>594667</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182137" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>594669</identifier>
<identifier>naruto-spin-off-rock-lee-his-ninja-pals</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
