<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="895" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2003-10-04</startdate>
<enddate>2004-04-17</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Planetes</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ΠΛΑΝΗΤΕΣ</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="synonym">Planètes</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Странники</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Planetes</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Планети</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Планетес</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Планети</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">星空清理者</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">PES</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">プラネテス</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Planetes</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Planetes</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Planetes</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Planetes</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Planetes</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">PLANET-ES</title>
<title xml:lang="el" type="official">ΠΛΑΝΗΤΕΣ</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="official">Мандрівники</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8865" approval="77" total="95">Uchuu Kyoudai</anime>
<anime id="4900" approval="58" total="63">Moonlight Mile: 1st Season - Lift Off</anime>
<anime id="196" approval="36" total="39">Ouritsu Uchuugun: Honneamise no Tsubasa</anime>
<anime id="262" approval="28" total="48">Memories</anime>
<anime id="1139" approval="15" total="26">Futatsu no Spica</anime>
<anime id="2447" approval="9" total="9">Oira Uchuu no Tankoufu</anime>
<anime id="4113" approval="8" total="11">Yomigaeru Sora: Rescue Wings</anime>
<anime id="4802" approval="6" total="13">Rocket Girls</anime>
<anime id="4691" approval="5" total="29">Nodame Cantabile</anime>
<anime id="7443" approval="4" total="18">Mouretsu Pirates</anime>
<anime id="1122" approval="1" total="5">Mujin Wakusei Survive</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="39">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="79753">I AGREE WITH SCOUTEN - FOR FANS ONLY!!!!! Despite all the good reviews for this anime, i personally did not connect with the plot and the characters (especially TANABE AI... sigh........)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="201320">A unique drawing style, which is sadly too realistic for anime and makes most of the character designs plain ugly. The story is also very weak. I cannot recommend this to anyone, although fans of the manga might like it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="256993">One of the very best anime i ve ever seen</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="8855">An overall good anime. Character development is the focus but is not necessarily very realistic. What amused me the most though was that the Indian guy had a son called "Musharraf".</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="834921">Scientifically accurate sci-fi drama with complex and interesting characters.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="92088">Probably the most realistic space anime ever made, and it`s not boring at all! Really enjoyable anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="292539">Def a must watch. Great ending that will leave you satisfied.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="191784">Being a "space enthusiast" i enjoyed this anime like crazy. Nice plot. Good character development. EXCELENT setting, the ambience of "living in space" is awesome.
Watch it!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="206351">I wasn`t impressed with this anime at first (it seems very heavy handed at the beginning), but if you stick with it, it gets really good towards the end. The description might make you think it`s a boring anime about mundane things, but it has lots of subplots and things like that. This anime is lighthearted at times, comedic often, but also hits some serious notes. The characters are very likeable and generally realistic. The human element is really there in all the episodes. Definitely recommended.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="378701">Quite an interesting anime, different than what I use to watch. At first I wasn`t sure whether I`d like or not but I ended up enjoying it. It`s a decent anime but that`s it, definitely not a masterpiece.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="313060">I can`t recommend this enough. It`s perfect. Are you considering watching it just from the title image? Do it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="130348">space, characters, music, story, romance. nothing bad to complain. everything very good</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="281023">I simply cannot recommend it enough.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="333550">My favorite.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="78404">Very realistic setting and characters plus an overall enjoyable experience.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="335977">The characters in this series seem the most "human" than any other series I`ve seen. The first half of this series defines the motivations that drive the behavior for each character. As the series drives to it`s uncertain end, you can see the individual behaviors from each character, not pushing the story forward but contributing to the final act. Highly recommended, not for the (impressive) realism, but for the impressive characters there in.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="490312">not much to say....almost equivalent to the great works of science fiction of Arthur Clarke or Isaac Asimov....(guys don`t get mad i said almost).anyway to all sci fi enthusiast Must See.to everyone else :watch and you become a scifi enthusiast</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="403447">One word: Realistic!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="76992">Perfect Ending! Made my cry because of it`s awesomeness!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="172236">Brace for impact at first few episodes, as they are pretty weak, probably designed to ease newcomers in with too much humor. But when development is done and Planetes starts rolling... it really is amazing.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="592613">Defintely a must see anime. Well it start funny, pass through drama and end with hope... love, politics, strong caracters and little action: such a good receipt!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="254003">Wery nice science fiction</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="120720">Great show for any SF fan. I was riveted, watched in one sitting!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="16524">The character development and facing one`s doubt in this anime truly is amazing along  with the plot line.  A MUST SEE!!!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.planet-es.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1" type="Direction">Taniguchi Gorou</name>
<name id="2256" type="Character Design">Chiba Yuriko</name>
<name id="4014" type="Original Work">Yukimura Makoto</name>
<name id="1573" type="Music">Nakagawa Koutarou</name>
<name id="1655" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nakatani Seiichi</name>
<name id="2256" type="Chief Animation Direction">Chiba Yuriko</name>
<name id="1652" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nakada Eiji</name>
</creators>
<description>It is the year 2075. In a world where travelling between Earth, the space stations and the Moon has become commonplace.
http://anidb.net/ch7236 [Hachimaki] is just an ordinary salaryman. He works at a space station collecting dangerous space debris. However, he dreams of owning his very own space ship someday. And so he spends his days collecting debris together with his colleagues http://anidb.net/ch15040 [Yuri], http://anidb.net/ch15039 [Fee] and his friend http://anidb.net/ch7237 [Tanabe]. Now it is his fourth year doing the same work and he is going to be 25 years old soon, which is why he starts to think about his life.
How does Hachimaki feel? Well, today, Hachimaki is going to do the same job...
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="6852">8.51</permanent>
<temporary count="6910">8.43</temporary>
<review count="21">8.61</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221809.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2654</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>329</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>10735</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1244</identifier>
<identifier>xkqkfo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.planet-es.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Planetes</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>プラネテス</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>152</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>319276</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6275</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/169</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2003/planetes</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8456</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1282" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>pet</name>
<description>A domestic animal kept for pleasure or companionship.</description>
<picurl>221616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1843" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-05">
<name>corporation</name>
<description>A corporation is a legal entity that is created under the laws of a state designed to establish the entity as a separate legal entity having its own privileges and liabilities distinct from those of its members.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2363" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-07">
<name>stubborn</name>
<description>Is a description of someone who has difficulty changing opinions. The word can also be used to describe objects that are difficult to move or change</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2572" parentid="2282" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-09">
<name>ninja</name>
<description>A ninja was a covert agent or mercenary of feudal Japan specializing in unorthodox arts of war.
The functions of the ninja included espionage, sabotage, infiltration, and assassination, as well as open combat in certain situations.
The ninja, using covert methods of waging war, were contrasted with the samurai, who had strict rules about honor and combat.</description>
<picurl>244347.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2643" parentid="2638" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>power suit</name>
<description>Power Suits are similar to Piloted Robots which are controlled from inside the robot except that Power Suits tend to be more directly tied to how the character moves and they are usually not as big as Piloted Robots can be. They are still mechanical and shouldn`t be confused with plug suits.</description>
<picurl>222235.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2659" parentid="2660" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Moon</name>
<description>The Moon is an astronomical body that orbits planet Earth, being Earth`s only permanent natural satellite. It is the fifth-largest natural satellite in the Solar System, and the largest among planetary satellites relative to the size of the planet that it orbits.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214385.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2764" parentid="2627" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>space colony</name>
<description>The human race (or possibly some alien race) has mastered space travel and founded at least one colony either in space, on a moon or another planet. This usually also includes colony-life episodes that not only show the technical staff of professionals (astronauts, scientists, etc.), but also their families (i.e. children).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4128" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-29">
<name>zero to hero</name>
<description>With his first appearance, this character is getting his ass kicked by nearly everyone, but as the plot continues, through training (mental or physical) or instant power-up, he changes into a killing/fighting/winning machine.
The best example: Makunouchi Ippo from Hajime no Ippo series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4314" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-04-11">
<name>psychological</name>
<description>Directed toward dealing with or affecting the mind, especially as a function of awareness, feeling, or motivation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4340" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-26">
<name>suicide</name>
<description>One or several characters in this anime commit suicide.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4347" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space exploration</name>
<description>To cross the last frontier and have a look, what lies beyond it.</description>
<picurl>242378.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4667" parentid="2846" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-20">
<name>hard science fiction</name>
<description>Hard science fiction is a category of http://anidb.net/t2846 [science fiction] characterised by an emphasis on scientific accuracy, technical detail, or both. The term is not defined precisely, and is often seen as an approximate way of describing works. Stories revolving around scientific and technical consistency were written as early as 1860s and 1870s; http://anidb.net/cr5973 [Jules Verne] is generally considered the creator of the genre. Although not always accurate in his scientific depictions, and though Verne himself denied writing as a scientist or seriously predicting machines and technology of the future, the attention to detail in his work became an inspiration for many future scientists and explorers.
Nowadays, the term http://anidb.net/t7086 [soft science fiction] is also often used to refer to science fiction stories which lack scientific focus or rigorous adherence to known science; the categorization "hard science fiction" thus represents a position on a broad continuum ranging from "softer" to "harder". There is a degree of flexibility in how far from "real science" a story can stray before it leaves the realm of hard science fiction; some authors scrupulously avoid such technology as faster-than-light travel, while others accept such notions but focus on realistically depicting the worlds that such a technology might make possible. In this view, a story`s scientific "hardness" is less a matter of the absolute accuracy of the science content than of the rigour and consistency with which the various ideas and possibilities are worked out. Furthermore, later discoveries do not necessarily invalidate the label of hard science fiction; the designation remains valid even when a crucial plot element is later discovered to be incorrect.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4860" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="false">
<name>lost love</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5865" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>manly tears</name>
<description>Somewhere down the line, it became the "norm" that boys don`t cry. The scenario does not matter; shedding tears is the ultimate no-no in terms of what you can and cannot do as a man (at least in the West, anyway). But there comes a time when a man`s emotions do get the better of him, and they pour forth - as prerequisite an impassioned speech may or may not be present - by cascading down his cheeks. These are what we like to call "manly tears". Extremely powerful. Not limited but often used in hot-blooded / super robot shows. Examples include Yuusha Ou GaoGaiGar, Getter Robo and Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann.
The opposite of manly tears are "girly tears".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6254" parentid="2872" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-23">
<name>terrorism</name>
<description>Terrorism is, in the broadest sense, the use of intentionally indiscriminate violence as a means to create terror among masses of people; or fear to achieve a religious or political aim. It is used in this regard primarily to refer to violence during peacetime or in war against non-combatants (mostly civilians and neutral military personnel). Some definitions now include acts of unlawful violence and war.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10657.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7236" type="main character in" update="2010-06-11">
<rating votes="33">6.77</rating>
<name>Hoshino Hachirouta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hachirota Hoshino is the protagonist of the series. Everyone simply calls him "Hachi" (Japanese for "eight" or "eighth") or "Hachimaki" (ハチマキ?), because he wears one during his EVAs. His dream has always been to own his own spaceship, but between the cost of purchasing one and his low-paying, seemingly dead-end job, Hachi struggles with even deciding whether or not to pursue his dream. Hachi`s father is a renowned engineer, a source of much ambivalence to Hachimaki. Much of Hachi`s drive is summed up in "bigger, faster, and further". However, this drive makes him conflicted about his own relationship with space.</description>
<picture>25605.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2976" picture="234380.jpg">Tanaka Kazunari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7237" type="main character in" update="2010-06-11">
<rating votes="45">6.82</rating>
<name>Tanabe Ai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tanabe Ai is the newest member of the Debris Section. She is the adopted daughter of a death metal band leader turned engineer and an elementary school teacher. Tanabe did not speak until she was three years old. She is bright and earnest, but mostly unsure of herself. As a newcomer to space, the Debris Section and to extra-vehicular activity all at the same time, she has to slowly learn the ropes from everyone else. She believes that love, or "ai" (possibly a pun intended on her name being the Japanese word for love) is the solution to every problem.</description>
<picture>3441.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="271" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15035" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-11">
<rating votes="16">3.39</rating>
<name>Clair Rondo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Clair is Hachimaki`s exgirlfriend. She was born in the (fictional) South American country of El Tanika. She`s a child of immigrants and couldn`t read until she was eight. She works in the Control Section as the supervisor of the debris Section. She has lived in space for three years.
She was given the nickname Swan by Gigalt because swans look all elegant and graceful as they glide along the water, but under the water their legs are paddling away like crazy. Clair pushes herself too hard.</description>
<picture>3338.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3130" picture="186156.jpg">Watanabe Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15036" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-14">
<rating votes="5">5.74</rating>
<name>Hoshino Gorou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hoshino Gorou is Hachimaki`s father. He is a famous engineer and has made 5 Earth-Mars trips as chief engineer (on ships that used traditional circuit coil fusion engines). He never comes home and hasn`t seen his son in years. Despite never coming home, he says he loves his wife.</description>
<picture>43029.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1986" picture="1919.gif">Iizuka Shouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15037" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-14">
<rating votes="7">7.34</rating>
<name>Werner Locksmith</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Locksmith is the director of the Jupiter project, the designer of the Von Braun and the developer of the tandem mirror engine. He describes himself as "a man of genius who is incapable of loving anything but spaceships".</description>
<picture>43030.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15038" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-01">
<rating votes="5">7.73</rating>
<name>Gigalt Gangaragash</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gigalt worked in Technora`s Debris Section until two years before the current timeline of the series starts. Later worked in the OSA (Orbital Security Agency).
He`s the man who trained both Hachimaki and Hakim, their Senpai. Also a close friend of Hachimaki`s father Goro, they were both part of the first manned mission to Mars.</description>
<picture>43031.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2" picture="16471.jpg">Wakamoto Norio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15039" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-11">
<rating votes="20">7.99</rating>
<name>Fee Carmichael</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fee Carmichael is the captain of the debris recovery ship Toy Box. She is addicted to smoking. She cares very much for her crew. She`s married and has a son.</description>
<picture>43032.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="588" picture="41015.jpg">Orikasa Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15040" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-11">
<rating votes="11">6.94</rating>
<name>Yuri Mihailokov</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuri Mihairokov is the Russian member of the Debris team. Calm, stoic, kind and compassionate, Yuri often acts as the level head of the group. Several years before the events of the story, he and his wife were in a low-orbit craft traveling to England when a small bolt slammed into one of the ship`s windows at high velocity, causing the plane to depressurize and make an emergency landing. Many died in the highly publicized incident, including Yuri`s wife, who was never found. The incident and Yuri`s desire to recover his wife`s lost keepsake, a compass she wore around her neck, drives him to collect more debris. In the anime, Yuri and the Debris Section Office Staff are responsible for looking after the ISPV 7`s resident animals. Gigalt apparently gave Yuri a nickname, though it is never spoken within the anime.</description>
<picture>43033.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15041" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-11">
<rating votes="7">3.70</rating>
<name>Philippe Myers</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Assistant section manager for Debris Section. Called `sachou` (meaning `chief`) thoughout the series. He believes he is good for nothing. He is very fond of crisps and cakes.</description>
<picture>43035.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13243" picture="43109.jpg">Okada Yoshihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15042" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-07-24">
<rating votes="9">3.86</rating>
<name>Arvind Lavie</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Arvind Lavie is the assistant chief clerk and self-described "Number 2" of the Debris Section who hails from India. He is a divorced father of seven children. He is portrayed as a trickster or prop comedian with a very flexible body. Seemingly obnoxious and opportunistic, he seems to always seek to climb the corporate ladder. However, this is because he pays a substantial amount of child support, and seeks a better life for his many children.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>43037.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="300" picture="226467.jpg">Gotou Tetsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15043" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-11">
<rating votes="17">6.23</rating>
<name>Edelgard Rivera</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Edelgard Rivera is temp staffer of the Debris Section. Very commited to her work. Has many jobs. Wears miniskirts and other daring outfits.</description>
<picture>3340.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2191" picture="21747.jpg">Itou Maiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18700" type="appears in" update="2010-06-11">
<rating votes="4">8.81</rating>
<name>Dorf Azalia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3337.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3357" picture="24387.jpg">Kamon Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18701" type="appears in" update="2010-06-11">
<rating votes="4">4.18</rating>
<name>Lucie Ascham</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3339.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="634" picture="18161.jpg">Kurata Masayo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18702" type="appears in" update="2010-06-11">
<rating votes="3">4.12</rating>
<name>Kho Cheng-Shin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kho Cheng-Shin is a spacecraft pilot based in the ISPV 7 Space Station. Became friends with Claire and Hachimaki, since they all came to the Space Station together. He is often playing confidant to Hachimaki. Cheng-Shin has a crush on Tanabe.</description>
<picture>3341.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18831" type="appears in" update="2010-06-14">
<name>Toy Box</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>Debris Collector Ship</description>
<picture>3349.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="40178" type="appears in" update="2012-01-03">
<rating votes="3">8.67</rating>
<name>Harry Roland</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A veteran astronaut who is in love with outer space.</description>
<picture>79419.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="420" picture="186676.jpg">Akimoto Yousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40179" type="appears in" update="2012-01-03">
<rating votes="4">7.82</rating>
<name>Nono</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is a "Lunarian", born and has lived her whole life on the Moon. Due to the effects of lower gravity, she appears to be twice her age due to her height.</description>
<picture>79420.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="556" picture="17848.jpg">Koorogi Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40180" type="appears in" update="2012-01-03">
<rating votes="3">1.66</rating>
<name>Colin Clifford</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Colin is the 2nd son of the chairman of INTO Jentro Clifford.</description>
<picture>79421.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="484" picture="17476.jpg">Kisaichi Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40188" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-07-24">
<rating votes="8">4.27</rating>
<name>Hakim Ashmead</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hakim Ashmead is a Jupiter Mission candidate, along with http://anidb.net/ch7236 [Hachimaki]. Hakim and Hachimaki had the same EVA instructor, and have some personal connection with each other. Prior to entering the Jupiter Exploration program, Hakim was a member of the Orbital Security Agency (OSA). It turns out that he is a member of the Space Defence Front, the terrorist organization that threatened to initiate the Kessler Syndrome in Earth`s orbit.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>79430.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2053" picture="23204.jpg">Ootomo Ryuuzaburou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40189" type="appears in" update="2012-01-03">
<rating votes="2">2.38</rating>
<name>Chapeau</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79431.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40190" type="appears in" update="2012-01-03">
<name>Vanli</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79432.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40197" type="appears in" update="2012-01-04">
<rating votes="2">7.60</rating>
<name>Jirainari Chad</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79452.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40198" type="appears in" update="2012-01-04">
<rating votes="2">4.95</rating>
<name>Sally Silverstone</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79453.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1813" picture="172159.jpg">Katsuki Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40199" type="appears in" update="2012-01-04">
<rating votes="4">5.56</rating>
<name>Leonov Norstein</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79454.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="211" picture="17028.jpg">Kanna Nobutoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40200" type="appears in" update="2012-01-04">
<rating votes="3">3.76</rating>
<name>Cita Sullivan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79455.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40201" type="appears in" update="2012-01-04">
<rating votes="1">4.37</rating>
<name>Sascha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79456.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3264" picture="24262.jpg">Dan Tomoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40202" type="appears in" update="2012-01-04">
<rating votes="2">7.69</rating>
<name>Temara Poitier</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79457.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="275" picture="17102.jpg">Tahara Aruno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107606" type="appears in" update="2019-12-22">
<name>Hoshino Haruko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3250" picture="24693.jpg">Fujita Toshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107607" type="appears in" update="2019-12-22">
<name>Hoshino Kyuutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="11636" update="2005-09-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="34">6.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大気の外で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Outside the Atmosphere</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Im unendlichen Weltall</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Dans l`espace infini</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiki no Soto de</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11638" update="2008-12-01">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-10-11</airdate>
<rating votes="29">6.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢のような</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Like a Dream</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wie ein Traum</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Comme un rêve</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume no You na</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11730" update="2005-08-22">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>6</length>
<rating votes="3">7.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo Extra</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11931" update="2007-02-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="30">5.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">帰還軌道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Return Trajectory</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Rückflug</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Retour</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikan Kidou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12088" update="2005-09-07">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-10-25</airdate>
<rating votes="23">6.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">仕事として</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Part of the Job</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Teil unserer Arbeit</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">C`est notre travail</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shigoto Toshite</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12243" update="2005-09-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-11-01</airdate>
<rating votes="23">6.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フライ・ミー・トゥ・ザ・ムーン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fly Me to the Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Nimm mich mit zum Mond</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Emmène-moi sur la lune</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fly Me to the Moon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12837" update="2005-09-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-11-08</airdate>
<rating votes="25">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">月のムササビ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Lunar Flying Squirrels</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Mond-Eichhörnchen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les écureuils lunaires</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuki no Musasabi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12838" update="2005-09-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-11-15</airdate>
<rating votes="24">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地球外少女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Extraterrestrial Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Eine junge Außerirdische</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une jeune extraterrestre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikyuugai Shoujo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12930" update="2005-10-25">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-11-22</airdate>
<rating votes="17">7.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">拠るべき場所</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Place to Cling to</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein Platz zum Verweilen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Là où tu dois être</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yorubeki Basho</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13218" update="2005-10-12">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-11-29</airdate>
<rating votes="19">7.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">心のこり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Regrets</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Reue</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Regret</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokoro no Kori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13219" update="2005-10-25">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-12-06</airdate>
<rating votes="21">8.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">屑星の空</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Sky of Stardust</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Sternennebel am Himmel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un ciel de poussières d`étoile</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuzuhoshi no Sora</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13220" update="2005-09-27">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-12-13</airdate>
<rating votes="20">9.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バウンダリー・ライン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Boundary Line</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Limit</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Limite</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boundary Line</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13429" update="2005-11-16">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-12-20</airdate>
<rating votes="24">8.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ささやかなる願いを</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Modest Request</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein bescheidener Wunsch</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une envie simple</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sasayaka Naru Negai o</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13430" update="2005-11-16">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="19">7.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロケットのある風景</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scenery with a Rocket</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Eine Rakete in der Landschaft</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une fusée dans le paysage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rocket no Aru Fuukei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13431" update="2005-11-16">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-01-17</airdate>
<rating votes="15">7.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ターニング・ポイント</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Turning Point</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wendepunkt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Revirement</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Turning Point</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13729" update="2005-11-16">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-01-24</airdate>
<rating votes="16">7.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">彼女の場合</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In Her Case</title>
<title xml:lang="de">In ihrem Fall</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pour elle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanojo no Baai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13730" update="2007-06-16">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-01-31</airdate>
<rating votes="18">8.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">イグニッション</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ignition</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Zündung</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mise à feu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ignition</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14238" update="2005-11-16">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-02-07</airdate>
<rating votes="16">7.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それゆえの彼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">His Reasons</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Aus diesem Grund ist er...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">C`est pour ça qu`il...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sore Yue no Kare</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14239" update="2007-06-16">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-02-14</airdate>
<rating votes="14">8.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">デブリ課, 最期の日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Debris Section, The Last Day</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Ende der Trümmer-Abteilung</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fin de la Section Débris</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Debris-ka, Saigo no Hi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14899" update="2005-11-16">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-02-21</airdate>
<rating votes="16">8.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">終わりは いつも...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Endings Are Always...</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Für immer vorbei</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Fini pour toujours</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Owari wa Itsumo...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14900" update="2005-11-16">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-02-28</airdate>
<rating votes="16">8.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ためらいがちの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Faltering Victory</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Zögerliche Schritte</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Hésitations</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tameraigachi no</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14995" update="2005-11-16">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-03-06</airdate>
<rating votes="16">8.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">タンデム・ミラー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tandem Mirror</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Tandem Mirror</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tandem Miller</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tandem Mirror</title>
</episode>
<episode id="15225" update="2005-11-16">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-03-13</airdate>
<rating votes="17">7.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暴露</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Exposure</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Enthüllungen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Révélations</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bakuro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="15542" update="2005-11-16">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-03-20</airdate>
<rating votes="17">7.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">デブリの群れ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Debris Cluster</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Trümmerhaufen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La bande des débris</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Debris no Mure</title>
</episode>
<episode id="15655" update="2005-11-16">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-04-03</airdate>
<rating votes="21">8.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Liebe</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`amour</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17548" update="2005-11-16">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-04-10</airdate>
<rating votes="15">7.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">惑い人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Lost</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Unentschlossene</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`indécis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Madoi Hito</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17549" update="2005-11-16">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="23">8.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そして巡りあう日々</title>
<title xml:lang="en">And the Days We Chance Upon...</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Tag des Wiedersehens</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le jour de nos retrouvailles</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soshite Meguri Au Hibi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47533" update="2017-06-20">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2003-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47534" update="2017-06-20">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2003-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68272" update="2007-03-09">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68273" update="2007-03-09">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<rating votes="2">7.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Drama 01</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68274" update="2007-03-09">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<rating votes="2">7.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Drama 02</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68275" update="2007-03-09">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<rating votes="2">7.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Drama 03</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68276" update="2007-03-09">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<rating votes="2">7.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Drama 04</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68277" update="2007-03-09">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<rating votes="2">7.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Drama 05</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68278" update="2007-03-09">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>3</length>
<rating votes="3">6.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Drama 06</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68279" update="2007-03-09">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>3</length>
<rating votes="3">6.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Drama 07</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68280" update="2007-03-09">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>3</length>
<rating votes="3">6.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Drama 08</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68281" update="2007-03-09">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>4</length>
<rating votes="3">6.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Drama 09</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68282" update="2007-03-09">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Preview 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68283" update="2007-03-09">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>10</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Phase Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134441" update="2011-10-29">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134442" update="2011-10-29">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134443" update="2011-10-29">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="143859" update="2012-09-15">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>7</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Creditless Epilogue</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188417" update="2017-06-19">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2004-10-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">オープニング素材集</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening Materials Collection</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Opening Sozai Shuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188418" update="2017-06-20">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-04-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1k</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188419" update="2017-06-20">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-04-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1j</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188420" update="2017-06-20">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-04-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1i</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188421" update="2017-06-20">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-03-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1h</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188422" update="2017-06-20">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-03-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1g</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188423" update="2017-06-20">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-02-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1f</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188424" update="2017-06-20">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-02-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188425" update="2017-06-20">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-01-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188426" update="2017-06-20">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-01-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188427" update="2017-06-20">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2003-12-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
