<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8968" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2012-01-26</startdate>
<enddate>2012-01-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Otome Nadeshiko Koi Techou</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Otome Nadeshiko Love Diary</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">乙女なでしこ恋手帖</title>
</titles>
<url>http://gagaga-lululu.jp/lululu/</url>
<creators>
<name id="14536" type="Character Design">Suzuki Yuusuke</name>
<name id="31659" type="Character Design">Touma Rei</name>
<name id="31660" type="Original Work">Miyama Kunoe</name>
<name id="32014" type="Work">Lululu Bunko Henshuubu</name>
<name id="1082" type="Work">Shogakukan</name>
<name id="39905" type="Direction">Sanpei Hijiri</name>
</creators>
<description>The story follows a 16-year-old girl who is experiencing her first love during Japan`s Taishou period (1912-1926).
Note: Bundled with special versions of [i]Otome Nadeshiko Love Diary 2 light novel.[/i]
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="194">3.55</permanent>
<temporary count="194">5.46</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>81237.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14035</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13673</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://gagaga-lululu.jp/lululu/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15181</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="44194" type="main character in" update="2012-05-02">
<rating votes="3">7.60</rating>
<name>Shinoaki Chizuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87061.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3601" picture="38507.jpg">Kawase Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44195" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-05-02">
<name>Ootsuki Toshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87062.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33784" picture="93013.jpg">Takeuchi Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44196" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-05-02">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Otobe Ranko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87063.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32609" picture="87647.jpg">Sudou Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44197" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-05-02">
<name>Nakane Mikiya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87064.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20551" picture="53967.jpg">Yoshimoto Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44198" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-05-02">
<name>Arimura Sayo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87065.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2868" picture="186239.jpg">Isshiki Mayu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="137028" update="2015-05-10">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2012-01-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
