<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8976" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2001-08-25</startdate>
<enddate>2001-08-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">X Yochou</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">X Episode 0</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="synonym">Épisode 0 - Un présage</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Предзнаменование</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="synonym">ลางร้าย?</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">X 予兆</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">X: An Omen</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">X - Das Omen (OVA)</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="30" type="Sequel">X (2001)</anime>
<anime id="457" type="Prequel">Tokyo Babylon</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="1865" type="Character Design">Kanemori Yoshinori</name>
<name id="747" type="Original Work">Clamp</name>
<name id="705" type="Direction">Kawajiri Yoshiaki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the manga by http://anidb.net/cr747 [Clamp].
The story is focused on the future as seen by http://anidb.net/ch25463 [Kuzuki Kakyou], the dreamgazer of http://anidb.net/ch40516 [Dragons of Earth], as he remembers the life and death of a remarkable young woman whom he met in his dreams. He also recounts his dreams of a tragic future in which the fate of the earth will be decided.
Note: This prequel is a teaser of the entire tv series and reveals some major plot points. Spoiler-full, so you might want to avoid it until you have seen the series.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="408">3.70</permanent>
<temporary count="413">5.96</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>157495.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>608</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>595</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>699</identifier>
<identifier>vbomuv</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>X_(manga)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>X_(漫画)#.E3.83.86.E3.83.AC.E3.83.93.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1.E7.89.88</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1974</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>234808</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5252</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7348" type="main character in" update="2010-12-02">
<rating votes="42">7.03</rating>
<name>Shirou Kamui</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shirou Kamui is a powerful esper whose destiny is to decide whether the world should be destroyed so it may be reborn without humanity or to save the world so humanity can continue to live in its current state. In his childhood, he lived across the street from Togakushi Shrine, and became friends with Fuuma and Kotori. At the age of nine he left Tokyo with his mother, and his return to Tokyo seven years later begins the events of the story.
Kamui also appears in Tsubasa Chronicle: Tokyo Revelations, as one of the vampire twins Seishirou is after. He leads the fighters of the City Hall faction (alternate versions of the Dragons of Earth) in a battle to protect their water source.</description>
<picture>25828.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="191" picture="17006.jpg">Suzumura Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7349" type="main character in" update="2009-05-25">
<rating votes="25">7.79</rating>
<name>Monou Fuuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>25832.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25415" type="main character in" update="2010-11-29">
<rating votes="20">3.54</rating>
<name>Monou Kotori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kotori is Fuuma`s younger sister, a delicate girl with a congenital heart condition, and a developing dreamseer. She was Kamui`s very close childhood friend, and remains kind to him despite his initial coldness.</description>
<picture>60012.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25463" type="main character in" update="2016-06-12">
<rating votes="5">5.36</rating>
<name>Kuzuki Kakyou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kuzuki Kakyou is dreamseer in a permanent coma, who appears as a tall man with golden eyes. His ability to see the future in dreams was discovered at an early age and for this he was imprisoned by some unknown political group. Having never seen the outside world, he drew Sumeragi Hokuto into his dreams and fell in love with her after she showed him the sea through her imagination. However, he foresaw her death at the hands of the Sakurazukamori and tried to save her by breaking out of his room. He was shot by one of the guards and failed to reach Hokuto in time to save her, and has remained in a coma ever since. Subsequently, he meets Monou Kotori in his dreams, but becomes associated with the Dragons of Earth, manipulating Princess Hinoto`s dreams to their ends.</description>
<picture>187596.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3002" picture="17154.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="12874" update="2017-12-27">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-25</airdate>
<rating votes="11">3.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
