<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8992" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2012-04-01</startdate>
<enddate>2012-06-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Yurumates 3D</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ゆるめいつ3でぃ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Yurumates3Dei</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">希望宅邸 3D</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9260" type="Sequel">Yurumates 3D Plus</anime>
<anime id="9144" type="Side Story">Yurumates (2012)</anime>
<anime id="8253" type="Other">Yurumates wa?</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.takeshobo.co.jp/sp/tv_yuru/</url>
<creators>
<name id="13150" type="Animation Work">C2C</name>
<name id="11759" type="Character Design">Oda Takeshi</name>
<name id="1394" type="Original Work">Saxyun</name>
<name id="8323" type="Direction">Yuuzumi Yoshihide</name>
<name id="21609" type="Chief Direction">Yamanashi Tomohiro</name>
<name id="33730" type="Work">Indigo Line</name>
<name id="33733" type="Music">Katayama Shuji</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the 4-koma comedy manga by http://anidb.net/cr1394 [Saxyun].
Rounin student http://anidb.net/ch11207 [Aida Yurume] has come to Tokyo in the hopes of getting into university. However, she finds out that the apartment she will be living in has only ever been occupied by other rounin students. Furthermore, none of its occupants had ever passed the entrance exams!
This does not bode well for Yurume`s future...
~ translated and adapted from official site by Cranston
Note: The first episode received an early screening together with both preceding OVAs at a special event held in Cinem@rt Shinjuku film theatre in Shinjuku, Tokyo on April 1, 2012. The regular TV broadcast started on April 3, 2012.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="368">4.05</permanent>
<temporary count="370">6.03</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>82038.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13801</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12123</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5071</identifier>
<identifier>yapoyr</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.takeshobo.co.jp/sp/tv_yuru/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Yurumates</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ゆるめいつ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2476</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>342134</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14469</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>yurumates3dei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="34">
<externalentity>
<url>https://ch.nicovideo.jp/yuru</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2805" parentid="2798" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>4-koma manga</name>
<description>Yonkoma manga (4コマ漫画, four cell manga, or 4-koma for short), a comic-strip format, generally consists of gag comic strips within four panels of equal size ordered from top to bottom. (They also sometimes run right-to-left horizontally or use a hybrid 2x2 style, depending on the layout requirements of the publication in which they appear.) Though the word yonkoma comes from the Japanese, the style also exists outside of Japan in other Asian countries as well as in the English-speaking market.</description>
<picurl>70558.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3092" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-02">
<name>important haircut</name>
<description>When a character cuts off his or her hair, it often symbolizes a rite of passage or bout of character growth. A princess striking out on an adventure, or a new recruit at boot camp, for instance. Hair is something that takes time and effort to grow, so parting with it voluntarily can be a powerful act.
This is particularly a big deal when women get haircuts. Yet in fiction, even an accidental hair slicing can leave a character with a surprisingly even cut.
In many religions (Western Christianity, Ancient Egyptian religion, and others) priests and/or monks cut/shave their hair. Roman Catholic nuns also tend to cut and mantain their hair short under their veils when they enter the nunneries. The cutting of one`s own hair is also a part of Buddhist mythology, specifically something done by Siddhartha himself early on in his path to enlightenment, so anime examples might draw from this as an allusion. There are also some cultures, including Native American and many Asians, where a person would cut his or her hair as an act of grief, disgrace, or even rebellion. In the Confucian tradition, hair (like the rest of your body) is considered a gift from your parents and may not be damaged without a very good reason. Furthermore, prisoners and psychiatric patients commonly have their heads shaved, often to prevent the spread of lice, but sometimes also as a demeaning measure.
Source: TVTRope</description>
<picurl>169641.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3667" parentid="2676" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo Tower</name>
<description>Tokyo Tower is a communications and observation tower in the Shiba-koen district of Minato, Tokyo, Japan. At 332.9 metres, it is the second-tallest structure in Japan. The structure is an Eiffel Tower-inspired lattice tower that is painted white and international orange to comply with air safety regulations.
Source: Wikipedia
Note: Not to be confused with the very much younger http://anidb.net/t3037 [Tokyo Skytree].</description>
<picurl>161123.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5763" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-19">
<name>rock-paper-scissors</name>
<description>Whenever a decision has to be made in anime, the Japanese protagonists seem to be awfully fond of playing rock-paper-scissors (or jan-ken-pon) to determine the outcome.</description>
<picurl>62869.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6399" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-25">
<name>episodic</name>
<description>An episodic anime consists of many successive short arcs that are generally 1-2 episodes in length, with strong plot continuity within each arc but generally little continuity from one arc to the next. For long shows (well upwards of 50 episodes), the episode count constraint is less tight; for example, a show with close to 250 episodes would also be considered episodic if it consisted of a majority of arcs of up to 3 or maybe 4 episodes and possibly also very few slightly longer arcs.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="11207" type="main character in" update="2009-08-15">
<rating votes="10">4.38</rating>
<name>Aida Yurume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2558.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="327" picture="17472.jpg">Momoi Haruko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11212" type="main character in" update="2009-08-15">
<rating votes="12">5.28</rating>
<name>Kawano Sae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2559.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="328" picture="17164.jpg">Kuwatani Natsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11213" type="main character in" update="2009-08-15">
<rating votes="10">3.47</rating>
<name>Tanaka Kumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2560.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="203" picture="38566.jpg">Matsuki Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11214" type="main character in" update="2009-08-15">
<rating votes="10">2.88</rating>
<name>Matsukichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2561.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30979" type="appears in" update="2012-01-20">
<rating votes="4">6.80</rating>
<name>Sae no Imouto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>80253.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42337" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-12">
<rating votes="3">2.19</rating>
<name>Semi Kaijin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>83452.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42338" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-12">
<rating votes="3">4.13</rating>
<name>Neko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>83451.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="43312" type="appears in" update="2012-04-07">
<rating votes="2">4.13</rating>
<name>Ooya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85455.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8888" picture="33273.jpg">Miyazaki Mayu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45530" type="appears in" update="2012-06-01">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Takuhaiya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88864.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30012" picture="130105.jpg">Odagaki Yuuta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46667" type="appears in" update="2012-07-03">
<name>Yurume no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90489.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24015" picture="67329.jpg">Satou Kanami</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="137762" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-04-01</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゆるめ上京する</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yurume Goes to Tokyo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yurume Joukyousuru</title>
<summary>Aida Yurume has just moved to Tokyo and her new neighbors greet her in peculiar ways.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>595005</identifier>
<identifier>yurumates3dei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138105" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フィーチャリング松吉</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Featuring Matsukichi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Featuring Matsukichi</title>
<summary>The girls of Maison Du Wish use different types of test to understand the complexity of Matsukichi. 
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>595011</identifier>
<identifier>yurumates3dei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138106" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">本当のウソ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A True Lie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hontou no Uso</title>
<summary>The April fools jokes at Maison Du Wish are getting stranger by the moment, until one of the jokes become true.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>595009</identifier>
<identifier>yurumates3dei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138107" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-04-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">イメージチキンレース</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Image Chicken Race</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Image Chicken Race</title>
<summary>Winter is changing into Spring and the residents of Maison Du Wish are changing with it.  New haircuts, robots, rich girls, change is in the air.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>595007</identifier>
<identifier>yurumates3dei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138522" update="2012-04-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-04-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138587" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-06-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">パターン妹</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pattern Sister</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pattern Imouto</title>
<summary>Sae comes from a very strict family, so when her sister announces she will be visiting. She needs the help of all her friends to make a good impression. 
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>595029</identifier>
<identifier>yurumates3dei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138588" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">つもり花見</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Packed for Cherry Blossom Viewing</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsumori Hanami</title>
<summary>Watching the cherry blossoms, a time honored event.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>595027</identifier>
<identifier>yurumates3dei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138589" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-06-12</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">開かずの扉</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unopened Doors</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akazuno Tobira</title>
<summary>Write an embarrassing secret that you can’t tell others.   Some take it as a joke, but one takes it to heart. 
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>595025</identifier>
<identifier>yurumates3dei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138590" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-06-05</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">年末年始の過ごし方</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How to Celebrate New Year`s</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nenmatsunenshi no Sugoshi Kata</title>
<summary>New Year’s traditions, dreams, and tricks are talked about, while Yurume receives a gift from her mother. 
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>595023</identifier>
<identifier>yurumates3dei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138591" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-05-29</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天板パズル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tabletop Puzzle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenban Puzzle</title>
<summary>Yurume is determined to not get out from under the Kotatsu, but after getting it stuck in the hallway her friends try to help remove it. 
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>595021</identifier>
<identifier>yurumates3dei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138592" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-05-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二択気象庁</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Japan`s Two Choice Weather Agency</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ni Taku Kishouchou</title>
<summary>The unpredictable weather is causing much grief to Yurume, and the residents bet on the weather pattern. 
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>595019</identifier>
<identifier>yurumates3dei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138593" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-05-15</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アイス危機一髪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ice Cream`s Close Shave</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ice Kikiippatsu</title>
<summary>The battle for the ice cream has begun; it’s going to get hot out there.  And the winner might actually be the loser. 
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>595017</identifier>
<identifier>yurumates3dei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138594" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-05-08</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スイカ割れ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Watermelon Splitting</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suika Ware</title>
<summary>A watermelon splitting contest brings out the inner savages of the residents.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>595015</identifier>
<identifier>yurumates3dei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="138595" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-05-01</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雨天決行七夕大会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tanabata Festival Rain or Shine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uten Kekkou Tanabata Taikai</title>
<summary>It’s Tanabata and as everyone writes wishes, things start to get out of hand. 
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>595013</identifier>
<identifier>yurumates3dei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148991" update="2013-04-07">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="224106" update="2019-11-12">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
