<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="90" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>94</episodecount>
<startdate>1996-01-10</startdate>
<enddate>1998-09-08</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Rurouni Kenshin: Meiji Kenkaku Romantan</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Rurouni Kenshin: Romance of a Meiji Swordsman</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Wanderer Kenshin</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Rurouni Kenshin TV</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Rurouni Kenshin - Wandering Samurai</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Rurouni Kenshin - Legend of Kyoto</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Rurouni Kenshin - Tales of the Meiji</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Бродяга Кэнсин</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">الرحالة كينشن</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Самурай Х</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Руроуні Кеншін ~Оповіді Мейджі~</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">浪客剑心</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">るろけん</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">るろ剣</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">rk</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">rktv</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">RuroKen TV</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">RuroKen</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">kenshin tv</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">rk tv</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">kenshin</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">るろうに剣心 -明治剣客浪漫譚-</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Rurouni Kenshin</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Kenshin, le vagabond</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Kenshin Samurai Vagabondo</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Kenshin: El Guerrero Samurái</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">ساموراي إكس</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Samurai X</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Samurai X</title>
<title xml:lang="nl" type="official">Kenshin</title>
<title xml:lang="el" type="official">Samurai X</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="official">Samurajai X</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">ซามูไรพเนจร</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="official">Samuray X</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="official">Samurai X</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Samurai X</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="195" type="Sequel">Rurouni Kenshin: Meiji Kenkaku Romantan - Seisou Hen</anime>
<anime id="73" type="Prequel">Rurouni Kenshin: Meiji Kenkaku Romantan - Tsuioku Hen</anime>
<anime id="422" type="Side Story">Rurouni Kenshin: Meiji Kenkaku Romantan - Ishinshishi e no Requiem</anime>
<anime id="8595" type="Summary">Rurouni Kenshin: Meiji Kenkaku Romantan - Shin Kyoto Hen</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="53" approval="13" total="32">Trigun</anime>
<anime id="407" approval="10" total="14">Kazemakase Tsukikage Ran</anime>
<anime id="1056" approval="3" total="11">Peace Maker Kurogane</anime>
<anime id="1663" approval="3" total="3">Mutsu Enmei Ryuu Gaiden: Shura no Toki</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="29">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="578176">A história de um samurai sanguinário que se tornou um pacifista quer evitar novas guerras.

Também conhecido como Samurai X no Brasil.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="599940">When i talk about MY favorite animes i talk about:
Dragon Ball z ; Berserk ; AND SAMURAI X !!!!!

Classic !</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="498732">A true classic of the Samurai genre, but too childish for its setting. If you`re up to some typical shounen and watching many bizarre super-powers, then go for it. If you`re looking for anything darker, watch the OVAs, they`re completely different things.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="147458">Excellent up to  episode 62 when the anime diverges from the manga and mediocre since.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="312775">Best anime series I have ever watched on television. Highly recommended!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="232437">A splendid anime, that is known to be one of the best swordfighting/meji-era animes.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="310110">History, swords and a great humble hero: one of the best animes ever</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="608137">This is good, but went off track sometime. They didn`t put the important part about his past into this anime, so watch the trust and betray ova to fill in the missing parts. It have action, comedy, and a little romance. I wish it have a little more romance.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="521116">Well, when i started watching this anime, I thought that there were going to be a lot of killings, and blood, because it`s about samurai, and mostly those kinds of animes are like this, but instead of killing, this anime is about protecting without killing. I was very surprised with the main character, who tries to repent for the things he`s done. A great story, a lot of laughter, well there were ofcoure sad moments. I truly recomend it to anyone. A great anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="524135">one of the best samurai anime drama ever</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="723948">I highly recommend watching this anime because of its poignant story about guilt and redemption.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="134982">one off my favorite animes..^^</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="422302">i think, the series is a little to long, sometimes there are important scenes, sometimes scenes like an allday-adventures that`s not important for the story of kenshin`s life...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="758856">An underrated gem. It`s in Shonen but it definitely doesn`t feel like it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="415527">This is one of the earlier animes I had watched and it was AWESOME!

Great characters and storyline! A MUST watch!!!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>https://www.kenshin-tv.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1410" type="Direction">Furuhashi Kazuhiro</name>
<name id="753" type="Animation Work">Gallop</name>
<name id="730" type="Animation Work">Studio Deen</name>
<name id="11898" type="Character Design">Hamasu Hideki</name>
<name id="5751" type="Character Design">Muroi Fumie</name>
<name id="509" type="Original Work">Watsuki Nobuhiro</name>
<name id="9204" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ishii Kuniyuki</name>
<name id="6883" type="Music">Asakura Noriyuki</name>
</creators>
<description>Ten years after the start of the Meiji Era, a Rurouni wanders into Tokyo to find a new life with his new friends. Vowing never to kill, he tries to escape his fate as the greatest killer of the Edo dynasty.
An old menace threatens the new Meiji Era, the villian is http://anidb.net/ch6584 [Shishio Makoto], the successor to the Hitokiri Battousai who was supposed to have died in the Boshin Wars. Shishio and his Juppon Gatana are ready to start a new revolution to correct the wrong doings of the Meiji Government and also to avoid colonization.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="8324">7.73</permanent>
<temporary count="8543">8.26</temporary>
<review count="14">8.18</review>
</ratings>
<picture>224003.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>73</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6591</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>45</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>4664</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>9716</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>10334</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>12067</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>317</identifier>
<identifier>ylrdkg</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.kenshin-tv.com/ruroken/tvanime/arasuji/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Rurouni_Kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>るろうに剣心_-明治剣客浪漫譚-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1560</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88943</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1470</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20308</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>5560</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B06XP3WVGH</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1589" parentid="2622" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-08">
<name>samurai</name>
<picurl>244341.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2677" parentid="2672" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Osaka</name>
<description>Osaka Prefecture is a prefecture located in the Kansai region on Honshu, the main island of Japan. The capital is the city of Osaka. It is the center of Osaka-Kobe-Kyoto area.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214384.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2679" parentid="2672" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Kyoto</name>
<description>Kyoto Prefecture is a prefecture of Japan in the Kansai region of the island of Honshu. The capital is the city of Kyoto.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214383.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2692" parentid="2641" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-10">
<name>Bakumatsu - Meiji Period</name>
<description>"Bakumatsu" (幕末, "Late Tokugawa Shogunate") occurred between 1853 and 1867 during which Japan ended its isolationist foreign policy and modernized from a feudal shogunate to the Meiji government. Bakumatsu represents the final years of the Edo period (when the Tokugawa shogunate ended) and preceded the Meiji era. The primary historical significance of Bakumatsu was the conflict between the pro-imperialist "Ishin Shishi" ("nationalist patriots"), and the shogunate forces, including the elite Shinsengumi ("New Selected Corps").
The Meiji Era (including Meiji Restoration) denotes the 45-year reign of Emperor Meiji, running from 23 October 1868 to 30 July 1912. During this time, Japan started its modernization and rose to world power status.
Be aware that this category should only be assigned to anime that take place in Japan during the years mentioned above, and not to every anime that has samurai in it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3515" parentid="2898" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-10">
<name>shinsengumi</name>
<description>The Shinsengumi were a special police force of the late shogunate period.</description>
<picurl>191098.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3575" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-13">
<name>damsel in distress</name>
<description>The damsel in distress is usually a young, nubile woman placed in a dire predicament by a villain or a monster and requires a hero to dash to her rescue. Often used to unite the cast of a show for this one goal, to make them put differences aside and become a band of nakama. 
Examples: Sakoshita Yanagi from Rekka no Honoo, Yuuki Miaka from Fushigi Yuugi or Higurashi Kagome from Inuyasha.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3806" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-13">
<name>tanabata</name>
<description>Tanabata (七夕, meaning "Evening of the seventh") is a Japanese star festival, originating from the Chinese Qixi Festival.
It celebrates the meeting of the deities Orihime and Hikoboshi (represented by the stars Vega and Altair respectively). According to legend, the Milky Way separates these lovers, and they are allowed to meet only once a year on the seventh day of the seventh lunar month of the lunisolar calendar. The date of Tanabata varies by region of the country, but the first festivities begin on July 7 of the Gregorian calendar. The celebration is held at various days between July and August.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160813.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4394" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-21">
<name>defeat means friendship</name>
<description>In a series based around an endless series of one-on-one fights, defeating a Worthy Opponent or The Rival will sometimes convert them to the hero`s side, if not always to his cause. 
Furthermore, no matter how many people the Worthy Opponent has killed, how much grief he has caused, even if he slaughtered helpless children or the hero`s own family, as soon as he shows a bit of remorse or goes out of his way to help the hero even once, he will be welcomed into the hero`s circle of True Companions with open arms.
(Source: TVTropes)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5863" parentid="2798" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-06">
<name>Weekly Shounen Jump</name>
<description>The Weekly Shounen Jump is a Japanese manga magazine released on a weekly basis. Its main target audience consists of young males and it features several manga titles. The magazine was created by http://anidb.net/cr780 [Shueisha] in July, 1968, and was originally only called Shounen Jump, because it was not published every week at the time. A number of very famous shounen manga were or are published in it, such as http://anidb.net/a386 [Hokuto no Ken], http://anidb.net/a231 [Dragon Ball], http://anidb.net/a942 [City Hunter], http://anidb.net/a826 [Saint Seiya], http://anidb.net/a590 [Slam Dunk], http://anidb.net/a312 [Yuu Yuu Hakushou], http://anidb.net/a69 [One Piece], http://anidb.net/a239 [Naruto], http://anidb.net/a2369 [Bleach], http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], http://anidb.net/a3468 [Gintama], to name a few of the most well-known.</description>
<picurl>66685.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6137" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-09">
<name>catchphrase</name>
<description>A catchphrase is a sound, word or phrase commonly used by a person. That may be simply out of habit, or in an attempt to deliver some form of image, like that of cuteness. In fiction, characters often use catchphrases as a way to deliver specific personality traits. Examples include Otohime Mutsumi`s "ara ara" in Love Hina, Yang Wenli`s "yare yare" in Legend of the Galactic Heroes, Misuzu`s "gao" in AIR, Sakura`s "hoe" in Card Captor Sakura, Suiseiseki`s "desu" in Rozen Maiden, and Ayu`s "uguu" in Kanon (as well as several other characters in the same show).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7075" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-05-07">
<name>adapted into Japanese movie</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a Japanese movie.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="435" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-29">
<rating votes="209">8.77</rating>
<name>Hiko Seijuurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiko Seijuurou XIII is Himura Kenshin`s master in the anime/manga series Rurouni Kenshin.
Hiko is shown to be sarcastic, misanthropic and a punishing taskmaster, often referring to Kenshin as "My stupid/idiot apprentice," and bringing up Kenshin`s past to provoke him into training harder. Kenshin describes his personality as "crude, cruel, and hateful." Despite this rough exterior, he has a deep sense of responsibility to Kenshin and those he protects, in the rare cases when he does get involved in a situation (usually at his own will). He has also been shown to be highly respectful and polite towards those he considers to be a true warrior, while at the same time condescending on those he considers to be weak. He loves sake, himself, and teasing Kenshin, although this is a testament to his excellent skill and powerful body. Master and student frequently have bouts of slapstick conflict between them. He dislikes socialising, and in order to avoid having to work with people, he makes his living as a pottery artist.</description>
<picture>14731.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="413" picture="151647.jpg">Ikeda Shuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="443" type="main character in" update="2012-03-22">
<rating votes="1034">9.06</rating>
<name>Himura Kenshin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Set in a fictional version of Japan, during the pre-Meiji period, Kenshin is a former legendary assassin known as "Hitokiri Battousai". At the end of the Bakumatsu, he becomes a wandering samurai, now wielding a sakabatou ("reverse-blade sword"), a katana that has the cutting edge on the inwardly curved side of the sword, thus being nearly incapable of killing. Kenshin wanders the countryside of Japan offering protection and aid to those in need, as atonement for the murders he once committed as an assassin. In Tokyo, he meets a young woman named Kamiya Kaoru, who invites him to live in her dojo despite learning about Kenshin`s past. Throughout the series, Kenshin begins to establish lifelong relationships with many people, including ex-enemies, while dealing with his fair share of enemies, new and old. Through these encounters and relationships, Kenshin begins to find true atonement for his past enabling him to fully conquer his "Battousai" nature.</description>
<picture>84396.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="388" picture="17234.jpg">Suzuki Masami</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="3011" picture="55684.jpg">Suzukaze Mayo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6130" type="appears in" update="2009-04-13">
<rating votes="1">9.98</rating>
<name>Shinsengumi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="6132" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="201">8.89</rating>
<name>Saitou Hajime</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saitou Hajime, based on the real-life personage of the same name, was the leader of the 3rd Squad of the Shinsengumi during the Revolution. He has a long-standing rivalry with Kenshin and firmly believes in "Swift Death to Evil".</description>
<picture>23318.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3136" picture="24121.jpg">Suzuoki Hirotaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6134" type="appears in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="6">4.04</rating>
<name>Okita Souji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23320.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3147" picture="49928.jpg">Ogai Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6584" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-14">
<rating votes="95">7.47</rating>
<name>Shishio Makoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85959.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5776" picture="30241.jpg">Ikeda Masanori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6618" type="main character in" update="2011-04-19">
<rating votes="64">4.48</rating>
<name>Myoujin Yahiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Myoujin Yahiko is a young boy, the son of a samurai. When he was younger, both of his parents died, and he was taken in by the Yakuza, who forced him to live as a pickpocket. Once he meets up with Kenshin and Kaoru, he decides to stand up to the Yakuza, and escapes with Kenshin`s help. He joins Kaoru`s dojo to become a stronger swordsman, becoming the first graduate of http://anidb.net/ch21040 [Kamiya Kasshin-ryuu]. Over the course of the series, he becomes a strong warrior. He hates being treated like a child.</description>
<picture>24367.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3940" picture="54324.jpg">Tominaga Miina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6619" type="main character in" update="2012-03-22">
<rating votes="190">6.62</rating>
<name>Kamiya Kaoru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kamiya Kaoru is a seventeen-year old dojo instructor and the first main character Kenshin meets. Kaoru is a teacher of the Kamiya Kasshin-ryuu style, a swords style used to protect people, and not harm others. Since her father was killed in the war, responsibility for running the family dojo fell to young Kaoru. After defending Kaoru from the fake Battousai and his allies, Kenshin is invited to live at the dojo. Kaoru quickly develops a crush on Kenshin, soon falling in love with him, although she tends to violently deny it. She recognizes that Kenshin, despite his violent past, is a gentle soul who only wants peace by atoning for the lives he stole during the revolution. Although, personality-wise, she is very different than Yukishiro Tomoe, Kenshin`s first love, (i.e. Kaoru is loud, brash, insecure, and cannot cook anything tasty), Kenshin sees that she is also selfless, compassionate, and caring of others almost to a fault. Her understanding of his nature and wanting to help him find the peace he so desires also draws him to her. In the manga, he is able to find atonement (and Tomoe`s smile) by protecting Kaoru`s happiness as well as his new friends. At the end of the series, she and Kenshin marry and have a son together.</description>
<picture>84399.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9823" picture="36572.jpg">Fujitani Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6620" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="123">7.47</rating>
<name>Sagara Sanosuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sagara Sanosuke is a street fighter who befriends Kenshin early in the series. As a youth, Sanosuke ran away from home to join the Sekiho Army, a group of farmers and merchants who fought for the Ishin Shishi during the Meiji Revolution. When the Sekiho were betrayed and executed by the other revolutionaries, Sanosuke escaped and began to pick fights to vent his anger. He challenges Kenshin, a former Ishin Shishi, but when Sanosuke is defeated he becomes one of Kenshin`s closest friends and strongest allies. Sanosuke enjoys fighting, gambling, and mooching off of other people.</description>
<picture>24369.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3382" picture="24410.jpg">Fuchizaki Yuriko</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="3002" picture="17154.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6621" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-31">
<rating votes="26">6.07</rating>
<name>Takani Megumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takani Megumi, 22 years old, originally forced to make opium for an industrialist, with Kenshin`s support and encouragement, she becomes a doctor to atone for her past misdeeds. Having an attraction for Kenshin herself but knowing that his heart belongs to Kaoru, she takes many opportunities to make Kaoru jealous by asserting herself onto Kenshin (much to Kenshin`s chagrin). Because she is a little older and wiser and can be quite cunning, she is nicknamed "fox lady" by Sanosuke. When it comes down to it, she is loyal and concerned over friends and is always there to patch them up (especially Sanosuke). She also tries to "help" Kaoru to come to terms with her feelings toward Kenshin so that Kenshin could lead a long, happy life. She is from the Aizu region, now Fukushima Prefecture.</description>
<picture>24372.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="542" picture="60897.jpg">Doi Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6622" type="appears in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="10">5.31</rating>
<name>Sanjou Tsubame</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sanjou Tsubame, a waitress at Tae`s restaurant, becomes Myoujin Yahiko`s sweetheart. She was saved by him from the ronin her family worked for as Yahiko stopped them from robbing the Akabeko. She is very shy and soft spoken. When Himura Kenshin enters a deep depression after the supposed death of Kamiya Kaoru at the hands of Yukishiro Enishi, Tsubame pleads for Kenshin to help Yahiko fight back against one of Enishi`s abandoned allies and brings Kenshin back into the world of the living. Tsubame and Yahiko become a couple in the manga storyline. Watsuki has mentioned in his notes Tsubame and Yahiko`s son Myoujin Shin`ya, who he considered using in a story idea. In Samurai X: Reflection (Rurouni Kenshin: Seisouhen), Tsubame and Yahiko had become a couple.
Watsuki said that he did not use a specific model for Tsubame`s personality. When the author thought of the concept "a young girl being a young man`s motivation to act" he used her as the heroine of the Yahiko storyline printed in Volume 5. The author used Tsubame as a "testament" of "wrong thinking of a previous age" and gave her a manner that contrasts with Yahiko`s "acts-before-he-thinks" manner. According to Watsuki the model originated from a popular "planet-themed" anime series. As Tsubame is "an average girl" the author decided that her hair should either be in a bowl cut or in pigtails. After watching the "planet-themed" series he decided to use a bowl cut. In the final chapter and Yahiko no Sakabatou Watsuki designed Tsubame to look "as cute as possible" since he wanted a story where she was the heroine." Originally he intended for the new waitress outfit, which looks similar to a maid outfit, to be exclusively for Yahiko no Sakabatou since the maid style was in fashion at the time. Watsuki feared that the fashion could be outdated by the time he wrote Yahiko no Sakabatou, so he used the new waitress outfit in the final chapter of Rurouni Kenshin. Tsubame`s name originates from places where Watsuki lived in Niigata.</description>
<picture>24373.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="437" picture="173174.jpg">Shiratori Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6624" type="appears in" update="2010-07-28">
<rating votes="6">8.02</rating>
<name>Yamagata Aritomo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yamagata Aritomo was one of Kenshin`s comrades. Yagamata grew a mustache since taking position of power in the Meiji government. Yamagata tries to convince Kenshin to stop carrying a sword, but Yamagata realizes that Kenshin`s openly-displayed sword and his actions as a rurouni ensure safety for others. In the anime, he appears again as the assassination target of a corrupt politician, Hashizume, but thanks to Kenshin, he was saved and Hashizume was arrested. Watsuki said that he could not get his version of Yamagata to resemble surviving photographs of the real Yamagata.</description>
<picture>24375.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22159">Mizutani Seiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6625" type="appears in" update="2009-05-03">
<name>Ujiki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>24376.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6626" type="appears in" update="2009-05-03">
<name>Kamiya Koshijirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>24377.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3096" picture="186182.jpg">Sawaki Ikuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6627" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="8">7.73</rating>
<name>Udou Jin`e</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kurogasa, otherwise known as Udou Jin`e, was a hitokiri during the Revolution, and there is evidence he continued killing people well after the end of the Revolution. A master of the Nikaidou Heihou technique (the forced character "Hei" is formed with the kanji for one, two, and eight), attacked high-ranking Imperialist officials of the Meiji government (leading some to believe he fought for the Tokugawa shogunate during the war, since he did state that he was a member of the Shinsengumi, though his thirst for blood led him to killing members of his own squad), killing anyone who stood in his way. He appears as a man dressed in a long scarf, straw hat, and long kimono, and has a unique isukumi (paralyzing terror) technique to project chi toward people, hypnotizing them with his eyes (known as the Shin no Ippou or "One Side of the Soul"). It can also be used to strengthen himself. Kurogasa is obsessed with defeating the famous Hitokiri Battousai (Himura Kenshin) when he meets him during Kurogasa`s attempted assassination of Tani Juusanrou, a government official. He leaves, stating that if Kenshin cannot fight him to his fullest potential, he does not want to fight him at all. Kurogasa kidnaps Kamiya Kaoru the next day, in an effort to force Kenshin to once again become a hitokiri. Kenshin follows Kurogasa`s trail to the forest, where the two duel once again. Despite Kaoru`s life being in danger, Kenshin still does not fight with the intent to kill, and Kurogasa overwhelms him. Not wanting to settle for Kenshin holding back Kurogasa paralyzes Kaoru`s lungs using his Shin no Ippou, therefore making her unable to breathe. The two resume the battle, and Kenshin becomes angry enough to turn into Hitokiri Battousai as Kurogasa looks on gleefully. Kenshin hits Kurogasa`s right arm with the sheath of his sword, crushing Kurogasa`s elbow and severing Kurogasa`s ligaments; therefore Kurogasa can no longer wield a sword with his right arm. Kenshin is about to kill Kurogasa when Kaoru breaks Kurogasa`s spell with her will; she yells "No!," releasing Kenshin from the Battousai spell. Kenshin then frees Kaoru, while Kurogasa picks up his wakizashi with his left hand, and stabs himself in the heart. Jin`e mortally wounded himself so the police would not discover the fact that Shibumi employed him.</description>
<picture>24379.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6628" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-12">
<rating votes="36">8.34</rating>
<name>Seta Soujirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Seta Soujirou is a teenage boy who is Shishio`s right-hand man. He is noted in the series for always smiling, and apparently displaying no emotions in battle.</description>
<picture>24381.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="268" picture="17093.jpg">Hidaka Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6629" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="27">4.02</rating>
<name>Komagata Yumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Komagata Yumi is an oiran, a courtesan in Yoshiwara, formerly an akasen. Because of that, she is beautiful, intelligent, dignified, well-cultured, and was brought up in a comfortable life. She was always interested in social issues and occurrences in Japan, and became reviled at the Japanese government`s stance regarding prostitutes. She came to love Shishio Makoto with an utmost passion, which he returned. Thus, she joined Shishio`s conspiracy to bring down the Meiji government. She is constantly concerned about Shishio`s medical state.
Yumi dies trying to protect Shishio when his body becomes overheated in his fight with Kenshin. After she hurls herself in between Kenshin and Shishio and convinces the former to spare the latter, Shishio runs her through with his sword, mortally injuring her in the process and wounding Kenshin as well. Knowing that she has finally been of use to Shishio in his most important battle, she dies happy and released of her former frustration for not being able to fight next to him. She appears with Shishio and Houji in hell.
Watsuki originally designed Yumi to be a "sexy" accessory for Shishio, as the Rurouni Kenshin author figured that a villain should have a "temptress" around him; Watsuki had not intended to develop Yumi into a character motivated by love. Watsuki had no particular personality model for Yumi. Yumi is a version of Ogin, a character played by the actress Kaoru Yumi in Mitokoumon Gaiden: Kagerou Ninpou-Chou, a spinoff series of Mitokoumon. Watsuki had no specific design model; he designed Yumi "on the spot" with the intention of her to "be sexy." Halfway through the development of Yumi throughout the story, Watsuki became a fan of Morrigan Aensland from Darkstalkers (Vampire Hunter) and as a result Watsuki began to expose more of Yumi`s cleavage and shoulders, "eventually increasing the sexiness by about 120%."
In the end Watsuki intended for Yumi to find happiness in following Shishio everywhere; Yumi`s motivation for sacrificing herself is not receiving death, but being with Shishio. Watsuki said that the concept of Yumi going with Shishio to hell "struck" him. Watsuki reported that he received response letters for Yumi`s sacrifice, including some praising the development and others criticizing it. Watsuki stated that some people who tried to cosplay as Yumi found difficulty in "keeping the top up."
Watsuki stated that drawing Yumi taught him that he could have fun with drawing female characters not just by making them appear "cute," but also making them "seductive, or even evil." Watsuki added that, since Yumi had a "sexed-up body," botching "even one line" could make the character appear "downright indecent." Watsuki stated that Yumi taught him the importance of "skillful sketching."</description>
<picture>24382.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22082" picture="57829.jpg">Irie Kanako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6630" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="5">6.64</rating>
<name>Sadojima Houji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sadojima Houji is Shishio`s second in command. He used to be an official in the Meiji government but lost faith in it when he saw no one in the government worthy of controlling the country. He abandoned his position in the government and eventually met Shishio. Houji, too, envisions Japan as a mighty power led by Shishio, ruling with the principles of basic animal survival. Houji is indeed unique; although he is not proficient in any fighting style, he is a cunning organizer and possesses frightening leadership qualities. His skills as a staff officer figure are quite amazing; he even manages to purchase Rengoku—the gigantic ship—on the black market. Houji`s plan with the Rengoku fails when Kenshin, Sanosuke, and Saitou arrive at the dock and Tsukioka Tsunan`s bombs, which Sanosuke carries, blow a hole into the ship, causing it to sink; since Houji did not have any members of the Ten Swords accompany the ship, Kenshin and his allies were able to destroy the ship. Houji was `baptized` by Shishio`s intense body heat to kindle in him a belief in hell.
Houji strongly believes in Shishio`s strength as he throws away a gun he had hidden after learning of Shishio`s fifteen minute limit. He is in utter disbelief when Shishio is finally defeated by Kenshin and then attempts to destroy the complex in which the fight took place so that if Kenshin died, there would be no victor; thus Shishio would never have been beaten. As the complex collapses, Houji was saved by Anji and Soujirou. Anji convinces Houji to surrender himself to the police, and Houji agreed with the intent of using the criminal courts to project Shishio`s ideals and plans. At the end of the Shishio arc, it was revealed that Houji committed suicide in prison after government officials decided that his voice was too dangerous and refused to grant him a trial. After slitting his throat, he wrote a message on the wall with his own blood: "This world is dead to me now. I go to follow my master to hell." The message was directed at the Meiji government to convey Houji`s disgust with the regime and his loyalty to Shishio. He is last shown in Hell with Shishio and Yumi, vowing to follow Shishio when he declares that he will conquer Hell.
Watsuki stated that much of the overall concept for Houji originates from a character from X-Men whose name sounds similar to Houji`s name; Watsuki said that the X-Men character gave him a "hint" for the story and that Houji`s personality does "not so much" originate from the X-Men character. The X-Men character did not directly fight but instead invents machines to help his team members, so Watsuki wanted a character who held a support role in the Ten Swords. At first Houji was an individual who was often surprised, but Watsuki decided that was would "get awfully dull." Watsuki that when he decided to make Houji Shishio`s second in command, then the character concept "struck chords in my heart." Watsuki stated that Houji`s character design is "100% original" to him and that the design is one which Watsuki is the most confident in; Watsuki reported that several people believed that the design originated from Giant Robo. Watsuki added that the one aspect he did not like about Houji is the costume; Watsuki wanted to make it more "European style authentic" to the time period, but he could not find sufficient resources to make the costume in this manner. Watsuki said that Houji becomes "a pretty cool guy" at the end of the Shishio arc.</description>
<picture>24383.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3142" picture="208354.jpg">Takahashi Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6631" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-22">
<rating votes="74">8.21</rating>
<name>Shinomori Aoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shinomori Aoshi, the leader of the http://anidb.net/ch20161 [Oniwabanshuu], is a skilled swordsman who is highly respected by his comrades. His goal for much of the series is to claim the title of "the strongest" for the pride of the Oniwabanshuu.</description>
<picture>84397.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3289" picture="203640.jpg">Yasuhara Yoshito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20109" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-28">
<rating votes="13">6.35</rating>
<name>Oguni Gensai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Oguni Gensai is the doctor who takes Megumi as his apprentice. In the anime he has two grandchildren, Ayame and Suzume.</description>
<picture>52090.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="107" picture="172060.jpg">Shioya Yoku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20110" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="8">7.53</rating>
<name>Ayame</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ayame and Suzume are Dr. Gensai`s grandchildren. They appear throughout several episodes in the anime.</description>
<picture>52119.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3139">Yuasa Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20111" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="4">5.76</rating>
<name>Suzume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ayame and Suzume are Dr. Gensai`s grandchildren. They appear throughout several episodes in the anime.</description>
<picture>52120.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="337" picture="223875.jpg">Namiki Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20113" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="7">6.24</rating>
<name>Sekihara Tae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sekihara Tae is the 20-something manager of the beef hot pot (gyuunabe, or sukiyaki) restaurant, the Akabeko. She has a twin sister named Sae managing in a similar restaurant called the Shirobeko in Kyoto. Sagara Sanosuke also owes her a seemingly large sum of money in which interest is accounted for. In the anime, and a bit in the manga, she has also tried to push the relationship between Himura Kenshin and Kamiya Kaoru since it seemed it to her that it was not working.
Watsuki originally created Tae as a plot convience in the Zanza story arc and he intended for Kaoru to patronize a restaurant operated by "a good friend"; the author said he used "no thought" while creating Tae, including a lack of planning in her character design. Tae`s personality originates from Kamiya Megumi in Watsuki`s first "Rurouni" story. As the story progressed Watsuki found himself adding additional details about Tae, such as her family name, her status as the daughter of the owner of Akabeko, and her collecting of Nishiki paintings. Watsuki said that Tae was his first character to evolve in the manner that she did. Watsuki did not give Tae lipstick so she would be easily distinguished against Megumi. Her character design originates from a rejected model for Kenshin with a prototype Kenshin hairstyle colored black and a "softer, female" face. Watsuki originally intended for Tae to have a Kansai dialect and had an assistant from the Kansai region to vet the dialog, but Watsuki ultimately rejected the idea after he felt the concept was becoming too strange.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>52168.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="508" picture="140061.jpg">Shimamoto Sumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20114" type="appears in" update="2011-04-11">
<rating votes="2">8.15</rating>
<name>Hiruma Gohei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiruma Gohei was a student at the Kamiya dojo, but when Gohei insisted using swords for killing and then unsuccessfully attacked the master of the dojo, Kaoru`s father, he received a broken thumb and an expulsion. In the story Gohei tries to take over the Kamiya dojo, but Kenshin prevents him from doing so. Gohei hires Sanosuke to defeat Kenshin, but this fails. Later, he hires the Kisaki brothers to defeat Kenshin. Though they almost succeed, Yahiko returns Kenshin`s Sakabatou, the brothers are defeated, and Yahiko sends Gohei limping away after kicking him in the genitals.</description>
<picture>52169.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1621" picture="28482.jpg">Komura Tetsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20115" type="appears in" update="2010-07-29">
<rating votes="1">3.61</rating>
<name>Shindou Tatewaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52171.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20118" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="4">6.35</rating>
<name>Keisatsu Shochou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A local police chief, Chief Muraki is a good friend of Kenshin`s and often informs him of local disturbances. During the Jinchuu arc, Uramura`s residence is attacked along with the Maekawa dojo and the Akabeko as part of Yukishiro Enishi`s plan to strike at the places in Tokyo most important to Kenshin; fortunately Uramura and his family are saved by Kenshin. As a favour to Kenshin, he deliberately points the police in the wrong direction when they attempt to arrest Sanosuke toward the end of the manga. He was not given a name until the Jinchuu arc in the manga.</description>
<picture>52196.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3253" picture="24232.jpg">Kameyama Sukekiyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20119" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<name>Tani Juusanrou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tani Juusanrou is a politician in the War Ministry and a former member of the Ishin Shishi. Tani is very wealthy, pompous and self-centered. http://anidb.net/ch6627 [Kurogasa] marks him as an assassination target, but http://anidb.net/ch443 [Kenshin] and http://anidb.net/ch6620 [Sanosuke] successfully defend Tani. Later in the story Tani and Sanosuke get into an altercation; Tani, the uncle of the yakuza Fudousawa, supports the tyranny in Fudousawa`s town. After Sanosuke defeats Fudousawa, Sanosuke goes to Tani`s residence, defeating the Hiruma brothers, who act as Tani`s bodyguards, before injuring Tani. At the hospital Tani, described by villagers as being "wrapped like a mummy," mutters "evil scary, evil scary." As a result, after the battle between Kenshin and Enishi, Sanosuke is forced to flee the Kamiya dojo due to legal troubles.</description>
<picture>52244.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20158" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="1">8.82</rating>
<name>Takeda Kanryuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takeda Kanryuu, a cunning money-minded industrialist, starts an opium dealing business in Tokyo and forces Takani Megumi to make the drug after the death of his previous opium maker. The opium is a stronger, faster-working recipe called "Spider`s Web." The purpose of his opium business is to generate enough profits to bring in modern Westernized weapons such as the Gatling gun and become an arms dealer. He hires his own private army in Tokyo, as well as the infamous Oniwabanshuu. He thinks he has the Oniwabanshuu under his thumb but when Himura Kenshin shows up at his mansion to save Megumi, he finds that he is mistaken. He resorts to using his Gatling gun to kill all his enemies in the mansion. He manages to kill the four Oniwabanshuu as they protect their leader Shinomori Aoshi with a suicide charge. In the manga Kanryuu uses all of his bullets killing the four members, and Kenshin defeats him. As Kanryuu is arrested, he tries to get the police to arrest Megumi, but Kenshin tells the police that Kanryuu had forced Megumi, so the police leave her alone as Kanryuu is taken away. In the anime, the feeding ramp of his gun is jammed with a dart, after which Kenshin renders him unconscious to be arrested by the police.
Watsuki modeled Takeda Kanryuu after Takeda Kanryuusai, the captain of the Shinsengumi`s Fifth Unit. Watsuki says that there is no model in terms of design; he describes Takeda Kanryuu as a "carryover" of Nishiwaki, a character in the second standalone Rurouni Kenshin story. Kanryuu wears white since Watsuki felt that "between Kenshin and Aoshi, there was too much black already." Watsuki felt that, since he put so much emphasis on Megumi and the Oniwabanshuu, Kanryuu never "became the character" Watsuki intended, which for Watsuki "was a bit of a letdown." The historical Takeda Kanryuusai was known as a homosexual; Watsuki considered making Kanryuu a homosexual, but dropped the idea as Watsuki felt it would "unnecessarily complicate things." He wondered how the story would have proceeded if Kanryuu was a homosexual.</description>
<picture>52247.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20159" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="2">6.59</rating>
<name>Beshimi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Beshimi, the smallest of the Oniwabanshuu, uses his speed to compensate for his lack of strength. Beshimi received no prosperous government job offers because he had competency in one skill. He is a bottom-ranked onmitsu. His favorite weapons are darts, with which he poisons Yahiko, and later on in the anime jams Kanryuu`s gatling gun. He was gunned down by Kanryuu shortly afterward to help Kenshin defeat him.
Watsuki stated that Beshimi was "largely created on-the-spot" and does not have a motif. Watsuki described the sketched out character sans an already-created personality as being "kind of timid." Not originally intended to be a standalone character, Beshimi became shorter than Kenshin. Watsuki said that Beshimi`s shortness and timidness gave him a group of fans who write to Watsuki saying "Beshimi KAWAII" ("Beshimi is cute!"). Watsuki said "not too sure how to feel about that one...".</description>
<picture>52248.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2799" picture="23198.jpg">Matsuno Taiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20160" type="appears in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="3">8.03</rating>
<name>Hannya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hannya is a pupil of Aoshi. The village he was born in was poor, so he was abandoned at birth to reduce the number of people to feed. Han`nya survived, but he could not return to the village so he wandered around like an animal until Aoshi found him and gave him a position in the Oniwabanshuu. After the Bakumatsu Hannya received no prosperous government job offers because of his appearance.
Hannya is the master of disguise within the group; he gained his ability by removing all his prominent facial features, which is why he wears the demonic mask on his face. Hannya burned his lips, cut off his ears and nose, and crushed his cheekbones so he could disguise himself as any individual. The anime mentions nothing of his reason for the mask, although his face is still disfigured. Since Aoshi gave him something to live for in the Oniwabanshuu, he is very loyal to him. Han`nya gives his life to allow Kenshin enough time to retrieve his sakabatou to defeat Kanryuu and save Aoshi. Although working as a spy is more his specialty, Hannya is still one of Aoishi`s most powerful men (even mildly difficult for Kenshin to defeat). His style of combat evolves primarily from his discipline from Aoshi. However, he adds his own bit to it by having painted, possibly tattooed, his arms in horizontal stripes. Giving them the appearance of being shorter than they actually are, thus luring opponents into a false sense of security regarding distance of attacks. He also wears steel gauntlets beneath his gloves, which help him to block attacks from other weapons. These gauntlets contain retractable steel claws, which he will resort to as a sort of trump card.
Hannya`s personality is derived from Yamazaki Susumu, a member of the Shinsengumi. Some readers proposed that Han`nya had a handsome face under his mask, was Aoshi`s kagemusha (such as Aoshi`s twin brother), or was a kunoichi (a female ninja). The design model for Hannya was a human skeleton. Originally Watsuki based Han`nya off of Joseph Merrick, the "Elephant Man." Watsuki initially intended for Han`nya`s face to be deformed since a person stepped on it while Hannya was still in his mother`s womb. In Watsuki`s original concept, other people treated Han`nya like a monster, and therefore he would live alone in the mountains. Aoshi discovers Hannya and Hannya becomes a member of the Oniwabanshuu. Therefore Hannya, who finds his raison d`être in fighting, says "Only in the Oniwabanshuu am I able to live as a human being." Watsuki and his editor discussed how this could mean "the shape of one`s destiny is determined by how one is born." Watsuki decided that this message would be inappropriate for a shounen series. Watsuki said that for him Hannya was a difficult character since it made Watsuki aware of the responsibilities of writing for children. The fact that Hannya`s left and right eyes have different shapes and sizes originates from the Merrick concept. Watsuki said that since Hannya`s design became "more and more blocky" in development his assistants referred to Hannya as "mobile suit," "robot," and other names. Watsuki said that Hannya is not a character one would describe as "evil." Hannya was not based on Masked Ninja Akakage.</description>
<picture>52606.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3093" picture="38195.jpg">Nojima Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20161" type="appears in" update="2011-04-19">
<name>Oniwabanshuu</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Oniwabanshuu were the protectors of Edo Castle during the Edo period. In Rurouni Kenshin, they are Shinomori Aoshi, Han`nya, Shikijou, Hyottoko, Beshimi, Okina, Misao, and the others at the Aoi-Ya. Aoshi`s group is referred as the Tokyo Group, while Misao and Okina`s squad are known as the Kyoto Group. After the Bakumatsu, of all of the Oniwabanshuu members, only Aoshi received job offers from government agencies, such as the intelligence services of the Army of Japan and protection services of political leaders; Aoshi instead chose to be a hired guard as his comrades would be able to work with him.
After Watsuki first discussed the "Megumi arc" with the editor, the editor replied with the opinion that, in Watsuki`s words, "having a swordsman of Kenshin`s caliber fighting a group of punk-thugs still coming into their first facial hair mi-i-ight not make for the most epic of manga." To solve this, Watsuki modified the Tokyo Oniwabanshuu to make them onmitsu (ninja; Watsuki does not like using the word "ninja" as he feels that using it "like that" is "cheesy"), and added details as publication progressed. Watsuki created various shapes and temperaments for the various Tokyo Oniwabanshuu characters. Watsuki describes the addition of the Oniwabanshuu as a "last minute" choice.
Source: wiki</description>
</character>
<character id="20362" type="appears in" update="2010-08-04">
<rating votes="1">4.88</rating>
<name>Hyottoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hyottoko is one of the Oniwabanshuu members that decided to go with Aoshi when he left Okina caring for Misao. His massive belly makes him nearly impervious to direct physical attacks. Hyottoko mainly breathes fire at his opponents, by means of a large oil bag he keeps stored in his stomach and a nozzle he keeps in his mouth. He lights the flames by using his front teeth, which he replaced with flint. Hyottoko received no prosperous government job offers because he had competency in one skill. He is a mid-ranked onmitsu. Hyottoko dies while charging for Kanryuu.</description>
<picture>52592.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1986" picture="1919.gif">Iizuka Shouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20372" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="1">4.88</rating>
<name>Shikijou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the Oniwabanshuu members, Shikijou (式尉) is a muscle-laden hand-to-hand fighter. Prior to joining the Oniwabanshuu, Shikijou was an onmitsu for the Satsuma faction of the Ishin Shishi. In the second year of Keiou (1866) Shikijou infiltrated Edo Castle so he could get information about an upcoming battle. 13-year old Shinomori Aoshi appeared, created scars all over Shikijou`s body, and defeated Shikijou. Aoshi gave Shikijou a chance to join the Oniwabanshuu and gain strength using Oniwabanshuu training methods and "medicines." Shikijou received no prosperous government job offers because he was a traitor. Shikijou is mainly a hand to hand fighter but he also swings around a large ball and chain. He fights Sagara Sanosuke at Takeda Kanryuu`s mansion and is (barely) defeated.
He is the first to die at Kanryuu`s hand, protecting Aoshi from the gatling gun.</description>
<picture>52608.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42809" picture="223789.jpg">Nakata Kazuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20484" type="appears in" update="2010-08-07">
<name>Akabeko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>A beef hot pot restaurant</description>
<picture>52867.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="20485" type="appears in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<name>Nagaoka Mikio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nagaoka Mikio is a thug who bullies Sanjou Tsubame. In previous eras her family served Mikio`s family, so Mikio forces Tsubame to give the mold for the key of the owners of the Akabeko. Yahiko tries to interfere, but Mikio`s group defeats Yahiko. As Mikio and his cohorts are about to rob the owner`s house, Yahiko appears a second time and, with the help of Kenshin and Sanosuke, defeat Mikio and his group, and they stopped bothering Tsubame again. Mikio fought with a sword style known as Kogen Ittou-ryuu.</description>
<picture>52869.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="211227.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20513" type="appears in" update="2010-08-08">
<rating votes="1">3.61</rating>
<name>Toramaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Toramaru is a sumo westler.</description>
<picture>52914.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="592" picture="170729.jpg">Tsuda Kenjirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20514" type="appears in" update="2010-08-08">
<name>Senryouyama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52915.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8057">Sasaoka Shigezou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20515" type="appears in" update="2010-08-08">
<name>Hamakaze Oyakata</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52916.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14755" picture="242189.jpg">Sawa Ritsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20516" type="appears in" update="2010-08-08">
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<name>Raikou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Raikou is a fake shaman who "cure" people with his "holy water" and live off the profits. Eventually, Megumi and the others catch on and defeat the gang, in the process make Raikou admit the truth.</description>
<picture>52917.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2021" picture="187129.jpg">Tsuji Shinpachi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20517" type="appears in" update="2010-08-08">
<name>Hachisuka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hachisuka is the leader of the Hishimanji Guren Gang. The Hishimanji gang appears a group of gangsters who spread rumors about Megumi Takani being a "quack-doctor" and rely on Raiko, a fake shaman, to "cure" people with his "holy water" and live off the profits. Eventually, Megumi and the others catch on and defeat the gang, in the process make Raiko admit the truth.</description>
<picture>52918.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3291" picture="24306.jpg">Takemura Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20518" type="appears in" update="2010-08-08">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Kanekura Kaede</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52920.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20279" picture="52921.jpg">Nakao Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20519" type="appears in" update="2010-08-08">
<name>Sasaki Heihachirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52923.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20520" type="appears in" update="2010-08-08">
<name>Sakaki Touma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakaki Touma is the captain of Jinpuu Tai.</description>
<picture>52924.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3142" picture="208354.jpg">Takahashi Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20521" type="appears in" update="2010-08-08">
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<name>Kumatsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52925.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20280" picture="81719.jpg">Matamura Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20522" type="appears in" update="2010-08-08">
<rating votes="1">4.88</rating>
<name>Hashizume Takuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52926.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3734" picture="25108.jpg">Muramatsu Yasuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20523" type="appears in" update="2010-08-08">
<name>Jinpuu Tai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Jinpuu Tai is a group of assassins.</description>
</character>
<character id="20524" type="appears in" update="2010-08-11">
<name>Kitamura</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52927.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17636" picture="189847.jpg">Yoshikawa Toranori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20525" type="appears in" update="2010-08-10">
<rating votes="2">4.78</rating>
<name>Ebisu Marimo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52928.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="388" picture="17234.jpg">Suzuki Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20526" type="appears in" update="2010-08-08">
<name>Ebisu Jirokichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52929.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="275" picture="17102.jpg">Tahara Aruno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20527" type="appears in" update="2010-08-08">
<name>Sumidaya Soubei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52930.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3790" picture="50436.jpg">Takiguchi Junpei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20531" type="appears in" update="2010-08-08">
<name>Onizaki Tekkan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52939.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3342" picture="34405.jpg">Tanaka Yasuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20532" type="appears in" update="2010-08-08">
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<name>Onizaki Gengo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>52940.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20546" type="appears in" update="2010-08-08">
<name>Tsukayama Yutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsukayama Yutarou is a young boy who wishes to become a better swordsman. Yutaro`s father, a well-known swordsman, is dead. Yutarou, who had inherited a lot of money after his parents died, wishes to learn swordsmanship to become as skilled as his father. When he sees Kenshin, he demands lessons on how to use a sword, but Kenshin refuses. Yutarou finds Raijuuta, who plans to overthrow the Meiji government, instead. During a scuffle one of Raijuuta`s men accidentally hits Yutarou, causing him to fall into the ocean. After Kenshin rescues him Yutarou gets to know Kenshin`s group. In a similar manner Raijuuta injures Yutarou`s right arm, and Yutarou goes to Germany for medical treatment. Yutarou appears in the Black Knights arc.
Watsuki developed Yutarou as Yahiko`s rival; Watsuki said there was no "real model" for Yutarou`s character. Watsuki gave Yutarou the traits of admiring Kaoru, an older woman, and admiring Kenshin`s strength while Yutarou could not "be honest" about this as Kenshin and Kaoru were Raijuuta`s enemies. Watsuki felt that Yutarou was a "good guy" who was "brought down a bit" by the "most disgraceful" Raijuuta and that Yutarou may not have been developed "to his full extent." Watsuki drew Yutarou to be the opposite of Yahiko. Watsuki initially found difficulty in drawing Yutarou`s hair but it became easy to him once he adjusted to it, and Watsuki enjoyed drawing Yutarou`s hair. Watsuki found difficulty in compensating for the all-white Yutarou in the page design, which would need more black.</description>
<picture>52955.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="322" picture="17159.jpg">Tanaka Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20547" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="1">8.82</rating>
<name>Isurugi Raijuuta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Isurugi Raijuuta`s personality and motives differ in the manga and anime. In the manga he is dissatisfied with the current state of swordsmanship in Japan and plans to revive the old style of swordsmanship (satsujin-ken, "swords that bring death" or "murderous sword technique") with the Shinko-ryuu by traveling around Japan and shutting down shinai dojos by force, gathering the strongest swordsmen he has met along the way. His Shinko-ryuu is not a formal sword school but a league of swordsmen. He uses the Tsukayama family`s money to fund his campaign. In the anime he aspires to form a "kingdom" of Japanese swordsmen with a rebel group of samurai, starting at the Tsukayama home in Izu Province by using his apprentice`s admiration of the swordsman to his own advantage.
Although Raijuuta appears to be a tough fighter, proficient in the Shinko-ryuu style, the Izuna techniques (a vacuum cut of unparalleled sharpness) are all show and no true power. Although he severed the nerves in Yutarou`s right arm, he got Kenshin`s as well, and is gleeful, thinking he has the upper hand. In the manga, Kenshin figures out that despite all his talk of the killing sword, Raijuuta has never killed anyone himself and is in fact a total fraud. In the story Kenshin knocks him down with a battoujutsu technique from outside Raijuuta`s zone (shortly after he stated he could not be struck). In the manga, after the battle, Raijuuta picks up Yahiko and threatens to kill him. Yahiko tells Raijuuta to kill him; when Raijuuta is finally confronted with the choice of killing Yahiko, he cannot because Kenshin explains what the killing sword truly entails. This, in effect, destroys his confidence as a swordsman, and as a result he is never able to pick up a sword again. In the anime, Raijuuta had been shown to have murdered the people that he hired to fake a kidnapping of Yutarou.
Raijuuta was originally based on a character in an American comic book. As the story progressed, Watsuki said that Raijuuta`s appearance and personality "deteriorated." Watsuki intended for Raijuuta to be "intelligently macho and a believer of satsujin-ken." Instead Raijuuta became "a total fake" who became "a smaller and smaller man" as the story progressed, until he was "defeated by a single blow - ending almost as a villain." Watsuki wondered how Raijuuta "sunk so low." Watsuki concluded that designing and developing Raijuuta taught him "quite a bit." Watsuki wanted to give Raijuuta "peace" in future stories, but added "then again...this guy-! Sigh." Watsuki experienced difficulty in trying to manage "the complicated details" of the Oniwabanshuu story arc, so he gave Raijuuta a relatively simple design. Watsuki used one design flourish and black feathers. Watsuki then experienced difficulty in drawing the feathers. Watsuki concluded that the development of Raijuuta taught him about character design and that he feels enjoyment in drawing "macho" characters.</description>
<picture>52957.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3383" picture="24325.jpg">Oobayashi Ryuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20548" type="appears in" update="2010-08-08">
<name>Shinkou-ryuu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="20549" type="appears in" update="2010-08-08">
<rating votes="1">4.88</rating>
<name>Oguni Hana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Oguni Hana is http://anidb.net/ch20109 [Dr. Gensai]`s younger sister.</description>
<picture>52962.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2276" picture="187770.jpg">Kataoka Tomie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20553" type="appears in" update="2010-08-08">
<rating votes="1">3.61</rating>
<name>Sakuramaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53008.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4185" picture="224827.jpg">Ushiyama Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20554" type="appears in" update="2010-08-08">
<name>Tsukio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53017.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2220" picture="188715.jpg">Inaba Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20555" type="appears in" update="2010-08-08">
<name>Tsuruzaemon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53018.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3096" picture="186182.jpg">Sawaki Ikuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20556" type="appears in" update="2010-08-08">
<name>Sakata</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53019.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3140" picture="24125.jpg">Mori Norihisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20649" type="appears in" update="2010-08-10">
<rating votes="2">6.12</rating>
<name>Sagara Souzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Based on the actual captain, Sagara Souzou was the leader of the Sekihou Army`s (Sekihou-tai) 1st Unit. Sanosuke looked up to him greatly; he was, to Sanosuke, the ideal role model. He was killed when the Meiji government purged the Sekihou Army, leading to Sanosuke`s embitterment towards the Meiji government. In the manga, Sagara`s head was placed on a platform and in a cage for all to see, haunting Sanosuke for many years. In the anime Sagara died of fatal gunshot wounds while protecting Sanosuke. In a flashback late in the Kyoto arc of the anime, it is also shown that Sanosuke remembers seeing Sagara`s head in the cage in a crowd. Sometime after his death, Sano took Sagara Souzou`s family name his name and became Sagara Sanosuke.
Watsuki said that since Sagara Souzou is an actual historical figure, "talking about his "motif" as a character seems beside the point." The author`s mental image of Sagara Souzou became important in the character development. According to Watsuki, the framework of Sanosuke`s memories glorifies Sagara Souzou in the story. Since, according to Watsuki, Sagara Souzou genuinely wanted equality for Japan`s people, Watsuki wonders about the fate of Japan if Sagara Souzou survived. Watsuki debated whether to include the Sekihou Army Incident due to its obscurity. Since he believed that the movement exposed the truths and lies of the Meiji Restoration, he decided to include the movement. One of Watsuki`s friends told the Rurouni Kenshin author that another one of his friends feared that Watsuki may be "getting in too deep." In addition, as Watsuki wrote the storyline, the popularity of the series fell to the lowest point since the debut of the series. Watsuki reasoned that he wished to explore the "true story of the Meiji Revolution" and therefore could not leave out the story of the Sekihou Army. Watsuki did not base the appearance of Sagara Souzou on actual historic photographs; he wondered about the appearance of the real Sagara Souzou. Watsuki instead formed his version of the character based on his mental image of the real person. He says that the character is popular "in the eyes (and hearts) of female readers."</description>
<picture>53145.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22085" picture="57831.jpg">Kikuchi Hidehiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20650" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="2">8.82</rating>
<name>Tsukioka Tsunan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Born Katsuhiro, Tsukioka Tsunan is a survivor of the Sekihou Army after it was disbanded by the government. Called Katsu by Sanosuke, Tsunan became a printmaker after the Meiji Restoration. He is an expert at explosive weapons and gunpowder, and intends to use them against the Meiji government. When he and Sano try to embark on a terrorist campaign against the Meiji government later in the series, they are stopped by Kenshin. Since then, Kenshin buried his bombs and Katsu became a journalist for his own newspaper (in the anime Katsu buried his own bombs). Later on in the anime series, he becomes a valuable source of information for Kenshin and Sanosuke, serving as their intelligence source during the Feng Shui arc. However, he still makes bombs solely as a hobby-he has several to give Sanosuke just before following Kenshin to Kyoto.
Watsuki says that Tsunan originated from a false advertisement, labeled "Mysterious Artist Appears," within the series. When Watsuki created the extra Sanosuke chapters he created a "comrade from the Sekihou Army — lone explosive expert plotting overthrow of the government." Watsuki believed that this alone did not give Tsunan "interesting" qualities, so he added the "fake artist" trait. In Volume 6 Watsuki expressed a desire to use Tsunan at a later point since, at that point, he is the sole character with a "mass media" connection and therefore could have further use at a later point. Despite the fact that Tsunan is "a little depressing," Watsuki likes Tsunan`s "straightforward personality." Tsunan had no design model. Due to a lack of time Watsuki used an earlier concept of a man with dreadlocks; Watsuki believed that the concept "to my surprise, turned out to be just right." The author added that the character could be "a good villain." After making some "tweaks" the design assembled "quickly." Watsuki added the bandanna and the "oddly-patterned" jacket as he wanted "artist-y" clothing.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>53148.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2016" picture="240331.jpg">Yanaka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="20280" picture="81719.jpg">Matamura Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20678" type="appears in" update="2010-08-11">
<rating votes="5">7.30</rating>
<name>Shura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shura is the daughter of the former pirate leader. She is now in charge of the pirates. At first, some pirates wanted to kidnap Kaoru but Shura didn`t accept that because, like she said, they don`t harm woman or children, so she took Kenshin to free Kaoru.</description>
<picture>53197.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22158" picture="1500.jpeg">Itou Kazue</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="6928" picture="211675.jpg">Matsumoto Miwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20679" type="appears in" update="2010-08-11">
<rating votes="1">3.61</rating>
<name>Senbonya Yohei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53200.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4438" picture="26713.jpg">Sakaguchi Yoshisada</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20680" type="appears in" update="2010-08-11">
<name>Gekki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53203.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2799" picture="23198.jpg">Matsuno Taiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20681" type="appears in" update="2011-04-14">
<name>Kairyuu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Kairyuu is the pirate group.</description>
</character>
<character id="20682" type="appears in" update="2010-08-11">
<name>Ginjou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53206.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22153" picture="58110.jpg">Komada Hajime</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20683" type="appears in" update="2010-08-11">
<rating votes="1">4.88</rating>
<name>Sarujirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53208.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5046" picture="28852.jpg">Nakai Masataka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20697" type="appears in" update="2010-08-12">
<name>Iwazou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53228.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3321" picture="228645.jpg">Tsujimura Mahito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20698" type="appears in" update="2010-08-12">
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<name>Ryuugorou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ryuugorou is Shura`s father and former Kairyuu pirate`s leader.</description>
<picture>53229.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3096" picture="186182.jpg">Sawaki Ikuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20699" type="appears in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="1">4.88</rating>
<name>Shibumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shibumi is a corrupt politician who employs assassins. He employs Udou Jin`e, Akamatsu Arundo, and Saitou Hajime. Shibumi orders Saitou to kill Kenshin, not knowing that Saitou is in actuality allied to Ookubo Toshimichi. After Saitou appears at Shibumi`s place and kills Arundo, Shibumi begs for his life and offers money to Saitou; Saitou refuses and kills Shibumi.</description>
<picture>53230.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="261" picture="151648.jpg">Ikeda Masaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20700" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="2">4.12</rating>
<name>Akamatsu Arundo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akamatsu Arundo is a mercenary of Shibumi, a corrupt politician. Arundo feels jealous that Shibumi told Saitou Hajime to kill Kenshin, but Saitou tells Arundo that Arundo could kill Kenshin and take credit for Kenshin`s death. Arundo ambushes Kenshin and tries to use a chain to immobilize Kenshin. Kenshin ultimately defeats Arundo. Arundo discovers that Saitou is actually allied with Ookubo Toshimichi. When Arundo, fearing for his safety, decides to cut ties with Shibumi and go out of the country, Saitou appears and decapitates Arundo with a strike from his sword; he kills Shibumi shortly afterward.
Watsuki stated "this character`s only here to get beat up." As Arundo appears to aid story development, Watsuki made Arundo arrogant (Watsuki`s favorite personality trait for villains) and added no other personality traits. Watsuki believes that he was unable to make Arundo`s chain-scythe to appear like real chains. His design originates from a superhuman soldier in an American comic book who has a name similar to Arundo`s, that being X-Men`s Russian supervillain Omega Red (赤 aka relating to "red", and 末 matsu corresponding to "end", equivalent to "Omega", which is the last letter of the Greek alphabet - also related to the Christian concept of Alpha and Omega); Arundo`s use of chains also parallels Omega Red`s carbonadium tentacles.</description>
<picture>53232.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="242" picture="238968.jpg">Nakata Kazuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20701" type="appears in" update="2010-08-12">
<rating votes="3">4.37</rating>
<name>Kawaji Toshiyoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kawaji Toshiyoshi is a government official who assists Ookubo.</description>
<picture>53233.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20322" picture="186181.jpg">Shiga Katsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20702" type="appears in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="2">6.28</rating>
<name>Ookubo Toshimichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>In history, Ookubo Toshimichi (大久保 利通) (1830-1878) was one of the five Ishin Shishi - Men of Spirit and the last of the three to have the highest honors in the government. He outlived Katsura Kogorou and Saigou Takamori. He was a leader of the Satsuma clan, who supported the restoration of imperial power. He was responsible for the suppression of the Satsuma rebellion in 1877, led by Ookubo`s university friend, Saigou Takamori. In Rurouni Kenshin, Ookubo appears to Kenshin for help in the Shishio Makoto crisis. In real life, Ookubo was murdered by six discontented clansmen on his way to Tokyo on May 14, 1878. In the Rurouni Kenshin series, Seta Soujirou murders him and the clansmen take responsibility.
Watsuki feels that many Japanese people have bias towards Saigou and that Ookubo was "sly" and "cunning." Watsuki expressed disappointment in this and instead stated that while Ookubo was a strategist during the Bakumatsu, Ookubo was ethical during the Meiji era and did not try to enrich himself while other politicians conspired with the wealthy to make money. To support his point, after Ookubo died he had few assets and many debts; many of his debts were due to his covering government shortfalls. Watsuki felt that Ookubo, who had been demonized during his time period, needed more appreciation from the population. In the design Watsuki tried to use portrait photographs, but he could not find any. He tried using a statue as a model, but Watsuki believes that the final character does not look at all similar to the statue. In retrospect he believed that the character resembles President of the United States Abraham Lincoln, another historical figure that Watsuki had respect for. He commented "that must have found its way in there, somehow..."</description>
<picture>53239.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4438" picture="26713.jpg">Sakaguchi Yoshisada</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20720" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-22">
<rating votes="43">6.16</rating>
<name>Makimachi Misao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Makimachi Misao is a kunoichi (female ninja) who was raised by the Oniwabanshuu. She idolizes Shinomori Aoshi.</description>
<picture>84398.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="419" picture="17271.jpg">Sakurai Tomo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20728" type="appears in" update="2010-08-13">
<rating votes="1">3.61</rating>
<name>Mishima Eiichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mishima Eiichirou is Mishima Eiji`s elder brother.</description>
<picture>53295.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20322" picture="186181.jpg">Shiga Katsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20729" type="appears in" update="2011-04-19">
<rating votes="1">4.88</rating>
<name>Mishima Eiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mishima Eiji is a young boy from Shingetsu Village who wants to take revenge against Shishio`s forces, who killed Eiji`s parents and brother, http://anidb.net/ch20728 [Mishima Eiichirou]. Saitou Hajime sent Eiichirou to Shingetsu to investigate the incidents there, hoping that he would not raise suspicion; Eiichirou`s cover was blown, and he failed to save his parents. Kenshin defeats Senkaku, who killed Eiichirou and Eiji`s parents, and Shishio and his forces leave. At that point Eiji tries to kill Senkaku with a sword; Saitou appears and stops Eiji. When Eiji insists that Senkaku needs to be killed in his family`s honor, Kenshin tells Eiji that his dead family wants him to be happy, not for him to kill someone. Saitou arranges for his wife, Tokio, to care for Eiji in the near future.
Watsuki created Eiji as the process of the tragedy in Mishima Village and the concept of a new beginning. Eiji`s main theme is revenge. In retrospect Watsuki wishes that Eiji developed as a character since he felt the plot pulled Eiji in its own direction. Watsuki used no model in Eiji`s design, as he had a lack of time. Watsuki at first created a "slightly long-haired" boy, but Watsuki whited out the design when he believed that it did not appear to be a village boy. Then Watsuki drew the final version. The first design appears in a panel in the initial weekly magazine version of the story; it was corrected for the graphic novel version. Since Watsuki had a lack of time, he asked his assistants to put a pattern on Eiji`s shirt and a tone on Eiji`s trousers. Watsuki felt the design looked too similar to Yahiko`s design.</description>
<picture>53297.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20280" picture="81719.jpg">Matamura Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20741" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="1">4.88</rating>
<name>Senkaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Senkaku is a minion of Shishio Makoto who oppresses Shingetsu Village. Senkaku killed Mishima Ei`ichirou and Ei`ichirou`s parents after he discovered that Ei`ichirou was spying for the Meiji Government. He claims to have killed 99 people. Senkaku fights with a pair of knuckle blades and has high speed, contrary to his size. However, this proves to be his undoing, as Kenshin defeats Senkaku in a battle by using the gigantic size as a way to stress out Senkaku`s limits, causing his leg to break. In the manga the police take Senkaku away, in which Saitou notes he would most likely be executed. In the anime he manages to escape and is killed by Seta Soujirou.
Originally Senkaku was one of the "Ten Swords" and so Watsuki put a lot of effort into his creation. Since Shishio and Soujirou were present and Kenshin needed to go to Kyoto, Watsuki decided to make Senkaku a "violent village despot." Originally Watsuki had Senkaku as an experimental character who could only say "Gaaaah" or "Guaaah" and not form any words. An editor commented that Senkaku "is not a wild animal" during a meeting, so Watsuki scrapped this idea. Senkaku had no model for his personality, and after the scrapping of the inarticulation trait Senkaku became "pretty much just muscle-head small fry." The origin of Senkaku`s design stems from the design of the four Abukuma priests, a group of minor antagonists. Watsuki felt no attachment towards the priest characters, but he had some interest in discovering how well he could draw the different bald heads, and one of those was cone-shaped. He felt the cone-shape design was "a waste for an unimportant character," so he instead used that design for Senkaku, who to Watsuki turned out to be "unimportant" anyways. In retrospect Watsuki felt that he may have been influenced by the Coneheads, characters in a Sega Saturn commercial, and the Giant Soldier in Nausicaä of the Valley of the Wind. When Watsuki wrote the creation profile of Senkaku in Volume 8 of Rurouni Kenshin, he still felt regret about the development of Senkaku; what he regretted most was how he was unable to use Senkaku`s hissatsu-wata special technique "Piercing Head-Butt" in the storyline. In Watsuki`s group of friends, Senkaku was referred to as "Sexy Dynamite," and Watsuki added that they said "especially in the groin area."</description>
<picture>53309.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1621" picture="28482.jpg">Komura Tetsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20748" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="5">8.81</rating>
<name>Yuukyuuzan Anji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuukyuuzan Anji is a warrior fallen-monk who fights alongside Shishio to destroy the Meiji government who did nothing to stop the anti-Buddhist purge which resulted in the destruction of his home and the deaths of the five orphaned children he cared for in his temple, who came from families who opposed the Meiji restoration and were wiped away during the war. Though he is a "fallen" monk he still maintains many of the Buddhist beliefs and now wishes to cleanse the world of those who are evil, driven by the goal of salvation, and is willing to side with evil to achieve this. Anji`s title, "The Bright King" (Myou-ou), comes from Acala, one of the Five Wisdom Kings, who shatters delusion and is a protector of the faith; Anji believes this to be his purpose. In the English dub, his title was changed to "Anji the destroyer."
Anji is the 3rd strongest and most merciful of the Ten Swords and has made an agreement with Shishio that Anji shall decide whether someone lives or dies. Despite being ranked as third most powerful, Usui seems to fear him to some extent, having declined from Anji`s challenge after the fallen monk protected Misao from the Blind Murderer. He does not use a blade directly in combat, instead utilizing Futae no Kiwami (Double Layer Limit or "Mastery of Two Layers") to strike the blade into the ground to attack from a distance, or more usually directly with his fists.
Upon meeting Sagara Sanosuke in a forest, he teaches him his secret technique, without realizing Sanosuke is allied with Kenshin. Before teaching Sanosuke, Anji asks Sanosuke about his opinion on the Meiji government, to which Sanosuke answers that he hates the Meiji government. In Shishio`s lair, Sanosuke battles Anji to a standstill, and then, despite Anji attacking with his final technique (using his secret move in combination with a short sword) gains the advantage by upgrading the power of the Double Layer Limit into a Triple Layer Limit (Sanjuu no Kiwami). (He strikes with his knuckles and then his fist, in the usual way, but then with the tips of the fingers.) After hitting Anji with the Sanjuu no Kiwami, Sanosuke convinces him that the life he has been living is not the one that the deceased children want for him like he believed. Anji stops in mid-attack and sees the spirits of children he used to take care of, sinking to his knees instead. After Shishio`s death, he chooses to serve 25 years in prison in Hokkaido.
Watsuki developed Anji before publication of Rurouni Kenshin; Anji appears as an extra in the "Rurouni" short story. Watsuki experienced difficulty in determining what Anji`s backstory would be and whether Anji would be a protagonist or an antagonist, so he did not use Anji until the stories published in Volume 9. When Watsuki determined that Sanosuke needed to become more powerful, he introduced Anji as being a counterpart to Sanosuke`s fighting style, so Watsuki would give Sanosuke a strong opponent and increase Sanosuke`s power. Watsuki used no model for Anji`s personality; Watsuki pictures Anji as being similar to Shinsengumi lieutenant Kai Shimada (JA) due to the "manly air." Watsuki said that Anji is his second attempt at "manly intelligence," as the first, Isurugi Raijuuta, "failed." Anji`s visual model originates from the lead vocalist of a band called "Angie," which had disbanded by the time of the publication of Volume 9 in Japan; the name "Anji" originates from "Angie." Watsuki believes that the band`s bandannas on shaved heads and the black makeup under the eyes gave an impression suggesting intelligence and appeared "cool," therefore Anji received these traits. Watsuki intended to give Anji a "power-fighter" design but instead used a "macho" design.
Watsuki reported that some people told him that Anji looks like Colossus in the "Fatal Attraction" story of X-Men. Watsuki said that this was not an influence in Anji`s design, since Anji was created one year before the Japanese publication of Rurouni Kenshin Volume 13, and that he read the Japanese version of "Fatal Attraction" afterwards. Watsuki reported that reader response to Anji`s story was mostly positive. Watsuki planned to give Anji more of a backstory, but he had to cut it down so it would not interrupt the flow of the fighting; Watsuki originally planned to have Anji`s heart momentarily stop due to the "Mastery of Three Layers." Watsuki`s assessment is that if one reads into the story deeply enough, one can see that Anji`s "rampage" to the dark side was stopped, but by the end of Volume 13, after his defeat at the hands of Sanosuke, Anji`s soul had not yet been "saved."</description>
<picture>53322.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3251" picture="24230.jpg">Hara Yasuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20769" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-22">
<rating votes="5">8.73</rating>
<name>Kashiwazaki Nenji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kashiwazaki Nenji, also known as Okina, is a strong fighter and a talented strategist. He is said to be the only one who can equal the former Oniwabanshuu leader in a fight, wielding steel tonfa to block sword blows. Okina was to become the next leader but refused the position, saying that it was the time for the young, not the old and recommended Aoshi to be the next leader. He was then made an agent in Kyoto for gathering information. Upon retiring, he gave up his fighting ways (although he was seen fighting Aoshi) and now lives peacefully in Kyoto at the Aoi-Ya (House of Malva), the headquarters of the Oniwabanshuu (which is now a hotel), where he raised Misao. Although old, Okina still possesses a quick mind and knows all of the outer and inner workings of Kyoto since the old intelligence network of the Oniwabanshuu is still active. He uses this network to help Kenshin find Arai Seikuu and Hiko Seijirou. Okina tends to like drinking games and pretty girls.
Watsuki had no particular model for Okina`s personality; Okina is Watsuki`s image of an "old soldier." Okina, a "gentle, run-down-at-the-seams" elderly man, summons his powers and corrects the younger generation when it is confused or does something wrong; Watsuki supposes that a bit of the character Kohei from Shoutarou Ikenami`s Kenkyaku Shoubai ("The Sword Trade") in Okina. Watsuki said that he likes Okina since as a character he can "tie up loose ends." Okina`s design model is Tokijirou Kaizou from Takeshi Obata`s Cyborg Jii-chan G ("Cyborg Grandpa `G`"). Watsuki said that while he is careful to not make his characters look too similar to their influences, his assistants guessed the design model "right away"; Watsuki added that his assistants are "too clever for their own good." Watsuki expressed disappointment with Okina`s hair; he intended for the hair to stand up when Okina is very angry, making Okina resemble "Sally`s dad from the anime." Because of a lack of available pages Watsuki concluded "this hasn`t ended up coming across too well."</description>
<picture>84402.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3284" picture="24296.jpg">Kitamura Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20770" type="appears in" update="2012-03-22">
<rating votes="4">2.78</rating>
<name>Arai Iori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Arai Iori is Seikuu and Azusa`s son.</description>
<picture>84405.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6928" picture="211675.jpg">Matsumoto Miwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20771" type="appears in" update="2012-03-22">
<rating votes="4">3.28</rating>
<name>Arai Seikuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Arai Seikuu is Azusa`s husband and Iori`s father.</description>
<picture>84403.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22083" picture="58333.jpg">Ishikawa Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20772" type="appears in" update="2012-03-22">
<rating votes="4">2.36</rating>
<name>Arai Azusa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Arai Azusa is Seikuu`s wife and Iori`s mother.</description>
<picture>84404.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1742" picture="20193.jpg">Honda Chieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20773" type="appears in" update="2012-03-22">
<rating votes="8">5.10</rating>
<name>Sawagejou Chou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sawagejou Chou, also known as Sword Hunter, possesses quite a collection of rare and unusual swords, including, his favourite, a long flexible sword he keeps hidden around his waist named urumi, and double bladed sword known as a renbatou. He is only a mediocre opponent when not using the former (despite using a master sheathing technique), but he will still begin battles with regular swords, preferring to toy with his opponents. Only if they prove a true challenge will he reveal his full ability. A native of Osaka, Chou has a very calm and cool exterior, and normally keeps one eye closed when talking, and only opens both eyes when excited in the heat of battle. He speaks with a Kansai-ben accent.
His fighting style is determined by the sword he uses, but he mainly uses the style Garyuorochi. The first is Orochi (Eight-Headed Hydra), in which Chou bounces his sword, Hakujin no Tachi (The Thin blade) on the ground in waves. He uses "Reverse Mid-Air Sheathing" (Sakasa Kuchu Noutou) on Arai Seikuu`s son Iori, threatening to kill Iori to intimidate Seikuu and Azusa, Seikuu`s wife, into revealing the location of the final sword of Shakkuu; Azusa reveals that the sword was placed in a temple as a godsword. Chou took Iori with him and threatened Iori`s life. Kenshin fought Chou with the broken sakabatou; after Seikuu gives Kenshin the sword, Kenshin defeats Chou. After Shishio Makoto`s death, Chou pays Kenshin and his friends a visit to inform them of what happened to members of the Ten Swords after Shishio`s demise, then he goes on to work under Saitou Hajime as a spy and informant.
Chou later appears in the anime when he tries to attack Amakusa but is soundly defeated. In the manga, he later appears in the Jinchuu Arc to help uncover information about Enishi.
Watsuki used no particular model for his personality; Watsuki said that if he had to say one, it would be the stereotyped depictions of people from the Kansai region. Watsuki stressed that Chou is not intended to represent the people from the Kansai region. An assistant from Kansai checked Chou`s accent. Watsuki then had the accent "broken down" so that everyone from Japan can understand it, so therefore Chou`s Kansai accent differs from the actual accent. Watsuki said that he created Chou`s design when he was 20 years old; originally the design was to be used for a space alien. While Watsuki did not use the alien aspect, for him the "horse-headed monkey-face" was "hard to throw out completely," so he used it for Chou. Originally the character design had swept back black, "messy" hair. To give the character more impact as the first Ten Swords member chronicled, Watsuki added a "punk rock" quality to Chou. Watsuki reported that his assistants incorrectly guessed that Galford D. Weller of Samurai Shodown was the model for Chou`s design, while readers incorrectly guessed that Benimaru Nikaido of King of Fighters was the model for Chou; Watsuki added "I guess that due to the punk rock hair it was understandable that readers thought of Benimaru".
Despite being a villain, Chou was a popular character with Rurouni Kenshin readers; Watsuki said that characters with Kansai dialects are "always pretty popular." Watsuki said that he enjoyed drawing Chou and that it would be "a waste" to "finish off" Chou after the conclusion of the Iori story. Therefore Watsuki made Chou appear at later points, though he would be in "a bit more of a neutral position" since he felt it would be strange for Chou to "become friendly with Kenshin and the others." Watsuki added that most of the sketches sent by fans to him with Chou also had Iori in the pictures; Watsuki found this humorous and reported having "quite a laugh."
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>84401.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22155" picture="58111.jpg">Fukumoto Shin`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20774" type="appears in" update="2010-08-14">
<name>Arai Shakku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Arai Shakkuu was the swordsmith who made Kenshin`s sword, since Kenshin hopes to get a replacement for his broken sakabatou.</description>
<picture>53370.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22084" picture="57830.jpg">Katou Tadayoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20775" type="appears in" update="2010-08-14">
<rating votes="1">3.61</rating>
<name>Kurojou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53373.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="173" picture="150067.jpg">Chafuurin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20776" type="appears in" update="2010-08-14">
<rating votes="2">4.78</rating>
<name>Masukami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53374.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20279" picture="52921.jpg">Nakao Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20777" type="appears in" update="2010-08-14">
<rating votes="2">2.78</rating>
<name>Oomime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53375.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="383" picture="24124.jpg">Okohira Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20801" type="appears in" update="2010-08-14">
<rating votes="1">3.61</rating>
<name>Shirojou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53383.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="280" picture="170840.jpg">Kiuchi Hidenobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20802" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="1">4.88</rating>
<name>Kariwa Hen`ya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kariwa Hen`ya, known as Hen`ya the Flighted, aids the attack on Aoi-Ya, the Kyoto secret headquarters of the Oniwabanshuu, with four other Juppongatana members. His battle technique is called Hiku Happa, in which he uses dynamite to lift himself into flight and attack with from above. He can descend to attack the opponent with a blade on his arm and then blow himself back into the air. The power of flight is harnessed because Hen`ya starves himself and is very emaciated; he is so light that the constant uplift from the explosions can easily keep him in the air, and a cape allows him to control his movement. Yahiko defeats Hen`ya by using a shouji door blown up by Hen`ya`s dynamite and then attacks from above. Later on, Henya is used as a government spy because of his aviation abilities.
Hen`ya`s personality was modelled after Matsubayashi Hen`yasai, a swordsman in the Edo period, who possessed "avoidance techniques," which would be called acrobatics in the modern era. Watsuki originally planned to introduce Hen`ya as a tengu during the Megumi arc; Watsuki said the arc was "not as well-planned as it otherwise might have been," so Watsuki could not introduce Hen`ya at that point and instead made Hen`ya into one of the Ten Swords. Originally Watsuki planned for Hen`ya to engage in a mid-air battle with Kenshin, but Watsuki felt that Kenshin would be too strong since Kenshin had gained the secret Hiten Mitsurugi-ryuu technique, so Kenshin made Yahiko the opponent of Hen`ya; Watsuki reported that some readers believed that Yahiko was too strong of an opponent for Hen`ya. For Hen`ya`s design Watsuki used the bat as a model; he added a streamline head and "a little bit" from Jet Link (Cyborg 002) of Cyborg 009. Watsuki intended for Hen`ya to be "monster-like" since, originally none of the Ten Swords aside from Soujirou were supposed to be "lookers." Watsuki reported that some people around him felt that Hen`ya was "still too good-looking," so Watsuki made his body "super-emaciated." Watsuki said Freak of Spawn was also a reference for Hen`ya.</description>
<picture>53384.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2796" picture="23212.jpg">Takemoto Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20803" type="appears in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="1">4.88</rating>
<name>Iwanbou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Iwanbou is a fat oaf who uses his immense size, his strength, and his ability to entrap weapons in his flab. He is armed with small blades worn on his fingertips. He is very stupid, and, apart from taking part in the battle of Aoi-Ya as well as grinning like an utter idiot, he does not say anything, and he does not do anything. He was last seen on a cliff outside of Kyoto. Iwanbou`s only weapons were the metal nails on the end of each of his fingers that could cause damage. It is also noted that Iwanbou`s skin was thick enough to withstand attacks.
As revealed in the Jinchuu, or "Revenge" arc of the manga, Iwanbou is in reality a mechanical puppet, a primitive mech, controlled by Gein, the puppetmaster. Gein reappears in this arc as one of the six comrades in a more dangerous form of Iwanbou and plays a major role in Enishi`s revenge.</description>
<picture>53385.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20423" picture="53731.jpg">Yashima Norito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20806" type="appears in" update="2012-03-22">
<rating votes="4">7.94</rating>
<name>Uonuma Usui</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Uonuma Usui, the "Blind Sword," used to be a swordsman working for the shogunate government. However, in a fight against Shishio Makoto, he was blinded and eventually left to die. He possesses the Shingan, which actually is superhuman hearing that lets him hear another`s heartbeat thus enabling him to sense people around him and detect the emotions of others. This ability is so advanced that it appears to be similar to the sonar of a dolphin or bat. Usui speculates that it was coming close to death and returning to life that is the origin of this ability. Usui and Shishio made a deal upon Usui joining the Ten Swords (Juppongatana): That Usui could try to kill Shishio anytime he gets the chance. Saitou points out that deep down Usui knows he will not be able to kill Shishio (because Shishio came closer to death than Usui and developed an even greater power than the Shingan) and just boasts about killing him to hide that fact from everyone else. Saitou also points out that Shishio knows this too and is just playing along to use Usui. Since Usui cannot kill Shishio, he kills people weaker than himself to boost his ego. According to Chou, he is the second strongest of the Ten Swords.
Usui, a native of the Ryukyu Islands, fights using a short spear with a weighted end - the rochin - to attack, and a tortoise shell - the tinbei - as a shield to deflect attacks and block the enemy`s vision. He dies during a fight with Saituu.
In the anime, he dies when Saitou uses the Gatotsu Zeroshiki (which Saitou originally reserved for Kenshin) and gets impaled above the door behind him. In the manga, he dies in a similar manner but instead, the force of the blow severs his upper body which is impaled above the door.
Usui originated from a chat Watsuki had with one of his assistants. The assistant proposed that Watsuki include a blind swordsman. Originally Watsuki was not interested in the idea, but after Watsuki and the assistant discussed "Shingan," the ability to read emotions of people by listening to their heartbeats and pulses, Watsuki decided to go forward with the idea. Watsuki originally planned to have Usui fight Kenshin while chasing him in the city in a similar manner to the Terminator; the plot went in a different direction, so instead Usui faced against and died at the hands of Saitou at Shishio`s place. Watsuki said that he regretted creating Usui, like he regretted creating Raijuuta, but Usui became more popular than Raijuuta was, so Watsuki concluded "that must also mean" Usui is "stronger." The model for Usui`s design is Tao Pai Pai from Dragon Ball by Akira Toriyama; Watsuki said that Tao Pai Pai made "a strong impression" as he was the first villain to defeat Son Goku, the main character of Dragon Ball. Watsuki said that many readers incorrectly guessed that Lau Chan from Virtua Fighter was Usui`s design model. Watsuki originally planned to give Usui a "tribal" outfit, but after Watsuki saw the "spider-like angel" in Neon Genesis Evangelion, he decided to give Usui an "eyeball-covered costume." Watsuki originally planned to make Usui a "handsome, long-haired type," but when he saw a sketch of the concept, Watsuki believed that it looked too much like Ukyo Tachibana from Samurai Shodown (Samurai Spirits), so Watsuki created the final Usui; the author of Rurouni Kenshin decided that while the final Usui originated from several sources, he believed "it came out pretty well."</description>
<picture>84400.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22081" picture="57828.jpg">Ryuuzanji Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20807" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="4">5.98</rating>
<name>Honjou Kamatari</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A crossdresser, Honjou Kamatari appears like a woman to the degree that he throws Makimachi Misao off completely when Kamatari reveals that he is a man; in the manga, he lifts his kimono to reveal his penis, showing that he is biologically a man. He is homosexual and loves Shishio Makoto deeply, but knows that he will never be loved like Komagata Yumi nor will he ever become as talented as Seta Soujirou, who serves as Shishio`s right hand man.
Kamatari uses a very heavy scythe-like weapon, a reaper, with a chain ball on the end of the weapon; this is called Ogama. Kaoru estimated that the weapon weighs at least 50 kan (30 kilograms or 78 pounds). He practices Honjou-ryuu, his own style of martial arts with his scythe, and three of his special techniques are seen in the series, two of which are named after Benten, the only female of the Buddhist Seven Lucky Gods: Midare Benten (Disheveled Benten) is when the scythe is whipped over his head, and the chain forms a sphere, therefore creating both an offensive and defensive attack. Benten Mawashi (Unwrapping Benten) makes use of his broken scythe by twirling the blade and chain rapidly like the blade of a helicopter. Kaoru and Misao defeat Kamatari. Kamatari tries to commit suicide with a pin, but Misao hits him, preventing him from driving it into his neck. As Kamatari recovers from his injuries, Sawagejo Chou convinces Kamatari that Shishio wanted for Kamatari to live so that the world will know of the work done by Shishio`s faction; Chou in fact made up the story so that Kamatari would not kill himself. Kamatari becomes a spy.
The concept for Kamatari originated from a play on words from Eiichiro Oda, who was one of Watsuki`s assistants at the time. In Japanese okama is a slang word for a homosexual, while the word for a scythe is a kama. Watsuki used ideas from assistants to create the Ten Swords, and the word play lead to the creation of Kamatari. Watsuki said that at first the concept "just wasn`t coming together." In the beginning some of his ideas were "male-appearing on the surface, but personality-wise, will be feminine," "A very erotic and seductive, womanly appearance from the outside, but a manly man on the inside," and "a big macho gay guy." The conflicting ideas for Watsuki became "a big tangle." A friend of Watsuki asked if Kamatari could be "just a `pretty girl` type," leading to the solidification of the character. Watsuki planned for Kamatari to have a "light-hearted and cheerful" personality, but Watsuki found complications when "the more serious side" began to emerge, leading him to feel some regret with the outcome. Watsuki added that when he writes with the character in the future he would have to "keep his outlook sunny" while not compromising the "essential self." Watsuki used Yui Ikari from Neon Genesis Evangelion as the visual model for Kamatari`s face; the author colored the hair black, exposed more of the forehead, and had the back of Kamatari`s hair "flip out as I`ve seen so many high-schoolers do these days." Watsuki added that he then made "Watsuki-style adjustments" to make the design origins less obvious. Watsuki found that the triangular silhouette has influences from Hsien-Ko (Lei-Lei) in Darkstalkers (Vampire Hunter). The type blade that Kamatari uses exists in real life; Watsuki made Kamatari`s blade larger to give it "a real super-impact look." In real life the type of blade is not intended to be used in the way that Kamatari uses it in Rurouni Kenshin.
Watsuki originally believed that Kamatari would be a "garden-variety character," but Kamatari took tenth place in a character popularity poll.</description>
<picture>53389.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="302" picture="17134.jpg">Takeuchi Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20808" type="appears in" update="2011-04-16">
<rating votes="1">4.88</rating>
<name>Saizuchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saizuchi is a cunning small old man who manipulates Fuji and lays out the battle plans for him; his real name is not stated in the series. He believes that his old age makes him the one who is right since he has lived so long. Saizuchi`s talents lie not in battle-abilities, but his proficient use of words: during the Ten Swords attack of Aoi-Ya, Saizuchi attempted to destroy the morale of the Oniwabanshuu by giving a speech as to why it is impossible for them to defeat Fuji and himself. Saizuchi was knocked unconscious when Fuji`s left arm fell on him, after Fuji was defeated by Hiko Seijuurou. Saizuchi later works for the Diplomacy Department in the government for sticky situations after Shishio`s death.
The overall model for Saizuchi is the evil elf who tricks the Jötunn (Frost Giant) in Norse mythology; Watsuki combined the concept with the "image of a giant-robot pilot." In addition Watsuki compared Saizuchi to Kushana in Nausicaä of the Valley of the Wind, using Fuji and the Gold-Soldier in Nausicaä of the Valley of the Wind as a comparison. Originally Watsuki planned for Okina to fight Saizuchi, but he cut the concept because he wanted to maintain the balance of the story and because his "inner story-editor" asked him if anyone would really like to see "two old codgers" fight each other. The design model is "Director-General Luchi of the Akuda Republic" from Purin Purin Monogatari ("Purin Purin Story"), an NHK puppet show. Watsuki said that the large size of Director-General Luchi`s head would "freak me out." Watsuki commented that Luchi`s design was "efficient" since one could tell that he was very intelligent at one glance.
Watsuki added that, of the Ten Swords, Saizuchi got the "short end of the stick" since the character did not have a chance to fully display his intelligence. He described this as the "Senkaku Effect," where the characters with the "best noggins" are not used to their "full potential."</description>
<picture>53390.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4475" picture="26748.jpg">Nishikawa Ikuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20812" type="appears in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Tsubaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Anji raised five children, including Tsubaki, Tasuke, and Gorou, at Juugaku Temple in Ezo, now Hokkaidou. Collectively they are known as "The children of Anji`s temple". The children lost their parents in the Boshin War. Tsubaki, the oldest of the children, looked after the others with Anji. The younger children kept asking Anji when he was going to marry their "sister", Tsubaki. The village chief asked Anji and the children to leave; he feared that there would be retaliation from the Meiji government since Tsubaki`s father, the previous village chief, had sided with the shogun. Anji agreed to leave the following day. However the chief orders Anji`s residence to be burnt to the ground before he had a chance to leave with the children. As a result all five died. In revenge Anji killed the village chief five years later.
Watsuki developed Tsubaki and the children after creating Anji`s past. Originally Watsuki planned to have Anji oversee an entire orphanage as opposed to five children, but he scaled back the number since he felt drawing an entire orphanage would be "a hassle." In restrospect he said that drawing the five was still "a lot of work." He gave Tsubaki a headband to distinguish her from Kamiya Kaoru and Takani Megumi; no other meaning was in the headband. Watsuki saw a headband in a fashion magazine, so he said that one could say the magazine was a model for Tsubaki`s design. The other characters had no models for their designs. Watsuki said that he got letters from readers who believed that Tsubaki "liked" Anji. In response he said that he does not disagree with the assessment. Watsuki also received letters from readers saying that Tsubaki looks like Kyo Kusanagi from The King of Fighters. Watsuki responded by saying "that`s a wrong way to look at it. Let`s both try and be more literal about this, huh? (Heh.)"</description>
<picture>53401.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="692" picture="188445.jpg">Hiramatsu Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20813" type="appears in" update="2011-01-24">
<name>Tasuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Anji raised five children, including Tsubaki, Tasuke, and Gorou, at Juugaku Temple in Ezo, now Hokkaido. Collectively they are known as "The children of Anji`s temple". The children lost their parents in the Boshin War. Tsubaki, the oldest of the children, looked after the others with Anji. The younger children kept asking Anji when he was going to marry their "sister", Tsubaki. The village chief asked Anji and the children to leave; he feared that there would be retaliation from the Meiji government since Tsubaki`s father, the previous village chief, had sided with the shogun. Anji agreed to leave the following day. However the chief orders Anji`s residence to be burnt to the ground before he had a chance to leave with the children. As a result all five died. In revenge Anji killed the village chief five years later.
Watsuki developed Tsubaki and the children after creating Anji`s past. Originally Watsuki planned to have Anji oversee an entire orphanage as opposed to five children, but he scaled back the number since he felt drawing an entire orphanage would be "a hassle." In restrospect he said that drawing the five was still "a lot of work." He gave Tsubaki a headband to distinguish her from Kamiya Kaoru and Takani Megumi; no other meaning was in the headband. Watsuki saw a headband in a fashion magazine, so he said that one could say the magazine was a model for Tsubaki`s design. The other characters had no models for their designs. Watsuki said that he got letters from readers who believed that Tsubaki "liked" Anji. In response he said that he does not disagree with the assessment. Watsuki also received letters from readers saying that Tsubaki looks like Kyo Kusanagi from The King of Fighters. Watsuki responded by saying "that`s a wrong way to look at it. Let`s both try and be more literal about this, huh? (Heh.)"</description>
<picture>53402.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21325" picture="55276.jpg">Akado Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20814" type="appears in" update="2011-01-24">
<name>Gorou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Anji raised five children, including Tsubaki, Tasuke, and Gorou, at Juugaku Temple in Ezo, now Hokkaido. Collectively they are known as "The children of Anji`s temple". The children lost their parents in the Boshin War. Tsubaki, the oldest of the children, looked after the others with Anji. The younger children kept asking Anji when he was going to marry their "sister", Tsubaki. The village chief asked Anji and the children to leave; he feared that there would be retaliation from the Meiji government since Tsubaki`s father, the previous village chief, had sided with the shogun. Anji agreed to leave the following day. However the chief orders Anji`s residence to be burnt to the ground before he had a chance to leave with the children. As a result all five died. In revenge Anji killed the village chief five years later.
Watsuki developed Tsubaki and the children after creating Anji`s past. Originally Watsuki planned to have Anji oversee an entire orphanage as opposed to five children, but he scaled back the number since he felt drawing an entire orphanage would be "a hassle." In restrospect he said that drawing the five was still "a lot of work." He gave Tsubaki a headband to distinguish her from Kamiya Kaoru and Takani Megumi; no other meaning was in the headband. Watsuki saw a headband in a fashion magazine, so he said that one could say the magazine was a model for Tsubaki`s design. The other characters had no models for their designs. Watsuki said that he got letters from readers who believed that Tsubaki "liked" Anji. In response he said that he does not disagree with the assessment. Watsuki also received letters from readers saying that Tsubaki looks like Kyo Kusanagi from The King of Fighters. Watsuki responded by saying "that`s a wrong way to look at it. Let`s both try and be more literal about this, huh? (Heh.)"</description>
<picture>53403.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2792" picture="26717.jpg">Kawata Taeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20815" type="appears in" update="2011-04-19">
<name>Mikan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Anji raised five children, including Tsubaki, Tasuke, and Gorou, at Juugaku Temple in Ezo, now Hokkaidou. Collectively they are known as "The children of Anji`s temple". The children lost their parents in the Boshin War. Tsubaki, the oldest of the children, looked after the others with Anji. The younger children kept asking Anji when he was going to marry their "sister", Tsubaki. The village chief asked Anji and the children to leave; he feared that there would be retaliation from the Meiji government since Tsubaki`s father, the previous village chief, had sided with the shogun. Anji agreed to leave the following day. However the chief orders Anji`s residence to be burnt to the ground before he had a chance to leave with the children. As a result all five died. In revenge Anji killed the village chief five years later.
Watsuki developed Tsubaki and the children after creating Anji`s past. Originally Watsuki planned to have Anji oversee an entire orphanage as opposed to five children, but he scaled back the number since he felt drawing an entire orphanage would be "a hassle." In restrospect he said that drawing the five was still "a lot of work." He gave Tsubaki a headband to distinguish her from Kamiya Kaoru and Takani Megumi; no other meaning was in the headband. Watsuki saw a headband in a fashion magazine, so he said that one could say the magazine was a model for Tsubaki`s design. The other characters had no models for their designs. Watsuki said that he got letters from readers who believed that Tsubaki "liked" Anji. In response he said that he does not disagree with the assessment. Watsuki also received letters from readers saying that Tsubaki looks like Kyo Kusanagi from The King of Fighters. Watsuki responded by saying "that`s a wrong way to look at it. Let`s both try and be more literal about this, huh? (Heh.)"
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>53404.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3133" picture="25830.jpg">Nishihara Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20816" type="appears in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<name>Yohei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Anji raised five children, including Tsubaki, Tasuke, and Gorou, at Juugaku Temple in Ezo, now Hokkaido. Collectively they are known as "The children of Anji`s temple". The children lost their parents in the Boshin War. Tsubaki, the oldest of the children, looked after the others with Anji. The younger children kept asking Anji when he was going to marry their "sister", Tsubaki. The village chief asked Anji and the children to leave; he feared that there would be retaliation from the Meiji government since Tsubaki`s father, the previous village chief, had sided with the shogun. Anji agreed to leave the following day. However the chief orders Anji`s residence to be burnt to the ground before he had a chance to leave with the children. As a result all five died. In revenge Anji killed the village chief five years later.
Watsuki developed Tsubaki and the children after creating Anji`s past. Originally Watsuki planned to have Anji oversee an entire orphanage as opposed to five children, but he scaled back the number since he felt drawing an entire orphanage would be "a hassle." In restrospect he said that drawing the five was still "a lot of work." He gave Tsubaki a headband to distinguish her from Kamiya Kaoru and Takani Megumi; no other meaning was in the headband. Watsuki saw a headband in a fashion magazine, so he said that one could say the magazine was a model for Tsubaki`s design. The other characters had no models for their designs. Watsuki said that he got letters from readers who believed that Tsubaki "liked" Anji. In response he said that he does not disagree with the assessment. Watsuki also received letters from readers saying that Tsubaki looks like Kyo Kusanagi from The King of Fighters. Watsuki responded by saying "that`s a wrong way to look at it. Let`s both try and be more literal about this, huh? (Heh.)"</description>
<picture>53405.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="20821" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<name>Juppongatana</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Juppongatana is an elite group of swordsmen (mostly) that acts as a special attack force. They fight under Shishio Makoto against the Meiji government. Watsuki said that several of his assistants suggested ideas for the Ten Swords and that many of the characters grew out of those ideas. In Watsuki`s original concept, with the exception of Soujirou none of the Ten Swords were intended to be "lookers." Watsuki added Kamatari and Fuji at a later point. When Watsuki believed that one member of the Ten Swords, Saizuchi, had not been used to his full potential, in retrospect Watsuki wondered if having six or seven members of the organization would have been sufficient instead of ten.</description>
<picture>53412.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="20843" type="appears in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="5">4.39</rating>
<name>Fuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fuji is a giant, considered a freak by everyone around him; his real name is not stated in the series. One day he was attacked and almost killed but the old man Saizuchi found him and took him in. The gentle, depressed Fuji was in an ideal state for Saizuchi to manipulate his emotions and turn him into an unbelievable fighter. Saizuchi keeps telling Fuji that he owes him for saving his life and uses that to control him. He was easily defeated by Hiko Seijuurou, though he spared his life, who unlocked his true martial artist`s soul and was the first to look at Fuji as someone other than a monster. Upon capture, the Meiji government assigned him to northern Hokkaido to develop land and act as a defending fighter during times of war.
The idea originated from the God-Soldier in Nausicaä of the Valley of the Wind; Watsuki saw the film and decided that he wanted to create a giant character. Around the same time he wondered if it would "even be interesting" for Kenshin to fight a giant. Watsuki decided to have Fuji fight against Hiko. Watsuki also received inspiration from Jötunn (Frost Giant), a Norse folktale in which a giant is revealed to have a compassionate heart; Watsuki used this idea with Fuji. The design had inspiration from the first Neon Genesis Evangelion Originally the face originated from Eva #2. The assistants believed the design looked too similar. One then-assistant of Rurouni Kenshin, Hiroyuki Takei, suggested a `skull-like riff on "Eva#1."` Watsuki added the skull biting the helmet anchor rope feature, finishing Fuji`s helmet face. Watsuki tried "very hard" to keep the face from being too similar to the designs of Neon Genesis Evangelion. Fuji`s actual face originates from Dogura Magura of Arabian Lamp-Lamp by Takeshi Obata; Watsuki wanted to work with the concept of a "monstrous character who`s somehow still good looking," which Watsuki says Dogura Magura is "the epitome of" the concept. Due to the "tight" schedule of the Fuji chapters Watsuki said that he had insufficient time to revise the design, resulting in "an essentially unoriginal face." Watsuki reported that people correctly guessed the influence of Fuji`s real face upon seeing it.
When Watsuki told his editor about the giant character idea, the editor asked "Are you sure?" as the editor was concerned that the character was too large. Watsuki`s assistants and friends told the author of Rurouni Kenshin that the idea "sound(ed) fun—do it, do it!" Watsuki decided to create the character; in retrospect he said that the "gamble" "seems to have paid off, so, I`m pleased."</description>
<picture>53451.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20846" type="appears in" update="2010-08-15">
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<name>Yanosuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yanosuke is Seta`s sibling.</description>
<picture>53471.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20322" picture="186181.jpg">Shiga Katsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20914" type="appears in" update="2010-08-18">
<name>Sekihoutai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Sekihoutai is a group of farmers and merchants who fought for the Ishin Shishi during the Meiji Revolution.</description>
</character>
<character id="20940" type="appears in" update="2010-08-19">
<rating votes="4">3.54</rating>
<name>Sekihara Sae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sekihara Sae is the owner of the Shirobeko restaurant in Kyoto and the twin sister of http://anidb.net/ch20113 [Tae]. In the manga Sae forces http://anidb.net/ch6618 [Yahiko] to wear a ribbon in his hair when he works at the restaurant.</description>
<picture>53626.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="508" picture="140061.jpg">Shimamoto Sumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20966" type="appears in" update="2010-08-21">
<name>Marcus Murakami</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53674.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1814" picture="20690.jpg">Saikachi Ryuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20972" type="appears in" update="2010-08-21">
<name>Shin-ouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53681.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3940" picture="54324.jpg">Tominaga Miina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20974" type="appears in" update="2010-08-21">
<rating votes="1">3.61</rating>
<name>Inagi Ukyou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53683.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="469" picture="17418.jpg">Umezu Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20975" type="appears in" update="2010-08-22">
<rating votes="5">6.12</rating>
<name>Amakusa Shougo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Amakusa Shougo, real name Muto Shougo, was taught Hiten Mitsurugi by his uncle. Shougo is also a Christian, and sought revenge for Christianity, and to make the Holy Land, after his parents were killed for their beliefs, when Christians were persecuted during the Shogunate. He mastered "God Speed" by the age of 14, and according to Kenshin, had surpassed even God Speed. His followers believe that he is the "Son of God". Some of his "miracles" were really just due to his education in Western Medicine, and other sciences.</description>
<picture>53695.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21351" picture="175696.jpg">Inoue Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20982" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="5">6.39</rating>
<name>Magdalia Sayo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lady Magdalia, real name Sayo Muto, is Shogo Amakusa`s younger sister. She serves as a holy mother to their crowd of followers and a teacher to the young children. She has suffered from consumption ever since she was a child (which she perhaps obtained from her mother, who suffered the same illness). She is often seen accompanied by Shozo, a childhood friend whom she and her brother saved from persecution. Magdalia is a devout Christian and believes in everything that her brother says and does, which leads to her and Sanosuke Sagara having clashing personalities. Her most prized possession is her mother`s holy medallion which is lost and eventually returned to her by Sanosuke. She comes to respect him and wishes that she had met someone like him earlier in life so that she could have had a more open heart to those outside her faith. She is shot as she protects the Dutch consul, who can save her townspeople, and refuses to be treated in the hope that the people she cares for will be saved. She dies in Sanosuke`s arms after telling him her real name. Shogo promises to make her dreams of a land of equality and peace a reality.</description>
<picture>53711.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="167" picture="16972.jpg">Kasahara Hiroko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20983" type="appears in" update="2010-08-22">
<rating votes="1">6.28</rating>
<name>Rorenzo Shouzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rorenzo Shouzou is Sayo`s bodyguard.</description>
<picture>53712.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="366" picture="17212.jpg">Gouda Hozumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20985" type="appears in" update="2010-08-22">
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<name>Nishida Hyouei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53714.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2246" picture="186215.jpg">Mikimoto Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20987" type="appears in" update="2010-08-22">
<rating votes="1">4.88</rating>
<name>Elstien</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53717.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3276" picture="24272.jpg">Nakagi Ryuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20988" type="appears in" update="2010-08-22">
<rating votes="1">6.28</rating>
<name>Kaiou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53718.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="601" picture="165793.jpg">Nakamura Hidetoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20989" type="appears in" update="2010-08-22">
<rating votes="1">4.88</rating>
<name>Santou Shoubu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53719.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2041" picture="215974.jpg">Ookura Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20991" type="appears in" update="2010-08-22">
<rating votes="1">3.61</rating>
<name>Guspal Genemon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53720.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3140" picture="24125.jpg">Mori Norihisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20992" type="appears in" update="2010-08-22">
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<name>Mutou Tokisada</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mutou Tokisada is Sayo and Shougo`s father.</description>
<picture>53721.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="297" picture="233915.jpg">Ootsuka Houchuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20993" type="appears in" update="2010-08-22">
<rating votes="2">4.13</rating>
<name>Tsuruyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53722.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="404" picture="151682.jpg">Takashima Gara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21021" type="appears in" update="2010-08-23">
<rating votes="2">5.18</rating>
<name>Ogawa Heizou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53781.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="604" picture="154161.jpg">Ogata Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21022" type="appears in" update="2010-08-23">
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<name>Anzai Juroubei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53783.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3394" picture="24430.jpg">Shibamoto Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21023" type="appears in" update="2010-08-23">
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<name>Shinta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53784.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1990" picture="171387.jpg">Ishibashi Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21024" type="appears in" update="2010-08-23">
<name>Sutezou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53785.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6928" picture="211675.jpg">Matsumoto Miwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21028" type="appears in" update="2010-08-24">
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<name>Higashiyama Ryuusaburou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53825.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="468" picture="17383.jpg">Kikuchi Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21040" type="appears in" update="2010-08-25">
<name>Kamiya Kasshin-ryuu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="21041" type="appears in" update="2010-08-25">
<rating votes="2">1.58</rating>
<name>Okuma Daigorou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53869.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21052" type="appears in" update="2010-08-26">
<name>Katsu Kaishuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53900.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20549" picture="53966.jpg">Yagi Kousei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21053" type="appears in" update="2010-08-26">
<rating votes="1">4.88</rating>
<name>Katsu Itsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53902.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2068" picture="28743.jpg">Iwao Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21054" type="appears in" update="2010-08-26">
<rating votes="1">4.88</rating>
<name>Ookubo Tetsuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53903.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="455" picture="17356.jpg">Matsumoto Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21055" type="appears in" update="2010-08-26">
<rating votes="1">3.61</rating>
<name>Shibata</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53905.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39" picture="16629.jpg">Mugihito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21056" type="appears in" update="2010-08-26">
<name>Tokugawa Yoshinobu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53907.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6848" picture="86100.jpg">Ooguro Kazuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21069" type="appears in" update="2010-08-27">
<name>Hans Hakase</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54011.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3256">Jinnai Tatsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21070" type="appears in" update="2010-08-27">
<name>Ludel Koushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54013.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5293" picture="186241.jpg">Ii Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21071" type="appears in" update="2010-08-27">
<name>Melders Chuui</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54015.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4494" picture="245665.jpg">Yamaji Kazuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21072" type="appears in" update="2010-08-27">
<rating votes="1">4.88</rating>
<name>Schneider Shoui</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54016.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22157" picture="58112.jpg">Takeoka Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21073" type="appears in" update="2010-08-27">
<name>Lentz Shoui</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54017.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21074" type="appears in" update="2014-10-01">
<rating votes="1">6.28</rating>
<name>Moriya Misanagi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54018.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="491" picture="38232.jpg">Yokoyama Chisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21085" type="appears in" update="2010-08-28">
<name>Kuro Kishi Dan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="21086" type="appears in" update="2010-08-28">
<name>Sanada Shinobi Gun</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="21087" type="appears in" update="2010-08-28">
<rating votes="1">3.61</rating>
<name>Kaita</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54030.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="296" picture="17124.jpg">Nishimura Tomohiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21088" type="appears in" update="2010-08-28">
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<name>Ren</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54034.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4926" picture="25983.jpg">Nishikawa Takanori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21089" type="appears in" update="2010-08-28">
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<name>Zan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54035.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="21090" type="appears in" update="2010-08-28">
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<name>Baku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54037.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="21107" type="appears in" update="2010-08-28">
<rating votes="2">1.94</rating>
<name>Saeki Yunoshin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54064.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6848" picture="86100.jpg">Ooguro Kazuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21109" type="appears in" update="2010-08-28">
<rating votes="2">2.68</rating>
<name>Jinpuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54069.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21110" type="appears in" update="2010-08-28">
<name>Reisui</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54071.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4586" picture="21115.jpg">Yuuki Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21118" type="appears in" update="2010-08-29">
<name>Horinaka Tadashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54122.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3285" picture="193568.jpg">Kimotsuki Kaneta</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="722" update="2019-09-25">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="29">6.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">伝説の美剣士... 愛ゆえに闘う男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Handsome Swordsman of Legend</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Battosai Himura</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Battousai Himura, O Lendário Esquartejador</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ตำนานนักรบซามูไร การต่อสู้เพื่อความรัก</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Yakışıklı Kılıç Ustası Efsanesi / Aşkı İçin Savaşan Bir Adam</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Densetsu no Bikenshi... Ai Yue ni Tatakau Otoko</title>
<summary>A mysterious wanderer known as Kenshin is taken at the Kamiya Kasshin Dojo, a martial arts school run by a young woman named Kaoru.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>647977</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="723" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-01-17</airdate>
<rating votes="20">6.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガキ侍 スッた!モンだ!で門下生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kid Samurai</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Yahiko Miyojin</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Yahiko Myoujin, O Aluno Rebelde</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ลูกศิษย์นักล้วงกระเป๋า</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Genç Samuray / Büyük Bir Zorluk ve Yeni Bir Öğrenci</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gaki-zamurai Sutta! Mon Da! de Monkasei</title>
<summary>Following an encounter with a young pickpocket named Yahiko, Kaoru risks her own freedom to gain his from some local gangsters.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>647979</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="724" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">心眼をとらえた狼・炸裂する牙突零式!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Wolf Destroys the Shingan</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le pouvoir de Gatotsu</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">O Lobo Que Caçou os Olhos de Uma Alma</title>
<title xml:lang="th">สุนัขจิ้งจองตาทิพย์ระเบิดพลังแรงแค้น</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Kurt, Kalbin Gözünü Yok Ediyor: Gatotsu`nun Vahşi Saldırısı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shingan o Toraeta Ookami: Sakuretsu Suru Gatotsu Zero Shiki!</title>
<summary>In his defeat of Usui, Saito exposes the blind warrior`s plot to kill Shishio. And while Kaoru, Yahiko and Misao are preparing to defend themselves from an ambush, Kenshin readies for his fight against Aoshi.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648063</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="725" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">62</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">京都... 刻まれた記憶・想いを馳せた出発</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kyoto, the Engraved Memory</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Souvenir de Kyoto</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">As Memórias de Tokyo</title>
<title xml:lang="th">เกียวโตเมืองแห่งอดีตและความทรงจำ</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Kyoto, Hafızalara Kazınan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyouto... Kizamareta Kioku: Omoi o Haseta Shuppatsu</title>
<summary>As Kenshin is nursing the wounds sustained in his fight with Shishio, Kaoru prepares the Peace Force for their return home.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648089</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="726" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-06-26</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雷十太の野望・禁じられた王国の幻想</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Raijuta`s Ambition</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les ambitions de Raijuta</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">A Fantasia do Reino Esquecido</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ท่านไรจูดะต้องการสร้างเมืองใหม่</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Raijuta`nın Hırsı / Yasak Krallık Fantezisi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Raijuuta no Yabou: Kinjirareta Oukoku no Gensou</title>
<summary>While on vacation at the home of Dr. Gensai`s niece, Kenshin and company attracts the attention of a wealthy but arrogant boy who wants to learn the art of swordfighting.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648003</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="727" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">涙を勇気にかえて! 神谷薫が選んだ道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Change Tears to Courage</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">En route pour Kyoto !</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">A Kaoru Vai a Edo</title>
<title xml:lang="th">เปลี่ยนน้ำตาให้เป็นความกล้า ทางเลือกของคามิยะ คาโอรุ</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Göz Yaşını Cesarete Dönüştür: Kaoru Kamiya`nın Seçimi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Namida o Yuuki ni Kaete! Kamiya Kaoru ga Eranda Michi</title>
<summary>Following Kenshin`s departure from the dojo, everyone, and especially Kaoru, are sad at being left behind. And while Saito tries to dissuade Sanosuke from following him, Megumi sends Kaoru to deliver some medicine that will aid in Kenshin`s fight
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648029</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="728" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-04-30</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">激突! 二重[ふたえ]の極み・唸る佐之助の拳</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crash! The Lethal Punch, Futae no Kiwami</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Coup de poing mortel</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">O Conflito</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ประทะพลังหม้ดซาโนสุเกะโลกมิรู้ลืม</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Çarpışma! Öldürücül Yumruk, Futae no Kiwami: Sonasuke Çığlıklarının Yumruğu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitotsu! Futae no Kiwami: Unaru Sanosuke no Kobushi</title>
<summary>As Shishio prepares for battle, a henchmen suggests a plan to weaken Kenshin and his forces, ridding them of any opposition once and for all. As the moment of truth draws near, Sanosuke is pitted against Anji.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648059</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="729" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">60</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="11">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勝利を許されし者・志々雄 対 剣心 終幕!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Man who is Chosen for Victory</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Shishio contre Kenshin</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Shishio Contra Kenshin</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ปิดฉากการต่อสู้ชิชิโอะหรือเคนชินใครจะชนะ</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Zafer İçin Seçilen Adam</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shouri o Yurusareshi Mono: Shishio tai Kenshin Shuumaku!</title>
<summary>Kenshin`s final effort to win the ultimate battle ends with Shishio destroying himself. But in the wake of Samurai X`s victory, Shishio`s closest aide vows revenge.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648085</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="730" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-06-12</airdate>
<rating votes="13">4.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢に向かって飛べ! 砲弾娘マリモの冒険</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fly to Your Dreams</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Marimo, le canon humain</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Marimo - A Bala Humana</title>
<title xml:lang="th">จงบินไปตามความฝันเถอะสาวน้อยเมอริโม</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Hayallerine Doğru Uç / İnsan Topu Marimo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume ni Mukatte Tobe! Houdan Musume Marimo no Bouken</title>
<summary>Samurai X protects a circus ringmaster and his talented human cannonball daughter from the threats of a jealous competitor.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>647999</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="731" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-11-13</airdate>
<rating votes="16">9.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">復讐の悪鬼・志々雄真実の謀略</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Devil of Vengeance</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La revanche démoniaque</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">A Vingança de um Demónio</title>
<title xml:lang="th">แผนแก้แค้นของปีศาจร้ายชิชิโอะ มาโคโตะ</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">İntikam Almaya Gelen Şeytan: Makoto Shishio`nun Oyunu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukushuu no Akki: Shishio Makoto no Bouryaku</title>
<summary>After stopping a fatal battle with Hajime Saito, a top government official asks Kenshin`s help in killing a shadowy assassin who`s threatening the future of the regime.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648025</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="732" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">翔ぶが如く! 戦艦煉獄 出航を阻止せよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">As if to Fly</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Comme un oiseau !</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Voando Contra o Tempo</title>
<title xml:lang="th">หยุดเรือรบเรนโกกคุให้ได้</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Uçarcasına: Savaş Gemilerini Durdurun!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tobu ga Gotoku! Senkan Rengoku Shukkou o Soshi seyo</title>
<summary>Reunited with Sanosuke, Kenshin lays plans to stop Shishio from burning Tokyo to create the confusion he needs to overthrow the government. But Shishio harbors a surprise with his newest weapon, an ironclad battleship hidden inside another
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648055</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="733" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-05-22</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">炎の暗殺集団, 神風隊走る!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Assassination Group of Five (Part 1)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Deux assassins légendaires</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Dois Lendários Esquartejadores</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ไล่ล่าเอามาเป็นพวก</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">İki Efsane Katil / İki Efsane İşkenceci</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Honoo no Ansatsu Shuudan, Jinpuu Tai Hashiru!</title>
<summary>A group radicals intent on assassinating political leaders attempt to recruit a local teacher into their cause. After finding that Heihachiro is a former foe who`s now dedicated his life to helping children, Kenshin steps in to repel the assassins.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>647995</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="734" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-03-12</airdate>
<rating votes="9">9.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">生と死の間で! 奥義・天翔龍閃[あまかけるりゅうのひらめき]の会得</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Between Life and Death</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La technique de succession</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Conhecer o Segredo</title>
<title xml:lang="th">อาโอชิและชิชิโอะ</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Ölüm ile Yaşam Arasında: Nihai Tekniğin Ustası!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sei to Shi no Hazama de! Ougi: Amakakeru Ryuu no Hirameki no Etoku</title>
<summary>As Kenshin struggles to learn, Sijuro teaches him the most secret of his fighting techniques. And though Kenshin doesn`t want to kill, it`s inevitable if he is to beat Shishio. Meanwhile, Sanosuke is arrested during his search for Samurai X.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648051</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="735" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-03-06</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最強の忍び軍団・恐怖の御庭番衆!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Strongest Group of Ninjas</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les Oniwaban Shu</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">A Poderosa Organização Oni</title>
<title xml:lang="th">จอมพลังโอนิวะบังชู ชิกิโจ</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">En Güçlü Ninja Grubu / Korkunç Oniwaban Grubu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikyou no Shinobi Gundan: Kyoufu no Oniwabanshu!</title>
<summary>Though her medical knowledge has saved Yahiko`s life, Sansosuke suspects Megumi of producing the opium responsible for a close friend`s death.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>647983</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="736" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-05-08</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">めざせ横綱! 虎丸のどすこい奮戦記</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Going for the Grand Championship</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Toramaru le Sumotori</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Toramaru - O Lutador Sumo</title>
<title xml:lang="th">พลังอันยิ่งใหญ่ของโทระมารู</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Büyük Şampiyona Mücadelesi / Toramaru`nun Sumo Savaşı!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mezase Yokozuna! Toramaru no Dosukoi Funsenki</title>
<summary>After jealous harassment forces an aspiring young man out of a sumo wrestling school, Kaoru steps in to take over his training.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>647991</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="737" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">58</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">時代は志々雄を選ぶのか? 剣心最大の危機!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Age Chooses Shishio?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Moment de gloire pour Shishio</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Será Que Esta Era Escolheu Shishio?</title>
<title xml:lang="th">โชคชะตาจะเลือกชิชิโอะอันตรายเคนชิน</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Seçilen Shishio Mu Olacak?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jidai wa Shishio o Erabu no ka? Kenshin Saidai no Kiki!</title>
<summary>In their long awaited battle, Kenshin and Shishio compare ideologies as well as fighting techniques. But once Shishio uses gunpowder to gain the upper hand, it looks like Samurai X is doomed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648081</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="738" update="2019-09-25">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-10-31</airdate>
<rating votes="13">8.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新たなる血戦への序曲・迫り来る狼の影!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Prelude to the Impending Fight</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le retour du Loup</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">O Regresso do Lobo</title>
<title xml:lang="th">การนองเลือดครั้งใหม่หมาป่าแห่งมิบุปรากฎตัว</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Dövüşe Sayılı Günler Kala: Kurdun Gölgesi Yaklaşıyor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aratanaru Kessen e no Jokyoku: Semarikuru Ookami no Kage!</title>
<summary>A persistent nightmare comes true when Kenshin`s old enemy, the former leader of a shadowy anti-Royalist organization, is hired to assassinate him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648021</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="739" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">飛天御剣流の奥義! 師匠比古清十郎との再会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ultimate Technique of the Hiten Mitsurugi Style</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le maître de Kenshin</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">O Reencontro Com o Mestre</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ปรมจารย์เซย์จูโร่เพลงดาบล่องนภาขั้นสุดยอด</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Hiten-Mitsurugi Stilinin Nihai Tekniği: Danışman Seijuro Hiko ile Buluşma</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hiten Mitsurugi Ryuu no Ougi! Shishou Hiko Seijuurou to no Saikai</title>
<summary>To prepare for Shishio, Kenshin asks a former teacher to help him master the last of his fighting techniques. However, Kenshin is distracted when Kaoru and Yahiko finally catch up with him after their long journey.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648047</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="740" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-02-21</airdate>
<rating votes="16">8.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">月下の死闘・愛する人を守れ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Deathmatch Under the Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bataille au clair de lune</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Luta ao Luar</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ผลจาการช่วยคนรัก</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Ay Işığı Altında Ölümcül Karşılaşma / Sevdiğin İnsanı Koru</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekka no Shitou: Ai Suru Hito o Mamore!</title>
<summary>After kidnapping Kaoru, the ruthless Jin-nai Udo draws Kenshin into the fight he`s been seeking for years. Though Kenshin tries to resist, Jin-nai`s powerful spell over Kaoru leaves him no other choice.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648367</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="741" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらば最強の男たち! 光と闇の激突</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fare Well, the Strongest Men</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ombre et lumière</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">O Confronto Entre a Luz e a Escuridão</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ฝ่ายธรรมะย่อมชนะอธรม</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">En Güçlü Adama Veda / Işık ve Gölgenin Çarpışması</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saraba Saikyou no Otoko-tachi! Hikari to Yami no Gekitotsu</title>
<summary>Kenshin defeats a local mob`s most powerful fighter, only to then face a gang leader who`s determined to spread powerful new guns across Japan.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>647987</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="742" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">56</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">極限の勝負! 瞬天殺 対 天翔龍閃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Duel With an Extreme Moment</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Combat ultime</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">A Batalha Final</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ดาบมังกรทะยานฟ้า</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Ekstrem Bir An İle Düello</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyokugen no Shoubu! Shuntensatsu tai Amakakeru Ryuu no Hirameki</title>
<summary>In the face of Kenshin`s probing questions, Souijuro`s concentration is broken. In defeat, the young assassin returns his prized sword to Shishio, warning him of the danger that lays ahead.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648077</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="743" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-09-04</airdate>
<rating votes="11">4.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">稲妻の化身! 誇り高き謎の女海賊, 朱羅</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lightning Incarnate</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Shura, la fille pirate</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Shura - A Misteriosa Mulher Pirata</title>
<title xml:lang="th">โจรสลัดสาวผู้หยิ่งในศักดิ์ศรีชูรา</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Yıldırımın Vücut Bulmuş Hali / Shura, Gizemli Kadın Korsan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inazuma no Keshin! Hokoritakaki Nazo no Onna Kaizoku, Shura</title>
<summary>After Kenshin`s kidnapping, a bond begins to develop between him and Shura. However, while Shura is confident in the loyalty of her crew, the profits to be made from dealing opium draws them into a mutinous plan.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648017</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="744" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-02-07</airdate>
<rating votes="15">7.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">逆刃刀対斬馬刀・闘いの果てに!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Reversed-Blade Sword vs. The Zanbatou</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Lame inversée contre Zanba</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">A Espada Zanza</title>
<title xml:lang="th">การประลองฝีมือริมฝั่งน้ำ</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Ters Tarafı Keskin Kılıç ve Zanbatou Karşı Karşıya / Savaştan Ötesi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakabatou tai Zanbatou: Tatakai no Hate ni!</title>
<summary>After accepting Sanosuke`s challenge, Kenshin encourages him to release his anger towards the corrupt Royalist forces.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648363</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="745" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">54</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">飛天対縮地! 宗次郎 天賦の能力[ちから]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hiten Versus Shukuchi</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Shukuchi</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">O Céu Contra a Terra</title>
<title xml:lang="th">เทพเจ้าสายฟ้าแลบดาบสวรรค์โซจิโร</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Hilten İle Shukuchi Karşı Karşıya</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hiten tai Shukuchi! Soujirou Tenpu no Chikara</title>
<summary>As Sanosuke looks on, Kenshin goes to battle with Souijuro, the emotionless assassin responsible for breaking his sword. Though Shishio is confident of the young warrior`s ability, Kenshin may be able to win without having to resort to killing.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648073</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="746" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="13">8.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真夜中の戦い! 左之助対剣心ふたたび</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Midnight Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Kenshin vs. Sanosuke : la revanche</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Kenshin contra Sanosuke</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ความในใจของซาโนะ</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Gece Yarısı Savaşı: Kenshin, Yeniden Sanosuke`ye Karşı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mayonaka no Tatakai! Sanosuke tai Kenshin Futatabi</title>
<summary>Following a lavish party at the dojo, Sanosuke can no longer resist joining his old army troop`s plot to punish the government. However, in an effort to stop them, Kenshin is forced to take on Sanosuke
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648013</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="747" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-01-24</airdate>
<rating votes="19">7.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">哀しみの剣士・過去を斬る男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Swordsman of Sorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Celui qui a effacé le passé</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">O Homem que Matou o Passado</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ดาบอำมหิตจิตใจอ่อน</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Kederli Kılıç Ustası / Geçmişini Silen Adam</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanashimi no Kenshi: Kako o Kiru Otoko</title>
<summary>After reining in some renegade police officers, Kenshin is recognized as the Samurai whose bravery helped establish the Meiji Era and is asked to rejoin the army.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>647981</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="748" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-02-12</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">逆刃刀を作った男・新井赤空最後の一振り!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Creator of the Reverse Blade</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le dernier sabre de Shakku</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">A Última Espada de Gume Invertido</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ดาบเล่มสุดท้ายของอารายซักคูผู้สร้างดาบสลับคม</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Ters Tarafı Keskin Kılıcın Yaratıcısı: Shakku Arai`nin Son Hamlesi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakabatou o Tsukutta Otoko: Arai Shakuu Saigo no Hitofuri!</title>
<summary>As the showdown with Shishio approaches, Misao finds someone who could produce the sword Kenshin needs, only to be is disappointed when Shakkuu Arai refuses
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648043</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="749" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-06-18</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">奇跡を呼び起こせ! 葵屋の攻防</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To make a Miracle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`attaque de l`Aoya</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">O Acordar de Um Milagre</title>
<title xml:lang="th">มหัศจรรย์มีจริงที่สำนักอาโออิ</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Mucize Yaratmak: Aoiya Savaşı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiseki o Yobiokose! Aoiya no Koubou</title>
<summary>After Yahiko`s fighting skills are stretched to the limit during his defeat of Shishio`s warrior, it`s now up to Kaoru to enter a battle of her own.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648069</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="750" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="12">2.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">初乗り! 暴走陸蒸気びっくり大事件</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Danger on a Runaway Locomotive</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Premier voyage en train</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">O Assalto ao Comboio</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ปล้นรถไฟ</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Kaçış Lokomotifindeki Tehlike / Kaçış Lokomotifindeki Sürpriz Olay</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hatsunori! Bousou Okajouki Bikkuri Daijiken</title>
<summary>During a train trip to Yokohama, Kenshin and his friends must save a wealthy English passenger from being robbed by thieves
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648009</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="751" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-01-29</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">衝撃! 折れた逆刃刀・天剣の宗次郎対剣心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shock! Reverse Blade Sword Broken</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le sabre divin de Sojiro</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Sojiro Contra Kenshin</title>
<title xml:lang="th">การประลองระหว่างเคนชินกับดาบสวรรค์เซอจิโร ดาบสลับคมหัก</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Şok! Ters Tarafı Keskin Kılıç Kırıldı: Sojiro`nun Ruhu ile Kenshin Karşılaşıyor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shougeki! Oreta Sakabatou: Tenken no Soujirou tai Kenshin</title>
<summary>Following Kenshin`s defeat of the giant Senkaku, Shishio pits him against the young, emotionless assassin responsible for the Home Minister`s murder.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648039</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="752" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-06-04</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">約束を果たす時・蒼紫と剣心の再戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Promised Time has Come</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Promesses à tenir</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Tempo de Honrar a Promessa</title>
<title xml:lang="th">กลับมาทวงสัญญาศึกนี้ระหว่างเคนชินกับอาโอชิ</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Söz Verilen Vakit Geldi: Aoshi ve Kenshin Yeniden Dövüşüyor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yakusoku o Hatasu Toki: Aoshi to Kenshin no Saisen!</title>
<summary>Kenshin sets out to honor his promises to both fight Aoshi and bring him back alive to Misao.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648065</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="753" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真古流の復活! 嵐を呼ぶ究極の殺人剣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Revival of the Shinko Style</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La résurrection de l`école Shinko</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">A Espada Mortífera Estilo Shinko</title>
<title xml:lang="th">การประทะกับชินโกริวซึ่งมีพลังมหาศาล</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Shinko Stilinin Yeniden Doğuşu / Ölümcül Kılıç – Shinko Stilinin – Yeniden Doğuşu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinko Ryuu no Fukkatsu! Arashi o Yobu Kyuukyoku no Satsujin Ken</title>
<summary>Though Kenshin tries to warn him of the bad influence, Yutaro continues to believe in Raijuta, unaware that the renegade is using him plot his revolution. So, when he`s told that the government is out to stop him, Yutaro sneaks away to warn Raijuta.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648005</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="754" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-01-15</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">奪われた村・襲いかかる志々雄の魔の手!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Conquered Village</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le village de Shingetsu</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">A Aldeia Roubada</title>
<title xml:lang="th">หมู่บ้านที่ถูกทอดทิ้ง ญี่ปุ่นในอุดมคติของชิชิโอะ</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Fethedilen Köy: Shishio`nun Ellerinin Kavradığı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ubawareta Mura: Osoikakaru Shishio no Ma no Te!</title>
<summary>When he and Misao come across a village terrorized by forces loyal to Shishio, Kenshin enlists Saito to help liberate it from the evil gang
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648035</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="755" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-12-11</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最強の称号を掴むまで! 蒼紫の新たなる闘い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">For the Title of Strongest</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le retour d`Aoshi</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">A Luta do Aoshi</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">En Güçlü Olarak Anılmak İçin: Aoshi`nin Yeni Çatışması</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikyou no Shougou o Tsukamu made! Aoshi no Aratanaru Tatakai</title>
<summary>In the wake of Samurai X`s departure, everyone at the dojo is anxious to join the battle against Shishio. With Sanosuke, Kaoru and Yahiko in pursuit, Kenshin encounters Misao, a young girl who also happens to be a clever thief.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648031</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="756" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-05-14</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">救世[ぐぜ]への再生・安慈の新たなる出発</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reborn to Salvation</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le salut d`Anji</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">O Recomeço de Anji</title>
<title xml:lang="th">อันจิคนใหม่กลับมาเพื่อกู้โลก</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Kurtuluş İçin Yeniden Doğuş: Anji`nin Yeni Yaşamının Başlangıcı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Guze e no Saisei: Anji no Aratanaru Shuppatsu</title>
<summary>During his battle with Sanosuke, the fallen monk recalls how his hatred was born during an anti-Buddhist movement.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648061</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="757" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">61</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">残された十本刀・生きてゆくための選択</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Juppongatana who Remain</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le choix de la vie</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">O Juppongatana</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ทางเลือกของเหล่าดาบทั้งสิบที่เหลือ</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Geriye Kalan Juppongatana</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nokosareta Juppongatana: Ikite Yuku Tame no Sentaku</title>
<summary>Following Shishio`s defeat, his remaining allies put their fate in the hands of the government. While Kenshin is reunited with his Peace Force, the vanquished Shishio vows to take over Hell.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648087</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="758" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">走れ! 弥彦・逆刃刀を取り返せ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Get Back the Reverse-Blade Sword</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Yahiko et l`épée à lame inversée</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">A Espada de Gume Invertido</title>
<title xml:lang="th">วิ่งเข้ายาฮิโกะ รีบไปตามเอาดาบสลับคมคืนมา</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Koş Yahiko! Ters Tarafı Keskin Kılıcı Ele Geçir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hashire! Yahiko: Sakabatou o Torikaese!</title>
<summary>After stopping a restaurant robbery, Yahiko`s boastfulness lands him in trouble with Kenshin`s old foe, Gohei Hiruma. And once Yahiko agrees to a fight, Gohei uses the opportunity to steal Samurai X`s Reverse Edged Sword.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648001</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="759" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="12">8.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">届かぬ想い...... 剣心の旅立ち!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Wish Unrequited</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`impensable</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Pensamentos Impossíveis</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ความในใจที่ส่งไปไม่ถึง จำใจจาก</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Yerine Gelmeyen Bir Dilek: Kenshin Ayrılıyor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Todokanu Omoi...... Kenshin no Tabidachi!</title>
<summary>While preparing to give his decision on helping to kill Shishio, Kenshin learns of the Home Minister`s murder.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648027</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="760" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">煉獄炎上! 志々雄真実の命運</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Purgatory Bursts into Flames</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le purgatoire</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">A Destruição do Reingoko</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ทะเลเพลิงบนเรนโกกคุ โชคชะตาของชิชิโอะ</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Araf Alevler Altında: Makoto Shishio`nun Kaderi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rengoku Enjou! Shishio Makoto no Meiun</title>
<summary>After Kenshin, Saito and Sanosuke destroy his battleship, Shishio issues his challenge for a final confrontation. And following Misao`s defeat of the blind Samurai, Usui, Kenshin vows to spare the life of her mentor, Aoshi.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648057</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="761" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-06-05</airdate>
<rating votes="12">8.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇気ある誓い! 燃えよ秘剣・紫電の太刀</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Assassination Group of Five (Part 2)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`épée secrète de Shinden</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">A Espada Secreta de Shiden</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ทำดีย่อมได้ดีทำชั่วย่อมได้รับผลกรรม</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">İçten Bir Vaat: Shiden`in Gizli Kılıç Tekniği</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuuki Aru Chikai! Moeyo Hiken: Shiden no Tachi</title>
<summary>After saving Heihachiro`s life, Kenshin sets out to stop the teacher`s misguided former student from being used as a pawn in a game of political corruption.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>647997</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="762" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-03-19</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">怒濤の決戦・最強集団十本刀集結!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Decisive Battle Like Violent Waters</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les Juppongatana</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">O Grupo Mais Poderoso</title>
<title xml:lang="th">แผนร้ายของชิชิโอ</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Sert Sulara Benzeyen Bir Savaş: En Güçlü Juppongatana Birliği</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dotou no Kessen: Saikyou Shuudan Juppongatana Shuuketsu!</title>
<summary>While waiting in jail, Sanosuke learns of Shishio`s plan to overthrow the government by recruiting a deadly band of Samurai, including the blind warrior Usui, to defeat Kenshin and Saito
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648053</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="763" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-05-15</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">小さな命を救え! 美人女医・恵の挑戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To Save a Small Life</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le défi de Megumi</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">A Doutora Megumi</title>
<title xml:lang="th">คุณหมอคนสวยกับคำท้าทายที่ไม่พึงปรารรถนา</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Küçük Bir Yaşamı Kurtarmak / Kurtarıcı Doktor Megumi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chiisana Inochi o Sukue! Bijin Joi: Megumi no Chousen</title>
<summary>After a shady faith healer discredits her medical skills, Megumi`s patients abandon her. And once a worried family panics and pays the phony shaman to heal their sick daughter, Megumi must intervene in order to save the young girl`s life.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>647993</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="764" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">59</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="9">9.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">命運尽きず! 闘志, 今よみがえる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Not Out of Luck!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La roue tourne</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">A Sorte Continua...</title>
<title xml:lang="th">อย่ายอมแพ้โชคชะตากลับมาเถอะเคนชิน</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Hala Şans Var!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meiun Tsukizu! Toushi, Ima Yomigaeru</title>
<summary>As Aoshi tries to stop a takeover of the country, Kenshin poses Shishio with his greatest challenge. In his defeat of Usui, Saito exposes the blind warrior`s plot to kill Shishio.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648083</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="765" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-11-06</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">史上最強の宿敵! 襲いかかる非情の牙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Strongest Opponent From the Past</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le pire ennemi</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">O Golpe da Serpente</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ศัตรูผู้แข็งเกร่งหมาป่าอหังการ์</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Geçmişten Gelen Güçlü Rakip: Acımasız Dişlerin Saldırısı!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shijou Saikyou no Shukuteki! Osoikakaru Hijou no Kiba</title>
<summary>Saito sets a trap for Samurai X by enlisting another assassin in his plan. And once Kenshin repels the accomplice, he`s left to take on his old rival.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648023</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="766" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-03-05</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">同盟成立・蒼紫が志々雄と手を組んだ日!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Formation of an Alliance</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Alliance et trahison</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">A Constituição de Uma Aliança</title>
<title xml:lang="th">อาโอชิและชิชิโอะ</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Bir İttifak Kuruluyor: Aoshi ile Shishio`nun Bir Araya Geldiği Gün</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Doumei Seiritsu: Aoshi ga Shishio to Te o Kunda Hi!</title>
<summary>Although Misao is excited by the return of her mentor and hero, she`s stunned to discover that Aoshi has betrayed one of their closest friends.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648049</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="767" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-02-28</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新たなる戦い! 飛び込んできた謎の美女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A New Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une femme mystérieuse</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">A Mulher Misteriosa</title>
<title xml:lang="th">การต่อสู้ที่ดุเดือด</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Yeni Bir Savaş! Nereden Geldiği Bilinmeyen Gizemli Güzel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aratanaru Tatakai! Tobikonde Kita Nazo no Bijo</title>
<summary>When local gangsters threaten the life of a beautiful woman, Kenshin and Sanosuke step in to save her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648369</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="768" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-05-01</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">少年剣士誕生! 一番弟子弥彦の戦い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Birth of a Boy Swordsman</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Naissance d`un jeune guerrier</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">A Primeira Luta do Yahiko</title>
<title xml:lang="th">การต่อสู้ของศิษย์คนแรก</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Genç Bir Kılıç Ustasının Doğuşu: İlk Çırak Yahiko`nun Savaşı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shounen Kenshi Tanjou! Ichiban Deshi Yahiko no Tatakai</title>
<summary>When a criminal gang threatens a young girl he loves, Yahiko seeks Kenshin`s advice on how to defend her in a lopsided fight.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>647989</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="769" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">57</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幕末を駆けた二人・志々雄 対 剣心 最終戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Two Men at the End of an Era</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les deux survivants</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Os Sobreviventes do Final da Era Tokugawa</title>
<title xml:lang="th">การต่อสู้ครั้งสุดท้ายของชิชิโอะและเคนชิน</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Bir Çağın Sonunda İki Adam</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bakumatsu o Kaketa Futari: Shishio tai Kenshin Saishuusen!</title>
<summary>As Kaoru and Yahiko anxiously await his return, a wounded but determined Kenshin arrives for his final showdown with Shishio, who is unwilling to have anyone stand in his way of controlling Japan`s future.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648079</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="770" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="12">4.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">燃え上がる戦慄の島! 真紅の海賊・完結編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Burn, Island of Terror</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fin des Kairyu</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Pirata Vermelho - O Final</title>
<title xml:lang="th">เกาะที่ลุกเป็นไฟ โจรสลัดกระหายเลือดตอนจบ</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Terör Adası! Kırmızı Korsan: Sonuç</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moeagaru Senritsu no Shima! Shinku no Kaizoku: Kanketsuhen</title>
<summary>After her trusted colleagues betray Shura, it`s left up to Kenshin to save her life and stop the pirate`s opium smuggling scheme.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648019</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="771" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-02-19</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恐るべき無情の刺客! 十本刀・張との死闘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Killer Without Mercy</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Combat fatal</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">A Luta Fatal</title>
<title xml:lang="th">เผชิญจุปปงคาตานะ โจ</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Acımasız Bir Katil: Juppangatanalı Cho ile Ölesiye Bir Dövüş</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Osorubeki Mujou no Shikaku! Juppongatana: Chou to no Shitou</title>
<summary>After watching an unarmed Kenshin bravely defend himself, Shakkuu Arai`s only chance at saving his own son is to deliver his father`s final reverse edge sword.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648045</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="772" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-02-14</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">闇からの訪問者・黒笠現る!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Appearance of Kurogasa</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Kurogasa, sombre visiteur</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">O Visitante Que Veio da Escuridão</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ผู้มาเยือนจากความมืด</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Kurogasa`nın Ortaya Çıkışı / Gölgelerin İçinden Gelen Ziyaretçiler</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yami kara no Houmonsha: Kurogasa Arawaru!</title>
<summary>With a ruthless ex-Samurai killing high ranking politicians, the Chief of Police asks Kenshin to catch him. But as Kenshin confronts the deadly Jin-nai Udo, Kaoru`s efforts to stop the battle end with her kidnapping.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648365</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="773" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-03-13</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蒼紫・美しすぎるほど怖い奴</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Aoshi</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Aoshi Shinomori</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Aoshi um Homem Temível</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ดาวรร้ายที่เต็มไปด้วยเขี้ยวเล็บ</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Aoshi: Korkutucu Bir Güzellik</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aoshi: Utsukushi Sugiru Hodo Kowai Yatsu</title>
<summary>Having pledged to save Megumi, the Peace Force must first take on a band of ruthless drug dealing mobsters. But when a rift inside the gang leads to a change in leadership, Kenshin must confront a fighter whose powers he`s underestimated.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>647985</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="774" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">55</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="8">9.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">嵐の夜の惨劇・宗次郎の過去</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Tragedy of a Stormy Night</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une nuit d`orage</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Tragédia Numa Noite de Tempestade</title>
<title xml:lang="th">โศกนาฏกรรมวันฝนตก</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Fırtınalı Gecenin Trajedisi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arashi no Yo no Sangeki: Soujirou no Kako</title>
<summary>In an effort to explain Souijuro`s emotionless posture, Kenshin recalls how the young assassin was rescued from a life of slavery and then taught to fight by Shishio.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648075</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="775" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真紅の海賊・引き裂かれた剣心と薫!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Crimson Pirate</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le dragon des mers</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">O Pirata Vermelho</title>
<title xml:lang="th">โจรสลัดกระหายเลือดเคนชินกับคาโอรุถูกพรากจากกัน</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Kızıl Korsan / Kırmızı Korsan – Kenshin ve Kaoru Ayrılıyor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinku no Kaizoku: Hikisakareta Kenshin to Kaoru!</title>
<summary>In order to earn money for their dojo, the Peace Force signs on to help protect a merchant ship from pirates. However, to keep Kaoru from falling into the hands of the pirate`s female leader, Shura, Kenshin offers himself in exchange.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648015</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="776" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-01-31</airdate>
<rating votes="15">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪の一文字・ケンカ屋左之助登場!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bad!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La voie de Sanosuke Sagara</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">O Lutador Sanosuke</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซาโนะสุเกะนักสู้ข้างถนน</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Kötü Haber! Kiralık Dövüşçü</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aku no Ichimonji: Kenkaya Sanosuke Toujou!</title>
<summary>Gohei enlists a vicious street-fighter known as Sanosuke to seek revenge against Kenshin. And even though Kenshin exposes Gohei`s plan, Sanosuke makes it clear that the two of them will fight each other one day.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648355</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="777" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">53</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">巨人対超人・絶望の淵に放たれた一矢!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Giant Versus Superman</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`arme destructrice</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">O Gigante e o Super Homem</title>
<title xml:lang="th">คนใหญ่คนจริงกับวันอวสานที่กำลังมาถึง</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Dev İle Süpermen Karşı Karşıya: Umutsuz Bir Anda Bir Ok Atışı Gibi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyojin tai Choujin: Zetsubou no Fuchi ni Hanatareta Isshi!</title>
<summary>Despite the overwhelming odds, Kaoru, Yahiko and Misao continue to face warriors sent to eliminate them. But it`s the arrival of Kenshin`s teacher that turns the tide in their favor.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648071</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="778" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-08-14</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">左之助の裏切り!? 運命の再会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sanosuke`s Betrayal</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le portrait de Sagara</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Sanosuke e os Desenhos Coloridos</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซาโนะสุเกะกับภาพพิมพิ์</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Sanosuke`nin İhaneti / Kaderdeki Buluşma</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sanosuke no Uragiri!? Unmei no Saikai</title>
<summary>An artist`s work leads Sanosuke to a reunion with an old army comrade, Tsukioka. But when his old friend wants him to join in avenging the death of their former leader, Sanosuke must stop him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648011</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="779" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-02-05</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">左之助, 極意の修行! 破戒僧・安慈への挑戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sanosuke`s Secret Training</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`entraînement de Sanosuke</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">O Severo Treino do Sanosuke</title>
<title xml:lang="th">การฝึกพิเศษของซาโนะสุเกะ</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Sanosuke`nin Gizli Eğitimi: Yok Edici Anji Sorunu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sanosuke, Gokui no Shugyou! Hakai Sou: Anji e no Chousen</title>
<summary>As Kaoru and Yahiko continue tracking Kenshin, Sanosuke encounters a fallen Buddhist monk who offers to teach him some powerful fighting techniques.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648041</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="780" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-06-11</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">目醒める時は今・満身創痍の決着!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wake up Now!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Réveille-toi, Aoshi !</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">A Batalha Final</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ตาสว่างอีกครั้งจุดจบของนักสู้พันแผล</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Uyan! Yaralarına Bakma ve Bitirmek İçin Savaş</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mezameru Toki wa Ima: Manshin Soui no Kecchaku!</title>
<summary>Following his defeat by Kenshin, Aoshi vows to renounce Shishio. And while Shishio looks for clues to help in his impending fight with Samurai X, Kaoru, Yahiko and Misao fight to stay alive.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648067</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="781" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1996-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪夢の崩壊! 雷十太の野望・完結編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dissolution of a Nightmare</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fin d`un cauchemar</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">O Fim de um Pesadelo</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ไรจูดะอาละวาดใครจะเอาอยู่</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Bir Kabusun Dağılışı / Bir Kabusun Yok Oluşu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akumu no Houkai! Raijuuta no Yabou: Kanketsuhen</title>
<summary>After learning the truth behind Raijuta`s duplicitous plan, an injury sidelines Yutaro, leaving Kenshin to fight the renegade Samurai alone.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648007</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="782" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幕末の時を超えて! 対峙した志々雄と剣心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Across the Boundary Between Edo and Meiji</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Makoto Shishio</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Shishio e Kenshin Frente a Frente</title>
<title xml:lang="th">การประจันหน้ากับชิชิโอ</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Edo ve Meiji Arasındaki Sınırın Ötesinde: Kenshin ve Shishio Karşı Karşıya!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bakumatsu no Toki o Koete! Taijishita Shishio to Kenshin</title>
<summary>Leaving Misao behind, Kenshin and Saito make their way inside Shishio`s fortress. Following a confrontation with one of his most powerful henchmen, Kenshin is ready to take on Shishio himself.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648037</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="783" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">追いはぎ少女・巻町操の隠された正体!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Girl Bandit</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Misao Makimachi</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">O Verdadeiro Segredo da Misao Makimachi</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ความลับของสาวน้อยมิซาโอะ</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Eşkıya Kız: Misao Makimachi`nin Gizli Tarafı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oihagi Shoujo: Makimachi Misao no Kakusareta Shoutai!</title>
<summary>After befriending Misao, Kenshin insists that she return the money she`s stolen before letting her accompany him on his quest to stop Shishio.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648033</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2170" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">77</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-02-10</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">下関に緋村道場? もう一人の抜刀斎現る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Himura Dojo in Shimonoseki?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un dojo Himura à Shimonoseki ?</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">O Mestre Battousai</title>
<title xml:lang="th">บัตโตซัยกำมะลอ</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Himura Dojo Shimonoseki`de Mi?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shimonoseki ni Himura Doujou? Mou Hitori no Battousai Arawaru</title>
<summary>When the Peace Force comes across a man posing as Kenshin, everyone else wants the impostor exposed. But Kenshin notes that he`s been using his profits to care for a group of orphans.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648119</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2171" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">90</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-06-23</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">風水の奇襲! 張り巡らされた五茫星の謎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Feng Shui, Surprise Attack!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Attaque surprise !</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">O Feng Shui</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Feng Shui Sürpriz Saldırısı!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuusui no Kishuu! Harimegurasareta Gobousei no Nazo</title>
<summary>Following a series of accidents in town, a master of feng shui blames an imbalance in the Ki, a force which keeps all of nature`s other forces in balance
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648145</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2172" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">75</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-01-27</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最後の聖戦・激突! ふたつの天翔龍閃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Last Crusade</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La dernière croisade</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">A Última Guerra Sagrada</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ศึกตัดสินเพลงดาบล่องนภา</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Son Savaş</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo no Seisen: Gekitotsu! Futatsu no Amakakeru Ryuu no Hirameki</title>
<summary>As Misao and the Dutch consul ask the Army delay to their attack, the sightless Kenshin pressures Shogo to prevent the martyrdom of his followers.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648115</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2173" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">73</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-01-13</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あざ笑う悪鬼! 庄三, 爆炎に散った火龍</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sneering Demon!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le démon railleur</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Um Dia Muito Quente</title>
<title xml:lang="th">มังกรเพลิงโชโงพิโรธสุดขั้ว</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Alaycı Şeytan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Azawarau Akki! Shouzou, Bakuen ni Chitta Karyuu</title>
<summary>Sir Kaioh unveils his plan to use Shogo Amarusa`s loyal followers to overthrow the government and control Japan himself.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648111</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2174" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">88</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-06-09</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふたつの道標・弥彦と由太郎永遠の約束</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Two Guides</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le serment de Yahiko et Yutarō</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">A Herança Perdida</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">İki Rehber</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futatsu no Michishirube: Yahiko to Yutarou Towa no Yakusoku</title>
<summary>As he faces off against the Black Knight`s leader, Kenshin must rely on his brains and not his sword to win the battle.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648141</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2175" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">71</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-12-16</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">傀王の陰謀・罠にかかった翔伍!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kaiou`s Conspiracy</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Shougo pris au piège</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Uma Maneira de Estar na Vida</title>
<title xml:lang="th">โชโงติดกับแผนร้ายของไคโอ</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Kaiou`nun Komplosu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaiou no Inbou: Wana ni Kakatta Shougo!</title>
<summary>Though blinded by his duel with Shogo Amakusa, Kenshin seeks another battle in hopes it will restore his sight.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648107</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2176" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">86</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地底を舞う赤い陽炎・殺鬼! 真田三人衆</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Heat Wave From Beneath the Earth</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les 3 démons</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Os Três Sanada</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Dünyanın Altından Geen Bir Isı Dalgası</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chitei o Mau Akai Kagerou: Sakki! Sanada Sanninshuu</title>
<summary>After surviving a fall into a volcano, the Peace Force comes across an injured Sanada Ninja who offers to help battle his former allies.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648137</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2177" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">84</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-05-05</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真田忍群と霊薬・お頭御沙薙の狙い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sanada Ninja Squad and the Elixir</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les ninjas Sanada</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Um Medicamento Miracoloso</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Sanada Ninja Ekibi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sanada Ninjagun to Reiyaku: Okashira Misanagi no Nerai</title>
<summary>When a letter from Dr. Hans reveals the story of the miraculous medicine, Yutaro joins the Peace Force in an effort to find it.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648133</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2178" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">69</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-12-02</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">対戦の地, 島原へ! 雌雄を決する時</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the Battlefield of Shimabara</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le champ de bataille de Shimabara</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">O Segredo de Shimabara</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ชิมาบาระดินแดนศักดิ์สิทธิ์ของโชโง</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Shimabara Savaş Meydanı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taisen no Chi, Shimabara e! Shiyuu o Kessuru Toki</title>
<summary>As Kenshin prepares to honor his promise to stop Shogo Amakusa, he and Sanosuke uncover a secret church that was built when Christian worshipers were forced underground.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648103</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2179" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">82</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勝海舟の決意・時代を超えた真実</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kaishu Katsu`s Determination</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La résolution de Kaishu-Katsu</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Mais Precioso do que Dinheiro</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Kaishu-Katsu`nun Kararlılığı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Katsu Kaishuu no Ketsui: Jidai o Koeta Shinjitsu</title>
<summary>Though Daigoro is wounded in the battle, Kenshin and company free Itsuko.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648129</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2180" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">67</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-11-18</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">煌めく伝説の剣! 神秘の剣士・天草翔伍</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Gleaming Blade of Legends</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La lame légendaire de Shiro Shougo</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Quando o Dia se Transformar em Trevas</title>
<title xml:lang="th">นักดาบในตำนานอะมาคุสะโชโง</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Efsanelerdeki Parıldayan Bıçak</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kirameku Densetsu no Ken! Shinpi no Kenshi: Amakusa Shougo</title>
<summary>Alerted by Misao, Kenshin and the rest of the Peace Force arrive to help Aoshi find a mysterious killer. Kenshin`s investigation uncovers evidence linking the killing to a Christian Samurai and of vengeance that`s been foretold.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648099</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2181" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">80</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-03-03</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">終わらない幕末・海舟に課せられた天命</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Unending Revolution</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La révolution sans fin</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">O Rapto</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Bitmeyen Devrim</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Owaranai Bakumatsu: Kaishuu ni Kaserareta Tenmei</title>
<summary>As Kaoru continues her training of Daigoro, Kenshin is warned to steer clear of the young man`s teacher, Kaishu Katsu.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648125</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2182" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">65</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-11-04</airdate>
<rating votes="8">2.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">消えたお宝を探せ! 名探偵犬・ノ太郎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Find the Lost Treasure!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">A la recherche du trésor perdu !</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">O Cão e a Chave</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ตามล่าหาสมบัติของเจ้าโนทาโร่</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Kayıp Hazineyi Bul!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kieta Otakara o Sagase! Meitanteiken: Notarou</title>
<summary>Sanosuke adopts a stray dog, unaware that it holds the key to a criminal gang`s plot to blackmail some local officials and gain political control. And when the gang finally tracks him down, Kenshin and Yahiko join Sanosuke to foil their plan.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648095</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2183" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">93</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-08-18</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">敵は戦場ヶ原にあり! 翡翠の紋章を求めて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Enemy Awaits in Senjogahara</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`ennemi attend à Senjogahara</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">A Insígnia de Ouro</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Düşman Senjogahara`da Bekliyor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Teki wa Senjougahara ni Ari! Hisui no Monshou o Motomete</title>
<summary>With help from the Wind family`s leader, Kenshin saves Kaoru`s life. But the Water family`s quest to redirect the Ki and gain control of Japan moves ahead as planned.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648151</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2184" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">63</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">願い螢の伝説・ある剣客を待ち続けた少女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Legend of the Fireflies</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La légende des Lucioles</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">O Vôo Dos Pirilampos</title>
<title xml:lang="th">เรื่องราวของหิงห้อยการต่อสู้ที่ยังไม่จบ</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Ateş Böcekleri Efsanesi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Negaibotaru no Densetsu: Aru Kenkaku o Machi Tsuzuketa Shoujo</title>
<summary>Back at home, Kaoru works to restore the dilapidated dojo, while Kenshin encounters a wise old fisherman who teaches him an important lesson about love.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648091</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2185" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">78</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-02-17</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">画学生の想う女性・箱根湯の街恋騒動!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crush!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Coup de foudre à Hakone !</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">O Pintor Apaixonado</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ร้านประทับใจที่ฮาบารี</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Aşk!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gagakusei no Omou Hito: Hakone Yu no Machi Koi Soudou</title>
<summary>When Kenshin accidentally loses all their money, the Peace Force must go to work at an inn in order to pay their bill.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648121</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2186" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">91</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">うごめく風水の魔力・狙われた神谷道場!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Magic of Feng Shui</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La magie du Feng Shui</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Uma Herança Aterradora</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Feng Shui Sihiri</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ugomeku Fuusui no Maryoku: Nerawareta Kamiya Doujou!</title>
<summary>As Kenshin learns of a battle between the Wind and Water families for control of the Ki, efforts to build a railroad are exposed as a Water clan plot to control Japan
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648147</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2187" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">76</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-02-03</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">旅立ちの海・希望は哀しみの波を越えて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bon Voyage</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bon Voyage</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">A Terra Prometida</title>
<title xml:lang="th">การเดินทางข้ามทะเลแห่งอดีต</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">İyi Yolculuklar</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tabidachi no Umi: Kibou wa Kanashimi no Nami o Koete</title>
<summary>Following Shogo`s surrender, Kenshin asks the government not to execute him. As a result, he and his followers are sent into exile in Holland.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648117</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2188" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">74</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-01-20</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">左之助の涙・二人に訪れた永遠の別離</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sanosuke`s Tears</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les larmes de Sanosuke</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">A Morte de Um Anjo</title>
<title xml:lang="th">น้ำตาแห่งการพลัดพรากชั่วนิรันดร์</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Sanosuke`nin Gözyaşları</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sanosuke no Namida: Futari ni Otozureta Towa no Wakare</title>
<summary>As Kenshin tries to stop the slaughter of the Christians as they march towards martyrdom, Sanosuke is unable to avert the death of Shogo`s terminally ill sister.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648113</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2189" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">89</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-06-16</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">まいえんじぇる操へ... 京都からの迎え</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To My Angel Misao</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">A Misao mon ange</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Um Dia na Cidade</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Meleğim Misao`ya</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">My Angel Misao e... Kyouto kara no Mukae</title>
<summary>As Aoshi arrives to bring her home, Misao joins Kaoru and some friends for a final shopping spree. However, Sanosuke and Yahiko`s efforts to keep an eye on the women lead to them to be mistaken for a pair of thieves
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648143</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2190" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">72</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-01-06</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">追憶の日々・翔伍と小夜の哀しき過去</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Days of Remorse</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Jour de remords</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Um Plano Diabólico</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ความหลังอันแสนเศร้าของสองพี่น้อง</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Pişmanlık Günleri</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuioku no Hibi: Shougo to Sayo no Kanashiki Kako</title>
<summary>Along with the story of his parent`s martyrdom, Misao uncovers the truth behind the alleged miracles that deified Shogo Amarusa.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648109</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2191" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">87</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-06-02</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シュナイダーの賭け・黒騎士団の崩壊!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Schneider`s Bet</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le parie de Schneider</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Os Jardins do Eden</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Schneifder`ın İddiası</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Schneider no Kake: Kurokishidan no Houkai!</title>
<summary>After their search leads them to the hidden cure, the leader of the Black Knights makes it clear that he has no intention of honoring his promise to cede control of Japan to the Sanada Ninjas.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648139</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2192" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">70</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-12-09</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雷龍閃の衝撃! 闇に葬られた剣心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shock of the Rairyu Sen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le choc de la Sen Rai Ryu</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">As Trevas Eternas</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ดิ่งสู่นรกที่เหมือนตายทั้งเป็น</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Rai Ryu Sen`in Uğradığı Şok</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rairyuusen no Shougeki! Yami ni Houmurareta Kenshin</title>
<summary>When neither Kaoru nor Kenshin can persuade Shogo Amakusa to abandon his plan to advance the Christian cause through violence, the stage for battle is set.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648105</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2193" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">85</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-05-19</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">迷走の旅・仕組まれた御神渡りの罠!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Straying Journey</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Journée d’errance</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">A Deusa da Mesericordia</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Yoldan Çıkmış Bir Yolculuk</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meisou no Tabi: Shikumareta Omiwatari no Wana!</title>
<summary>Using the clues left behind by Dr. Hans, Kenshin and company are led to the hidden shrine that holds the key to the miracle cure.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648135</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2194" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">83</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-04-21</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">由太郎帰国・影に潜む黒騎士団の野望</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yutaro Returns</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le retour de Yutaro</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Yutaro e o Doutor Hans</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Yutaro Geri Dönüyor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yutarou Kikoku: Kage ni Hisomu Kurokishidan no Yabou</title>
<summary>With his arm nearly healed, Yutaro and his doctor arrive for a visit at the dojo.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648131</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2195" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">68</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-11-25</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">運命のメダリオ・左之助と小夜の出会い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Medallion of Destiny</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le médaillon du destin</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">O Mundo de Deus</title>
<title xml:lang="th">สร้อยคอแห่งการพบเจอ</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Kader Madalyonu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unmei no Medallion: Sanosuke to Sayo no Deai</title>
<summary>In an effort to prevent more revenge killings, Kenshin must take on Shogo Amakusa, the Christian warrior known as God`s Child.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648101</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2196" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">81</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-03-10</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">紅葵の策謀・海舟を狙う幕末の生霊!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Conspiracy of the Beniaoi</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le complot des Beniaoi</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">A Prova Final em Shinagawa</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Beniaoi`nin Komplosu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Beniaoi no Sakubou: Kaishuu o Nerau Bakumatsu no Ikiryou!</title>
<summary>Despite Kaishu`s determination to free his daughter on his own, Kenshin joins the Peace Force and Daigoro for a rescue.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648127</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2197" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">66</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-11-11</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">薫 感激 剣心のぷろぽーず!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kaoru Ecstatic!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Demande en mariage</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">O Dia de Tanabata</title>
<title xml:lang="th">แหวนสื่อรักในวันทางาบาตะ</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Kaoru Mest Oldu: Kenshin`den Gelen Teklif?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaoru Kangeki Kenshin no Propose!?</title>
<summary>After Kenshin finds a ring inside a catfish, he`s persuaded to give it to Kaoru. Thinking it`s an engagement ring, Kaoru is sure that he`s asking her to get married.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648097</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2198" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">94</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-09-08</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">風と水の挽歌・今ここに死力尽くす!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Elegy of Wind and Water</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`effort ultime</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">O Desenlace Final</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Rüzgârın ve Suyun Ağıdı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaze to Mizu no Banka: Ima Koko ni Shiryoku Tsukusu!</title>
<summary>With Kenshin`s help, the Wind family derails their rival`s plan to redirect the flow of the Ki and ends their effort to dominate Japan
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648153</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2199" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">64</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-10-28</airdate>
<rating votes="9">2.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">弥彦王子誕生? 華麗なる社交界でびゅー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Birth of Prince Yahiko?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Début en société</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">O Príncipe Gémeo</title>
<title xml:lang="th">กำเนิดองชายยาฮิโกะสู่สังคมที่แตกต่าง</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Prens Yahiko`nun Doğuşu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yahiko Ouji Tanjou? Karei Naru Shakoukai Debut</title>
<summary>After stepping in to stop what appears to be a robbery, Kenshin and Kaoru meet a young prince who looks exactly like Yahiko.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648093</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2200" update="2013-03-10">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-12-02</airdate>
<rating votes="16">2.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">流浪の最果て- 緋と瑠璃の絆は潮騒の中に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">End of Wanderings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rurou no Saihate, Hi to Ruri no Kizuna wa Shiosai no Uchi ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2201" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">79</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-02-24</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勝海舟と剣心・幕末を生きた二人の宿縁</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kaishu Katsu and Kenshin</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Kaishu-Katsu et Kenshin</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Dois Homens Que Viveram no Final da Era Tokugawa</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Kaishu-Katsu ve Kenshin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Katsu Kaishuu to Kenshin: Bakumatsu o Ikita Futari no Shukuen</title>
<summary>Kaoru offers to take on a scholarly young student who`s been expelled by his teacher until he learns how to fight.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648123</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2210" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">92</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-08-04</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戒厳令の東京府! ばく進する凶器の龍脈</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tokyo Under Martial Law!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le terrible Ryumyaku</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">A Guerra do Ki</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Tokyo Sıkı Yönetim Altında</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaigenrei no Tokyo-fu! Bakushin Suru Kyouki no Ryuumyaku</title>
<summary>The Water family`s efforts to gain control of the Ki have left Kaoru seriously wounded.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648149</identifier>
<identifier>rurouni-kenshin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="8568" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">1.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">"Special Techniques" Special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9491" recap="true" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>50</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 56b - Summer Special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9493" update="2009-05-29">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1998-02-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9494" update="2009-05-29">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1997-11-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9495" update="2009-05-29">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1997-02-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9496" update="2010-05-15">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1996-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44445" recap="true" update="2011-07-01">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-03-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Review Special</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">O Fim da Viagem</title>
<summary>In this episode, Kaoru and Yahiko were plushies. This special has two parts. In the first part of the special, they had a very basic summary of Kenshin (who he was and how he came to be in Tokyo with Kaoru and the gang).
In the second part of the special, "Himura Kenshin’s Greatest Hits" they show him using his Hiten Mitsurugi Ryuu moves on various opponents, though it doesn’t go into detail of how they work like the "Special Techniques" special.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="45021" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="5">P1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Legendary Samurai! The man who fights for love.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68245" update="2007-03-06">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">~第一章~ 東京編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The First Chapter: The Tokyo Book</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daiisshou: Tokyo Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="68246" update="2007-03-06">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">~第二章~ 京都編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Second Chapter: The Kyoto Book</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daini Shou: Kyoto Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="103258" update="2010-03-24">
<epno type="3">C13</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1998-02-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 6b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="103259" update="2010-05-15">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1997-11-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 6a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="103260" update="2009-05-29">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>1997-11-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="103261" update="2010-05-15">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1997-06-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="103262" update="2010-05-15">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1997-02-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="103263" update="2010-05-15">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1996-10-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="103264" update="2010-05-15">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1996-05-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="103265" update="2010-05-15">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1996-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="103266" update="2010-05-15">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1998-03-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="103267" update="2010-05-15">
<epno type="3">C14</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1998-03-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191365" update="2017-10-01">
<epno type="6">O1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Box Special Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
