<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9010" restricted="true">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>2012-05-25</startdate>
<enddate>2012-07-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kyonyuu Fantasy</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Big Breasts Fantasy</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">거유 판타지</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Cycata fantazja</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">巨乳ファンタジー</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="1725" approval="20" total="24">Viper GTS</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="109723">Never thought I`d say this about hentai, but I really enjoyed the plot. If you suspend your disbelief of how a bumbling fool fucked his way into becoming a hero that is. I enjoyed it. Great tits, scenes, good animation, voice acting.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.a1c.jp/~majin/lineup/kf01.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="32321" type="Animation Work">Majin</name>
<name id="942" type="Original Work">Waffle</name>
<name id="32114" type="Direction">Ayano Kunio</name>
<name id="42564" type="Character Design">Citizen</name>
<name id="45017" type="Music">Corey &amp; Carter</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the erotic game by http://anidb.net/cr942 [Waffle].
http://anidb.net/ch45189 [Lute] is a fresh graduate of the Royal Knights Academy. Although he does not much mind it himself, he is regularly looked upon in contempt for having graduated at the bottom of his class. Almost immediately after graduation, Lute is assigned to Boan, the poorest district of the realm. Rumors have it that Boan is also the place where surviving devils have taken refuge and continue to work evil.
~ translated and adapted from official site by Cranston</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="440">6.30</permanent>
<temporary count="449">6.91</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>83105.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14512</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13221</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5153</identifier>
<identifier>ldoxuj</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.a1c.jp/~majin/product/kf02.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.a1c.jp/~majin/product/kf01.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15148</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2762</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="301" parentid="2848" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-10">
<name>lactation</name>
<description>Capable of secreting breast milk, sometimes referred to as Mother`s milk.</description>
<picurl>176139.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1774" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-05">
<name>gigantic breasts</name>
<description>Gigantic breasts are unnaturally large breasts, even by anime standards; they are true gargantuan monstrosities, either because of sheer size or through the combination of size and exceedingly unnatural shape. Essentially, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are gigantic; smaller breasts are the more common http://anidb.net/t2741 [large breasts], even if they`re as big as the character`s head.</description>
<picurl>160446.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2143" parentid="2646" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-28">
<name>succubus</name>
<description>A demon who takes the form of a woman to seduce men in dreams to have sexual intercourse. In modern times, a succubus is often depicted as highly attractive, while in the past succubi were depicted as frightening and demonic. Succubi draw energy from men to sustain themselves, often until the victim becomes exhausted or dies. The male counterpart is the incubus.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2615" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-25">
<name>18 restricted</name>
<description>This isn`t really an "audience".
While some anime might feature sexual content they still might not be considered pornography. This category is meant only for when the content is clearly *not* intended for minors. The distinction is made by whether the content is sold only to adults.</description>
<picurl>67867.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2647" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>high fantasy</name>
<description>Generally a serious and epic story set in an invented world. The world may be more or less based on real world environments or history. Typical fantastical elements are usually dominating, such as elves, dwarves, magicians, invented languages, quests; just to name a few.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2702" parentid="2848" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-16">
<name>mammary intercourse</name>
<description>Mammary intercourse is a sex act, performed as foreplay or as non-penetrative sex, that involves the stimulation of the male penis by the female breasts. Commonly, this sex act involves the man placing his penis in the woman`s cleavage and thrusting between her breasts, while the breasts are squeezed around the penis for additional stimulation, and fellatio may also be performed in combination. Mammary intercourse is also commonly known as titty-fucking or titfuck in the United States, as well as tit wank or French fuck in the United Kingdom. The Japanese term, paizuri (from oppai, breasts, and the verb suru, used in this context to describe the sexual act), is commonly used in the anime fandom. A variant term is "naizuri" (a pun on nai, the negative of the verb aru, indicating existence/presence), which describes an attempt to do a paizuri, but with insufficient cleavage.</description>
<picurl>174692.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2705" parentid="2848" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-20">
<name>creampie</name>
<description>The act of a man ejaculating inside a girl`s vagina, leaving the semen oozing out of her.</description>
<picurl>160720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2707" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-20">
<name>internal shots</name>
<description>Internal shots are pictures that display the interior of the body of a living being, either through the skin, kind of as an "x-ray" of sorts, or from the inside, as if the camera was also inside. This is generally used during sex scenes to display the inside of any area being penetrated. Those shots may happen either by making an area of the body transparent or by displaying the same area again, but from the inside; the latter method is shown in the picture.</description>
<picurl>213307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2713" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>oral</name>
<description>Oral sex is sexual activity involving the stimulation of the genitalia of a sex partner by the use of the mouth, tongue, teeth or throat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2715" parentid="7220" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-11">
<name>rape</name>
<description>Rape means to force someone to engage in sexual interaction without their consent. If the rape is not successfully executed (both fellatio and penetration did not occur), tag with http://anidb.net/t7238 [attempted rape] instead.</description>
<picurl>212186.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2718" parentid="2715" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male rape victim</name>
<description>Contrary to the more common situation, the rape victim is a male instead of a female. 
A common situation in hentai anime, a male character, commonly a lucky http://anidb.net/t1931 [harem lead], is sexually overpowered by their enticing and overly seductive female counterparts. These situations are usually undesired by the male character... though as a viewer, one might wonder why.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2721" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-13">
<name>public sex</name>
<description>Public sex refers to sexual acts that take place in public or semi-public places.</description>
<picurl>175406.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2733" parentid="2715" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-20">
<name>enjoyable rape</name>
<description>This anime features a rape scene during which the raped character also reaches orgasm or somehow else derives sexual pleasure from the act.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2895" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>dark-skinned girl</name>
<description>The anime features a girl with dark skin. A fetish of sorts, since the other protagonists are usually as white-skinned as porcelain dolls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2896" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-23">
<name>deflowering</name>
<description>Deflowering is the act of breaking the hymen of a female who hadn`t yet had vaginal intercourse. This tag can be applied only to pornographic anime in which a female is seen being deflowered; most often, one knows she had been a virgin because blood is seen coming out of her vagina during sex or after it, but her word on the matter is also considered valid.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2901" parentid="2729" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-09">
<name>bondage</name>
<description>Bondage is the use of restraints for the sexual pleasure of the parties involved. It may be used in its own right, as in the case of rope bondage and breast bondage, or as part of sexual activity or BDSM activity. When a person is sexually aroused by bondage, it may be considered a paraphilia, known as vincilagnia (from Latin vincio, to bind or fetter with chains, and lagneia, lust).
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42021.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2918" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>cunnilingus</name>
<description>Cunnilingus is an oral sex act performed on a female. It involves the use by a sex partner of the mouth, lips and tongue to stimulate the female`s clitoris and vulva. A female may receive cunnilingus as part of foreplay before sexual intercourse, or the sex partner may proceed until the female reaches orgasm.
The term is derived from the Latin words for the vulva (cunnus) and tongue (lingua).</description>
<picurl>161636.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4049" parentid="2721" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-13">
<name>outdoor sex</name>
<description>Popular place for sex in visual novels and manga.</description>
<picurl>175405.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4318" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-07-28">
<name>plot with porn</name>
<description>Any adult-rated work where porn is not the only point to it. As in, it has a plot that is not merely an excuse for having sex on screen. Even better if the sex is actually plausibly worked into said plot or used for characterization.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6268" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>fellatio</name>
<description>Fellatio is oral sex performed upon the penis. It may be performed to induce male orgasm and ejaculation of semen, or it may be used as foreplay prior to sexual intercourse.</description>
<picurl>165408.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="43825" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-26">
<rating votes="64">7.93</rating>
<name>Roxanne de Desir</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>86533.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32657" picture="50066.jpg">Kazuha</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43826" type="main character in" update="2012-11-21">
<rating votes="66">8.25</rating>
<name>Shamsiel Shahar</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128389.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32656" picture="74816.jpg">Kanamatsu Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44753" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-12">
<rating votes="41">6.16</rating>
<name>Isis Petrovna Elenskaya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130605.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27994">Sakurai Alice</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44754" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-12-02">
<rating votes="41">6.39</rating>
<name>Gladys von Wackenheim</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128390.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29449" picture="77579.jpg">Saki Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45189" type="main character in" update="2012-05-26">
<rating votes="4">7.33</rating>
<name>Ryuuto Henge</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88446.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="45190" type="appears in" update="2012-05-26">
<name>Fersen Kyou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88448.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="137429" update="2012-03-08">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2012-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シャムシェル×ロクサーヌ 爆乳のススメ 編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shamsiel x Roxanne Bakunyuu no Susume Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139663" update="2012-05-15">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2012-07-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アイシス×グラディス 爆乳の宣言! 編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Isis x Gladys Bakunyuu no Sengen! Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139664" update="2012-05-15">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139932" update="2012-05-29">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="141469" update="2012-08-06">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV Ep2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
