<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="904" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>1999-10-13</startdate>
<enddate>2000-01-19</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">The Big O</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Big O Roger</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">The Big-O</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">THEビッグオー</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The Big O</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">The Big O</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8941" type="Sequel">The Big O (2003)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="964" approval="6" total="7">Giant Robo The Animation: Chikyuu ga Seishi Suru Hi</anime>
<anime id="78" approval="4" total="9">Metropolis</anime>
<anime id="5671" approval="2" total="4">Nijuu-Mensou no Musume</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="5">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="466624">Ok I don`t like this anime but one of my friend`s said it was a tribute to Batman and well, maybe for those of you who liked Will Smith`s Independence Day or The Others with Nicole Kidman might like this as it has some similarities.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="231746">a very good mecha anime with things from the 90`s</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="424296">What if Bruce Wayne had a giant robot instead of his bat suit?</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="346924">40 years ago something awful happened which left the world in ruins and made all the people and androids of Paradigm city to lose all their memories to that day, and turned the rest of the world to one big desert.
This is the basis of the plot of "The Big O", and believe me, it gets much more interesting.
Plot twists, huge and epic robots fights and one guy who`s the best negotiator in Paradigm city named Roger Smith which pilots the megadeus called "Big O" - though he does not know why - this (and much more) is what awaits he who watches this great series. Recommended!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.sunrise-anime.jp/sunrise-inc/works/detail.php?cid=74</url>
<creators>
<name id="3728" type="Character Design">Satou Keiichi</name>
<name id="3742" type="Series Composition">Konaka Chiaki</name>
<name id="1760" type="Series Composition">Katayama Kazuyoshi</name>
<name id="1352" type="Original Work">Yatate Hajime</name>
<name id="1760" type="Direction">Katayama Kazuyoshi</name>
<name id="3174" type="Music">Sahashi Toshihiko</name>
<name id="726" type="Animation Work">Sunrise</name>
</creators>
<description>* Script written by http://anidb.net/cr3742 [Konaka Chiaki].
It is 40 years after an incident called "The Event" occurred, which destroyed the city of Paradigm and erased the memories of the citizens. Even though their lives eventually return back to normal, remembering the use of technology like electricity and vehicles, they are still plagued with the problem of not knowing what had exactly happened to them over 40 years ago.
http://anidb.net/ch16043 [Roger Smith] is known as the Negotiator, and he sees it as his duty to protect the people while he deals with his own mysterious past. His allies are; the android http://anidb.net/ch16042 [Dorothy], his butler http://anidb.net/ch16698 [Norman] and a giant robot called the Big O.
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1515">6.05</permanent>
<temporary count="1529">7.24</temporary>
<review count="5">7.86</review>
</ratings>
<picture>11311.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>231</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>567</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1083</identifier>
<identifier>pnzuky</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.sunrise-anime.jp/sunrise-inc/works/detail.php?cid=74</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>The_Big_O</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>THE_ビッグオー</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>102</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>159390</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1393" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-03-08">
<name>drill</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2852" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>thriller</name>
<description>The thriller is a genre of fiction in which tough, resourceful, but essentially ordinary heroes are pitted against villains determined to destroy them, their country, or the stability of the free world. The hero of a typical thriller faces danger alone or in the company of a small band of companions. The protagonist may be a law enforcement agent, a journalist, or a soldier, but typically he or she is cut off from the resources of "their" organization. More often the hero is an ordinary citizen drawn into danger and intrigue by circumstances beyond their control.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214683.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2861" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>cyberpunk</name>
<description>Cyberpunk focuses on computers or information technology, usually coupled with some degree of breakdown in social order. The plot often centres on a conflict among hackers, artificial intelligences, and mega corporations, tending to be set within a near-future dystopian Earth.</description>
<picurl>211264.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2870" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-17">
<name>steampunk</name>
<description>Steampunk is a sub-genre of science fiction that typically features steam-powered machinery, especially in a setting inspired by industrialized Western civilization during the 19th century. Steampunk works are often set in an alternative history of the 19th century`s British Victorian era or American "Wild West", in a post-apocalyptic future during which steam power has regained mainstream use, or in a fantasy world that similarly employs steam power.
Noteworthy attributes of the theme include large amounts smoke pollution from wood or coal burning, the affinity to metal constructs like cogs and metal tubing, and the mechanization of everyday objects.
Steampunk perhaps most recognisably features anachronistic technologies or retro-futuristic inventions as people in the 19th century might have envisioned them, and is likewise rooted in the era`s perspective on fashion, culture, architectural style, and art.
Such technology may include fictional machines like those found in the works of H. G. Wells and Jules Verne, or the modern authors Philip Pullman, Scott Westerfeld, Stephen Hunt and China Miéville. Other examples of steampunk contain alternative history-style presentations of such technology as lighter-than-air airships, analog computers, or such digital mechanical computers as Charles Babbage`s Analytical Engine.
Steampunk can also exemplify everything that is bad about unrestrained technological progress (dead matter), when compared to life and nature. The anime usually makes a point to propound the latter.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162830.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2882" parentid="2952" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-17">
<name>dystopia</name>
<description>A dystopia (from Ancient Greek: δυσ-, "bad, ill", and Ancient Greek: τόπος, "place, landscape"; alternatively cacotopia, or anti-utopia) is, in literature, an often futuristic society that has degraded into a repressive and controlled state, often under the guise of being utopian. Dystopian literature has underlying cautionary tones, warning society that if we continue to live how we do, this will be the consequence. A dystopia, thus, is regarded as a sort of negative utopia and is often characterized by an authoritarian or totalitarian form of government. Dystopias usually feature different kinds of repressive social control systems, a lack or total absence of individual freedoms and expressions and constant states of warfare or violence. Dystopias often explore the concept of humans abusing technology and how humans individually and collectively cope with technology that has evolved too quickly such as the car, the flamethrower or the microwave. A dystopian society is also often characterized by widespread poverty and brutal political controls such as a large military-like police.</description>
<picurl>69879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2962" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-14">
<name>neo-noir</name>
<description>Neo-noir is a style that prominently utilizes elements of the now declined film noir, but with updated themes, content, style, visual elements, or media that were absent in films noirs of the 1940s and 1950s.
Films noirs were typically crime dramas or psychological thrillers featuring a pessimistic worldview and starring conflicted antiheroes trapped in difficult situations and making choices out of desperation or nihilistic moral systems, with crime, especially murder, being featured on the majority of them. Some of the most obvious visual elements included low-key lighting, striking use of light and shadow, black-and-white filming, and unusual camera placement such as low-angle, wide-angle, and Dutch angle shots.
Film noir is often associated with urban settings, private detectives, femmes fatales, and bleak endings, but they are not necessary to the genre; a large number of these films, including some of the genre classics, take place in small towns, suburbia, rural areas, or on the open road, feature neither character type, and have clearly happy endings.
Film noir and the early neo-noir would come to influence the formation of tech noir, a crossover of neo-noir and science fiction, in the late 1970s; some the most influencial tech noir works are the American movies Alien (1979), Blade Runner (1982), and The Terminator (1984). Tech noir itself would also help form http://anidb.net/t2861 [cyberpunk] in the early 1980s.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3569" parentid="1278" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-17">
<name>human-android love</name>
<description>There is a romance going on between a human (often male) and an android (usually female).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3981" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-11-27">
<name>ninja maid</name>
<description>This is an old tag for anime which had characters that were maids and also ninjas, or at least able to use ninjutsu. The tag will be removed once all maids in question are properly tagged. See also the http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=animelist&amp;do.search=Search&amp;ctags.include=ninja,maid [list of anime with characters tagged ninja and maid] and the http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=animelist&amp;do.search=Search&amp;ctags.include=ninjutsu,maid [list of anime with characters tagged ninjutsu and maid].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4521" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>lost technology</name>
<description>Any advanced technology or science-related knowledge that was lost for some reason fits the description. This could be technology from a time before a post-apocalyptic cataclysm, knowledge gained a long time ago but forgotten, or the relics of an old alien civilization only recently discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4612" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep?</name>
<description>The title of Philip K. Dick`s SF novel (movie: Blade Runner). 
The phrase implies a set of existential questions: Do artificial beings (e.g. Replicants, Bioroids, or other AI constructs) dream, feel, or have a soul? If memories can be implanted, what makes real memories real? By contrast — what makes humans human? What is reality? 
These are central themes e.g. in all of the Ghost in the Shell and Appleseed series / movies.</description>
<picurl>210067.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4786" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>negotiator</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5172" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-05">
<name>vigilante</name>
<description>A vigilante is a civilian, or rarely organization, acting in a law enforcement capacity or in the pursuit of self-perceived summary justice without legal authority.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5609" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-27">
<name>dieselpunk</name>
<description>Dieselpunk is a genre that combines the aesthetics of the diesel-based technology of the interwar period through to the 1950s with retro-futuristic technology and postmodern sensibilities.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5807" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2007-08-08">
<name>cosmic reset</name>
<description>All events that occurred up to a certain point are mysteriously undone, as if the Universe pressed a rewind button. This usually means some characters are being given another chance to unknowingly play out events differently, perhaps to prevent certain consequences from the previous time line`s actions. Occasionally they become doomed to repeat portions of their life over and over again until an individual event or series of events are performed correctly in just the right way, as seemingly to gain the Universe`s approval.</description>
<picurl>36685.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5859" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-30">
<name>monster of the week</name>
<description>On a pretty much regular basis — weekly or episodic — the protagonists engage in some kind of conflict. This can be an actual showdown between mecha, or the all-out fight against an enemy, or a (car) race that needs to be won.
This can make the anime quite repetitive.</description>
<picurl>60013.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5881" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-06-07">
<name>childhood memory</name>
<description>The childhood memory of one of the protagonists plays an important part as plot device in this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5917" parentid="2794" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-24">
<name>classical music</name>
<description>Classical music is art music produced or rooted in the traditions of Western music (both liturgical and secular). It encompasses a broad span of time from roughly the 11th century to the present day.
Anime tagged have classical music as a central theme.</description>
<picurl>169132.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6070" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>mystery</name>
<description>The mystery film is a sub-genre of the more general category of crime film. It focuses on the efforts of the detective, private investigator or amateur sleuth to solve the mysterious circumstances of a crime by means of clues, investigation, and clever deduction. (Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="16042" type="main character in" update="2013-01-24">
<rating votes="34">8.80</rating>
<name>R. Dorothy Wayneright</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>R. Dorothy Wayneright is Roger`s assistant. Introduced as Dorothy Soldano, daughter of rich scientist Miguel Soldano, she is later revealed to be an android constructed by him. Her actual "father" would be Timothy Wayneright, the man who commissioned her construction and father of the real and presumably late Dorothy Wayneright. To show her gratitude, and as a form of payment for Roger`s help, she decides to move in with him and help out Norman with the chores. In occasional episodes, Dorothy accompanies Roger in his work as a negotiator.</description>
<picture>59736.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16043" type="main character in" update="2013-01-24">
<rating votes="17">8.77</rating>
<name>Roger Smith</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Roger Smith is the series protagonist. He is the Negotiator. His job entails finding a resolution for the troubles of Paradigm City, the "City of Amnesia". He`d negotiate anything for anyone, but he is a professional and expects the parties to behave professionally. Despite this, he displays a certain aversion to the Paradigm Corporation, and takes the jobs he gets from them only if they happen to involve a threat to the city itself or are of personal interest to him. When memories betray the people and force them to reawaken monstrosities of the city`s past, Roger`s only option is to fight back with a monstrosity of his own, the black megadeus Big O.</description>
<picture>59735.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="398" picture="17243.jpg">Miyamoto Mitsuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16698" type="main character in" update="2013-01-24">
<rating votes="7">8.42</rating>
<name>Norman Burg</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Norman Burg is Roger`s butler. Forty years before the commencement of the story, Norman, like the rest of Paradigm, lost all memories from before that day, but he would not think twice before going once more unto the breach for his master. Resourceful and talented, he is also caretaker of the Big O. Norman`s skills give him a purpose and a mission to accomplish for Roger.</description>
<picture>59739.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="564" picture="146195.jpg">Kiyokawa Motomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16699" type="main character in" update="2013-01-24">
<rating votes="7">7.06</rating>
<name>Dan Dastun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dan Dastan is the middle-aged Chief of the Military Police. He is Roger`s former commander and the Negotiator`s contact in the police force. Roger describes him as "a hard-nosed cop completely devoted to the force" and with "more pride in the Military Police than anything else."</description>
<picture>59738.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16701" type="main character in" update="2019-10-19">
<rating votes="18">7.19</rating>
<name>Angel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Angel is the beautiful woman Roger encounters throughout the series. Introduced as Casey Jenkins, investigator for Paradigm Power Management, then again as Patricia Lovejoy, secretary for the publisher of Paradigm Press. Angel`s true identity is a mystery, her motives questionable and her allegiance to no one but herself.</description>
<picture>239983.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="295" picture="25758.jpg">Shinohara Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16703" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-24">
<rating votes="2">3.14</rating>
<name>Alan Gabriel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59745.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="281" picture="151723.jpg">Futamata Issei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16704" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-24">
<rating votes="4">2.31</rating>
<name>Alex Rosewater</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59741.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16705" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-24">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Big Ears</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59740.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2021" picture="187129.jpg">Tsuji Shinpachi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16708" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-14">
<rating votes="2">3.88</rating>
<name>Bonnie Fraser</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46298.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="454" picture="17354.jpg">Furuya Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16709" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-14">
<name>Eugene Grant</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46299.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2583" picture="23188.jpg">Furukawa Toshio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16710" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-14">
<name>Gieseng</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46301.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3278" picture="24273.jpg">Terashima Mikio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16711" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-24">
<name>Gordon Rosewater</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59743.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1818" picture="20692.jpg">Naya Gorou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16713" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-14">
<rating votes="1">1.10</rating>
<name>Kelly</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46305.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5026" picture="151676.jpg">Sawada Toshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16714" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-24">
<rating votes="3">5.39</rating>
<name>Jason Beck</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59744.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="297" picture="233915.jpg">Ootsuka Houchuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16715" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-14">
<rating votes="3">7.71</rating>
<name>Laura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46306.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="394" picture="17239.jpg">Ikezawa Haruna</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16717" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-14">
<name>Melissa Fraser</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46308.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="494" picture="17485.jpg">Ichijou Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16720" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-14">
<name>Miguel Soldano</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46311.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="604" picture="154161.jpg">Ogata Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16721" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-14">
<name>Oliver</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46312.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16722" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-14">
<name>Paul Readerman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46313.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32" picture="16618.jpg">Tachiki Fumihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16723" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-14">
<name>Rick Fraser</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46314.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3312" picture="24691.jpg">Ikemizu Michihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16724" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-02">
<name>Roscoe Fitzgerald</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46315.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="456" picture="17358.jpg">Ootsuka Chikao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16725" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-24">
<rating votes="2">2.61</rating>
<name>Schwarzwald</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59742.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="710" picture="228657.jpg">Hori Katsunosuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16726" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-02">
<rating votes="2">3.63</rating>
<name>Timothy Wayneright</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46317.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1416" picture="18579.jpg">Ishimori Takkou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16727" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-24">
<rating votes="1">3.39</rating>
<name>Vera Ronstadt</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59746.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2221" picture="83141.jpg">Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16728" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-14">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Dundee Wise</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46320.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28" picture="23184.jpg">Aono Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16730" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-02">
<rating votes="1">7.58</rating>
<name>R. Instro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46321.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3093" picture="38195.jpg">Nojima Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87466" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-03">
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<name>Big O</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>piloted robot</description>
<picture>197760.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="87469" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-03">
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<name>Big Duo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>197764.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="87471" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-03">
<rating votes="1">5.77</rating>
<name>Dorothy-1</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>197777.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="101762" type="appears in" update="2019-04-03">
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<name>Red Destiny</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67337.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="9437" update="2012-05-06">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Roger The Negotiator</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Roger the Negotiator</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Roger the Negotiator</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9438" update="2012-05-06">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Electric City</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Electric City</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Electric City</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9439" update="2012-05-06">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-11-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Bring Back My Ghost</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bring Back My Ghost</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bring Back My Ghost</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9440" update="2012-05-06">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-11-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">A Legacy of Amadeus</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Legacy of Amadeus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">A Legacy of Amadeus</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9441" update="2012-05-06">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Dorothy Dorothy</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dorothy, Dorothy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dorothy Dorothy</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9442" update="2012-05-06">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Underground Terror</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Underground Terror</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Underground Terror</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9443" update="2012-05-06">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-01-12</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Enemy as Another Big!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Enemy Is Another Big!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Enemy as Another Big!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9444" update="2012-05-06">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-12-01</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Missing Cat</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Missing Cat</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Missing Cat</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9445" update="2012-05-06">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-01-05</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Daemonseed</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Daemonseed</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daemonseed</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9446" update="2012-05-06">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-01-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">R・D</title>
<title xml:lang="en">R.D.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">R.D</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9447" update="2012-05-06">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Winter Night Phantom</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Winter Night Phantom</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Winter Night Phantom</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9448" update="2012-05-06">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-12-08</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Beck Comes Back</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beck Comes Back</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Beck Comes Back</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9449" update="2012-05-06">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-11-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">The Call from The Past</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Call from the Past</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Call from the Past</title>
</episode>
<episode id="87818" update="2019-01-27">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1999-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="113361" update="2019-01-27">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>1999-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212266" update="2019-01-27">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1999-10-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
