<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9060" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1997-07-25</startdate>
<enddate>1997-07-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Field ni Soyogu Kaze</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">フィールドにそよぐ風</title>
</titles>
<creators>
<name id="1833" type="Direction">Katsumata Tomoharu</name>
<name id="48713" type="Work">Shinano Kikaku</name>
<name id="5504" type="Character Design">Kubo Hidemi</name>
<name id="10235" type="Original Work">Ikeda Daisaku</name>
</creators>
<description>Trying to prove he is the better soccer player, Kenji tackles and injures Yuta`s leg during a trial for the school team. Impressed by the fact that Yuta still does what he can to contribute to the team, Kenji begins to realize the true meaning of sportsmanship.
Source: MAL</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="9">4.21</permanent>
<temporary count="9">4.77</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>245850.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19961</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18443</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>235849</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11164</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="997" parentid="2881" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>association football</name>
<description>Football is a sport that involves kicking a ball in order to score a goal, while the other team tries to stop you by kicking the ball in the other direction to score a goal of their own. In the United States, this sport is known as soccer; the inappropriately titled "American" football (which in fact is played with the egg-shaped "ball" being carried around) is some kind of rugby for babies.</description>
<picurl>40031.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="138018" update="2012-03-18">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-07-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
