<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="908" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>3</episodecount>
<startdate>1997-01-25</startdate>
<enddate>1997-07-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gundam-W: Endless Waltz</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">新機動戦記ガンダムW エンドレス・ワルツ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">New Mobile Report Gundam Wing: Endless Waltz</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Shin Kidou Senki Gundam W: Endless Waltz</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">GUNDAM-W Endless Waltz</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Gundam Wing Endless Waltz OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Gundam Wing - Endless Waltz</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Mobile Suit Gundam Wing - Endless Waltz - OAV</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">기동전사 건담 Wing: Endless Waltz</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Gundam Wing: Endless Waltz</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Gundam Wing: Endless Waltz</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="229" type="Prequel">Shin Kidou Senki Gundam Wing</anime>
<anime id="496" type="Summary">Shin Kidou Senki Gundam Wing: Endless Waltz Tokubetsu Hen</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="312269">a great sequel for a legendary series!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="498732">A great sequel to the average series that Gundam Wing was. If you want an improved sequence of Gundam Wing with better animation, soundtrack and a more decent pace, this is definetely a must.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.gundam-w.jp/ova/index_frame.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="1352" type="Original Work">Yatate Hajime</name>
<name id="147" type="Original Work">Tomino Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="5680" type="Direction">Aoki Yasunao</name>
<name id="4144" type="Music">Ootani Kou</name>
<name id="1761" type="Character Design">Murase Shuukou</name>
</creators>
<description>After Colony 196 - One year has passed since the war between Earth and its colonies ended. Heero, Duo, Trowa and Quatre bid farewell to their Gundams and jettison them to the sun. Relena Darlian is now the deputy minister of the Earth Sphere Unified Nation. But as the Gundam pilots are adjusting to the peace on Earth, Relena is kidnapped and a new threat appears, led by Marimeia Khushrenada - daughter of the late dictator Treize Khushrenada and heir to the Barton Foundation. To make matters more complicated, Gundam Nataku pilot Wufei has sided with this faction. The Gundam pilots must recover their mobile suits and once again engage in battle before Marimeia`s forces succeed on their bid for global domination.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1202">6.45</permanent>
<temporary count="1213">7.42</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>149066.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>255</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>91</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>195</identifier>
<identifier>dqpvgt</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gundam-w.jp/ova/index_frame.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Gundam_Wing:_Endless_Waltz</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>新機動戦記ガンダムW_Endless_Waltz</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>814</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88187</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>159447</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>新機動戰記GUNDAM_W_無盡的華爾茲</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2880" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-01">
<name>Christmas</name>
<description>Christmas, also referred to as Christmas Day, is an annual holiday celebrated on December 25 that commemorates the birth of Jesus of Nazareth. The day marks the beginning of the larger season of Christmastide, which lasts twelve days. The nativity of Jesus, which is the basis for the Anno Domini system of dating, is thought to have occurred between 7 and 2 BC. December 25 is not known to be Jesus` actual date of birth, and the date may have been chosen to correspond with either a Roman festival or the winter solstice.
On the Julian calendar, followed by most Orthodox churches, Christmas Day also falls on O.S. December 25th; this corresponds to N.S. January 7th on the Gregorian calendar, followed by Western churches.
Modern customs of the holiday include gift-giving, Church celebrations, and the display of various decorations—including the Christmas tree, lights, mistletoe, nativity scenes, and holly. Santa Claus (also referred to as Father Christmas, although the two figures have different origins) is a popular mythological figure often associated with bringing gifts at Christmas for children. Santa is generally believed to be the result of a syncretization between Saint Nicholas and elements from pagan Nordic and Christian mythology, and his modern appearance is believed to have originated in 19th century media.
Christmas is celebrated throughout the Christian population, but is also celebrated by many non-Christians as a secular, cultural festival. Because gift-giving and several other aspects of the holiday involve heightened economic activity among both Christians and non-Christians, Christmas has become a major event for many retailers.</description>
<picurl>160837.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3575" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-13">
<name>damsel in distress</name>
<description>The damsel in distress is usually a young, nubile woman placed in a dire predicament by a villain or a monster and requires a hero to dash to her rescue. Often used to unite the cast of a show for this one goal, to make them put differences aside and become a band of nakama. 
Examples: Sakoshita Yanagi from Rekka no Honoo, Yuuki Miaka from Fushigi Yuugi or Higurashi Kagome from Inuyasha.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3852" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-09">
<name>Bright slap</name>
<description>"You hit me! Not even my father ever hit me!" 
You are the commander of a spaceship, leader of a faction or a team and your best mecha pilot stops fighting and grows increasingly hysterical and angsty, while the enemy could strike you at any time. What are you going to do? 
You slap or punch him, preferably in the face, and back to his senses while delivering a heroic speech that would turn any wimp into a man of destiny.
Named after Bright Noa of Mobile Suit Gundam, a prominent user of this for-sure method.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5929" parentid="2846" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>space opera</name>
<description>Space opera is a sub-genre of fiction that emphasizes romantic adventures in space. Space opera generally involves large-scale conflicts between opponents with powerful abilities and technology. The genre will often be melodramatic, sometimes playing music that can be nothing short of awesome. Warfare and a battle of wits are usually less emphasized, preferring romance (with exceptions, e.g. Ginga Eiyuu Densetsu). Some space operas tend to be formulaic and sometimes even prosaic, often employing very simple devices and somewhat obvious strategies. An example of this would be the infamous laws of physics in the Macross universe, in which the main male lead will hardly ever get hit in battle.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2851" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-24">
<rating votes="41">6.10</rating>
<name>Heero Yuy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>This mysterious youth was sent from the L1 space colony cluster to fight against Oz. He goes by the alias Heero Yuy, after the martyred leader of the space colonies; his real name, like almost everything else about him, is unknown. Heero has been trained since childhood for his role as pilot of the Wing Gundam, an upbringing that has made him cold and ruthless. But thanks to his years of training, Heero has become a perfect soldier equally skilled in personal combat, explosives, and computer hacking.</description>
<picture>72625.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2852" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-24">
<rating votes="39">5.63</rating>
<name>Relena Darlian</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Relena is the pampered daughter of the Earth Alliance`s vice minister for foreign affairs. Her father is responsible for the negotiations with the space colonists, an assignment which leaves Mr. Darlian little time for his wife and child. Her family`s wealth and status make Relena the star of her private school`s social scene, but do little to reduce her boredom and loneliness. When her quiet existence is disrupted by the Gundam pilots, this poor little rich girl discovers her own, previously untapped, reserves of strength and courage.</description>
<picture>72617.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2853" type="main character in" update="2011-10-24">
<rating votes="21">7.05</rating>
<name>Duo Maxwell</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Duo is a member of the scavenger organisation known as the Sweeper Group, which sent him to Earth to battle Oz. Despite the hardships he`s suffered in his young life, and the seriousness of his mission, Duo is always cheerful and good-natured. But when he goes into battle as pilot of the Gundam Deathscythe, striking from the shadows with its lethal beam scythe, he truly earns his nickname "God of Death."</description>
<picture>72899.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="384" picture="17230.jpg">Seki Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2854" type="main character in" update="2011-10-24">
<rating votes="13">2.24</rating>
<name>Trowa Barton</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The most mysterious of the Gundam pilots, the young man who calls himself Trowa was sent to Earth as the pilot of the Gundam Heavyarms. The cool, quiet Trowa has nerves of steel and superb reflexes, qualities which serve him well in his cover identity as an acrobatic clown in a traveling circus troupe. He also has soldiering experience far beyond his years. When combined with his heavily-armed Gundam, Trowa`s tactical skill and combat ability make him a veritable one-man army.</description>
<picture>72900.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2218" picture="226178.jpg">Nakahara Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2855" type="main character in" update="2011-10-24">
<rating votes="14">4.45</rating>
<name>Quatre Rabarba Winner</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Quatre is a young aristocrat, the thirtieth child - and only son - of a wealthy family of space colony developers. Though he`s the most tender-hearted and gentle of the Gundam pilots, Quatre is just as brave and determined, and has defied his family`s wishes in order to join the battle against Oz. Quatre is aided by a troop of forty loyal underlings and can draw on the Winner family`s vast resources, assets which more than make up for his relative lack of fighting skill.</description>
<picture>72932.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="588" picture="41015.jpg">Orikasa Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2856" type="main character in" update="2011-10-24">
<rating votes="8">2.57</rating>
<name>Chang Wufei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wufei is the descendant of a legendary Chinese warrior clan, who sent him to Earth to fight against Oz. This proud fighter lives by a strict code of honour, punishing evil and enforcing justice as he sees fit. Wufei prefers to operate solo, since he has little patience for lesser warriors. These high standards make him equally contemptuous of his own failings in battle. The only ally he trusts is his Shenlong Gundam, which he has nicknamed "Nataku" after a hero of Chinese mythology.</description>
<picture>72933.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2219" picture="23794.jpg">Ishino Ryuuzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2857" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-24">
<rating votes="13">7.74</rating>
<name>Zechs Merquise</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>This masked warrior is Oz`s top mobile suit pilot. Up until now, Oz has disguised itself as the Earth Federation`s elite "Specials" taskforce, and Zechs has accumulated numerous distinctions during his career in the Specials. He earned the highest marks in the history of the Lake Victoria military academy, received the first two-rank promotion in the history of the Specials, and acquired the nickname "Lightning Baron" for his exploits. Zechs` accomplishments have made him a hero among Oz`s soldiers, but this master soldier is cunning enough not to overestimate his own abilities or underestimate those of his enemies.</description>
<picture>72934.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2858" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-24">
<rating votes="20">7.41</rating>
<name>Lucrezia Noin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Noin is a good friend of Zechs from his days at the Lake Victoria military academy. After graduation, she joined the academy`s staff, and now trains new Specials recruits in the art of space combat. Though Noin is a formidable mobile suit pilot, she doesn`t much care for fighting, and she often uses her influence with Oz`s leader to try to resolve crisis situations peacefully.</description>
<picture>72939.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="491" picture="38232.jpg">Yokoyama Chisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2860" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-24">
<rating votes="28">4.84</rating>
<name>Lady Une</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lady Une is Treize`s loyal aide and agent, whom he often assigns to assassinate enemies or command important field operations. While she is passionately devoted to Treize, Lady Une shows no mercy to her master`s foes, and is infamous for her overzealous cruelty. One day she`s demurely running water for Treize`s bath, the next she`s bombing diplomats or threatening to attack unarmed space colonies. You`d almost think she had some kind of split personality..</description>
<picture>72961.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2221" picture="83141.jpg">Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2861" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-24">
<rating votes="13">4.63</rating>
<name>Sally Po</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sally is a honest and well-meaning young officer, assigned to the Earth Alliance`s intelligence bureau. She captures Heero early in the story, and is intrigued by the mysterious young Gundam pilot. She will reappear later in the story, and encounter Heero and his friends again...</description>
<picture>72962.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1446" picture="19314.jpg">Touma Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2862" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-08">
<name>Rashid Kurama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The leader of the Maganac Corps, the large, bearded Rashid is one of Quatre`s best friends and allies. Above all else, he values his teammates` lives and treats each of them as family.</description>
<picture>18496.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42809" picture="223789.jpg">Nakata Kazuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2864" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-24">
<rating votes="22">5.95</rating>
<name>Catherine Bloom</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A talented acrobat and knife-thrower, Catherine is the star performer of Trowa`s circus troupe. At first, she finds Trowa somewhat creepy, but she eventually warms up to her clown comrade and ultimately comes to think of him as a surrogate little brother.</description>
<picture>72966.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2222" picture="25843.jpg">Suzuki Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2867" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-24">
<rating votes="3">1.63</rating>
<name>Doctor J</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The engineer and creator of Wing Gundam and Heero`s mentor, he is an expert in the field of beam weaponry. His distinguishing features include mechanical-looking goggles and a cybernetic right arm. Quirky but affable, Doctor J is immensely proud of Heero`s abilities and encourages the young man to choose his own fate, including protecting Darlian and rejecting Operation Meteor. It was J who chose Heero`s codename, which he thinks is highly appropriate.</description>
<picture>72977.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2220" picture="188715.jpg">Inaba Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2868" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-24">
<name>Professor G</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The engineer and creator of Deathscythe, as well as co-creator of the spaceship Peacemillion and Duo`s mentor. He is distinguished by his long nose, mushroom-shaped hair and a long scar on his cheek. Sardonic and, like Doctor J, rather eccentric, he tends to describe Deathscythe as "the ultimate work of art", perhaps due to his specialization in stealth systems. A member of the Sweeper group, he was impressed by Duo cracking his security codes and offered to train him as a Gundam pilot.</description>
<picture>72979.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3135" picture="24120.jpg">Fujimoto Yuzuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2870" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-24">
<name>H Kyouju</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The engineer and creator of Sandrock and Quatre`s mentor. He is rather fat, with a receding hairline and a thin, dark mustache that stands straight out at each end. A worker at MO-III, he originally met Quatre when the young heir`s shuttle was hijacked by the Maganac Corps. After learning of the youth`s strength and resolve, he ended up taking a job as Quatre`s tutor while borrowing Winner family resources to build Sandrock.</description>
<picture>72988.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27206" picture="73948.jpg">Taguchi Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39139" type="appears in" update="2011-11-29">
<rating votes="8">6.84</rating>
<name>XXXG-00W0 Wing Gundam-0</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>77782.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="39140" type="appears in" update="2011-11-29">
<name>XXXG-01D2 Gundam Deathscythe Hell</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>77783.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="39141" type="appears in" update="2011-11-29">
<name>XXXG-01H2 Gundam Heavyarms Kai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>77784.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="39142" type="appears in" update="2011-11-29">
<name>XXXG-01SR2 Gundam Sandrock Kai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>77785.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="39143" type="appears in" update="2011-11-29">
<name>XXXG-01S2 Altron Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>77786.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="39144" type="appears in" update="2011-11-29">
<name>OZ-00MS2B Tallgeese III</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>77787.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="39145" type="appears in" update="2011-11-29">
<name>MMS-01 Serpent</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>77788.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="39146" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-29">
<rating votes="6">5.72</rating>
<name>Mariemaia Khushrenada</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young child, Mariemaia is apparently the daughter of Leia Barton and Treize Khushrenada, conceived during the meeting between the two on Colony X-18999 (as detailed in the Episode Zero manga). Supposedly dying at an early age, Mariemaia later resurfaced as the figurehead of the Mariemaia Army, which largely consisted of soldiers who had been loyal to Treize. Thanks to her grandfather Dekim`s grooming, she was fully prepared to ravage the Earth and take her place as the World Sovereign, believing this to be what her father, Treize, would have wanted. She continued believing this until Relena slapped some sense into her-- literally. When Lady Une explained to the young girl that Dekim`s goals were not the same as Treize`s, Mariemaia realized her mistake and jumped in front of Relena to save her from being killed by Mariemaia`s enraged grandfather, resulting in Mariemaia being shot through the spine. She was given medical attention, and is later shown (in a wheelchair, though later appearances show her to have healed) visiting her father`s grave with Lady Une.</description>
<picture>77789.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="555" picture="23759.jpg">Sakuma Rei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39147" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-29">
<name>Dekim Barton</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Once one of Heero Yuy`s top aides, Dekim was present when the colonial leader was assassinated. From that moment on, he began plotting his revenge. However, even after he killed Odin Lowe (the man who shot Yuy), Dekim was not satisfied; he was convinced that the only way to make things equal after the decades of colonial oppression was for the colonies to take over the Earth Sphere, with the Barton family as the ruling family. To that end, he tracked down five of the engineers who had created the Tallgeese and commissioned them to create the Gundams for use with his ultimate plan: Operation Meteor. The original plan entailed dropping colonies onto Earth at strategic locations, and using the Gundams to take control in the ensuing chaos. For Dekim, the scientists and their young pilots didn`t agree with this plan, and stole the Gundams, using them instead to fight for the colonies` independence without resorting to genocide. Infuriated, Dekim began working out a new version of Operation Meteor. Using the Serpent mobile suit left behind by OZ, and the fact that his daughter Leia supposedly had a child with Treize Khushrenada, Dekim launched another Operation Meteor on Christmas Eve AC 196. However, his plan began to crumble once again, thanks to the intervention of the Gundam pilots (and later the common people themselves). Attempting to kill Relena Darlian, Dekim shot Mariemaia when she ran in front of Relena to protect her, then was himself shot in the head and killed by one of his soldiers, who immediately apologized to Treize for betraying his vision.</description>
<picture>77791.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3281" picture="154160.jpg">Yoda Eisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="9469" update="2003-07-31">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">静かなる軌道[サイレント·オービット]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Silent Orbit</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le silence de l`espace</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Silent Orbit</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9470" update="2005-12-30">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">過ぎ去りし流星[オペレーション·メテオ]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Operation Meteor</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Opération Meteor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Operation Meteor</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9472" update="2005-12-30">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1997-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">永遠への回帰[リターン·トゥ·フォーエバー]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Return To Forever</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Retour vers l`infini</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Return to Forever</title>
</episode>
<episode id="164363" update="2014-11-22">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>1997-07-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="164364" update="2014-11-22">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1997-04-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
