<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9090" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>10</episodecount>
<startdate>2012-10-13</startdate>
<enddate>2012-12-15</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Seitokai no Ichizon Lv.2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Seitokai no Ichizon 2</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">学生会的一己之见2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">seizon 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">生徒会の一存 Lv.2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Student Council`s Discretion Lv. 2</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6556" type="Prequel">Seitokai no Ichizon</anime>
<anime id="9474" type="Side Story">Seitokai no Ichizon Lv.2: Watasu Seitokai</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="5">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="545921">I think first season was better, may be even much better. So this one I can recommend only for fans.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="655071">The main character will mature. And he`s just more hentai than season 1 =))</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="432674">For me, this was better than season 1.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="594546">This season was much better than the last! There was more Romance/Drama/Seriousness and had the right amount of comedy etc. I`m also hoping for a season 2, come on everybody, make this a must see so we can receive a season 3!!!!!!!!!! I give this a 9.7</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="302786">During the last few weeks I shed tears of joy considering how amazing this show is, but now since we`re at the end I`m also shedding tears of sadness, knowing it`s over.

The best anime of 2009 got an amazing sequel. I can recommend everybody to watch this, it`s easily one of the best show I`ve seen in years and most likely the best anime of 2012. You`ll miss out on great entry in the comedy genre is you skip this.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://kadokawa-anime.jp/seitokai/</url>
<creators>
<name id="732" type="Animation Work">AIC</name>
<name id="1790" type="Series Composition">Yoshida Reiko</name>
<name id="2196" type="Direction">Imaizumi Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="9949" type="Original Work">Inugami Kira</name>
<name id="9950" type="Original Work">Aoi Sekina</name>
<name id="11999" type="Character Design">Onoda Masato</name>
<name id="6585" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yoda Masahiko</name>
<name id="11999" type="Chief Animation Direction">Onoda Masato</name>
<name id="10966" type="Music">Anzai Takaaki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a light novel series by http://anidb.net/cr9950 [Aoi Sekina], with illustrations by http://anidb.net/cr9949 [Inugami Kira].
http://anidb.net/ch11644 [Sugisaki Ken], through diligence and academic excellence, has successfully entered the paradise that is the Hekiyou Private Academy`s Student Council. There, he boldly embarks on his plan to create his personal harem with the four girls who are the other council members, namely:
The incredibly youthful president http://anidb.net/ch11624 [Sakurano Kurimu]; the cool and kindly yet super-sadistic secretary http://anidb.net/ch11641 [Akaba Chizuru]; the tomboyish and hot-blooded vice-president http://anidb.net/ch11642 [Shiina Minatsu]; and the ephemerally beautiful yet complicated treasurer http://anidb.net/ch11643 [Shiina Mafuyu].
While every day since then has been non-stop fun, Graduation Day now looms near. Could this spell the end of their carefree days?
~ translated and adapted from official site by Cranston</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="974">5.91</permanent>
<temporary count="982">7.07</temporary>
<review count="2">5.41</review>
</ratings>
<picture>94635.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13222</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10464</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5069</identifier>
<identifier>rokwbt</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://kadokawa-anime.jp/seitokai/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Seitokai_no_Ichizon</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>生徒会の一存</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2776</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>343787</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15336</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>seitokai-no-ichizon-student-councils-discretion</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2455" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>tsundere</name>
<description>Tsundere (ツンデレ) (pronounced /(t)sʌnˈdɪə(r)/ in English or /t͡sun.de.ɽe/ in Japanese) is a Japanese concept of a character archetype which describes a person with a conceited, irritable, and/or violent personality that suddenly becomes modest and loving when triggered by some sort of cause (such as being alone with someone). The inverse scenario, where a modest and loving person becomes conceited/irritable/violent, is also a tsundere.
The default state does not matter. The character can default to "tsuntsun" or "deredere"; the key concept is the fact that there`s a (generally very quick) flip from one mode to the other.
It can also describe a contradictory personality which is good-willed on the inside, but with a harsh attitude on the outside. Originally found in Japanese bishoujo games, the word is now part of the otaku moe phenomenon, reaching into other media such as anime, manga, novels, and even mass media.
Tsundere is a portmanteau of the two words tsuntsun (ツンツン), and deredere (デレデレ). Tsuntsun is defined as "aloof, morose, pointed", and deredere is defined as "exhausted, lovestruck". Tsunderekko (ツンデレっ娘) is a related noun, referring to a girl with a tsundere personality. Like nekomimi, tsundere is considered a moe-inspiring character trait. The concept has received increasing attention in Japan, with a tsundere cafe opened in Akihabara and tsundere-themed products released (like Tomy Co.`s portable television set), and the concept increasingly reflected in recent anime, from an extended discussion of the meaning of the concept and its origin on the internet in http://anidb.net/a4777 [Lucky Star]`s Lucky Channel segment to merchandise for http://anidb.net/a3651 [The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya] classifying the characters according to tsundere-ness. Another accepted definition of tsundere is a girl who has a combative attitude toward others but is also kind on the inside. She usually plays out as having an attitude toward the main character, usually a male, and often criticizing him in one way or another, but as the series progresses she eventually warms up to him and sometimes even falls in love with him.</description>
<picurl>30388.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4176" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-05-14">
<name>OP and ED sung by characters</name>
<description>OP and/or ED in this anime is sung by the characters and animation shows them singing.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6577" parentid="2869" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-17">
<name>student government</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="11624" type="main character in" update="2018-04-06">
<rating votes="68">4.67</rating>
<name>Sakurano Kurimu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakurano Kurimu is a senior in Hekiyou Academy and the president of its student council.</description>
<picture>35164.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9511" picture="35179.jpg">Honda Mariko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11641" type="main character in" update="2017-06-04">
<rating votes="117">7.88</rating>
<name>Akaba Chizuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chizuru is the Secretary of the Student Council. She has a tall and model-like figure. She is a mature woman who seems to spend most of her time being quite serious. However, she has a sadistic side to her, which is shown when she "brain-washes" Ken and Kurimu. Also, she makes a lot of references to her sadism in the anime. She loves to cuddle and "abuse" the President (Kurimu) in a little sister way, and is an avid reader. Sometimes, it is hinted towards her wanting to be involved with Kurimu. She is hinted towards having a couple part-time jobs despite being too young legally to even have a job. While she is identified as the cool, serious type, she can embrace her more cutesy side to her once hopping around dressed as a cute sheep. Chizuru and Ken met in autumn when Ken was suffering from a broken heart. Their meeting healed it and showed him compassion for others. Like the season she represents, she always seems a bit gloomy and hard to approach but has a certain elegance to her.</description>
<picture>45071.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5889" picture="30436.jpg">Mina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11642" type="main character in" update="2017-06-04">
<rating votes="67">7.59</rating>
<name>Shiina Minatsu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Minatsu is a bold character and Student Council Vice-president. A tomboy with impressive athletic skills, and is surprisingly also good at maths, which Ken considers to be uncharacteristic of her. She`s popular among girls and has a bit of a yuri taste. She`s in the same class with Ken but she`s an orthodox tsundere without any `dere` to be found. She also has a little sister, Mafuyu. She`s very protective of Mafuyu and despises anyone who tries to hurt her. She is into Shounen manga and most of her suggestions tend to be based on typical Shounen manga plots. Minatsu and Ken met in the summer. Because of how she was, he looked up to her and to be like her. Their meeting taught him not to be lazy and work if he desires something. Like the season she represents, she`s fired up and is always ready to take action, especially when it has something to do with anime or manga.</description>
<picture>45069.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9512" picture="35180.jpg">Togashi Misuzu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11643" type="main character in" update="2017-06-04">
<rating votes="64">6.96</rating>
<name>Shiina Mafuyu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mafuyu is the Student Council Treasurer. Minatsu`s sister and the only freshman in the Council. She is a swaying bishoujo, and is afraid of males (though she lightens up to Ken). Ken thought her to be "the easiest character to see the ending" but later turns out to be the most feared one by some reason, even when compared to Chizuru, particularly the fact that she`s into yaoi, and that she fantasizes pairing Ken romantically with a boy named Nakameguro (who turns out to be an actual person). When it comes to yaoi, Mafuyu can actually be just as perverted, if not worse, than Ken. She`s addicted to video games, and spends much of her free time playing with a handheld game console that resembles a pink PlayStation Portable. Despite her shy personality (or based on Ken`s logic, because she`s shy) she confesses her love to Ken, although she says she just wanted to share her feelings with him rather than start a relationship, because she loves the Student Council`s atmosphere most of all, implying that even when she loves him she doesn`t want to change how things are at the moment. Mafuyu and Ken met in the winter chatting online with him as Yuki (with Ken as Key) and even having a more spirited personality online. Ken fell asleep once in the snow and, despite her fear of men, took him out of the freezing cold. Their meeting showed him a clear understanding about what strength really is. Like the season she represents, she`s extremely passive and keeps a lot to herself, but she will show her real self and her real feelings if she feels comfortable.</description>
<picture>45070.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5886" picture="30429.jpg">Nomizu Iori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11644" type="main character in" update="2017-06-04">
<rating votes="87">7.88</rating>
<name>Sugisaki Ken</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ken is a 2nd Year student, and holds the Student Council "Blue Chip" Seat and Vice President. He entered the student council as the top-scoring student in his year; the highest scoring student automatically receives a place on the student council. He had to work hard to improve his score, being in the lowest score bracket when he enrolled. He is referred to as "Kii-kun" by Chizuru, from his given name Ken which also can be read as Kagi (a key). Loves playing eroge and galge, and plans on making the rest of the student council members his harem. On the surface, he seems to be lazy and carefree, but he is actually very hardworking and always stays behind after dismissal to finish all the student council work so that the student council can have fun as always. Ken also has a serious side to him, and he truly cares for those around him; According to Kurimu, they are yet to find someone Ken dislikes. Ken reveals to Lilicia that the student council itself is his "dream", where his goals and happiness co-exist.</description>
<picture>45068.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="616" picture="18138.jpg">Kondou Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12456" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-02">
<rating votes="26">6.07</rating>
<name>Magiru Satori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39576.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1431" picture="25110.jpg">Kosuge Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12458" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-23">
<rating votes="32">5.54</rating>
<name>Toudou Lilicia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The President of the Journalism Club, and ranked fifth in the school`s popularity poll; just falling short of getting into the Student Council. Lilicia and Kurimu are constantly at loggerheads. Lilicia also seems to be extremely afraid of Chizuru. She claims that she despises the current Student Council because they always laze around, doing nothing.</description>
<picture>45072.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13265" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-26">
<rating votes="38">6.33</rating>
<name>Toudou Ellis</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39336.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="550" picture="151677.jpg">Shimizu Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47038" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-12-25">
<rating votes="7">4.65</rating>
<name>Uchuu Meguru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129935.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="357" picture="32000.jpg">Shintani Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47039" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-12-25">
<rating votes="14">7.44</rating>
<name>Sugisaki Ringo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129934.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1961" picture="222838.jpg">Yonezawa Madoka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47040" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-12-25">
<rating votes="6">6.24</rating>
<name>Matsubara Asuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129932.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49424" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-06-04">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Uchuu Mamoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203509.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5666" picture="157275.jpg">Satou Yuudai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49425" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-03">
<rating votes="13">5.94</rating>
<name>Minase Runa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129933.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51641" type="appears in" update="2012-12-25">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Misaki-sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129936.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8843" picture="33258.jpg">Sakakibara Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53840" type="appears in" update="2013-03-15">
<name>Komiyama</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="27341" picture="74876.jpg">Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53841" type="appears in" update="2013-03-15">
<name>Oba-chan (Koubaibu)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="36317" picture="133733.jpg">Ootsuka Sato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53842" type="appears in" update="2013-03-15">
<name>Kikuchi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="11091" picture="39961.jpg">Manaka Keigo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53843" type="appears in" update="2013-03-15">
<name>Lacrosse-bu Buchou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="1611" picture="70006.jpg">Horikawa Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53844" type="appears in" update="2013-03-15">
<name>Ten`in</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="32034" picture="85884.jpg">Mizuno Takao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53845" type="appears in" update="2013-03-15">
<name>Nakai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="36258" picture="226031.jpg">Oohashi Setsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53846" type="appears in" update="2013-03-15">
<name>Wakai Nakai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="9113" picture="124968.jpg">Itou Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="143691" update="2012-09-01">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144787" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">すぎさきメモリアル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Memories of Sugisaki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sugisaki Memorial</title>
<summary>Sugisaki believes he can make himself over into one of the characters in his game.  All is 
going well until the top ranked student in the school forces him to choose the correct path.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617177</identifier>
<identifier>seitokai-no-ichizon-student-councils-discretion</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="145193" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-11-24</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">歓迎する生徒会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Student Council Welcomes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kangei Suru Seitokai</title>
<summary>An unexpected guest shakes the student council down their core leaving them void of their once blissful ignorance.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617671</identifier>
<identifier>seitokai-no-ichizon-student-councils-discretion</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="145194" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-11-17</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">聖戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crusade</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seisen</title>
<summary>Sugisaki and Sakurano are the only ones in the student council room and the tension is killing them.  Later, Sugisaki must admit to his sister his evil deeds.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617669</identifier>
<identifier>seitokai-no-ichizon-student-councils-discretion</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="145195" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-11-10</airdate>
<rating votes="8">9.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">回収する生徒会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Student Council Collects</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaishuu Suru Seitokai</title>
<summary>Jealousy burns between Ken and Minatsu as they go around collecting the student surveys.  
Things reach the point of no return when Minatsu pins Ken down and goes in for the… 
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617667</identifier>
<identifier>seitokai-no-ichizon-student-councils-discretion</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="145196" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">就職する生徒会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Student Council Seeks Employment</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuushoku Suru Seitokai</title>
<summary>The student council agrees that they don’t want to end up like Mafuyu, so they discuss their future plans when they are finished with school. 
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617665</identifier>
<identifier>seitokai-no-ichizon-student-councils-discretion</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="145197" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">疑う生徒会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Student Council`s Suspicions</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Utagau Seitokai</title>
<summary>The Presidents cake is missing and the entire student council are her prime suspects. The case is going well until Sugisaki suffers mysterious head trauma. 
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617663</identifier>
<identifier>seitokai-no-ichizon-student-councils-discretion</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="145198" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">テコ入れする生徒会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Student Council`s New Direction</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tekoire Suru Seitokai</title>
<summary>The Student Council brainstorms ways to get new viewers to watch a boring show about nothing.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617661</identifier>
<identifier>seitokai-no-ichizon-student-councils-discretion</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="145875" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="7">9.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">終わらない生徒会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Eternal Student Council</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Owaranai Seitokai</title>
<summary>This is Sugisaki last chance to tell his harem how he truly feels.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617677</identifier>
<identifier>seitokai-no-ichizon-student-councils-discretion</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="145876" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-12-08</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">追いかける生徒会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Student Council Chases</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oikakeru Seitokai</title>
<summary>A frantic call from Ringo leads the Student Council hunting for a kidnapped Sugisaki.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617675</identifier>
<identifier>seitokai-no-ichizon-student-councils-discretion</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="145877" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-12-01</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Sサイズハンター</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Size S Hunter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">S Size Hunter</title>
<summary>Mafuyu is afraid she is just a secondary character while Sugisaki has been assigned to shadow a 
real secondary character. 
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617673</identifier>
<identifier>seitokai-no-ichizon-student-councils-discretion</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146704" update="2013-01-11">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-12-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146705" update="2013-01-11">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-12-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146706" update="2013-01-11">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-12-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146707" update="2013-01-11">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-11-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146708" update="2013-01-11">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-11-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146709" update="2013-01-11">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-11-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146710" update="2013-01-11">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-11-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146711" update="2013-01-11">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-10-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146712" update="2013-01-11">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-10-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146713" update="2013-01-11">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-10-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146714" update="2013-01-11">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-10-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155827" update="2013-11-04">
<epno type="3">C21</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode C21</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155828" update="2013-11-04">
<epno type="3">C20</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode C20</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155829" update="2013-11-04">
<epno type="3">C19</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode C19</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155830" update="2013-11-04">
<epno type="3">C18</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode C18</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155831" update="2013-11-04">
<epno type="3">C17</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode C17</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155832" update="2013-11-04">
<epno type="3">C16</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode C16</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155833" update="2013-11-04">
<epno type="3">C15</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode C15</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155834" update="2013-11-04">
<epno type="3">C14</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode C14</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155835" update="2013-11-04">
<epno type="3">C13</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode C13</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155836" update="2013-11-04">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode C12</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
