<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9153" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2012-10-09</startdate>
<enddate>2013-03-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sakura-sou no Pet na Kanojo</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Кошечка из Сакурасо</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Дівчатко-звірятко із Сакура-со</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">sakurasou</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">さくら荘のペットな彼女</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The Pet Girl of Sakurasou</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">사쿠라장의 애완 그녀</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">ซากุระโซว หอพักสร้างฝัน</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">樱花庄的宠物女孩</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="5909" approval="82" total="133">Toradora!</anime>
<anime id="10288" approval="68" total="82">Bokura wa Minna Kawai-sou</anime>
<anime id="7903" approval="51" total="82">Denpa Onna to Seishun Otoko</anime>
<anime id="2835" approval="29" total="54">Hachimitsu to Clover</anime>
<anime id="288" approval="7" total="15">Maison Ikkoku</anime>
<anime id="11352" approval="4" total="18">Imouto sae Ireba Ii.</anime>
<anime id="8620" approval="4" total="17">Ano Natsu de Matteru</anime>
<anime id="9801" approval="2" total="10">Nourin</anime>
<anime id="1055" approval="2" total="3">Koko wa Green Wood</anime>
<anime id="12" approval="1" total="15">Chobits</anime>
<anime id="6780" approval="1" total="13">Working!!</anime>
<anime id="4691" approval="1" total="9">Nodame Cantabile</anime>
<anime id="10295" approval="1" total="6">Mangaka-san to Assistant-san to: The Animation</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="27">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="165460">Mildly interesting slice of life romance/drama that gets tiring from constant overdramatization. Still somewhat enjoyable.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="298465">A show where it shows you that you can learn from failure. The main female lead is quite interesting but the male lead is lacking. Visible character development.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="107121">didnt think much about it, but after watching i must say i wasnt disappointed. if you are looking for an anime that will inspire you to never give up or a bit of a good laugh, i honestly believe this anime will do it :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="409371">I am usually a person that do not show much emotion, but this series really made tears fall down my cheeks. Yes, this series really moved me. 

The characters are all very memorable (Mashiro-chan, go for it! You can win over Sorata!), the OP`s an ED`s and in-series music are all very good, but most of all, it have a moving story. 

I sincerely hope this series will get a second season.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="332307">I started the serie without expectations and it fulfilled them. It`s heart warming, comic, and enjoy to watch. No sulking or driving crazy pratogonist and all the characters are easy to handle. May be a final in love triangle should be nicer in ending but not necessary. Watch it omae!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="240447">A good series to watch. Each character has their own unique traits which adds colour to the series. While it does have the cookie cutter boy-meets-girl with a love-triangle tossed in, I did enjoy the overall story. 

The story has some darker moments but ultimately I particularly like the overall message of never giving up on your dreams and how life is unfair sometimes. The message resonates easily with me and (I bet) with a lot of its viewers.

A good pick-me-up kind of series.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="373896">I liked the characters, liked the plot, liked the ending. There were lukewarm moments but that just happens. I wasn`t swept off my feet, but I think this is a heart warming series and it was well paced. Nothing was too slow or too fast. It made me laugh and it made me smile :)
Recommended! ^^</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="398618">The situations that the characters are in thrown in may be cliche, but the portrayal of the characters is so compelling that they seem real. This is more than a simple ecchi comedy.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="90663">Very touching and heartful. Be sure to stock up tissues and be ready for a show you can not wait to see, what will happen in the next episode. I really hope this one gets a sequel. I`d recommend this anime even to those who arn`t that much into slice of life/schooldays genre. For those who are, it is a must see.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="759628">It`s about friends living on their own and enjoying love stories.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="239305">great for school, daily life fans

was fun and easy to watch although I would liked smarter male protagonists</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="557271">This is the best anime I`ve ever seen and I`ve seen some really good ones. I laughed in every single episode! Even when I was crying a damn river out of heart-warmingness, they still made me laugh my butt off! The characters were all very unique in their own way, they all had their specific problems and characteristics, they were all funny! I enjoyed it so very much! I had been looking for an anime this good for a long time! A huge thanks to the creators, this was one of the best experiences I have ever had! :D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="250106">From the first to the last episode, I could not stop laughing. Defitinely a must see if you like comedy, romance, and a mix of these when used in a fun and heartwarming anime. One of the very best I`ve seen so far!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="265326">The moment when i stumbled upon this anime. Is the moment i fell in love . 

The story , the cast , the emotions , the voice acting . Everything about it is memorable.  I will curse myself if i ever forget about this anime.  The joy i had watching it is beyond words . A truly heartwarming  story . DON`T MISS IT ! . 

And don`t let the rating fool you , I`m amazed its so underrated</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="446059">It has been awhile since i laughed and smiled this much watching an anime :X I can`t even put into words how much i love it!! You`ll be hooked after the 1st episode, so if u want an original plot, characters and jokes don`t hesitate, u won`t wasting your time!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="37962">So much fun, so much drama, so good! Mashiiro banzai! Sorata banzai!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="432591">Even if you`re not into these genres, I definitely think it`s a must watch. Loved every episode of it, the characters are unique, you really get inspired by them. It is a pretty slow paced romance but I`m gonna repeat myself, it`s unique and you will understand as soon as you watch it. The fact that they didn`t plan on another season makes me sad. Good plot continuity, awesome character development, remarkable dramatic moments; gave it a 10.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="387237">Don`t let the recommendations and reviews phase you. This anime is the greatest of all time, and I am difficult to enthrall! 11/10

It is not a generic harem or love triangle. 
It is not a generic romance story. 
It is not entirely cliche, done-to-death, or pandering fan service moeblob. These buzzwords need to STOP.

This IS some of the greatest type of slice of life, drama, comedy and everything all together. The characters are so full of life, and the execution, development and feeling throughout the entire animation was amazing.
I can`t wait for the Blu Rays.

I solemnly believe that the "General Lack of Common Sense" category tag is inaccurate. Every other anime deserves this more than Sakurasou.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="561560">In my opinion: one of the best animes of 2012. It has a great sense of humor and loads of creativity, which led me to viewing all episodes twice. Nearly every time I found little details that I missed at first glance. A superb mix of comedy and drama with a hint of ecchi.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="492628">Completely underrated, from what seams to be a simple situation comedy, turns into a well constructed drama about deep issues that torment us not only as teenagers but adults as well.
A good laugh is guaranteed with the bonus of being something more then that, smart, intelligent and well delivered.
Must see</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="727529">warm, deeply touching anime that can get you motivated. it shows that no matter how far you`ll have to go to keep being yourself, it`s worth it - and often fun, because life is full of surprises.

also, it`s ALIVE.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://sakurasou.tv/</url>
<creators>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="3744" type="Character Design">Fujii Masahiro</name>
<name id="122" type="Series Composition">Okada Mari</name>
<name id="6692" type="Direction">Ishizuka Atsuko</name>
<name id="32834" type="Original Work">Kamoshida Hajime</name>
<name id="5670" type="Music">Hayashi Yuuzou</name>
<name id="3076" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hiyamizu Yukie</name>
<name id="3744" type="Chief Animation Direction">Fujii Masahiro</name>
<name id="3082" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tomioka Hiroshi</name>
</creators>
<description>The second-year high school student http://anidb.net/ch43396 [Kanda Sorata] lives in Sakurasou, the dormitory for problem children at Sorata`s school. One day, http://anidb.net/ch43395 [Shiina Mashiro] — a cute girl who happens to be also a cosmopolitan, brilliant artist — moves into Sakurasou.
Sorata knowing the weirdos at the dormitory feels he should protect Mashiro. Surprisingly she seems to need more help than expected: she has no idea how to take care of herself, i.e. often gets lost, and her room is a complete mess. Sorata`s dorm mates designate him as the master of Mashiro, and thus, an ordinary boy and a brilliant girl live like a master and his pet.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="4211">7.15</permanent>
<temporary count="4260">7.64</temporary>
<review count="6">6.41</review>
</ratings>
<picture>225540.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14238</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13759</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5161</identifier>
<identifier>azgjxy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://sakurasou.tv/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Sakurasou_no_Pet_na_Kanojo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>さくら荘のペットな彼女</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2665</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>343777</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15234</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=3dWyWX7y3Xo</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=ab4fs9No18g</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=zadEh-7NGHM</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=HPTtuR1EF_U</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>the-pet-girl-of-sakurasou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="618" parentid="2565" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>trap</name>
<description>A trap is a plot device where a male character is mistaken for a female, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the male (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the male, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the male character as a female; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through his behaviour, and/or language. A male character misinterpreted by others as female, without action from the male (explicitly feminine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t1637 [reverse trap].
Note: the tag image is from http://anidb.net/a10475 [Himegoto].</description>
<picurl>161537.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2666" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-16">
<name>art school</name>
<description>The education in art plays an important part in this anime.
Art school is a general term for any educational institution with a primary focus on the visual arts, especially illustration, painting, photography, sculpture, and graphic design. The term applies to institutions with elementary, secondary, post-secondary or undergraduate, or graduate or postgraduate programs in these areas. They are distinguished from larger institutions which also may offer majors or degrees in the visual arts, but only as one part of a broad-based range of programs (such as the liberal arts and sciences). France`s École des Beaux-Arts is, perhaps, the first model for such organized instruction, breaking with a tradition of master and apprentice instruction when it was formed.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2671" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>school dormitory</name>
<description>A school dormitory or residence hall is the student living quarters at an elite academy, boarding school, or military school. The main characters may live or work at the dormitory, and it often becomes the backdrop for a reoccurring part of the story.</description>
<picurl>223167.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2779" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>multiple couples</name>
<description>More than one couple is developed in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2821" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sudden naked girl appearance</name>
<description>A character or group of characters are simply minding their own business, when suddenly, a naked girl appears. It does not matter how or why, but a naked someone is there. Sometimes the naked girl is not happy about this. 
Usually this is a fanservice element, but not always.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3037" parentid="2676" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo Skytree</name>
<description>Tokyo Skytree is a broadcasting, restaurant, and observation tower in Sumida, Tokyo, Japan. It became the tallest structure in Japan in 2010 and reached its full height of 634.0 metres in March 2011, making it the tallest tower in the world, displacing the Canton Tower, and the second tallest structure in the world after Burj Khalifa (829.8 m).
Source: Wikipedia
Note: Not to be confused with the very much older http://anidb.net/t3667 [Tokyo Tower].</description>
<picurl>161122.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4112" parentid="3842" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-14">
<name>excessive censoring</name>
<description>There are basically two cases to which this term can be applied to:
1) creative censorship
The TV station airing the anime does its best to remove most ecchi parts from the show, using various and original methods. Usually, an uncensored BD/DVD is released later. Apart from the publisher`s greed - sometimes the censorship is used intentionally to make a scene look more obscene than it actually is.
2) convenient censorship
Another case of it - more often known under the term of "convenient censoring/ship" - is a blatant substitute for mosaic/steam/etc. over nether regions. This applies both to normal shows with occasional nudity as a normal part of human life (or just occasional flash of fanservice), as well as to heavy ecchi / borderline hentai shows where /literally/ everything is a fair (and far more "obscene" no matter how to look at it) game, except that misinterpreted taboo nonsense coming from §175 of JPC.</description>
<picurl>169459.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4198" parentid="5604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-14">
<name>hard work and guts</name>
<description>One of the character`s motto in the anime. Because there is nothing that cannot be achieved by hard work and guts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4222" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>walls of text</name>
<description>Walls of text refers to Japanese text that appears in large quantities within the anime itself. This text is most likely vital to the storyline and may come in the form of charts and diagrams or pieces of paper, notes or even thoughts that are only partially or entirely unspoken.
May also be taken as a fair warning to viewers unable to translate Japanese text on their own, suggesting that thorough subtitle support may be required as well as making use of the pause button on their media players so that all text can be read.
Normally, tags don`t refer to physical translations of text, subtitle appearances and karaoke styling added by 3rd parties. But those who seek to describe an anime that is heavy on SPOKEN dialogue (which may tend to create a large quantity of natural subtitling to read for those not fluent in the language being used) could consider this tag but may make clearer reference with the dialogue driven tag.</description>
<picurl>32534.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4228" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-09">
<name>subtle OP ED sequence change</name>
<description>A (small) part of the opening or ending sequence changes after a certain episode, usually to reflect a plot milestone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4761" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-11">
<name>love letter</name>
<description>One of the characters in the anime receives a love letter, usually stashed away in their school shoe locker. Or in other cases a girl might directly give the love letter to the boy she loves.
Plot device to further the relationship between characters, may also be used as comedic element creating awkward situations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5640" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-16">
<name>video game development</name>
<description>Part of the anime`s story relates to creating video games.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5862" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-08">
<name>melodrama</name>
<description>A melodrama is a dramatic work that exaggerates plot and characters in order to appeal to the emotions, often with strongly stereotyped characters. Language, behaviour, or events which resemble melodramas are also called melodramatic. In scholarly and historical musical contexts melodramas are dramas of the 18th and 19th centuries in which orchestral music or song was used to accompany the action.
Melodrama is a style of drama that has been applied on the stage, in movies and television, and radio formats, from the 18th century to the present. Because of the long timeframe in which the style has existed, it is difficult to derive a precise definition. The term melodrama is most often used pejoratively, to suggest that the work to which the term is applied lacks sophistication or subtlety.
The term originated from the early 19th-century French word mélodrame, which is derived from Greek melos, music, and French drame, drama (from Late Latin drāma, which in turn derives from Greek drān, to do, perform).
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="43392" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-09-17">
<rating votes="41">3.18</rating>
<name>Mitaka Jin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jin is a senior taking the general curriculum, and a childhood friend of http://anidb.net/ch43393 [Misaki]`s. His goal is to be a scriptwriter, and he writes the scripts for Misaki`s anime. He`s also a fearsome playboy.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>92289.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43393" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-09-17">
<rating votes="67">7.28</rating>
<name>Kamiigusa Misaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Misaki is a senior taking the fine arts curriculum. Though her talent earned her a spot as a scholarship student, she`s a strange person who had her scholarship revoked for only making anime. She`s also childhood friends with http://anidb.net/ch43392 [Mitaka Jin].
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>92285.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23312" picture="205591.jpg">Takamori Natsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43394" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-09-17">
<rating votes="41">5.42</rating>
<name>Sengoku Chihiro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chihiro is an art teacher living in Sakurasou to keep an eye on its residents. She`s doing everything she can to find a partner. She`s also http://anidb.net/ch43395 [Mashiro]`s stepsister, but she pushes care of her off onto http://anidb.net/ch43396 [Sorata].
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>92288.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43395" type="main character in" update="2012-09-23">
<rating votes="153">7.30</rating>
<name>Shiina Mashiro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mashiro is a world-famous artist, but she came to Japan from England in order to be a manga artist. She`s a sophomore student taking the fine arts curriculum. She`s incapable of living normally on her own.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>92282.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43396" type="main character in" update="2013-09-17">
<rating votes="67">2.32</rating>
<name>Kanda Sorata</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sorata is a sophomore student taking the general curriculum. He was told to live in Sakurasou against his wishes. Because he`s a helpful person, the dorm students place him in charge of http://anidb.net/ch43395 [Mashiro].
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>92281.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20249" picture="186289.jpg">Matsuoka Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43397" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-23">
<rating votes="61">6.92</rating>
<name>Akasaka Ryuunosuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ryuunosuke is a sophomore programmer taking the general curriculum. He`s also a shut-in who only talks through chat or e-mails. Most of his e-mail replies are sent by Maid-chan, an auto-reply AI program he developed.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>92286.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43398" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-07-24">
<rating votes="102">7.70</rating>
<name>Aoyama Nanami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nanami is a sophomore taking the general curriculum, and http://anidb.net/ch43396 [Sorata]`s classmate. She`s a hardworker who supports herself with a part-time job while commuting to a voice actor training school.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>92283.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30438" picture="81362.jpg">Nakatsu Mariko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43399" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-01">
<rating votes="32">6.13</rating>
<name>Maid-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>127240.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49389" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-12-11">
<rating votes="29">4.57</rating>
<name>Kanda Yuuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kanda Yuuko is the little sister of http://anidb.net/ch43396 [Kanda Sorata].</description>
<picture>128597.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16794" picture="214757.jpg">Ogura Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49390" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-10-16">
<rating votes="15">3.76</rating>
<name>Iida Ayano</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126949.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49788" type="appears in" update="2012-10-10">
<rating votes="3">4.61</rating>
<name>Hikari</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126697.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49851" type="appears in" update="2012-10-13">
<rating votes="3">1.86</rating>
<name>Obasan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126834.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33929" picture="93420.jpg">Nagisa Una</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49852" type="appears in" update="2012-10-13">
<rating votes="2">1.67</rating>
<name>Naruse Meat no Ojisan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126832.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28471" picture="57632.jpg">Yamamoto Itaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49853" type="appears in" update="2012-10-13">
<rating votes="2">1.67</rating>
<name>Naruse Meat no Obasan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126833.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38121" picture="223543.jpg">Okada Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49854" type="appears in" update="2012-10-13">
<rating votes="4">3.75</rating>
<name>Miyahara Daichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126837.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23534" picture="74510.jpg">Murata Taishi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49855" type="appears in" update="2012-10-13">
<rating votes="2">1.67</rating>
<name>Kouchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126836.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2339" picture="151715.jpg">Taketora</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49856" type="appears in" update="2012-10-13">
<rating votes="2">1.67</rating>
<name>Sakanaya no Ojisan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126835.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32890" picture="89265.jpg">Nogawa Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49903" type="appears in" update="2014-02-16">
<rating votes="3">4.00</rating>
<name>Noriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150328.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1918" picture="225099.jpg">Sakurai Harumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49904" type="appears in" update="2013-09-25">
<rating votes="4">2.54</rating>
<name>Takasaki Mayu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143563.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28392" picture="224735.jpg">Kubo Yurika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50277" type="appears in" update="2012-12-19">
<rating votes="4">3.05</rating>
<name>Shirayama Koharu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129700.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="216" picture="171983.jpg">Takahashi Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50602" type="appears in" update="2012-11-14">
<rating votes="5">3.59</rating>
<name>Momoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128077.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50603" type="appears in" update="2012-11-14">
<rating votes="6">4.48</rating>
<name>Youseijo no Sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128079.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34901" picture="130616.jpg">Lynn</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50770" type="appears in" update="2012-11-25">
<rating votes="2">2.35</rating>
<name>Nanba Shiori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128599.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="643" picture="228609.jpg">Kojima Sachiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50771" type="appears in" update="2012-11-25">
<rating votes="2">2.35</rating>
<name>Yatai no Oyaji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128598.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28471" picture="57632.jpg">Yamamoto Itaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50772" type="appears in" update="2013-04-25">
<rating votes="6">4.23</rating>
<name>Sorata no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60287.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50773" type="appears in" update="2013-04-25">
<rating votes="4">6.63</rating>
<name>Sorata no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60286.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50891" type="appears in" update="2012-11-27">
<rating votes="6">2.97</rating>
<name>Fujisawa Kazuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128690.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="567" picture="80605.jpg">Asanuma Shintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50892" type="appears in" update="2012-11-27">
<rating votes="2">1.67</rating>
<name>Keibiin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128692.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50893" type="appears in" update="2012-11-27">
<rating votes="2">1.67</rating>
<name>Mensetsukan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128691.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31390" picture="151711.jpg">Shiga Madoka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50894" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-11-27">
<rating votes="35">5.32</rating>
<name>Rita Ainsworth</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128693.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51104" type="appears in" update="2013-09-25">
<rating votes="4">3.05</rating>
<name>Honjou Yayoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143562.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23686" picture="224554.jpg">Uchiyama Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51105" type="appears in" update="2013-02-28">
<rating votes="6">3.87</rating>
<name>Fukaya Shiho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132883.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34449" picture="171791.jpg">Oonishi Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51273" type="appears in" update="2012-12-18">
<rating votes="9">4.62</rating>
<name>Himemiya Saori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129584.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51274" type="appears in" update="2012-12-18">
<rating votes="3">3.74</rating>
<name>Tatebayashi Souichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129585.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51507" type="appears in" update="2012-12-19">
<rating votes="5">3.11</rating>
<name>Usagi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129697.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33633" picture="151771.jpg">Takahashi Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51508" type="appears in" update="2012-12-19">
<rating votes="2">1.67</rating>
<name>Shimauma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129696.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31313" picture="84218.jpg">Hanae Natsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51509" type="appears in" update="2012-12-19">
<rating votes="10">4.40</rating>
<name>Kamiigusa Fuuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129695.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51648" type="appears in" update="2014-02-16">
<rating votes="3">5.06</rating>
<name>Nakano Otoha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150327.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27218" picture="223318.jpg">Ootsubo Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52676" type="appears in" update="2013-02-05">
<rating votes="2">1.67</rating>
<name>Taiiku Kyoushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>131836.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5632" picture="158531.jpg">Sugisaki Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52926" type="appears in" update="2013-02-13">
<rating votes="3">1.66</rating>
<name>Jin (Youchien)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132126.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="26922" picture="73460.jpg">Dendou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52927" type="appears in" update="2013-02-13">
<rating votes="3">3.69</rating>
<name>Sennin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132125.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="564" picture="146195.jpg">Kiyokawa Motomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52928" type="appears in" update="2013-02-13">
<rating votes="6">4.27</rating>
<name>Kamiigusa Misaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132127.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23312" picture="205591.jpg">Takamori Natsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53953" type="appears in" update="2014-02-15">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Kyoutou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150281.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32890" picture="89265.jpg">Nogawa Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53954" type="appears in" update="2013-09-25">
<rating votes="2">1.67</rating>
<name>Shin Seito Kaichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143564.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10776" picture="77627.jpg">Shimazaki Nobunaga</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54378" type="appears in" update="2013-03-26">
<rating votes="6">3.30</rating>
<name>Himemiya Iori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59979.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="10776" picture="77627.jpg">Shimazaki Nobunaga</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54379" type="appears in" update="2013-03-26">
<rating votes="5">4.65</rating>
<name>Hase Kanna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59980.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="29353" picture="186153.jpg">Yamazaki Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105025" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-08-13">
<rating votes="2">7.02</rating>
<name>Akasaka Ryuunosuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237292.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="141530" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="22">7.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ねこ・しろ・ましろ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cat. White. Mashiro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Neko, Shiro, Mashiro</title>
<summary>Sorata is a normal student living in an abnormal dorm and has one goal: ESCAPE!   
But those plans are thrown when a new student moves in.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>612921</identifier>
<identifier>the-pet-girl-of-sakurasou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="144411" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-10-30</airdate>
<rating votes="19">8.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">色を変える世界</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A World of Changing Colors</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iro o Kaeru Sekai</title>
<summary>Big changes are happening at the Hall when Sorata finally makes his decision.  Will the other residents admit their true feelings, too?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>612929</identifier>
<identifier>the-pet-girl-of-sakurasou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="144412" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="20">7.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">近すぎて遠い...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">So Close and Yet So Far...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikasugite Tooi...</title>
<summary>Sorata’s determination to move out of Sakura Hall is being questioned by his dorm mates. As he tries to distance himself from Shiina, rumor of her visiting a love hotel causes him to rush to her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>612927</identifier>
<identifier>the-pet-girl-of-sakurasou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="144413" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="18">7.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絵を描いてきたの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Drew a Picture</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">E o Kaitekita no</title>
<summary>Sorata is tasked with watching over Shiina Mashiro, her naivety is slowing corrupting his life.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>612925</identifier>
<identifier>the-pet-girl-of-sakurasou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="144695" update="2013-04-18">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144696" update="2013-04-18">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144906" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="17">9.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">どでかい花火をあげてみろ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Set Off a Huge Firework</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dodekai Hanabi o Agetemiro</title>
<summary>Sorata has based the first round of the game competition! His time is now devoted to mastering his oral presentation and dealing with Mashiro new found interest in discovering what love is.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>612937</identifier>
<identifier>the-pet-girl-of-sakurasou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="144907" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="17">6.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">彼女のきょうしゅう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Her Homesickness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanojo no Kyoushuu</title>
<summary>If Mashiro and Nanami wasn’t enough, Sorata has to deal with someone who has known him all his life.  The jealous between these three rivals will bring Sorata to his knees.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>612935</identifier>
<identifier>the-pet-girl-of-sakurasou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="144908" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-11-13</airdate>
<rating votes="16">6.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雨あがりの青</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Blue After the Rain</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ame Agari no Ao</title>
<summary>Nanami has overworked herself with taking care of Shiina, her jobs, and voice acting school.  Her midterm 
presentation is coming up and she is in no shape to take it.  Can Sorata do anything to help her?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>612933</identifier>
<identifier>the-pet-girl-of-sakurasou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="144909" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-11-06</airdate>
<rating votes="16">7.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくら荘のまじめな彼女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Serious Girl of Sakura Hall</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura-sou no Majime na Kanojo</title>
<summary>A new girl is moving into Sakura Hall and things are going to get even more awkward.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>612931</identifier>
<identifier>the-pet-girl-of-sakurasou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="144915" update="2013-01-09">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-10-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145667" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-12-18</airdate>
<rating votes="13">8.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">銀河猫にゃぼろん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Milky Way Cat, Nyapollon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ginga Neko Nyaboron</title>
<summary>Even though the festival has started, a last minute change by Sorata has everyone in Sakura Hall rushing to implement his changes.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>612945</identifier>
<identifier>the-pet-girl-of-sakurasou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="145668" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-12-11</airdate>
<rating votes="13">9.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キライキライ, ダイスキ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hate Hate, Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kirai Kirai, Daisuki</title>
<summary>Work on Nyapollon is starting to back up; the idea is to bring in an additional artist.  But the only one who can match Mashiro’s work is Rita…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>612943</identifier>
<identifier>the-pet-girl-of-sakurasou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="145669" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="14">7.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">秋の嵐がやってきた</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fall Storm Is Here</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aki no Arashi ga Yattekita</title>
<summary>One night, Mashiro`s English school friend, Rita, turns up on the doorstep to flip everyone`s world upside-down. Meanwhile, the gang finally meets the elusive occupant of Room 102: Akasaka Ryunosuke!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>612939</identifier>
<identifier>the-pet-girl-of-sakurasou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="145670" update="2013-05-07">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-11-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145671" update="2013-05-07">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-11-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145672" update="2012-11-25">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-11-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145673" update="2012-11-25">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-11-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145674" update="2012-11-25">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-10-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145675" update="2012-11-25">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-10-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145676" update="2012-11-25">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-10-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146043" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="14">7.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">冬の一歩手前で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">One Step Before Winter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuyu no Ippo Temae de</title>
<summary>The residents of Sakura house continue to enjoy the fame of their successful show, but as it begin to fade as Christmas approaches and the idea, the thought, and the want for love begins to take over.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616689</identifier>
<identifier>the-pet-girl-of-sakurasou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146044" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="16">9.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛のパワーin文化祭</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Power of Love in the Cultural Festival</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai no Power in Bunkasai</title>
<summary>The production of Milky Way Cat, Nyapollon is going well until the audience is asked to “Shout your love”.  Who will be the first to speak up?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>612947</identifier>
<identifier>the-pet-girl-of-sakurasou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146409" update="2012-12-30">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-12-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 13</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146410" update="2012-12-30">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-12-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146411" update="2013-06-26">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-12-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146412" update="2012-12-30">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-12-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146413" update="2012-12-30">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-11-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146630" update="2013-01-08">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146631" update="2013-01-09">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146632" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-15</airdate>
<rating votes="14">8.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">イヴの窓辺とそれぞれの灯り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Windows and Lights of Christmas Eve</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eve no Madobe to Sorezore no Akari</title>
<summary>Christmas Eve is the will be the night when truths are aired among the residents. But more than one person will have their heart broken.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616691</identifier>
<identifier>the-pet-girl-of-sakurasou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146715" update="2013-01-11">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-01-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 14</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146754" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-12</airdate>
<rating votes="13">6.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙人に初恋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Love with an Alien</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuujin ni Hatsukoi</title>
<summary>Time is running out for Jin and Misaki; their friends rush to bring them together, but the past makes an invisible barrier.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616699</identifier>
<identifier>the-pet-girl-of-sakurasou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146755" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-05</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バレンタインはチョコの日よ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Valentine`s Day Is Chocolate Day</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Valentine wa Choco no Hi yo</title>
<summary>Mashiro has asked Sorata to meet her on the roof, his mind races considering today is Valentine’s Day.  But a frantic call from Nanami throws everything out the window.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616697</identifier>
<identifier>the-pet-girl-of-sakurasou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146756" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-29</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ずっと, 好きでした......</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`ve Always Loved You</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zutto, Suki Deshita...</title>
<summary>The results of Sorata hard work and prep will finally show when he submits his pitch.  At the same time, Nanami is prepping for her next chance.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616695</identifier>
<identifier>the-pet-girl-of-sakurasou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146757" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="14">8.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いつもの自分はどこにいる?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Where Is My Usual Self?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itsumo no Jibun wa Doko ni Iru?</title>
<summary>Sorata gets roped into taking the women of Sakura Hall to his home, where he must contend against his manly father and bro-con sister.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616693</identifier>
<identifier>the-pet-girl-of-sakurasou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146833" update="2013-01-18">
<epno type="2">S14</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-01-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 15</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147147" update="2013-02-01">
<epno type="2">S16</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-02-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 17</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147148" update="2013-02-01">
<epno type="2">S15</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-01-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 16</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147180" update="2013-02-11">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2013-01-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">TV PV 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147285" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">この先もただいまを言うために</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In Order to Keep Saying We`re Home</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kono Saki mo Tadaima o Iu Tame ni</title>
<summary>The residents start a campaign to save Sakura Hall but one resident is the lone holdout.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616703</identifier>
<identifier>the-pet-girl-of-sakurasou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147286" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-19</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">住めば都のさくら荘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">There`s No Place Like Sakura Hall</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sumeba Miyako no Sakura-sou</title>
<summary>The shock of Sakura Hall closing has Sorata remembering his first days of moving into the hall and the cats his picked up along the way.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616701</identifier>
<identifier>the-pet-girl-of-sakurasou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147408" update="2013-05-05">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-10-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">TV PV 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147419" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-26</airdate>
<rating votes="22">8.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくら荘へようこそ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to Sakura Hall</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura-sou e Youkoso</title>
<summary>A new school year is starting with new and old faces.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616711</identifier>
<identifier>the-pet-girl-of-sakurasou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147420" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-19</airdate>
<rating votes="13">8.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">卒業式</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Graduation Ceremony</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sotsugyoushiki</title>
<summary>Fight to the very end!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616709</identifier>
<identifier>the-pet-girl-of-sakurasou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147421" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-12</airdate>
<rating votes="12">8.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">きらめく日々を駆け抜けろ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Run Through Those Sparkling Days</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kirameku Hibi o Kakenukero</title>
<summary>Mahiro knows she is the reason for Sakura hall closing, as she prepares to leave school to protect those she loves. The residents search desperately to find her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616707</identifier>
<identifier>the-pet-girl-of-sakurasou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147422" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-05</airdate>
<rating votes="14">7.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">誰のせいでもなく雨は降る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Not Anyone`s Fault That It Rains</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dare no Sei de mo Naku Ame wa Furu</title>
<summary>Sometimes you have to let go of a dream and face reality.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616705</identifier>
<identifier>the-pet-girl-of-sakurasou</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147580" update="2013-02-19">
<epno type="2">S18</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-02-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 19</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147581" update="2013-02-19">
<epno type="2">S17</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-02-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 18</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148166" update="2013-03-26">
<epno type="2">S24</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>2013-02-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">電撃20年祭「20年だよ! 大人の階段のぼっちゃうよ!? さくら荘会議」イベント映像</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dengeki 20-nensai "20-nen Da yo! Otona no Kaidan Nobocchau yo!? Sakura-sou Kaigi" Event Eizou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148618" update="2013-03-26">
<epno type="2">S23</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-03-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 24</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148619" update="2013-03-26">
<epno type="2">S22</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-03-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 23</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148620" update="2013-03-26">
<epno type="2">S21</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-03-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 22</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148621" update="2013-03-26">
<epno type="2">S20</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-02-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 21</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148622" update="2013-03-26">
<epno type="2">S19</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-03-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 20</title>
</episode>
<episode id="149695" update="2013-04-18">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-01-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150382" update="2013-05-05">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-09-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">放送告知映像 空太&amp;ましろver.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV Sorata &amp; Mashiro ver.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Housou Kokuchi Eizou: Sorata &amp; Mashiro Ver.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150383" update="2013-05-05">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-12-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">そして冬がやってくる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV Winter is Coming</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soshite Fuyu ga Yattekuru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151963" update="2013-07-16">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">OP・EDテーマCD CM集</title>
<title xml:lang="en">OP &amp; ED CD CM</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">OP ED Theme CD CM-shuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152743" update="2013-08-24">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CMs DVD/BD</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
