<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="916" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>50</episodecount>
<startdate>1999-04-09</startdate>
<enddate>2000-04-14</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Turn A Gundam</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">∀ガンダム</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">∀GUNDAM CALLED TURN "A" GUNDAM</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">كاندام `بالمقلوب</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">倒A高达</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">TaG</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">∀GUNDAM</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Turn A Gundam</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2812" type="Summary">Turn A Gundam II: Gekkou Chou</anime>
<anime id="2813" type="Summary">Turn A Gundam I: Chikyuukou</anime>
<anime id="715" type="Other">Kidou Senshi Gundam</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8260" approval="3" total="6">Last Exile: Gin`yoku no Fam</anime>
<anime id="584" approval="2" total="11">Ginga Eiyuu Densetsu</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="229973">Gundam with mechs not as a primary focus. However the character and mech designs are rather questionable and weird. Plot is good but it takes heavy beating by the poor pacing. Animation is poor and i only remember single good track after watching it. Definitely unique work but presented in questionable way.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="320567">The End of all gundam (or at least what the creator says)
it boast a very good character development, and music.
if you`re looking for these quality then it`s your anime.

If you`re looking for a gundam fight skip this anime :D

I would say that this "HIge (mustache) Gundam" is epic on his own a must watch for a gundam fans that can tolerate the "Hige"

PS: skip "Heroes Legend" Translation very inaccurate (still better than nothing tho)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="428986">Turn A is not crappy design unit, 

It`s not a gundam, 
but it`s a gundam

Well it`s better than SEED and Gundam OO.
A must watch Gundam</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.turn-a-gundam.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1352" type="Original Work">Yatate Hajime</name>
<name id="147" type="Original Work">Tomino Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="147" type="Chief Direction">Tomino Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="241" type="Music">Kanno Youko</name>
<name id="3412" type="Character Design">Hishinuma Yoshihito</name>
<name id="741" type="Work">Fuji TV</name>
<name id="726" type="Work">Sunrise</name>
</creators>
<description>It is the far future, in the year 2345 of a new calendar - two thousand years, that is, after the dawn of the space age. After centuries of peace, the people of Earth have lost the technology they once possessed and forgotten that they once traveled in space. But a lost tribe of lunar settlers, the Moonrace, have retained the scientific arts... and now they regard their mother planet with envious eyes.
Hoping to return to their ancestral home, the Moonrace contact Earth`s feudal lords and attempt to negotiate the transfer of a chunk of the planet`s territory. But soon, unable to make a deal with Earth`s rulers, the Moonrace decide to seize the land they desire by force. Anticipating an extraterrestrial invasion, Earth`s feudal lords organize militias armed with cars and biplanes to do battle with the Moonrace`s army of giant two-legged war machines.
Caught in the middle of this war of the worlds is a youth named Loran Cehack, who finds a mysterious artifact - a relic of Earth`s forgotten space age - entombed in stone. Will this ancient mobile suit enable Loran to avert the conflict and make peace between Earth and moon?
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="993">6.50</permanent>
<temporary count="1009">7.36</temporary>
<review count="6">7.77</review>
</ratings>
<picture>9992.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>917</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>95</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>404</identifier>
<identifier>xpflar</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.turn-a-gundam.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Turn_A_Gundam</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>∀ガンダム</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>71</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>90320</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2064</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2659" parentid="2660" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Moon</name>
<description>The Moon is an astronomical body that orbits planet Earth, being Earth`s only permanent natural satellite. It is the fifth-largest natural satellite in the Solar System, and the largest among planetary satellites relative to the size of the planet that it orbits.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214385.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2832" parentid="2630" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Americas</name>
<description>The Americas, also collectively called America, encompass the totality of the continents of North America and South America. Together they make up most of Earth`s western hemisphere and comprise the New World.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192247.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2867" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>politics</name>
<description>From commies to fat capitalist pigs, all the stuff done by the "guys with the power", mainly evil tactics for gaining more power over the masses.
Watching this title may remind you why CNN is boring.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2870" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-17">
<name>steampunk</name>
<description>Steampunk is a sub-genre of science fiction that typically features steam-powered machinery, especially in a setting inspired by industrialized Western civilization during the 19th century. Steampunk works are often set in an alternative history of the 19th century`s British Victorian era or American "Wild West", in a post-apocalyptic future during which steam power has regained mainstream use, or in a fantasy world that similarly employs steam power.
Noteworthy attributes of the theme include large amounts smoke pollution from wood or coal burning, the affinity to metal constructs like cogs and metal tubing, and the mechanization of everyday objects.
Steampunk perhaps most recognisably features anachronistic technologies or retro-futuristic inventions as people in the 19th century might have envisioned them, and is likewise rooted in the era`s perspective on fashion, culture, architectural style, and art.
Such technology may include fictional machines like those found in the works of H. G. Wells and Jules Verne, or the modern authors Philip Pullman, Scott Westerfeld, Stephen Hunt and China Miéville. Other examples of steampunk contain alternative history-style presentations of such technology as lighter-than-air airships, analog computers, or such digital mechanical computers as Charles Babbage`s Analytical Engine.
Steampunk can also exemplify everything that is bad about unrestrained technological progress (dead matter), when compared to life and nature. The anime usually makes a point to propound the latter.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162830.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2906" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>nanomachines</name>
<description>The anime features sub-microscopic (nano = 10E-9 = one billionth) machines, machines that float in the bloodstream and affect the human body. They can be used both for good (repairing human cells in situ) or for evil (nano-machine warfare, attacking human cells in situ).</description>
<picurl>183210.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4521" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>lost technology</name>
<description>Any advanced technology or science-related knowledge that was lost for some reason fits the description. This could be technology from a time before a post-apocalyptic cataclysm, knowledge gained a long time ago but forgotten, or the relics of an old alien civilization only recently discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="6477" type="main character in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="32">8.23</rating>
<name>Loran Cehack</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Born in the positive calendar November 2, 2328, Loran is a 17 years old boy belonging to the Moonrace and the main character of the series and the pilot of the eponymous mobile suit, WD-M01 ∀ Gundam. Loran and his friends Keith and Fran are secretly sent to Earth by Dianna Soreil in advance of her main colonial force, to ensure that Moonrace settlers can still survive there. The three of them separate upon landing and integrate themselves into the Terran population.</description>
<picture>23992.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6478" type="main character in" update="2010-10-24">
<rating votes="10">7.90</rating>
<name>Laura Rolla</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Laura is a fake personality Loran has to assume when being presented as the pilot of the Turn A.</description>
<picture>2795.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6479" type="main character in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="37">7.80</rating>
<name>Kihel Heim</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kihel Heim is the oldest daughter of the Heim family. Though Kihel is a wealthy heiress, she chooses to look for work and gain real-world experience rather than attend university. She sticks close to Guin Lineford during Dianna Counter`s first attack and uses the opportunity to become his assistant. Her new position brings her to the attention of the leaders of the Moonrace.
Kihel bears a striking resemblance to Dianna Soreil, which allows her to become the Queen`s double. She takes Dianna`s place at the Queen`s behest and, due to events beyond their control, ends up having to impersonate Dianna and lead the Dianna Counter on a long-term basis. The two go on to switch names and roles several times. Kihel and Dianna share many qualities beyond appearance and their ideals are so aligned that for a time they consider themselves a single person. Even so, Kihel has much more energy than Dianna, and does not share Dianna`s longing for an ordinary life. She is very good at masking her insecurity over whether or not she can live up to Dianna`s example.</description>
<picture>2015.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="608" picture="18012.jpg">Takahashi Rieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6480" type="main character in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="25">6.58</rating>
<name>Sochie Heim</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sochie Heim is the second daughter of the Heim family. Sochie is a spoiled, headstrong tomboy who is continually overshadowed by her sister Kihel. She was determined to join the Inglessa Militia even before Dianna Counter`s attack, and is among the first to pilot one of Sid Munzer`s excavated mobile suits. Eventually Sochie becomes a well-respected soldier, though her AMX-109 Kapool is one of the weakest mobile suits in the series.
The death of Sochie`s father causes her to hate the Moonrace and she feels betrayed when she discovers that her crush Loran is from the Moon. It takes a long time for her to grow up and soften her views. While Sochie suffers a great deal of loss over the course of the series, her trials make her a stronger person, and she never loses her fighting spirit.</description>
<picture>2016.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3087" picture="23993.jpg">Murata Akino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6481" type="main character in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="53">8.39</rating>
<name>Diana Soriel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Queen of the Moon, Dianna Soreil is the hereditary ruler of the Moonrace. Now that the Earth has regenerated from the destruction wrought by the Dark History, she believes that it is time for her subjects to return to Earth. Dianna lands a colonial force on the Earth in the hopes that they will be allowed to live in America`s sparsely-populated sunbelt area. Unfortunately, she fails to take Terran resistance to the migration into account, and does not anticipate that her more ambitious subjects might turn against her in her absence. Events quickly spiral out of her control.
Dianna has lived for centuries using the Moonrace`s cryogenic techniques. Her desire to live on Earth is a product of her weariness with her unchanging life on the Moon. She is an intelligent and commanding leader, but she lacks the drive of her young double, Kihel Heim. Dianna is overjoyed when assuming Kihel`s identity allows her to lead a simple life with Loran. She only returns to the Moon in order to correct the mistakes she made in her rash rush towards repatriation.</description>
<picture>2019.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="608" picture="18012.jpg">Takahashi Rieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6482" type="main character in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="21">5.67</rating>
<name>Harry Ord</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Harry Ord is the head of Dianna`s Royal Guard, and reports directly to the Queen herself. He pilots a distinctive gold-plated MRC-F20 SUMO and is easily one of the most skilled fighters in the series. An accomplished military strategist, Harry judges situations with a cool and rational demeanor. He is the only person who is readily able to distinguish between Kihel Heim and Dianna Soreil.
Harry remains loyal to Dianna throughout the series. Though he falls in love with Kihel, his duty to the throne always comes first. He uses a large pair of red sunglasses to mask his true feelings.</description>
<picture>2020.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="1616" picture="23191.jpg">Inada Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6483" type="main character in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="7">2.04</rating>
<name>Guin Sard Rhineford</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Guin Sard Rhineford is a charming young nobleman who rules the principality of Inglessa. He seems dedicated to brokering a peaceful agreement between the Terrans and the Moonrace, and to building up the Earth Militia in case those talks fall through. After his base of power Nocis City is destroyed he masterminds the Terrans` journey into space to confront the Moonrace. He uses his relationship with the Luziannan princess Lily Borjarno to retain his influence after the fall of Inglessa.</description>
<picture>2021.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3090" picture="23995.jpg">Aoba Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6484" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="13">6.50</rating>
<name>Lily Borjarno</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The youngest child of Lord Borjarno, who rules over the Luzianna territory. Lily initially appears to be little more than a spoiled dilettante. She behaves pettily towards the disguised Diana Soreil, she claims to work for the Militia out of boredom, and it seems like she`s willing to allow Guin to use her as a pawn so long as he indulges her infatuation.
As the series progresses, it becomes clear that Lily is in fact an insightful and astute politician. She knows the importance of gathering powerful friends and allies, and has no qualms about ditching Guin once he becomes a liability instead of an asset. Lily negotiates with Agrippa Maintainer on the Earth`s behalf and takes control of the Willgame after Guin`s fall from grace.</description>
<picture>2022.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3092" picture="23997.jpg">Kobayashi Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6485" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<name>Sid Munzer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An elderly archeologist searching for remnants of the Earth`s "dark history". He works on the excavation of mobile suits which are used by the the Earth Militias to fight the Moonrace.</description>
<picture>2023.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3093" picture="38195.jpg">Nojima Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6486" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="2">5.39</rating>
<name>Gym Ghingham</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The leader of the armed forces of the Moon. Gym is a forceful, swaggering man who carries a katana as an affectation. He believes that humanity can only live up to its true potential during times of war, and seeks to use the Turn X Gundam to sow strife and re-kindle the brutal conflicts that raged throughout the Dark History
Both Agrippa Maintainer and Guin Sard Lineford think that they can use Gym to their own ends, but they fail to understand his lust for battle. Neither politician is able to control him.</description>
<picture>2025.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6487" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<name>Yanny Oviess</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A sergeant in the Inglessa Militia, later promoted to second lieutenant. He has a stubborn personality and works against Dianna with Michael Gern.</description>
<picture>2026.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="294" picture="53586.jpg">Kirimoto Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6488" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<name>Michael Gern</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A colonel in the Inglessa Militia. Michael Gern is a proud and straightlaced man who follows orders until they are completed. He has a wife and young son.</description>
<picture>2027.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3094" picture="50367.jpg">Kanao Tetsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6489" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="3">1.13</rating>
<name>Joseph Yaht</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leader of the Inglessa Militia`s Jalopy Squad. Joseph comes from an ethnic minority that is persecuted in Adeska. He left his homeland to assist Sid Munzer and only departs the excavation team once he is needed to pilot the Militia`s FLAT-LO6D FLAT. Joseph is a brave man with a good heart. He quickly forms a romantic relationship with Fran Doll in spite of his brusque, taciturn personality.</description>
<picture>2028.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2786" picture="211228.jpg">Satou Setsuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6490" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="3">1.13</rating>
<name>Miashei Kune</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ladderrum`s daughter, and one of the Inglessa Militia`s top pilots. Miashei is Sochie`s best friend and the one who taught her how to operate machines. She is a bright, sensible girl, and is often called upon to act as a voice of reason when Sochie is being too hot-headed.</description>
<picture>2029.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3095" picture="23998.jpg">Kitou Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6491" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<name>Ladderrum Kune</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miashei`s father, Ladderrum is skilled fighter pilot and aircraft developer. He performs mechanical maintenance for the Militia.</description>
<picture>2032.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3096" picture="186182.jpg">Sawaki Ikuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6492" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="6">3.01</rating>
<name>Bruno</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Initially one of Nander`s subordinates and a member of the Dianna Counter forces, he later joins the Earth Militia. Bruno is an MS Gozzo pilot and Jacop`s partner.</description>
<picture>2033.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2976" picture="234380.jpg">Tanaka Kazunari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6493" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="6">4.49</rating>
<name>Jacop</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Initially one of Nander`s subordinates and a member of the Dianna Counter forces, he later joins the Earth Militia. Jacop is an MS Gozzo pilot and Bruno`s partner.</description>
<picture>2034.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3098" picture="36733.jpg">Ugaki Hidenari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6494" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-04-28">
<rating votes="1">6.13</rating>
<name>Horace Niven</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Horace Niven is an engineer from the Moon who defects to the Earth Militias when it becomes clear that Dianna Counter can`t provide for all of the civilian settlers. Without him the Terrans would not be able to use a great deal of their recovered technology.</description>
<picture>172721.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3099" picture="24698.jpg">Kakegawa Hirohiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6495" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<name>Mallygan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A lieutenant-colonel in the Luzianna Militia. An old-fashioned man with aristocratic tastes, he dresses in a manner he believes suits his power and status.</description>
<picture>2035.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6496" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="2">1.63</rating>
<name>Gavane Goonny</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Captain of the Luzianna Militia`s Suicide Squad. The Suicide Squad is a group of skilled soldiers who pilot Luzianna`s prized MS-06 Bojarnon (these are in fact salvaged MS-05 Zaku I and MS-06 Zaku II units). Gavane is well-liked by his men and very proud of his squadron. He develops feelings for Sochie Heim and tries to protect her even though he respects her skills as a warrior.
The pair become engaged in spite of Sochie`s lingering feelings for Loran, but Gavane is killed before they can be married.</description>
<picture>2036.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="297" picture="233915.jpg">Ootsuka Houchuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6497" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="2">1.63</rating>
<name>Aims</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of the Suicide Squad.</description>
<picture>2037.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="637" picture="151727.jpg">Matsumoto Dai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6498" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<name>John</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of the Suicide Squad.</description>
<picture>2038.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3101" picture="186161.jpg">Tsuchiya Toshihide</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6499" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<name>Borjarno no Ooyake</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lord Borjarno, the lord of Luzianna. He has thirteen children, including Lily Borjarno.</description>
</character>
<character id="6500" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-04-28">
<name>Heim-fujin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Heim-fujin is http://anidb.net/ch6501 [Dylan]`s wife andhttp://anidb.net/ch6479 [ Kihel] and http://anidb.net/ch6480 [Sochie]`s mother.
She is driven mad by her husband`s death.</description>
<picture>172720.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3103" picture="66844.jpg">Houjou Fumie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6501" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-04-28">
<rating votes="2">1.63</rating>
<name>Dylan Heim</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dylan Heim is the head of the Heim family and the father of http://anidb.net/ch6479 [Kihel] and http://anidb.net/ch6480 [Sochie]. Also, he is the president of the Heim family`s mining company.
He is killed during the Dianna Counter`s first show of force on Earth.</description>
<picture>172706.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3102" picture="24178.jpg">Chou Katsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6502" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="2">1.63</rating>
<name>Caharan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Heim family`s driver.</description>
<seiyuu id="3101" picture="186161.jpg">Tsuchiya Toshihide</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6503" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-11-13">
<name>Sam</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A servant of the Heim family.</description>
<picture>179356.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3098" picture="36733.jpg">Ugaki Hidenari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6504" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-11-13">
<name>Jessica</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An elderly retainer of the Heim family. Jessica is tasked with caring for Kihel and Sochie`s mother in their absence.</description>
<picture>179353.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3104" picture="157226.jpg">Akimoto Chikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6505" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<name>Will Game</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young man who is descended from Dianna Soreil`s lost love, the original Will Game. He is obsessed with going to the Moon to prove that his ancestor really did romance the legendary Queen. This leaves him vulnerable to manipulation by Teteth Halleh.
Will located and began the excavation of the Terrans` sole spaceship. After his death it is named the "Willgame" in his honor.</description>
<picture>2039.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3106" picture="24006.jpg">Sakaguchi Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12682" type="appears in" update="2019-04-02">
<rating votes="3">3.52</rating>
<name>WD-M01 Turn A Gundam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The WD-M01 Turn A Gundam is a mecha from the Correct Century (正暦 Seireki) calendar system in the anime Turn A Gundam. It is mainly piloted by the hero of the series, and acted as the symbol of the earth militia forces against the superior moonrace.
∀ Gundam is designed by Syd Mead, for the series Turn A Gundam. The original design of the mecha was rejected by Yoshiyuki Tomino due to its exotic appearance and Tomino decided that he wanted a figure that is closer to the previous Gundam designs. The old design was renamed and used for the Mobile Suit Sumo instead. The design is still exotic to Gundam anime fans, however, Syd Mead designed ∀ Gundam using real world industrial design aspects, which was aimed to make it look simple and realistic. The shield was designed by Syd Mead with little constraint form the production team, it needs to be big enough so that the suit can hide behind it, making it easier for the anime production staff to draw. Syd Mead imagined it to be like a clam shell and finally settled with a design that looked like MS-14 Gelgoog`s shield.
The System-∀99 (WD-M01) ∀ Gundam (also known as "Turn A") first appeared in the show when the Moonrace`s Diana Counter army arrived on Earth and attacked the city of Nocis; which at the time was holding a Coming of Age ceremony for Loran Cehack and Sochie Heim, who danced and offered prayers in front of the "White Doll" statue. When the Moonrace forces attack, the "White Doll" statue crumbled, revealing the Turn A. Loran and Sochie take shelter inside the cockpit, which activates and automatically fires at the unaware Moonrace forces. After several battles with the Moonrace, the Turn A became the symbol of the struggle to resist the Moonrace`s attempts at colonizing Earth.</description>
<picture>231941.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="51409" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-12-17">
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<name>Teteth Halleh</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>10310.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="1446" picture="19314.jpg">Touma Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57684" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-04-28">
<name>Keith Laijie</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Keith Laijie originally accompanies http://anidb.net/ch6477 [Loran Cehack] as they come to Earth two years prior to the arrival of the Diana Counter forces. While on Earth, Keith takes up an apprenticeship as a baker and soon falls in love with the owners daughter, Verlaine Bond. As the war between the Dianna Counter and Earth Militia escalates, Keith attempts to run the business as neutrally as possible, supplying baked goods to both sides.
Source: Gundam Wikia</description>
<picture>10782.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89545" type="appears in" update="2017-05-27">
<name>AMX-109 Kapool</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>202978.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="89546" type="appears in" update="2017-05-27">
<name>AMX-109 Kapool Corin Nander Custom</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>202980.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="89547" type="appears in" update="2017-05-27">
<name>MS-05 Borjarnon Gavane Goonny Custom</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>202981.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="89548" type="appears in" update="2017-05-27">
<name>MS-06 Borjarnon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>202982.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="91232" type="appears in" update="2017-09-02">
<name>Hahaoya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A woman that meets her http://anidb.net/ch91233 [daughter] after spending over 50 years in a hibernation capsule.</description>
<picture>206756.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2986" picture="144766.jpg">Sasaki Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91233" type="appears in" update="2017-09-03">
<name>Musume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A woman that meets her http://anidb.net/ch91232 [mother], who spent over 50 years in a hibernation capsule.
Although she is credited as just 娘 (daughter), her real name is Betty: the mother calls her by the name at the beginning of their conversation.</description>
<picture>206757.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51488" picture="206749.jpg">Yuki Tsuyako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93142" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-03">
<name>Fran Doll</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>10984.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3130" picture="186156.jpg">Watanabe Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93143" type="appears in" update="2018-01-03">
<rating votes="1">5.81</rating>
<name>Dona Roroi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>10985.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93144" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-03">
<name>Merrybell Gadget</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>10986.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="1917" picture="151688.jpg">Natsuki Rio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101749" type="appears in" update="2019-04-02">
<name>SPA-51 Cannon Illefuto</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>231930.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="101753" type="appears in" update="2019-04-02">
<name>MRC-F20 Silver SUMO</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>231934.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="101754" type="appears in" update="2019-04-02">
<name>MRC-F20 Gold SUMO</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>231936.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="101756" type="appears in" update="2019-04-02">
<name>Concept-X6-1-2 Turn X</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>231937.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="101757" type="appears in" update="2019-04-02">
<name>G-838 Mahiroo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>231938.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="101758" type="appears in" update="2019-04-02">
<name>G-M1F Bandit</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>231939.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="101759" type="appears in" update="2019-04-02">
<name>G-M2F Zssan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>231940.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="101760" type="appears in" update="2019-04-02">
<name>MRC-F31 Muttowoooo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>231942.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="101761" type="appears in" update="2019-04-02">
<name>MRC-F31 Muttowoooo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>231944.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="10017" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">月に吠える</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Howling at the Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuki ni Hoeru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10038" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">成人式</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Coming Of Age Ceremony</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seijinshiki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10588" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">祭の後</title>
<title xml:lang="en">After the Festival</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Matsuri no Ato</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10609" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-04-30</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふるさとの軍人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hometown Soldier</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Furusato no Gunjin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10610" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-05-07</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ディアナ降臨</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Diana`s Arrival</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Diana Kourin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10611" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-05-14</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">忘れられた過去</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Forgotten Past</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wasurerareta Kako</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10637" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">貴婦人修行</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Noble Lady Practice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kifujin Shuugyou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11925" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ローラの牛</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Laura`s Cow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Laura no Ushi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12380" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-06-04</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コレン, ガンダムと叫ぶ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Corin Calls it a Gundam</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Corin, Gundam to Sakebu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12388" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-06-11</airdate>
<rating votes="4">9.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">墓参り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tomb Sweeping</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakamairi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13085" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-06-18</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ノックス崩壊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Norse City is Destroyed</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nocris Houkai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19806" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-12-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ザックトレーガー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Zacktraeger</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zacktraeger</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19807" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-10-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夜中の夜明け</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sunrise at Midnight</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yonaka no Yoake</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19808" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-03-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ディアナ帰還</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dianna Returns to Earth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dianna Kikan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19809" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミリシャ宇宙決戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Militia`s Space Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Militia Uchuu Kessen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19810" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-02-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ターンX起動</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Turn X Activates</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Turn X Kidou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19811" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-11-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神話の王</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The King of Myth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinwa no Ou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19812" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-01-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦闘神ギンガナム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fighting God, Ghingnham</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sentoushin Ghingnham</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19813" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハリーの災難</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Harry`s Disaster</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Harry no Sainan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19814" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ウィルゲム離陸</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Willgem`s Take-Off</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Willgem Ririku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19815" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アニス・パワー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Anis` Power</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anis Power</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19816" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-01-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦いの決断</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Decision to Fight</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tatakai no Ketsudan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19817" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-03-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">月光蝶</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Moonlight Butterfly</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekkou Chou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19818" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-10-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ソレイユのふたり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Two Diannas</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Solleil no Futari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19819" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黄金の秋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Golden Autumn</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ougon no Aki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19820" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-10-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">託されたもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Entrusted Things</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Takusareta Mono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19821" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-11-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マニューピチ攻略</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Captured Manupichi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Manupichi Kouryaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19822" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-01-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">月面の海戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sea Battle Under the Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Getsumen no Kaisen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19823" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-02-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">裏切りのグエン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Guin`s Betrayal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uragiri no Guin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19824" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-12-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">飛べ! 成層圏</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Flight into the Ozone Layer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tobe! Seisouken</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19825" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-02-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">敵, 新たなり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The New Enemy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Teki, Arata Nari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19826" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キエルとディアナ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kiel and Dianna</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiel to Dianna</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19827" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ソシエの戦争</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sochie`s War</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sochie no Sensou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19828" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-03-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ギンガナム襲来</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ghingnham Attacks</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ghingnham Shuurai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19829" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">テテスの遺言</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Last Words of Teteth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Teteth no Yuigon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19830" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">年上のひと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Elder Woman</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toshiue no Hito</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19831" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ディアナ奮戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dianna`s Struggle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dianna Funsen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19832" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-01-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">小惑星爆烈</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Exploding Planet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shouwakusei Bakuretsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19833" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ローラの遠吠え</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Laura`s Long Cry</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Laura no Tooboe</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19834" recap="true" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ターンAの全て</title>
<title xml:lang="en">All About "Turn A Gundam"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Turn A no Subete</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19835" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-11-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">胸に抱えて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Holding you in my Arms</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mune ni Kakaete</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19836" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-02-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">衝撃の黒歴史</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dark History`s Impact</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shougeki no Kuro Rekishi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19837" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-10-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悟りの戦い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To be Awakened</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Satori no Tatakai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19838" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">別離, 再び</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seperated, Again</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Betsuri, Futatabi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19839" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">思い出は消えて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dissapearing Memory</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omoide wa Kiete</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19840" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-11-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">追撃! 泣き虫ポゥ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crying Pou`s Attack</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuigeki! Nakimushi Pou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19841" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地下回廊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Underground Corridor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chika Kairou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19842" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-03-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">再び, 地球へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Back to Earth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futatabi, Chikyuu e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19843" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-12-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">月世界の門</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Moon Gate</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gessekai no Mon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19844" update="2010-06-18">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">建国のダストブロー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blowing Dust for the Founding of a Nation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kenkoku no Dust Blow</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39804" update="2010-05-20">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>1999-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39805" update="2010-05-20">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2000-01-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39806" update="2010-05-20">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>1999-04-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39807" update="2010-05-20">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2000-01-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="169440" update="2015-06-29">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Interview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="169441" update="2015-06-29">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="169442" update="2015-06-29">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="169443" update="2015-06-29">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="169444" update="2015-06-29">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="174901" update="2016-02-05">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2000-04-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
