<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9166" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-01-06</startdate>
<enddate>2013-03-24</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Senran Kagura</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Senran Kagura: Ninja Flash</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">閃乱カグラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Senran Kagura</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Senran Kagura</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">섬란 카구라</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">闪乱神乐</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="13341" type="Sequel">Senran Kagura: Shinovi Master - Tokyo Youma Hen</anime>
<anime id="10885" type="Side Story">Senran Kagura: Estival Versus - Mizugi Darake no Zen`yasai</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://senran.tv/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3730" type="Series Composition">Yoshioka Takao</name>
<name id="8405" type="Chief Animation Direction">Torii Takashi</name>
<name id="999" type="Animation Work">Artland</name>
<name id="8405" type="Character Design">Torii Takashi</name>
<name id="34844" type="Original Work">Takaki Ken`ichirou</name>
<name id="2120" type="Direction">Watanabe Takashi</name>
<name id="1417" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kobayashi Toshimitsu</name>
<name id="5818" type="Music">Kawada Ruka</name>
<name id="999" type="Work">Artland</name>
</creators>
<description>There was a time when there were ninja serving the powerful, hired for intelligence missions, destruction, or assassination. While the times have changed, the need for ninja has not vanished. In a particular school, there are girls who are secretly in training to become ninja. Ninjas-in-training, http://anidb.net/ch47683 [Asuka], http://anidb.net/ch47685 [Katsuragi], http://anidb.net/ch47687 [Hibari], http://anidb.net/ch47684 [Ikaruga], and http://anidb.net/ch47686 [Yagyuu] each have a secret technique scroll that they protect at all times. A tumultuous school life unfolds as they pursue the path of the ninja!</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1022">2.69</permanent>
<temporary count="1039">5.49</temporary>
<review count="1">5.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>92287.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14280</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15119</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>17345</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5287</identifier>
<identifier>xmecjl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://senran.tv/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Senran_Kagura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>閃乱カグラ_-少女達の真影-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2814</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>344504</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15639</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2069" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-15">
<name>delinquent</name>
<description>Delinquents - Every school has them, but not all anime with school setting make delinquents a central topic. There are several versions of these delinquents, though some are grounded on a misunderstanding:
* The student with a really bad image and attitude, based on his real criminal actions outside of the school and is even feared by teachers.
* The primitive "class bully" that pushes around ("clobbers") his classmates for no apparent reason, possibly extorting lunch money.
* The student with an sinister complexion or "evil eye", but is actually a "good" student (unfoundedly feared character).
* The rebellious student, who does not care for studying, but is otherwise docile. Called a "delinquent" as a joke.</description>
<picurl>243713.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2396" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-08">
<name>swimsuit</name>
<description>A swimsuit is one of several kinds of garments designed to be worn by people engaging in water-based activities or sports or during certain activities under sunlight. Most kinds of swimsuit reveal a large portion of the body surface area, but exceptions exist. The more revealing kinds may also be worn as undergarment in sports that require wetsuits, or when there is a need to display the body, as in the case of beauty pageants or bodybuilding contests.
There is a very wide range of styles of modern swimsuits, which vary in relation to body coverage and materials. The choice of style of swimsuit is dependent on current fashions, community standards of modesty, and plain personal preference. Swimsuits for men usually expose the chest, while those for women do not usually do so; however, many women prefer to engage in water or sun activities with their torso uncovered, in a practice commonly described as toplessness or topfreedom. Since the early twentieth century a naturist movement has developed in western countries that seeks a return to non-sexual nakedness when swimming and during other appropriate activities; in some places around the world, nude beaches have been set aside for people who choose to engage in normal beach activities in the nude, and such beaches may or may not enforce nudity onto their goers.
In anime, it is common for at least one episode to feature the characters in swimsuits, usually as an excuse for gratuitous fanservice; when that happens, the episode is usually labeled a pool or beach episode, after the place the characters went to. Swimsuits, and in particular one-piece swimsuits, are a very common fetish in Japan; while the reason for that is uncertain, a common folk explanation is the fact that boys throughout their entire adolescence are commonly exposed to their female classmates wearing them, in what might be called an experiment in sexual discovery waiting to happen.</description>
<picurl>149786.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2419" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-10-17">
<name>glutton</name>
<description>A character (who quite often is anything but fat) eats enough for an entire football team, usually devastating the whole table — and perhaps entire restaurants — with their insatiable hunger. Often combined with a speed-eating technique that makes food seem to vanish spontaneously from the plate.</description>
<picurl>239821.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2572" parentid="2282" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-09">
<name>ninja</name>
<description>A ninja was a covert agent or mercenary of feudal Japan specializing in unorthodox arts of war.
The functions of the ninja included espionage, sabotage, infiltration, and assassination, as well as open combat in certain situations.
The ninja, using covert methods of waging war, were contrasted with the samurai, who had strict rules about honor and combat.</description>
<picurl>244347.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2662" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>school excursion</name>
<description>True for almost all anime with school setting, there will be a school excursion or field trip. Tokyo and Kyoto seem to be particularly popular as sightseeing destinations. So are hiking excursions into the local mountains. This also is a good excuse to present the prefecture`s / city`s food specialities.
Potential for ecchi moments: Obviously the "boys" will get all sorts of ideas with the "girls" sleeping so close by.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2822" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>skirt flipping</name>
<description>Naughty characters — usually boys — flip the skirts of female protagonists to ascertain what panties they are wearing (also see Pantsu category).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2823" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>paper clothes</name>
<description>Worn clothing appears paper-thin and takes little abuse to be shredded or torn from the body. This is common in ecchi anime where the main storyline involves some type of fighting but consists primarily of dialogue and fanservice (Ikkitousen and Platonic Heart). Various girls’ clothing exploding as if made of rice paper is a very enticing prospect.</description>
<picurl>150776.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2828" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-26">
<name>borderline porn</name>
<description>Breaks the bounds of "excessive fanservice".
While the physical interactions and dialogue between characters may be extremely sexual, the most sexual situations do *not* have sex itself take place.
Specifically descriptive of containing all the plentiful features of (excessive) fanservice in addition to the interactions between characters being quite sexual — at most, sexual in NATURE only. This means physical touching such as groping, molesting, or bondage will focus primarily on the revealed (i.e. nude) upper portion of the body or through/over clothing on the lower half of the body. This is all WITHOUT actual sex acts (penetration, etc.) taking place.</description>
<picurl>214855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2829" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-21">
<name>shower scene</name>
<description>The anime contains a shower scene, obligatory for ecchi anime. The person under the shower will most likely be female — providing "fanservice".</description>
<picurl>208635.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2830" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>furo scene</name>
<description>Furo (polite: Ofuro) is Japanese for bath, specifically a type of bath which originated as a short, steep-sided wooden bathtub. Baths of this type are found all over Japan in houses, apartments and traditional Japanese inns (Ryokans).
Furo are part of the Japanese ritual of bathing, not used for washing but for relaxing and warming oneself. Washing is carried out separately outside the furo, and only when completely clean does the bather enter the water. Generally Japanese bathrooms are small, so the bathroom is set up much like a walk-in shower area but containing the ofuro.
The cheapest and shortest way to show naked skin on TV, at least as much as allowed. It usually only takes up few minutes at most and as such it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales while still maintaining a "non-filler" episode.
Compare to the big brothers http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode] and http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160785.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2894" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>female student</name>
<description>Pretty much exclusive to hentai shows only unless an ecchi show has implied sex and/or a strong indicator of nudity. A character is considered a student if she goes to school, doesn`t matter if it`s high school, college or homeschooling, but she should be of appropriate age for a student; a housewife going to college should not get this category.</description>
<picurl>210611.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3012" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-02">
<name>pillow fight</name>
<description>A fight involving the use of pillows, as weapons, in a melee or projectile capacity. Usually they do not inflict harm but in the arms of certain individuals they are deadly weapons which, unlike real life pillow fights, can involve fatal injuries.</description>
<picurl>167002.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3444" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>hot springs visit</name>
<description>An onsen is a term for hot springs in the Japanese language, though the term is often used to describe the bathing facilities and inns around the hot springs. Often the cast of a show somehow ends up going to an onsen because of various reasons, such as winning a lottery ticket. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters nude and raise the DVD sales.
Another cheap variant is the http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160784.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4148" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-11">
<name>late for school</name>
<description>A common device for a series opening or Establishing Character Moment. Things begin in a frantic rush which usually results in taking short cuts, such as eating breakfast on the run. The classic image is of someone running down the street with a slice of toast hanging out of their mouth, dragging their backpack with one hand while trying to put on their jacket or sweater one-handed with the other, bumping into important people in a manner that gets the plot started.
Basically, they`re never on time for school. While some are Heavy Sleepers, it would appear that they may have simply set their alarm clocks so as to give them insufficient time to get to class. 
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>161002.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="47683" type="main character in" update="2012-12-23">
<rating votes="30">6.70</rating>
<name>Asuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129857.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5878" picture="45926.jpg">Harada Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47684" type="main character in" update="2012-08-22">
<rating votes="31">6.98</rating>
<name>Ikaruga</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92834.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4715" picture="223209.jpg">Imai Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47685" type="main character in" update="2012-08-22">
<rating votes="35">6.58</rating>
<name>Katsuragi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92835.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47686" type="main character in" update="2012-12-23">
<rating votes="29">5.67</rating>
<name>Yagyuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129858.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="591" picture="226209.jpg">Mizuhashi Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47687" type="main character in" update="2012-08-22">
<rating votes="27">6.51</rating>
<name>Hibari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92837.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48520" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-12-23">
<rating votes="22">6.88</rating>
<name>Haruka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129859.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48521" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-12-23">
<rating votes="19">4.96</rating>
<name>Mirai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129862.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="355" picture="71573.jpg">Gotou Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48522" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-12-23">
<rating votes="21">7.58</rating>
<name>Hikage</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129860.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="208" picture="20458.jpg">Shiraishi Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48523" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-04">
<rating votes="21">6.14</rating>
<name>Yomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>131796.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48524" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-12-23">
<rating votes="20">5.79</rating>
<name>Homura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129861.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50938" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-01">
<rating votes="5">5.96</rating>
<name>Suzune</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132992.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20025" picture="132938.jpg">Mimori Suzuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50939" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-04-18">
<rating votes="20">6.64</rating>
<name>Daidouji-senpai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132990.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="82" picture="216596.jpg">Asakawa Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50940" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-02">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Kiriya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132991.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="211227.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51595" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-03">
<rating votes="2">4.75</rating>
<name>Hanzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134618.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17523" picture="223264.jpg">Yamamoto Kanehira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54593" type="appears in" update="2013-04-03">
<name>Murasame</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134619.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54594" type="appears in" update="2013-04-03">
<name>Ikaruga no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134620.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3161" picture="69050.jpg">Yamanoi Jin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54595" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-03">
<rating votes="1">1.64</rating>
<name>Dougen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134621.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55810" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-14">
<rating votes="7">5.48</rating>
<name>Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136643.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20025" picture="132938.jpg">Mimori Suzuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55811" type="appears in" update="2013-05-14">
<name>Kouji</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="146591" update="2017-06-03">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-27</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">臨海修行・忍島</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seaside Training: Shinobi Island</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rinkai Shugyou: Shinobitou</title>
<summary>The class members travel to Shinobi Island, a training ground used by shinobi for centuries. Upon their arrival, they are tasked with cleaning the boarding house, where Hibari discovers the written aspiration of a past student to become a "Super-ninja."
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="146592" update="2017-06-03">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-20</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">月下の侵入者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Moonlight Intruder</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekka no Shinnyuusha</title>
<summary>Ikaruga and Asuka are confronted by an overpowering Yomi outside the supermarket. Following the confrontation, Ikaruga is left with doubts about her abilities. Meanwhile, Ikaruga`s adpoted brother turns up missing. Asuka faces her fear of frogs.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="146593" update="2017-06-03">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-13</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">伝説の忍あらわる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Legendary Shinobi Appears</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Densetsu no Shinobi Arawaru</title>
<summary>Asuka and the others continue training, but are fobbidden from any contact with those outside the school. Asuka feels disappointed when everyone but herself is able to perform the ninja animal-summoning technique. Asuka`s Grandpa Hanzo visits the school.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="146594" update="2017-06-02">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-06</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">摩天楼に立つ忍者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ninja That Stand Atop Skyscrapers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Matenrou ni Tatsu Ninja</title>
<summary>A young shinobi named Asuka carries out a daring mission. The following day, she returns to Hanzo Academy in Asakusa, Tokyo, where she secretly trains with four other classmates. Their afternoon field work holds an unexpected surprise in store for them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="146618" update="2013-01-07">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-01-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146619" update="2013-01-07">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-01-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147114" update="2013-01-30">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-01-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147115" update="2017-06-03">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-24</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">追憶の忍教室</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Shinobi Classroom Retrospective</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuioku no Shinobi Kyoushitsu</title>
<summary>Kiriya`s training of the girls turns especially strict. Afterward, he reminisces about the time two years earlier when Ikaruga and Katsuragi were new students. As Asuka, Hibari, and Yagyu join in later on, the road to the team`s formation is revealed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="147116" update="2017-06-03">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-17</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恐怖のハイキング</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hiking Terror</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoufu no Hiking</title>
<summary>Still reeling from the blow they were dealt by Hebijo, Kiriya decides to ramp up the girls` training with a mountain-climbing training excursion. This so-called "Hai-kin-gu" training provides many challenges to the Hanzo team, both together and separately.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="147117" update="2017-06-03">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-10</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">連動忍結界</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Interlocking Shinobi Kekkai Barriers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rendou Shinobi Kekkai</title>
<summary>The Hanzo shinobi continue to fight one-on-one against the Hebijo shinobi. When Yagyu manages to defeat her opponent and free herself from her pocket of kekkai space, she attempts to enter Hibari`s pocket to protect her, at great physical risk to herself.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="147118" update="2017-06-03">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-03</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">奇襲! 半蔵学院</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sneak Attack! Hanzo Academy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kishuu! Hanzou Gakuin</title>
<summary>The Hanzo girls train even harder to be ready for the Hebijo shinobi`s next move. The Hebijo girls sneak onto campus to locate the Hanzo girls` training facility. Upon finding the old schoolhouse, it is placed in a kekkai, trapping the Hanzo girls inside!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="147698" update="2017-06-02">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">超秘伝忍法</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Super-Secret Ninja Art</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chou Hiden Ninpou</title>
<summary>Fierce battles continue to be waged as the Hanzo Academy shinobi try to reach the castle`s top floor. Meanwhile, outside, Kiriya, Daidoji, and Suzune have a confrontation of their own. With everything at stake, Asuka and Homura engage in one last showdown.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="147699" update="2017-06-03">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-17</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦天守閣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Castle Showdown</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen Tenshukaku</title>
<summary>Yomi waits in ambush to keep the Hanzo shinobi from moving forward. As Ikaruga takes matters into her own hands, Hibari is desperate to escape her cell and tell the others not to fight the Hebijo students, as it will mean their deaths if they lose.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="147700" update="2017-06-03">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-10</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">陰と陽</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yin and Yang</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">In to You</title>
<summary>With the map from Suzune, the Hanzo Academy shinobi prepare to attack the Hebijo base. As Hibari learns more about Hebijo`s training methods, she is determined to take back the secret scroll. Suzune gets in hot water for luring the Hanzo shinobi to Hebijo.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="147701" update="2017-06-03">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-03</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">秘立蛇女子学園</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hebijo Clandestine Girls` Academy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hiritsu Hebi Joshi Gakuen</title>
<summary>Under Haruka`s control, Hibari breaks into Hanzo Academy`s depository and takes the super-secret ninja art scroll. After Haruka leaves with the scroll, Hibari feels that she has betrayed the others, and runs away from the academy to get the scroll back.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="148742" update="2013-04-02">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-02-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148789" update="2014-11-25">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2013-06-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">お忍び女子会 第四話「パンツはき忘れた」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 10</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oshinobi Joshikai Daiyonwa: Pantsu Hakiwasureta</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148790" update="2015-04-06">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-06-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">爆乳ハイパーオリジナルアニメーション「斑鳩式エクササイズ」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bakunyuu Hyper Original Animation: Ikarugashiki Exercise</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148791" update="2014-11-25">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2013-05-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">お忍び女子会 第三話「淫乱ピンク枠」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 9</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oshinobi Joshikai Daisanwa: Inran Pink Waku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148792" update="2014-11-25">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-05-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">爆乳ハイパーオリジナルアニメーション「その胸に顔を埋めたい!」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bakunyuu Hyper Original Animation: Sono Mune ni Kao o Uzumetai!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148793" update="2014-11-25">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2013-04-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">お忍び女子会 第二話「先輩の本気」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 8</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oshinobi Joshikai Dainiwa: Senpai no Honki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148794" update="2014-11-25">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2013-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">爆乳ハイパーオリジナルアニメーション「雲雀の裸を隠すのだ!」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bakunyuu Hyper Original Animation: Hibari no Hadaka o Kakusu no Da!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148795" update="2014-11-25">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2013-03-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">お忍び女子会 第一話「忍者の先輩」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 7</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oshinobi Joshikai Daiichiwa: Ninja no Senpai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148796" update="2013-04-03">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2013-03-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">爆乳ハイパーオリジナルアニメーション「どきどき身体測定」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bakunyuu Hyper Original Animation: Dokidoki Shintai Sokutei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150884" update="2013-05-31">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150885" update="2013-05-31">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152328" update="2015-02-04">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">爆乳ハイパーオリジナルアニメーション「禁断! 開かずの間の恐怖!」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bakunyuu Hyper Original Animation: Kindan! Akazunoma no Kyoufu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152435" update="2013-08-09">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2013-08-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">お忍び女子会 第六話「忍者ごっこのお約束」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 12</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oshinobi Joshikai Dairokuwa: Ninjagokko no Oyakusoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152436" update="2014-11-25">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">爆乳ハイパーオリジナルアニメーション「仁義なきライバル対決!」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bakunyuu Hyper Original Animation: Jinginaki Rival Taiketsu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152437" update="2014-11-25">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2013-07-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">お忍び女子会 第五話「ヒモでアフレコに」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 11</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oshinobi Joshikai Daigowa: Himo de Afreco ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152438" update="2013-08-09">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV-CF 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152439" update="2013-08-09">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV-CF 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152440" update="2013-08-09">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">PV微にゅうver.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">PV Binyuu ver.</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
