<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9240" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2012-06-09</startdate>
<enddate>2012-06-09</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Persona 4 The Animation: The Factor of Hope</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ペルソナ4 the Animation -the Factor of Hope-</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8378" type="Full Story">Persona 4 The Animation</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.p4a.jp/foh/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="1648" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ueda Youichi</name>
<name id="6441" type="Character Design">Morita Kazuaki</name>
<name id="5071" type="Series Composition">Kakihara Yuuko</name>
<name id="910" type="Work">AIC A.S.T.A</name>
<name id="4489" type="Direction">Kishi Seiji</name>
<name id="4360" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nakahara Kiyotaka</name>
<name id="24686" type="Music">Meguro Shouji</name>
</creators>
<description>Note: The film not only recaped the entire 25-episode http://anidb.net/a8378 [television anime series] with new cuts, but also the unaired "True End Episode" that was included in the 10th Blu-ray Disc/DVD volume.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="129">5.72</permanent>
<temporary count="131">6.65</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>224720.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14342</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14267</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5104</identifier>
<identifier>nqwidr</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.p4a.jp/foh/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Persona_4:_The_Animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ペルソナ4</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>342914</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/3409</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15685</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2801" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>RPG</name>
<description>Any anime that is based on a role-playing game aka RPG. A role-playing video game is a video game which includes elements of non-electronic role-playing games. The player assumes control of one or several fictional characters (a party) who have joined forces in order to perform quests and overcome a great number of challenges and enemies, usually monsters inspired by fantasy, and, to a lesser extent, science fiction and classic mythology. During the course of the game the characters, or avatars, which are generally defined by quantized characteristics, evolve and improve in that their various attributes increase, as well as by gaining more powerful artefacts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2843" parentid="7220" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-08">
<name>sexual abuse -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is to be split into the following new tags under the http://anidb.net/t7220 [sexual abuse] category. Afterwards, delete this tag.

* http://anidb.net/t7222 [groping / molestation]
* http://anidb.net/t1306 [chikan]
* http://anidb.net/t7221 [psychological sexual abuse]
* http://anidb.net/t2715 [rape / attempted rape]
</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2863" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>proxy battles</name>
<description>In our terms, a proxy battle is a battle where humans use creatures/robots to do the fighting for them, either by commanding those creatures/robots or by simply evolving them/changing them into battle mode. Often the training aspect is also involved, or in some cases the proxies are nothing more than holographic representatives of some other variation of competition (like for example a card game). While many popular shounen anime fit under this category, it`s not limited to shounen anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3955" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>DESCRIPTION MISSING</name>
<description>The description for this entry is missing. e.g plot, biography...
Please help by adding it, and remove this tag afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="31093" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-09">
<rating votes="40">6.75</rating>
<name>Amagi Yukiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An elegant, introverted girl with long groomed black hair and a red hairband. Yukiko usually wears either a red cardigan over her school uniform blouse or a pink yukata, and is sometimes also seen carrying a paper fan, which she uses in battle, or a red umbrella. Her family owns a famous ryokan in the city and Yukiko is always busy preparing herself to take over the business. She is named the next owner of the ryokan and feels oppressed by her expected duties. Despite her elegant appearance, she carries a whimsical side prone to fits of laughter.
Her Persona is Konohana-sakuya of The Priestess Arcana, resembling a Tokusatsu heroine and being almost completely pink in color, her uniform is reminiscent of a high school cheerleader`s uniform. Like Yukiko, it appears to carry a pair of fans. Yukiko is skilled with healing and fire spells. Konohana Sakuya will evolve into Amaterasu once Yukiko`s Priestess Social Link is maxed out.
Her Shadow takes the form of a caged red lovebird with Yukiko`s hair, that is able to summon a prince-like Shadow to assist it. It represents her resentment towards having her destiny already chosen for her as inheritor of the Amagi Inn and her desires to be rescued and taken far away by her "prince" Chie, as she feels "caged" in Inaba. Her Midnight Channel dungeon is a pink Romanesque castle filled with medieval furniture.</description>
<picture>156474.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31094" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-09">
<rating votes="21">4.89</rating>
<name>Hanamura Yousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An awkward boy with slightly unkempt reddish-brown hair, who usually walks around with a music player and red/orange headphones around his neck. He dual wields blades ranging from blunt wrenches to knives to daggers in battle. He is usually very clumsy and often used as comic relief through physical comedy. When going from place to place, he is usually on his bike. Yousuke is the most vocal of the investigation team, and is the one often to create theories on the murders as well as piece evidence together. Although it often falls on the player to decipher the clues Yousuke ponders, his deductive skills allow him to create solid theories, and he is the self-appointed second in command, often saying what the player is unable to.
His Persona is Jiraiya of The Magician Arcana, whose head vaguely resembles that of a cartoon frog, and wears a white disco suit with a distinctive "V" on its chest along with a red scarf. Jiraiya uses wind spells and is also able to use minor healing spells. Once his Social Link, The Magician Arcana, is maxed out, Jiraiya will evolve into Susanoo.
Yousuke`s Shadow takes the form of a cartoon frog with a body on top; the body and frog resemble his Persona. It represents his resentment of living in a small country town with little to do, as well as his inner wish for something exciting to happen.</description>
<picture>156476.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="143" picture="23260.jpg">Morikubo Shoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31095" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-09">
<rating votes="45">7.31</rating>
<name>Satonaka Chie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An upbeat girl with short light-brown hair, who usually wears a green athletic jacket decorated with buttons. Her weapon is a pair of greaves. She has an obsession with Kung fu, and even uses their techniques in battle, similar to Lisa Silverman of Persona 2. Most of the time, she is friendly, cheerful, and energetic, but she has a short temper. Chie, Yukiko, and Rise are unskilled at cooking, often providing the main cast with unpalatable to terribly awful dishes through the course of the story. Yousuke refers to their horrible cooking as "Mystery Food X."
Her Persona is Tomoe of The Chariot Arcana, a muscular female figure wearing a yellow outfit reminiscent of Bruce Lee`s famous tracksuit (referencing her love for Kung-fu movies), wielding a double bladed naginata. Tomoe is shown to use both physical and low-level ice spells. Tomoe evolves into Suzuka Gongen after maxing out the Chie`s Social Link, the Chariot.
Chie`s Shadow takes the form of a masked dominatrix with long black hair, supported by three pale female students. It represents her jealousy of Yukiko`s feminine side and her talents, as well as her wish and need to maintain control over Yukiko.</description>
<picture>156473.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31096" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-09">
<rating votes="55">8.11</rating>
<name>Narukami Yuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156477.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32390" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-09">
<rating votes="19">6.47</rating>
<name>Kuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156471.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32391" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-07-26">
<rating votes="27">7.94</rating>
<name>Doujima Nanako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>175771.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="349" picture="79057.jpg">Kanda Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32392" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-07-26">
<rating votes="8">6.03</rating>
<name>Doujima Ryoutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>175772.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32393" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-12">
<rating votes="22">6.41</rating>
<name>Tatsumi Kanji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>157935.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32394" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-07-26">
<rating votes="19">4.24</rating>
<name>Adachi Tooru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>175770.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="231" picture="23486.jpg">Madono Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32710" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-07-26">
<rating votes="46">7.81</rating>
<name>Kujikawa Rise</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kujikawa Rise is a cheerful-looking girl with violet-red hair tied in two pigtails. She was one of the most popular idols in Japan, but suddenly quit her job and transferred to Yasogami High School as a freshman to take a break from the spotlight and lead a normal life, away from the stress of fame. Rise grew up in Inaba, and her grandmother runs a shop in the shopping district, Marukyu Tofu, which Rise initially helps out at after her return. Her look is reminiscent to that of Yuka Ayase from Shin Megami Tensei: Persona. She takes over the role of support character once Teddie`s Persona awakens.</description>
<picture>175768.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32814" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-07-26">
<rating votes="65">7.57</rating>
<name>Shirogane Naoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Young, serious-looking, and possessing an androgynous appearance, Naoto almost always wears a newsboy cap, conveying an appearance not unlike the classical gakuran school uniforms of the late 19th century. Combined with body language and gestures, she is reminiscent of Raidou Kuzunoha, combined with the protagonist of Persona 3. Naoto uses a revolver in combat. A well-known detective, Naoto moves to Inaba in order to aid the police in investigating the serial-murder case. Naoto is dubbed the "Detective Prince" by the media.</description>
<picture>175769.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39681" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-17">
<rating votes="11">6.65</rating>
<name>Kuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kuma`s human form while outside of the Midnight Channel.</description>
<picture>78610.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="139842" update="2012-05-27">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>90</length>
<airdate>2012-06-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168949" update="2015-06-09">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="184550" update="2017-11-14">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2</title>
<summary>30 sec Persona 3 Trailer included with Blu-ray of Persona 4 the Animation ~The Factor of Hope~</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
