<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9257" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-01-03</startdate>
<enddate>2013-03-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Yama no Susume</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ヤマノススメ Encouragement of Climb</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Encouragement of Climb</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">야마노스스메</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">向山进发</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">¡Atrévete a escalar!</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="10293" type="Sequel">Yama no Susume: Second Season</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="12743" approval="37" total="38">Yuru Camp</anime>
<anime id="10684" approval="6" total="10">Koufuku Graffiti</anime>
<anime id="7438" approval="6" total="7">Tamayura</anime>
<anime id="6257" approval="3" total="10">K-On!</anime>
<anime id="9722" approval="1" total="8">Non Non Biyori</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="63560">I liked this well enough, but it was too short, would have preferred a couple of regular length OVAs to flesh out a slice of life story.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="48697">Surprisingly good for a short.
Actually has its share of a story and character development :D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="801594">Recommended to the people who enjoy watching cute girls doing cute thing type of anime .And story was pretty interesting, even though it had only 3 minutes long. And don`t bother by the score.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.yamanosusume.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="21883" type="Animation Work">8bit</name>
<name id="575" type="Character Design">Matsuo Yuusuke</name>
<name id="6520" type="Direction">Yamamoto Yuusuke</name>
<name id="34716" type="Original Work">Shiro</name>
<name id="38550" type="Music">Flyingpan</name>
<name id="575" type="Chief Animation Direction">Matsuo Yuusuke</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch48708 [Aoi] is an indoors-type girl who is afraid of heights. http://anidb.net/ch48744 [Hinata] likes the outdoors, specifically climbing mountains. When the two were young, they once shared a sunrise on a mountaintop. Now, they decide to attempt to relive that experience. They start small by challenging a small hill nearby. Slowly, they gain experience and comrades. How long will it take before they are able to once again witness a sunrise like they did all those years ago?
~ translated and adapted from official site by Cranston</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1170">4.97</permanent>
<temporary count="1172">6.42</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>157537.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14777</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14355</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>17341</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5224</identifier>
<identifier>uehico</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.yamanosusume.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Yama_no_Susume</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ヤマノススメ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2845</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>344496</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15680</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>encouragement-of-climb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2634" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>countryside</name>
<description>The anime takes place far from the any densely populated areas like cities, i.e. out in the suburbs, in the countryside with many fields and forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3395" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-18">
<name>promise</name>
<description>A dramatically-made promise that serves as foreshadowing. The promise will eventually be called in and action will be required.
Whether they succeed, fail or refuse to keep their promise depends almost entirely on the idealism-level of the story. Other factors, such as whether they were told what they had to do, or if it was a Leonine Contract, may come into play. Even Releasing from the Promise is usually a scene of high drama.
Source: TVTropes</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4085" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-17">
<name>unlikely duo</name>
<description>Comedy element: There is usually not only a difference in gender but also in appearance, character, and background concerning the main characters of this anime. Making it very unlikely for them to appear in the same context. Non-the-less they share the same adventure, as in "opposites attract".
These differences are exploited to come up with all sorts of wacky situations.
Examples: A demon-killer or Hero and the daughter of the Demon King. A girl from a normal family and a very intelligent and attractive boy from a very rich background (Shoujo). A very energetic outgoing girl and her very calm almost introverted best friend.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4222" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>walls of text</name>
<description>Walls of text refers to Japanese text that appears in large quantities within the anime itself. This text is most likely vital to the storyline and may come in the form of charts and diagrams or pieces of paper, notes or even thoughts that are only partially or entirely unspoken.
May also be taken as a fair warning to viewers unable to translate Japanese text on their own, suggesting that thorough subtitle support may be required as well as making use of the pause button on their media players so that all text can be read.
Normally, tags don`t refer to physical translations of text, subtitle appearances and karaoke styling added by 3rd parties. But those who seek to describe an anime that is heavy on SPOKEN dialogue (which may tend to create a large quantity of natural subtitling to read for those not fluent in the language being used) could consider this tag but may make clearer reference with the dialogue driven tag.</description>
<picurl>32534.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4246" parentid="3395" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-01">
<name>childhood promise</name>
<description>Sweet childhood promises... who remembers them other than the Japanese anime characters?
It keeps the main characters obsessed with promises that they made when they were children, mostly related to love, with lines like "I will always protect you" or "I will marry you when we grow up".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4344" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-26">
<name>motivational anime</name>
<description>The anime motivates doing something which is shown in the show (for example club activity, sports, choosing a job, a hobby etc).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4712" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-01">
<name>childhood ties</name>
<description>At least two of the characters share a childhood experience together that plays a part in the plot of the anime. The experience can be anything that ties them together, be it a memory, friendship, promise, tragedy, etc. Something happened to them in their childhood which binds them in a way that is unique.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5881" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-06-07">
<name>childhood memory</name>
<description>The childhood memory of one of the protagonists plays an important part as plot device in this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6075" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-12">
<name>educational</name>
<description>The entire series (at least a major part of it) is centred on a particular subject. Information is fed to the audience in a sublime manner. Most of the time an on-screen written comment by the narrator (or translator) can be seen, e.g. biological specimen, medicine, process, etc. Sometimes at the end of every episode’s closing song, a 20 seconds educational clip is presented.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6448" parentid="2881" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-16">
<name>mountaineering</name>
<description>Mountaineering is the sport of climbing mountains.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7146" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-14">
<name>cute girls doing cute things</name>
<description>Cute girls doing cute things with each other (CGDCT): when girls are super friendly with each other and do all sorts of http://anidb.net/t798 [cute/moe] things with each other, but there is no yuri or shoujo ai subtext -- more specifically, there is no romantic subtext.

* CGDCT applies where the main focus is on moe/cute girls and their interactions with each other. Good examples include http://anidb.net/a9722 [Non Non Biyori] (600 weight / 3.0 stars) and http://anidb.net/a9579 [Kin`iro Mosaic] (600 weight / 3.0 stars).
* Generally, CGDCT is applicable only if the anime is also tagged predominantly female cast or all female cast.
* CGDCT does not apply if girls doing cute things is incidental to a larger motive/theme/meta. For example, in http://anidb.net/a8168 [Nichijou] the focus is comedy, using cute girls; the tag would not apply.

CGDCT is often mistaken as low level yuri or shoujo ai. If there is also actual romantic subtext, use the http://anidb.net/t2695 [yuri (18+)] and http://anidb.net/t2782 [shoujo ai] tags as well. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>223153.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="48708" type="main character in" update="2016-01-28">
<rating votes="37">6.46</rating>
<name>Yukimura Aoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130006.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48744" type="main character in" update="2016-01-28">
<rating votes="27">6.60</rating>
<name>Kuraue Hinata</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130007.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48745" type="main character in" update="2016-01-28">
<rating votes="40">7.20</rating>
<name>Aoba Kokona</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132693.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16794" picture="214757.jpg">Ogura Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48746" type="main character in" update="2016-01-28">
<rating votes="42">6.52</rating>
<name>Saitou Kaede</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130008.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68384" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-03">
<rating votes="1">9.11</rating>
<name>Kuraue Ken`ichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>157536.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3337" picture="211147.jpg">Ogino Seirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68417" type="appears in" update="2014-07-05">
<name>Joshi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>157607.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2228" picture="21776.jpg">Gibu Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68418" type="appears in" update="2014-07-05">
<name>Hahaoya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>157608.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34225" picture="127053.jpg">Narumi Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68419" type="appears in" update="2014-07-05">
<rating votes="1">9.11</rating>
<name>Tenchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>157609.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="60" picture="171602.jpg">Kawada Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68420" type="appears in" update="2014-07-05">
<name>Scooter no Otoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>157611.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3337" picture="211147.jpg">Ogino Seirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68421" type="appears in" update="2014-07-05">
<name>Tozankyaku C</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>157610.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3337" picture="211147.jpg">Ogino Seirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68422" type="appears in" update="2014-07-05">
<name>Waiter (Image)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>157615.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3337" picture="211147.jpg">Ogino Seirou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="146325" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-01-03</airdate>
<rating votes="9">3.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">山だけはダメ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Anything but Mountains!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tout sauf la montagne</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yama dake wa Dame!</title>
<summary>Aoi spends most of her time alone, but an old friend from middle school has arrived to make good on an old promise.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616973</identifier>
<identifier>encouragement-of-climb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146445" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-01-24</airdate>
<rating votes="9">3.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">対決! 山料理!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Showdown! Mountain Cooking!?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Concours de cuisine en montagne ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiketsu! Yama Ryouri!?</title>
<summary>Aoi and Hinata have a camping cook-off.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616979</identifier>
<identifier>encouragement-of-climb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146446" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-01-17</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">登山って, 命がけ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mountain Climbing Is Dangerous!?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">C`est dangereux, l`alpinisme ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tozantte, Inochigake!?</title>
<summary>Hinata convinces Aoi they should start with a small mountain and work their way up to the big ones.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616977</identifier>
<identifier>encouragement-of-climb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146447" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふたりで行こう!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Go Together</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Allons-y toutes les deux</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari de Ikou!</title>
<summary>With the help of Hinata’s dad, the girls familiarize themselves with the necessary gear to climb.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616975</identifier>
<identifier>encouragement-of-climb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147107" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-02-14</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">デイパック, どれにする?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Which Daypack Do You Want?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Quel sac choisir ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daypack, Dore ni Suru?</title>
<summary>Aoi picked the mountain but now she needs the right equipment.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616985</identifier>
<identifier>encouragement-of-climb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147108" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-02-07</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決めるのは, わたし!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m the One Deciding!?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">C`est moi qui décide ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimeru no wa, Watashi!?</title>
<summary>It’s Aoi’s turn to pick the mountain, so she calls on her new friend to help.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616983</identifier>
<identifier>encouragement-of-climb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147109" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-01-31</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シュラフって何?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What`s a Schlafsack?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">C`est quoi, un schlafsack ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Schlafsack tte Nani?</title>
<summary>Aoi meets a girl from her school who is crazy about 
backpacking.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616981</identifier>
<identifier>encouragement-of-climb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147598" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-03-07</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">降りるまでが登山!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Climb Isn`t Over Until You Descend!?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La descente, c`est aussi l`aventure ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oriru made ga Tozan!?</title>
<summary>Aoi, Hinata, and Kokona help each other down the mountain.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616991</identifier>
<identifier>encouragement-of-climb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147599" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-02-28</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">森の中で森ガール!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Forest Girl in the Forest!?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fille de la forêt ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mori no Naka de Mori Girl!?</title>
<summary>Hinata teaches Aoi, mountain manners and learn about giant flying squirrels.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616989</identifier>
<identifier>encouragement-of-climb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147600" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-02-21</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">高尾山に登ろう!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Climb Mount Takao!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">À l`assaut du mont Takao !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Takaosan ni Noborou</title>
<summary>Aoi and Hinata embark on their second climb and meet some interesting people along the way.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616987</identifier>
<identifier>encouragement-of-climb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147943" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-03-21</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そして, 次の景色へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the Next Landscape</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Vers de nouveaux paysages</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soshite, Tsugi no Keshiki e</title>
<summary>Aoi, Hinata, Kaeda, and Kokona meet up for a picnic at Hannou River.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616995</identifier>
<identifier>encouragement-of-climb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147944" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-03-14</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">明日はアウトドア!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tomorrow Is Outdoors!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On sort demain !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ashita wa Outdoor!</title>
<summary>In preparation for their next trip, Aoi invites Kokona over to help her cook snacks.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616993</identifier>
<identifier>encouragement-of-climb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150817" update="2014-07-05">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2013-05-24</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">壁って怖くないの?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You`re Not Scared of the Wall?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kabette Kowakunaino?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150956" update="2013-06-13">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="2">3.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="182123" update="2018-10-18">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617145</identifier>
<identifier>encouragement-of-climb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
