<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9299" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>4</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-11-23</startdate>
<enddate>2016-01-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Persona 3 the Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">劇場版「ペルソナ3」</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Персона 3 филмът</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">P3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">P3M</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">PERSONA3 THE MOVIE</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5544" type="Sequel">Persona: Trinity Soul</anime>
<anime id="8378" type="Sequel">Persona 4 The Animation</anime>
<anime id="13331" type="Same Setting">Persona 5 the Animation</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="663539">One time that A1 does a good thing (besides Shin Sekai Yori) but mostly thanks to the source material being good</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="570904">For some reasons I can`t post a review even if the movies are imo standalone.
Anyway, to make it short, Spring of Birth is a generally convincing production that stays very faithful to the source material. Unfortunately, I will go into this a little more in a review some time in the future, I think the source material is a priori not very suited for a movie adaptation, which makes some scenes and concepts appear somewhat artificial and out of place. Nevertheless, recommended for both the fans of the videogames and the general anime audience alike.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.p3m.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="24350" type="Direction">Taguchi Tomohisa</name>
<name id="1303" type="Work">A-1 Pictures</name>
<name id="24686" type="Music">Meguro Shouji</name>
<name id="39014" type="Music">Kobayashi Tetsuya</name>
<name id="9257" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ishikawa Tomomi</name>
<name id="15243" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ootsuka Yae</name>
<name id="4516" type="Chief Animation Direction">Watabe Keisuke</name>
<name id="910" type="Animation Work">AIC A.S.T.A</name>
<name id="4516" type="Character Design">Watabe Keisuke</name>
<name id="28849" type="Persona Design">Aki Kyouma</name>
<name id="11137" type="Direction">Akitaya Noriaki</name>
<name id="10305" type="Chief Animation Direction">Asaki Akiko</name>
<name id="11549" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takahashi Mizuka</name>
<name id="1539" type="Direction">Motonaga Keitarou</name>
<name id="1039" type="Original Work">Atlus</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the RPG game of the same name.
Terrible creatures lurk in the dark, preying on those who wander into the hidden hour that lies between one day and the next—the Dark Hour. A secret school club known as SEES defends humanity from horrors and disasters while working to solve the mystery of the Dark Hour once and for all.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="516">6.37</permanent>
<temporary count="517">7.11</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>224713.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16103</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>14449</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>15771</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>17257</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14407</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>21473</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>31149</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>24543</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5169</identifier>
<identifier>apzewy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.p3m.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Persona_3_The_Movie:_No._1,_Spring_of_Birth</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>Persona_3_The_Movie:_No._2,_Midsummer_Knight's_Dream</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>Persona_3_The_Movie:_No._3,_Falling_Down</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>Persona_3_The_Movie:_No._4,_Winter_of_Rebirth</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ペルソナ3#.E5.8A.87.E5.A0.B4.E7.89.88</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>348490</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>350738</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>346650</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>353674</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16402</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/4628</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>P3movie</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18041</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>19955</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>19250</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>18813</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>19566</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1244" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>summoning</name>
<description>Ability to call/materialize some kind of creature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2801" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>RPG</name>
<description>Any anime that is based on a role-playing game aka RPG. A role-playing video game is a video game which includes elements of non-electronic role-playing games. The player assumes control of one or several fictional characters (a party) who have joined forces in order to perform quests and overcome a great number of challenges and enemies, usually monsters inspired by fantasy, and, to a lesser extent, science fiction and classic mythology. During the course of the game the characters, or avatars, which are generally defined by quantized characteristics, evolve and improve in that their various attributes increase, as well as by gaining more powerful artefacts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2863" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>proxy battles</name>
<description>In our terms, a proxy battle is a battle where humans use creatures/robots to do the fighting for them, either by commanding those creatures/robots or by simply evolving them/changing them into battle mode. Often the training aspect is also involved, or in some cases the proxies are nothing more than holographic representatives of some other variation of competition (like for example a card game). While many popular shounen anime fit under this category, it`s not limited to shounen anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4340" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-26">
<name>suicide</name>
<description>One or several characters in this anime commit suicide.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4537" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-15">
<name>time skip</name>
<description>The plot features at least one skip or jump in time.
Example: A skip from the present into the past, or time skips in increments, e.g. every hour there is a time skip by a day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4612" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep?</name>
<description>The title of Philip K. Dick`s SF novel (movie: Blade Runner). 
The phrase implies a set of existential questions: Do artificial beings (e.g. Replicants, Bioroids, or other AI constructs) dream, feel, or have a soul? If memories can be implanted, what makes real memories real? By contrast — what makes humans human? What is reality? 
These are central themes e.g. in all of the Ghost in the Shell and Appleseed series / movies.</description>
<picurl>210067.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5952" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-25">
<name>end of the world</name>
<description>The imminent end of the world may range from the total destruction of the planet Earth, to the destruction of Earth`s surface, or to the point where human life on the planet is no longer possible, aka the end of humanity.
In any case it looks grim, and the protagonists battle to preserve what they can.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="37509" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-01-23">
<rating votes="15">6.14</rating>
<name>Igor</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A mysterious, long-nosed gentleman who resides in the Velvet Room. Igor`s purpose is to provide insight to the protagonists regarding their powers, emotional bonds, and possible dangers that await them in their journey. It is revealed by http://anidb.net/ch37510 [Margaret] that Igor creates the Velvet Room himself and bases its appearance on who the protagonist is at the time, as well as their situation.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>175780.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2942" picture="23713.jpg">Tanonaka Isamu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54403" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-22">
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<name>Elisabeth</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140322.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54404" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-22">
<name>Iori Junpei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140316.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54405" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-22">
<rating votes="2">9.90</rating>
<name>Yamagishi Fuuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140319.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54406" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-22">
<rating votes="6">8.15</rating>
<name>Takeba Yukari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140315.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54407" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-22">
<rating votes="10">7.00</rating>
<name>Kirijou Mitsuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140317.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54408" type="main character in" update="2013-07-22">
<rating votes="8">8.94</rating>
<name>Yuuki Makoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140314.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54409" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-22">
<name>Sanada Akihiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140318.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58068" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-22">
<rating votes="2">6.25</rating>
<name>Aragaki Shinjirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140320.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="259" picture="17082.jpg">Nakai Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="64372" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-14">
<rating votes="2">8.96</rating>
<name>Koromaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150261.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="64373" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-14">
<rating votes="14">7.22</rating>
<name>Aegis</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150258.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="227" picture="205854.jpg">Sakamoto Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="64374" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-14">
<name>Amada Ken</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150260.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="187" picture="17002.jpg">Ogata Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66681" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-15">
<name>Takaya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153796.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="211" picture="17028.jpg">Kanna Nobutoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66682" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-15">
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<name>Jin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153797.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="183" picture="16992.jpg">Onosaka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66683" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-15">
<rating votes="2">5.80</rating>
<name>Chidori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153798.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71213" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-11-07">
<name>Mochizuki Ryouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>163778.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="141344" update="2012-08-02">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-08-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 00 (0:13)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148639" update="2018-09-14">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>90</length>
<airdate>2013-11-23</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Spring of Birth</title>
<title xml:lang="bg">Пролетта на раждането</title>
<summary>The young Makoto moves to the city of Iwatodai, where strange things happen: when he arrives by train at midnight, the inhabitants of the city suddenly turn into coffins in the so-called dark hour. Meanwhile, a boy with a strange contract is waiting for him in Gekkoukan High school`s dorm. In a fight against a giant creature, Makoto suddenly becomes persona and discovers unimaginable abilities.
Source: ProSieben MAXX</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="152228" update="2013-07-30">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-07-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 02 (1:26)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152229" update="2013-07-30">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-03-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 01 (0:42)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156577" update="2018-09-14">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>100</length>
<airdate>2014-06-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Midsummer Knight`s Dream</title>
<summary>Makoto is happy with his life and learns new friends in the summer, like the elementary student Ken and the Android Aegis. But this carefree state is threatened by new dangers, and Makoto must take all his courage to insist.
Source: ProSieben MAXX</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="163950" update="2018-09-14">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>90</length>
<airdate>2015-04-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Falling Down</title>
<summary>It`s autumn, and for Makoto and the other S.E.E.S. members, the last battle against the Shadows is imminent. In the fights some have to deal with the death of their loved ones. The new pupil Ryoji Mochizuki suddenly seems to be all too abundant...
Source: ProSieben MAXX</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="169457" update="2018-09-16">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>105</length>
<airdate>2016-01-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Winter of Rebirth</title>
<summary>Exchange student Ryoji forces the S.E.E.S. team to make a decision: either the members face the hopeless battle against the being Nyx or they kill Ryoji, which would also mean that their memories are erased and they continue to live peacefully. However, the group will not agree and time is pressing...
Source: ProSieben MAXX</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
