<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9305" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-01-06</startdate>
<enddate>2013-03-31</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ore no Kanojo to Osananajimi ga Shuraba Sugiru</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">My Girlfriend and Childhood Friend Have Too Much Relationship Difficulties</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">내 여자친구와 소꿉친구가 너무 아수라장</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">俺修羅</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">OreShura</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">俺の彼女と幼なじみが修羅場すぎる</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">OreShura</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">我女友与青梅竹马的惨烈修罗场</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8419" approval="74" total="91">Boku wa Tomodachi ga Sukunai</anime>
<anime id="8883" approval="59" total="85">Chuunibyou demo Koi ga Shitai!</anime>
<anime id="9903" approval="40" total="52">Nisekoi</anime>
<anime id="9310" approval="12" total="19">Yahari Ore no Seishun LoveCome wa Machigatte Iru.</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="10">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="21092">Having watched through this mildly amusing, but overwhelmingly common "harem-comedy" (no less only due to a [b]recommendation[/b] by a friend); apart from the scant few gags that happen not to be cringe-worthy, Ore Shura is unfortunately, [b]yet another pile of forgettable dross.[/b]
Credit where it`s due however - the voice acting is probably the only saving grace of the show.
Plenty of better "harem-comedies" out there, or so one might hope.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="602436">looking for a harem? this is prefect for you. 

looking for a real love story with a real conclusion? don`t bother with this. 

it has it`s moments, and the girls are kinda cute, but it doesn`t go anywhere. and the last episode (especially the ending) is a giant middle finger to everyone who actually enjoyed the series and wanted to know who the main character will end up with.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="432184">Don`t understand me wrong, it is a nice watch. It began with such a promising turn of events but very soon, after few episodes, became a standard mix, of standard characters with standard personalities and standard slapstick jokes in a standard harem. *sigh* shame... had such a promising start...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="477067">This show actually picks up towards the end, ending at a pretty watchable harem show with pretty good jokes along the way. Glad I didn`t drop it. What`s good is that the MC isn`t stupidly ignorant. The ending is kinda abrupt though.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="533674">This is NOT a copy of "Chuunibyou", true it uses the eight-grade syndrome as focus in the first series, but then it quickly becomes a maybe not so typical fighting between the girls over the protagonist.

Also the relationship between Masuzu and Eita is unique in such way that it is awkward. This is a light watch and recommended for anyone who likes romance/harem.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="328122">Ok this anime is good, from the start until midway, i enjoy it watching but why does the protagonist always be so dense even all the person surrounding him notice it he didnt get it even slight a bit, in majority of anime, i hate that kind of personality. Sometimes i even stop watching that kind of anime because it gets to my nerve.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="382805">very funny harem comedy</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="121177">Wow!  A harem anime that strikes the right balance between comedy and drama.  The characters all have some depth to them, but not so much that it becomes a tragedy.  I would put this one in the same class as Love Hina.  Easily the best harem I`ve seen in years.  Highly recommended!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="629998">one of the most interesting romance anime out there. the male lead of this anime actually goes somewhere and this series has clear end unlike most harem animes. if anything i would recommend this to anyone :)</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.oreshura.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3405" type="Series Composition">Urahata Tatsuhiko</name>
<name id="5014" type="Music">Oota Masatomo</name>
<name id="4255" type="Character Design">Ootsuka Mai</name>
<name id="4255" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ootsuka Mai</name>
<name id="1303" type="Work">A-1 Pictures</name>
<name id="34535" type="Original Work">Yuuji Yuuji</name>
<name id="2886" type="Direction">Kamei Kanta</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a light novel series of the same name, written by http://anidb.net/cr34535 [Yuuji Yuuji] and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr9167 [Ruroo].
http://anidb.net/ch48954 [Kidou Eita] is a first-year high school student, excelling academically and expressing contempt for romantic relations. He lives a normal school life along with http://anidb.net/ch48955 [Harusaki Chiwa], his childhood friend whom he regards as a younger sister.
One day, the school`s prettiest girl, http://anidb.net/ch48956 [Natsukawa Masuzu], suddenly declares her love to him. However, her real purpose is to establish a fake relationship, deterring those around her from asking her out. To this end, she makes Eita her boyfriend over his objections.
The carnage becomes even more vicious when Eita`s former girlfriend http://anidb.net/ch49815 [Akishino Himeka] and fiancée http://anidb.net/ch49816 [Fuyuumi Ai] are less than amused by the present developments.
~ translated and adapted from official site by Cranston</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2385">4.65</permanent>
<temporary count="2399">6.62</temporary>
<review count="2">3.50</review>
</ratings>
<picture>128683.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14450</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14749</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5235</identifier>
<identifier>rmwxca</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.oreshura.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ore_no_Kanojo_to_Osananajimi_ga_Shuraba_Sugiru</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>俺の彼女と幼なじみが修羅場すぎる</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2819</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>344499</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15643</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>oreshura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1446" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-15">
<name>energetic</name>
<description>An energetic character, often also called a genki character, shows great, often excessive levels of activity or vitality, and seems to always be doing everything extra fast. Genki characters are often slightly, or sometimes very, eccentric, and are filled with confidence and determination, regardless of whether they are competent or not; in fact, they often have little to no actual competence at whatever they generally do. Although genki characters are usually played exclusively for comedy effect, sometimes they may slow down for a serious or introspective moment. The most common genki character archetype is the genki schoolgirl, who will often be late to school and run with a toast in her mouth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1645" parentid="2751" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-03">
<name>kendo</name>
<description>Kendo, or kendou in Japanese, is a popular sport from Japan. It consists of swordplay with one or two http://anidb.net/t1817 [shinai], a two-handed bamboo sword which may also be held with one hand only, while wearing armour.</description>
<picurl>163593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2396" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-08">
<name>swimsuit</name>
<description>A swimsuit is one of several kinds of garments designed to be worn by people engaging in water-based activities or sports or during certain activities under sunlight. Most kinds of swimsuit reveal a large portion of the body surface area, but exceptions exist. The more revealing kinds may also be worn as undergarment in sports that require wetsuits, or when there is a need to display the body, as in the case of beauty pageants or bodybuilding contests.
There is a very wide range of styles of modern swimsuits, which vary in relation to body coverage and materials. The choice of style of swimsuit is dependent on current fashions, community standards of modesty, and plain personal preference. Swimsuits for men usually expose the chest, while those for women do not usually do so; however, many women prefer to engage in water or sun activities with their torso uncovered, in a practice commonly described as toplessness or topfreedom. Since the early twentieth century a naturist movement has developed in western countries that seeks a return to non-sexual nakedness when swimming and during other appropriate activities; in some places around the world, nude beaches have been set aside for people who choose to engage in normal beach activities in the nude, and such beaches may or may not enforce nudity onto their goers.
In anime, it is common for at least one episode to feature the characters in swimsuits, usually as an excuse for gratuitous fanservice; when that happens, the episode is usually labeled a pool or beach episode, after the place the characters went to. Swimsuits, and in particular one-piece swimsuits, are a very common fetish in Japan; while the reason for that is uncertain, a common folk explanation is the fact that boys throughout their entire adolescence are commonly exposed to their female classmates wearing them, in what might be called an experiment in sexual discovery waiting to happen.</description>
<picurl>149786.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2751" parentid="2881" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-27">
<name>combat</name>
<description>Combat involves a violent conflict with the goal to establish dominance over an opponent.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2784" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>sudden girlfriend appearance</name>
<description>Sudden Girlfriend Appearance anime involve a sudden change in the main character`s life where (s)he suddenly gets confronted with an individual (s)he`s sexually attracted to, the two of them inevitably becoming a couple.</description>
<picurl>210066.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2845" parentid="2611" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-04-30">
<name>blackmail</name>
<description>In general usage, blackmail is a crime involving unjustified threats against a person or organization in order to make a gain or harm or cause material loss to them unless a demand is met. It may be considered similar to or a form of extortion, although some jurisdictions will consider them as separate crimes. Most often, blackmail involves the threat of revealing some secret to a given third party, which may be another person, a rival organization, or a state institution such as the police, or to the general public. In anime and related media, and more specifically in pornographic works, blackmail is also a device used to coerce people, generally female and often schoolgirls, into having sex with another or others; in such cases, it may be considered similar to or a form of rape.</description>
<picurl>136031.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3129" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-13">
<name>fake relationship</name>
<description>A relationship where characters just play the boyfriend and girlfriend roles.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4560" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-02-23">
<name>psychological manipulation</name>
<description>Psychological manipulation is a type of social influence that aims to change the perception or behaviour of others through underhanded, deceptive, or even abusive tactics. By advancing the interests of the manipulator, often at the other`s expense, such methods could be considered exploitative, abusive, devious, and deceptive. 
Social influence is not necessarily negative. For example, doctors can try to persuade patients to change unhealthy habits. Social influence is generally perceived to be harmless when it respects the right of the influenced to accept or reject it, and is not unduly coercive. Depending on the context and motivations, social influence may constitute underhanded manipulation.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4729" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-07-06">
<name>colour coded</name>
<description>Every single character on the main cast has a unique hair colour to help less perceptive viewers distiguish between them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="13560" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-09-30">
<rating votes="188">7.50</rating>
<name>Taneshima Popura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Taneshima Popura is a waitress at Wagnaria, and the first employee of the odd restaurant that Takanashi meets. While she is a year older than Takanashi (who calls her `senpai`, as she is his upperclassman at the same school), she is very small for her age, and is too weak to perform some of the menial tasks at the restaurant. She does not take kindly to remarks about her small size, even when they are meant to be complimentary.</description>
<picture>39733.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48954" type="main character in" update="2012-10-15">
<rating votes="39">2.89</rating>
<name>Kidou Eita</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kidou Eita is the main character who aims to attend medical school after graduating from high school. He is very smart and always places at the top of the class during term exams. He has a strong distrust for love and romance because of his parents divorcing when he was in junior high school.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>126916.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29979" picture="223317.jpg">Oosaka Ryouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48955" type="main character in" update="2012-10-15">
<rating votes="70">5.58</rating>
<name>Harusaki Chiwa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Harusaki Chiwa is Eita`s childhood friend. Her friends sometimes call her "chihuahua" because of her petite physique. She used to practice kendo starting in elementary school, but had to give it up due to a critical injury in a car accident the year before the story begins. She does not give up easily and constantly fights Masuzu for Eita`s affections. She is a terrible cook.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>126915.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18198" picture="228672.jpg">Akasaki Chinatsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48956" type="main character in" update="2013-03-10">
<rating votes="103">6.34</rating>
<name>Natsukawa Masuzu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Natsukawa Masuzu is Eita`s classmate who spent nine years overseas. She is considered to be the school beauty and is constantly confessed to by male students, but always shoots them down. However, just like Eita, she hates romance, and used Eita`s notebook filled with embarrassing things to blackmail him to form a faux romantic relationship with her. When she isn`t together with Eita, she is bold and cold; but when she is, she acts more evil and very devious, and loves to use words to trick him. Her family was in Sweden and also has complicated relationship especially with her father, what made her form her twisted personality. Like Chiwa, she is a terrible cook. Masuzu likes to quote scenes from the manga http://anidb.net/a788 [JoJo`s Bizarre Adventure], and being Eita`s official girlfriend, Chiwa, Himeka, and Ai often join forces against her when battling for him.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>126917.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49815" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-10-15">
<rating votes="51">5.38</rating>
<name>Akishino Himeka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126918.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12266" picture="56026.jpg">Kanemoto Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49816" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-10-15">
<rating votes="83">7.76</rating>
<name>Fuyuumi Ai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126919.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51491" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-01">
<rating votes="13">6.44</rating>
<name>Kiryuu Saeko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134555.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51492" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-20">
<rating votes="14">5.00</rating>
<name>Asoi Kaoru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134554.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32750" picture="227075.jpg">Taneda Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51493" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-01">
<rating votes="18">1.81</rating>
<name>Natsukawa Mana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134556.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51924" type="appears in" update="2013-05-04">
<name>Yamamoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60388.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="23534" picture="74510.jpg">Murata Taishi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51925" type="appears in" update="2013-01-06">
<name>Tannin Kyoushi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130401.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23484" picture="151668.jpg">Keichou Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52066" type="appears in" update="2013-01-13">
<name>Sakagami Otouto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130684.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31313" picture="84218.jpg">Hanae Natsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52067" type="appears in" update="2013-01-20">
<name>Akano Mei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>131080.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27218" picture="223318.jpg">Ootsubo Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52068" type="appears in" update="2013-01-20">
<name>Aoba Satsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>131081.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29353" picture="186153.jpg">Yamazaki Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52274" type="appears in" update="2013-01-20">
<name>Sakagami Takuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>131079.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="191" picture="17006.jpg">Suzumura Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52411" type="appears in" update="2013-01-27">
<name>Kanojo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>131416.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34901" picture="130616.jpg">Lynn</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52412" type="appears in" update="2013-01-27">
<name>Kareshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>131415.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34784" picture="129957.jpg">Yamashita Daiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52642" type="appears in" update="2013-05-05">
<name>Sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60390.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="28471" picture="57632.jpg">Yamamoto Itaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52643" type="appears in" update="2013-02-09">
<name>Yasuoka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>131975.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10906" picture="200861.jpg">Yanagita Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53236" type="appears in" update="2013-02-25">
<name>Waitress</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132777.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34426" picture="128153.jpg">Suzaki Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53237" type="appears in" update="2013-02-25">
<name>Zombie</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132774.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23534" picture="74510.jpg">Murata Taishi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53238" type="appears in" update="2013-02-25">
<name>Shintani</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132775.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23805" picture="66166.jpg">Masuda Toshiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53239" type="appears in" update="2013-02-25">
<name>Tanaka Yoshie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132776.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4007" picture="25937.jpg">Mikami Shiori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53240" type="appears in" update="2013-02-25">
<name>Koushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132778.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30309" picture="80361.jpg">Saitou Hironori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53407" type="appears in" update="2013-03-03">
<name>Junji-san</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="30309" picture="80361.jpg">Saitou Hironori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53408" type="appears in" update="2013-03-03">
<name>Shutsuensha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133128.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33060" picture="157977.jpg">Koyanagi Ryoukan</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53409" type="appears in" update="2013-03-03">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Osanai Eita</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133129.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29353" picture="186153.jpg">Yamazaki Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53411" type="appears in" update="2013-03-03">
<rating votes="2">4.40</rating>
<name>Fuyuumi Ai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133127.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54557" type="appears in" update="2013-04-01">
<name>Cameraman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134531.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10906" picture="200861.jpg">Yanagita Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54558" type="appears in" update="2013-04-01">
<name>Kawachi Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134533.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34426" picture="128153.jpg">Suzaki Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54559" type="appears in" update="2013-04-01">
<name>Suzumiya Yoshino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134532.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29353" picture="186153.jpg">Yamazaki Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="146352" update="2015-07-16">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-06</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">高校生活のスタートは修羅場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Start of My High School Life is a Battleground</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koukou Seikatsu no Start wa Shuraba</title>
<summary>Kidou Eita, abandoned by his parents after their divorce, has a rather cynical attitude towards love and relationships, much to the frustration of his childhood friend Harusaki Chiwa, and prioritises his studies above all, so he can get a scholarship to medical school and become a doctor. An incredibly beautiful girl named Natsukawa Masuzu transfers into his class after living overseas for nine years. One day, Masuzu suddenly asks him to walk home with her after declaring that she`s in love with him. He agrees to do so reluctantly, and eventually she says that so many other boys have confessed their love for her since she transferred and she wants it to stop, so she chose Eita to be her fake boyfriend. He is initially reluctant, but after she suddenly produces his old notebook full of his embarrassing chuunibyou fantasies and blackmails him with its contents he grudgingly agrees to her proposal.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617507</identifier>
<identifier>oreshura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146404" update="2013-03-24">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-12-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">~自らを演出する乙女の特番~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Advance Special</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mizukara o Enshutsu Suru Otome no Tokuban</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146405" update="2015-07-17">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-27</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">男の戦いは修羅場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fighting over a Guy is a Battlefield</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otoko no Tatakai wa Shuraba</title>
<summary>The next day Eita changes his plans to study and instead goes to the rendezvous where Chiwa is supposed to meet Sakagami, and is surprised to see Masuzu already there. Chiwa is made to wait over an hour, and it turns out Sakagami set her up as a bet at her expense, and humiliates her in front of his friends. Masuzu seems to have intended for this to happen so Chiwa would become as cynical as she and Eita are about love, but this infuriates Eita, who charges out to fight Sakagami and his friends in his chuunibyou persona "Burning Fighting Fighter", but winds up getting beaten bloody. They are about to attack Chiwa as well, but someone tosses her a pole which she uses like a kendo shinai, and gives them a sound drubbing. The shameful scene exposes Sakagami for the sort of person he is to the whole school.
Masuzu doesn`t show up for school the next day, and Eita tries to visit her. She meets him out in the street, and as they talk, she suddenly kisses him. As usual her behaviour is ambiguous.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617513</identifier>
<identifier>oreshura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146406" update="2015-07-17">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-20</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幼なじみの涙で修羅場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Battleground Over the Tears of a Childhood Friend</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Osananajimi no Namida de Shuraba</title>
<summary>Masuzu proposes that Chiwa act out incidents from her previous life and has her and Eita act out a scene she creates. This impresses their classmates who believed they were performing a drama sketch. Masuzu then decides it`s time for Chiwa to ask Sakagami out. She agrees, and does so by putting a letter into his shoe locker. Much to everyone`s surprise he meets up with her and agrees to a date the following Sunday. Eita cooks all of Chiwa`s favourite foods to celebrate. However, she is disturbed that Eita seems to be so happy for her and leaves, wishing they weren`t childhood friends. Eita later recalls how he originally wanted to become a doctor so he would be able to help Chiwa after she was injured and could no longer do kendo.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617511</identifier>
<identifier>oreshura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146407" update="2015-07-16">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-13</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新しい部を結成して修羅場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Starting a New Club Is a Battleground</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atarashii Bu o Kessei Shite Shuraba</title>
<summary>Chiwa sees Eita and Masuzu walking together arms linked and she objects, saying that anyone who wants to date him should have her permission first, because she knows him best. Masuzu handles her intrusion with great finesse. She later tells Eita to bring Chiwa with him to the former tea club room, and there says that she is forming a new club called the "Maiden`s Society For Performing Your Own Life" (自らを演出する乙女の会, Mizukara wo Enshutsu-suru Otome no Kai), for girls to learn how to become popular. Chiwa is convinced to join. She tells Masuzu that she sort of has an interest in a member of the basketball team named Sakagami, and Masuzu suggests that she bring around an empty guitar case to give people the impression that she is into music and to attract the attention of Sakagami. Masuzu later asks Eita to be more serious with their pretence and not to look at other girls.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617509</identifier>
<identifier>oreshura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146547" update="2013-01-05">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-01-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146750" update="2013-01-12">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-01-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146863" update="2015-08-05">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-24</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">映画館Wデートで修羅場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Movie Theater Double Dates are a Battlefield</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eigakan Double Date de Shuraba</title>
<summary>Eita is convinced that Ai`s boyfriend is real, remaining oblivious to her dubious behaviour towards him, though Masuzu remains sceptical. Nevertheless, after Kaoru invites Eita and Ai to the cinema with free tickets, Masuzu tells him get Ai to fall in love with him, so even if her boyfriend proves to be real they`ll have something to use against her to get the club reinstated. Chiwa tags along paired with Kaoru, while Masuzu follows behind them to observe. On the way to the theatre, Ai is trying to get Eita to remember kindergarten, as it seems they knew each other back then, but Chiwa interferes. The film allows audience interaction and as the relationships between the characters seem to parallel theirs, Ai and Chiwa get caught up, with Eita in the middle.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617521</identifier>
<identifier>oreshura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146864" update="2015-08-04">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-17</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏期講習なのに修羅場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">They`re Only Summer Classes, But They Too Are a Battlefield</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakikoushuu na no ni Shuraba</title>
<summary>The club is caught making a disturbance at the infirmary after Himeka tries to seduce Eita, and finally Fuyumi Ai, the chief of the hall monitors, brings the hammer down on them and has their club shut down. Masuzu and Chiwa bait her by saying she`s jealous of their club`s goal of making girls popular, to which she brags that she has a boyfriend named "Murata Michel Daigorou" who is obviously completely fictitious, but they can`t actually prove it.
The club thus shut down, Eita goes to summer classes, where he finds Ai is in the same class as him. When Masuzu learns about this she orders Eita to try to prove that Ai is lying about having a boyfriend. Ai in the meantime sends clear signals that she likes Eita, and one day when he is having dinner with Ai and Kaoru, Ai is about to admit the truth, but Chiwa and Himeka see them and she is forced to keep up the pretence.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617519</identifier>
<identifier>oreshura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146865" update="2015-07-29">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-10</airdate>
<rating votes="8">3.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">灰色の世界を切り裂く修羅場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Battlefield Where the Gray World is Cut to Shreds</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haiiro no Sekai o Kirisaku Shuraba</title>
<summary>Everyone, including Eita, is flabbergasted when Himeka introduces herself as Eita`s ex-girlfriend. After a chat with Kaoru he wonders exactly what she sees in him. Himeka is later invited by Masuzu to the club, and after Chiwa and Masuzu are chased off by the hall monitors for performing unsanctioned activities he gets to talk to her alone. She explains how she had found her current world grey and boring and found the way he fought against those bullies the other day so cool.
As punishment for their unsanctioned activities, that weekend the club is made to clean the pool. Masuzu`s sister Mana comes by to visit, who informs her that her father is angry and has ordered her to go back to Sweden. Masuzu agrees to leave, which upsets everyone, even Chiwa. Mana then takes a poem Himeka wrote and mockingly recites it, which angers Eita enough that he tries to attack her, but he is beaten up by her bodyguard. This convinces Masuzu to change her mind and remain in Japan despite her father`s orders, and she forces Mana to apologise. Later, Himeka is made an official member of the club.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617517</identifier>
<identifier>oreshura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146866" update="2015-07-17">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-03</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラブレターの真相は修羅場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Truth of the Love Letter Is a Battleground</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Love Letter no Shinsou wa Shuraba</title>
<summary>Eita begins receiving anonymous love letters in his shoe locker, he tries to to unravel the mystery himself, keeping the letters secret from Chiwa and Masuzu. At first he suspects it might be Chiwa writing those letters.
Masuzu suspects that he is hiding something, but is interrupted by the sudden appearance of her sister Mana, who threatens her with veiled threats involving their father, and steals a kiss from Eita. She refuses to talk about it but is actually bothered by that kiss. Later, Chiwa gets sick, and while he is nursing her he realises that she can`t be the one writing the letters.
Eita receives a third letter, nearly getting caught by Chiwa and Masuzu, this time saying they should meet, and he finds the letters were from a girl he has never seen before, Akishino Himeka, who claims to have been his lover in a past life. She seems to have crafted her chuunibyou fantasies around his, after seeing him fight as "Burning Fighting Fighter". She embraces him, despite his objections, when Chiwa and Masuzu see them.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617515</identifier>
<identifier>oreshura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147531" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-24</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦略の結末は修羅場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Result Following a Scheme Is a Battlefield</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senryaku no Ketsumatsu wa Shuraba</title>
<summary>Masuzu and Eita ruse is being questioned by other members of the group.  Masuzu 
believes they have to take their fake relationship to the next level.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617529</identifier>
<identifier>oreshura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147532" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-17</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">合宿前夜のワクワクは修羅場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Excitement the Night Before a Trip Is a Battlefield</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gasshuku Zen`ya no Wakuwaku wa Shuraba</title>
<summary>Saeko is offering the girls the chance of a lifetime…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617527</identifier>
<identifier>oreshura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147533" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-10</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏合宿の会議で修羅場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summer Training Camp Meetings Are a Battlefield</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu Gasshuku no Kaigi de Shuraba</title>
<summary>A planned club trip to the beach requires the girls to get new swim suits and they all need Eita’s help in picking out the right one.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617525</identifier>
<identifier>oreshura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147534" update="2015-08-08">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-03</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">よみがえる約束は修羅場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Promises That Come Back are a Battlefield</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yomigaeru Yakusoku wa Shuraba</title>
<summary>One day, after classes, Eita finds a notebook someone left behind filled with rather embarrassing love poetry dedicated to someone called `Takkun`.  It is actually Ai`s, and she unsuccessfully attempts to retrieve it before he realises what it is. As penance for reading her private notebook, she gets him to come with her to the fireworks festival the following evening. He had previously refused invitations made by the other girls to the same event as he wanted to just study.
He meets with Ai at the school, and as they go around town Eita begins to remember some key things from kindergarten life, such as the spot he discovered was the best vantage point from which to see the fireworks. Finally, he remembers that he used to be called `Takkun` by Ai, whom he called `A-chan`, back in kindergarten. As the fireworks festival starts Ai she admits that her boyfriend was fake, and reminds him that he also promised to marry her back then, and produces an old `marriage contract` that they produced before, in crayons and childish handwriting, and asks him to sign it. He tries to escape, running into Chiwa and Himeka who get him to attend the rest of the festival.
The next day he meets with Masuzu at the club room, who asks him to explain what he was doing with Ai, as she saw them. She has him kiss her as penance, and then tries to poke him in the eyes but fails. Ai has also rescinded the order to disband the club, and joins the club herself.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617523</identifier>
<identifier>oreshura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147950" update="2013-03-06">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview eps 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148030" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-31</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新しい世界への修羅場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Battlefield That Leads to a New World</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atarashii Sekai e no Shuraba</title>
<summary>Eita makes a declaration that brings the battle to a close, but at what cost?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617531</identifier>
<identifier>oreshura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148707" update="2013-03-30">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-03-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="149086" update="2013-04-11">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview eps 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="149087" update="2013-04-11">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview eps 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150277" update="2013-05-01">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview eps 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150278" update="2013-05-01">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview eps 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150940" update="2013-06-01">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview eps 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150941" update="2013-06-01">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview eps 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151895" update="2013-07-13">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview eps 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151896" update="2013-07-13">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview eps 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152441" update="2013-08-09">
<epno type="4">T11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview eps 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152442" update="2013-08-09">
<epno type="4">T10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview eps 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="153268" update="2013-09-01">
<epno type="4">T12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview eps 13</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
