<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9306" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-06-30</startdate>
<enddate>2015-07-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon Crystal</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">美少女戦士セーラームーンCrystal 第2期</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">美少女戦士セーラームーン Crystal Season I</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">美少女戦士セーラームーン Crystal Season II</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">美少女戦士セーラームーン クリスタル</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">美少女戦士セーラームーンCrystal 第1期</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pretty Soldier Sailor Moon (2014)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Sailor Moon Remake</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pretty Guardian Sailor Moon: Crystal</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Sailor Moon Crystal</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Прекрасная воительница Сейлор Мун: Кристалл</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Красавица-воин Сейлор Мун: Кристалл</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Красивата пазителка Сейлър Муун: Кристал</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon Crystal Season II</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon Crystal Season I</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">sm2014</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">SMC</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">美少女戦士セーラームーン Crystal</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Pretty Guardian Sailor Moon Crystal</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Sailor Moon Crystal</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Sailor Moon Crystal</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Sailor Moon Crystal</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Sailor Moon Crystal</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="11665" type="Sequel">Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon Crystal Season III</anime>
<anime id="235" type="Alternative Setting">Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon</anime>
<anime id="2539" type="Alternative Setting">Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon R</anime>
<anime id="10743" type="Other">Moon Pride</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="161" approval="5" total="8">Tokyo Mew Mew</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="520752">Normally as a director (or writer) if you remake something, you try to improve it. In this case, they just made it look modern and that`s it. The original anime 20 years ago was a reflection of up to date animation and storytelling, witch by current standards isn`t going to work any more. The use of CGI made the animation look weird instead of better.
If only they chose to replaced the stupid main weapon (tiara) with something believable, remove the annoying postures and leave out announcing every single attack move or transformation, than perhaps this would be watchable.
Maybe the soul purpose of this remake was to "create" a show for girls 10 to 15 years old or to give hardcore fans something to revive their long lost feelings. The final thought therefore is: FANS and MASOCHIST ONLY.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="27321">An excellent new adaptation of the manga. Animation is spot on, the transformation sequence is wondrous. I remember the original anime well and the 1st episode of Crystal is nearly identical to the original series but different.. and faster pace, I think. But that is understandable. If they wish to do all four lieutenants and Beryl by the end of 26 epsodes (and not turn the 1st arc in to 2 seasons or something), they would have to cut a lot of filler as the original season 1 (Dark Kingdom arc) was 46 episodes.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="239672">Just seen the first Episode and I was really suprised how the story starts compared to the "old" series.
I`m just flashed waching the start of the whole series, everything is looking more mature and more attached to the drawing style of the manga. The story in the first episode is the same, but made differently.
I was direcly drawn into the story. It is like watching a movie. Sailor Moon is with this on a completly new level and I can`t wait to see more of it!
It is a must see for this season!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="114582">First of all, it`s a new adaptation of the manga, not a remake of the anime from 1992 and it`s more mature with plot continuity and it feels just like the manga. It has wonderful background music, it keeps the mahou shoujo elements and Sailor Moon trademarks. If you`ve read the manga, you`ll be pleased. Now, if you just watched the original anime, then you`ll notice improvements in the relationship between Usagi/Mamoru and Sailor Moon/Tuxedo Kamen respectively, in the scenes, the story and its pace. Watching the Act 1 in 1080p and then the transformation, it`s majestic.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://sailormoon-official.com/animation/</url>
<creators>
<name id="9182" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sakou Yukie</name>
<name id="9182" type="Character Design">Sakou Yukie</name>
<name id="2754" type="Music">Takanashi Yasuharu</name>
<name id="11159" type="Direction">Sakai Munehisa</name>
<name id="23959" type="Series Composition">Kobayashi Yuuji</name>
<name id="3636" type="Original Work">Takeuchi Naoko</name>
<name id="11487" type="Chief Animation Direction">Komatsu Kozue</name>
<name id="1834" type="Animation Work">Toei Animation</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a manga of the same name by http://anidb.net/cr3636 [Takeuchi Naoko], serialised in http://anidb.net/cr30441 [Nakayoshi].
http://anidb.net/ch7320 [Tsukino Usagi] is a little clumsy and a crybaby, but she is also one spirited eighth grader. One day she meets http://anidb.net/ch7481 [Luna], a black cat with a crescent moon mark on her forehead, and transforms into the pretty sailor-suited guardian of love and justice, http://anidb.net/ch7321 [Sailor Moon]. As a chosen guardian of justice, Usagi apparently has a mission to protect a princess, and to find her fellow Guardians and the Legendary Silver Crystal.
Meanwhile, http://anidb.net/ch7605 [Queen Beryl] of the Dark Kingdom sends her subordinates to the town where Usagi lives. They cause strange events to occur there, all in an effort to acquire the tremendously powerful Silver Crystal.
Can Sailor Moon and the other Guardians successfully find the Legendary Silver Crystal, and protect the princess?
Note: Commemorating the 20th anniversary of Sailor Moon. The first episode received advance premiere screening on Usagi`s birthday 30.06.2014 at the collaboration birthday party with women`s fashion magazine ViVi. Male attendees were not allowed, unless accompanied by a female attendee.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="703">3.75</permanent>
<temporary count="712">5.93</temporary>
<review count="3">3.49</review>
</ratings>
<picture>151528.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15693</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14751</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://sailormoon-official.com/animation/1_2/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.viz.com/anime/streaming/sailor-moon-crystal</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Sailor_Moon_Crystal</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>List_of_Sailor_Moon_Crystal_episodes</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>美少女戦士セーラームーンCrystal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3452</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>348671</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>351073</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17300</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=v9Ft3viBgtQ</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=sJmn-pyEwfk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>sailor-moon-crystal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19676</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>19905</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="34">
<externalentity>
<url>https://ch.nicovideo.jp/sailormoon-Crystal</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3159" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-11-27">
<name>emotions awaken superpowers</name>
<description>During an extreme emotional state — rage, love, hate, angst, sadness, compassion — something inside the character will "click" that will increase greatly his/her power or a new superpower awakes, that surpasses anything achieved by him/her until then.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3322" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-04">
<name>remake</name>
<description>This anime is a remake of a previously released story, anime, or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3528" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-05-13">
<name>reincarnation</name>
<description>One of the main characters was reborn in another body.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3667" parentid="2676" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo Tower</name>
<description>Tokyo Tower is a communications and observation tower in the Shiba-koen district of Minato, Tokyo, Japan. At 332.9 metres, it is the second-tallest structure in Japan. The structure is an Eiffel Tower-inspired lattice tower that is painted white and international orange to comply with air safety regulations.
Source: Wikipedia
Note: Not to be confused with the very much younger http://anidb.net/t3037 [Tokyo Skytree].</description>
<picurl>161123.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3824" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-01-05">
<name>sentai</name>
<description>In Japanese, sentai is a military unit, and may be translated as "squadron", "task force", "group" or "wing". In the anime fandom, however, it usually refers to the Super Sentai Series, a long-running superhero team franchise of http://anidb.net/t5000 [tokusatsu] shows featuring live action characters and colorful special effects, and other similar shows. A prominent characteristic of such shows is that the colour- and elemental-coded heroes, usually numbering around five or more, fight to save the world from the evil that terrorizes the area, which may even span the entire universe.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5882" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>secret identity</name>
<description>The (usually main) protagonist has a secret identity that he or she desperately tries to keep secret.
This can lead to all sorts of amusing misunderstandings, thus is used as comedy element in some anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6004" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>development hell</name>
<description>Due to unforeseen circumstances, the production or release of this anime has been pushed back, stalled, or cancelled one or more times from when it was first announced.
While some of them have eventually been completed, others might have only had a trailer released or have been changed into another format (e.g. a TV series turned into an OVA).
Common reasons for a work to become stuck in development hell include creative differences, legal issues, financial problems, scheduling conflicts or the death of an involved creator.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6006" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>Tokyo is the centre of the universe</name>
<description>Whether it`s the big bad evil aiming for world domination, demons bringing the hell over to this site or aliens attacking the Earth, their centre of attention is always Tokyo, as if the rest of the world did not even exist!
But worry not if you happen to live there, because your neighbour could just be the leader of a senshi team or the pilot of a giant mecha and they are surely going to save the day again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6019" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-20">
<name>brainwashing</name>
<description>Brainwashing, the application of coercive techniques to change the values and beliefs, perceptions and judgements, and subsequent mindsets and behaviours of one or more people, usually for political, financial, personal, or religious purposes. Often features in dark anime or pornography.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7320" type="main character in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="341">7.40</rating>
<name>Tsukino Usagi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsukino Usagi is a carefree schoolgirl who can transform into the de facto leader of the series` primary heroines, the Sailor Senshi.</description>
<picture>154978.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7321" type="main character in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="358">7.40</rating>
<name>Sailor Moon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154979.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7326" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="302">7.57</rating>
<name>Mizuno Ami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154974.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12266" picture="56026.jpg">Kanemoto Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7330" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="177">7.56</rating>
<name>Sailor Mercury</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154975.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12266" picture="56026.jpg">Kanemoto Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7335" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-08-17">
<rating votes="240">8.06</rating>
<name>Hino Rei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hino Rei is the real identity of http://anidb.net/ch7337 [Sailor Mars]. She works as a miko at the Hikawa Shrine, and is shown to have an affinity with two crows who live there, named Phobos and Deimos (the same as Mars` two moons).
Rei is fiery, boy-crazy, practical and ambitious, longing to one day become a singer, model, and voice actress envisioning herself as ultimately getting married.
Rei and Usagi have a very tempestuous relationship and argue frequently. Though these arguments are usually petty, early in the series Rei tries to take Usagi`s role as Senshi Leader. Her loyalty to Usagi becomes much stronger later in the series, and affection replaces the earlier resentment.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>154972.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7337" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="137">7.53</rating>
<name>Sailor Mars</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154973.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7341" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="197">7.65</rating>
<name>Kino Makoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154976.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7342" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="171">7.36</rating>
<name>Sailor Jupiter</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154977.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7344" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="212">6.99</rating>
<name>Aino Minako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154970.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7345" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-27">
<rating votes="178">7.58</rating>
<name>Sailor Venus</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154971.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7374" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-28">
<rating votes="114">5.76</rating>
<name>Chiba Mamoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chiba Mamoru is an university student who live in the same town as Usagi. They hate each other initially but later become lovers.
Chiba Mamoru is the reincarnation of http://anidb.net/ch9313 [Prince Endymion] and the civilian identity of http://anidb.net/ch7375 [Tuxedo Kamen]. In the 30th century, he will be known as http://anidb.net/ch7487 [King Endymion].</description>
<picture>137248.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7375" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-22">
<rating votes="85">7.25</rating>
<name>Tuxedo Kamen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tuxedo Kamen is a fictional character and one of the primary protagonists of the Sailor Moon metaseries. He disguises himself in order to support the series` central heroines, the Sailor Senshi.
Wearing a mask to conceal his identity, he interferes with enemy operations, offers the Senshi advice, and sometimes physically aids them in battle.
Like the Senshi, Tuxedo Mask possesses a power item like theirs: a Sailor Crystal, which gives him guardianship over the planet Earth.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>135712.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7463" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-03-26">
<rating votes="132">3.54</rating>
<name>Chibiusa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>166530.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="304" picture="17139.jpg">Fukuen Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7464" type="appears in" update="2012-02-26">
<rating votes="47">5.07</rating>
<name>Sailor Chibi Moon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>82278.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="304" picture="17139.jpg">Fukuen Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7467" type="appears in" update="2013-04-29">
<rating votes="14">6.09</rating>
<name>Sailor V</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sailor V is a preliminary form, under which http://anidb.net/ch7344 [Minako] fought alone before the other Sailor Senshi were awakened. The V is short for Venus. She wore a different uniform under this name, most notably a red mask, and her appearance and powers incorporated the use of a crescent motif.
In the early storyline of Sailor Moon, she is something of a celebrity figure, of whom Usagi is a great fan.
Sailor V was first introduced as the protagonist of Takeuchi Naoko`s much-shorter manga series, Codename: Sailor V, of which Sailor Moon is a sequel.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>136004.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7481" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-29">
<rating votes="162">6.89</rating>
<name>Luna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26339.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="346" picture="17184.jpg">Hirohashi Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7486" type="appears in" update="2009-06-13">
<rating votes="17">6.44</rating>
<name>Neo-Queen Serenity</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28710.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="407" picture="17254.jpg">Koyama Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7487" type="appears in" update="2009-06-13">
<rating votes="8">6.27</rating>
<name>King Endymion</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28711.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7490" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-29">
<rating votes="75">7.13</rating>
<name>Artemis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26338.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9912" picture="65378.jpg">Oobayashi Youhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7524" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-03-14">
<rating votes="70">6.27</rating>
<name>Sailor Pluto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>166531.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1660" picture="53927.jpg">Maeda Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7567" type="appears in" update="2014-02-11">
<rating votes="10">6.79</rating>
<name>Black Lady</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>When she returns to the future with Sailor Moon, Chibiusa becomes Black Lady (Wicked Lady in the English adaptation) when she is captured outside of the Palace. Wiseman comes across the lonely Chibiusa, who is feeling frustrated after a failed attempt to revive her mother, and twists her memories of her family to make her do his bidding. Wiseman converts her by laying the seeds of guilt for what she has done, and by telling her nobody loves her.
Infected with the power of the Black Crystal, she grows older, donning an organdy and satin dress and the earrings worn by the Black Moon Clan. Her hair becomes even longer than Usagi`s. Her crescent becomes that of the Clan, and she is frequently seen with Prince Demand or Wiseman. As Chibiusa`s dream is to become a beautiful lady like her mother, Black Lady`s form is something like a femme fatale.
Her history and personality differ between the anime and the manga. In the anime, Black Lady hates her family and the Sailor Senshi and tries to kill them because she believes she is unloved. She also considers her toy, Luna-P, as her only friend. In the manga, she throws away the Luna-P after her transformation and derides it as a childish toy.
Black Lady uses her brainwashing powers to try to seduce her future father, Mamoru Chiba, and tries to destroy the Senshi for their various acts of insensitivity toward her. She first appears in Act 20 of the manga and Episode 85 of the anime. In the anime, Black Lady tries to kill Sailor Moon and Tuxedo Mask, but is saved from her anger by Sailor Moon, who changes into Neo-Queen Serenity and embraces her daughter, allowing her to turn back into Chibiusa. In the manga, her sorrow over the death of Sailor Pluto shatters Wiseman`s power over her, her tears activating the future Silver Crystal, and she changes into Sailor Chibi Moon for the first time.</description>
<picture>26342.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="304" picture="17139.jpg">Fukuen Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7600" type="appears in" update="2019-12-15">
<rating votes="3">3.95</rating>
<name>Shitennou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Shitennou (Four Heavenly Kings) are sub-leaders of the Dark Kingdom, working directly under Queen Beryl.
Each member has epaulettes on his uniform, which indicate their respective ranks.
The four where brainwashed by Queen Beryl, truly they are the knights of Prince Endymion and lovers of the sailor warriors.</description>
<picture>35900.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7602" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-30">
<rating votes="17">5.76</rating>
<name>Jadeite</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jadeite is the first of the Shiten`ou to appear. He is the head of the Dark Kingdom`s Far-Eastern Division and his primary mission is hunting energy.
He is named after the mineral jadeite.</description>
<picture>135792.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="63" picture="186695.jpg">Kishio Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7605" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-29">
<rating votes="18">4.35</rating>
<name>Queen Beryl</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26378.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25" picture="16608.jpg">Watanabe Misa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7700" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-30">
<rating votes="11">6.54</rating>
<name>Nephrite</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nephrite is the second of the Shiten`ou to appear. Queen Beryl appoints him to continue the energy hunting job following Jadeite being condemned to Eternal Sleep. Nephrite hypothesizes that more energy can be taken by concentrating on a single human than by drawing from a crowd as Jadeite usually.
Establishing himself in an abandoned church, he uses intonation with the stars to detect the energy potential of individual people before attacking them when he implants the essence of one of his Youma into a specific person`s object.
He, in turn, is mocked by his would-be successor, Zoisite. Nephrite uses one alter ego, Sanjouin Masato, a wealthy businessman and socialite.
He is named after the mineral nephrite.</description>
<picture>135947.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7702" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-30">
<rating votes="13">3.85</rating>
<name>Zoisite</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Zoisite is the third of the Shiten`ou.
Zoisite is introduced along with Nephrite, ridiculing him in each episode.
After Queen Metalia was awakened, Queen Beryl appointed Zoisite to find the Rainbow Crystals. He is more successful than either of his predecessors, obtaining all seven fragments of the Silver Crystal.
He is named after the mineral zoisite.
Note: He is a female in the english and german version.</description>
<picture>136053.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="263" picture="186711.jpg">Matsukaze Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7704" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-30">
<rating votes="16">6.01</rating>
<name>Kunzite</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kunzite is the fourth and final member of the Shiten`ou, and the highest in rank and by far the strongest. Unlike the others, he wears a white cape in addition to his uniform.
Kunzite and Zoisite are very close in the anime, lovers as well as allies. He has occasionally assisted Zoisite in obtaining the Rainbow Crystals.
He is named after the mineral kunzite.</description>
<picture>136055.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2796" picture="23212.jpg">Takemoto Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7747" type="appears in" update="2013-05-07">
<rating votes="5">3.54</rating>
<name>Queen Metalia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Queen Metalia is a malignant, amorphous energy being. She was born as a result of radioactivity in the sun and is the true mastermind behind the Dark Kingdom.</description>
<picture>2316.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="4020" picture="28744.jpg">Matsuoka Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7748" type="appears in" update="2009-05-31">
<rating votes="14">5.97</rating>
<name>Queen Serenity</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26690.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="407" picture="17254.jpg">Koyama Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7749" type="appears in" update="2009-05-31">
<rating votes="33">7.31</rating>
<name>Princess Serenity</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26691.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7871" type="appears in" update="2018-08-24">
<rating votes="22">5.53</rating>
<name>Tsukino Ikuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222693.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1870" picture="186893.jpg">Mizutani Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7872" type="appears in" update="2018-09-08">
<rating votes="10">3.41</rating>
<name>Tsukino Shingo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223402.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34409" picture="127935.jpg">Ryuu Seira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7873" type="appears in" update="2018-08-26">
<rating votes="7">2.88</rating>
<name>Tsukino Kenji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222776.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="231" picture="23486.jpg">Madono Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7974" type="appears in" update="2013-10-24">
<rating votes="12">4.09</rating>
<name>Kooan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kooan is the youngest of the sisters and represents a counterpart of Hino Rei. Her name is short for kouankou (紅安鉱), the Japanese word for kermesite.
Kooan, like all of her sisters, is very vain about her appearance to the point of swearing death upon anyone who smudges her make-up or ruins her hair, and she relies on her charms to get what she wants. She believes that she and Rubeus are in a relationship, and competes with her sisters for his love.
Her attack is Dark Fire, in which she threw blue fire at her target.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>144738.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="271" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7975" type="appears in" update="2013-10-24">
<rating votes="12">5.62</rating>
<name>Berthier</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Berthier is the second youngest sister. Her name is French, coming from the mineral berthierite. She fears Rubeus but has no love interest for him unlike her other sisters.
Berthier has a very darkly playful personality, but is shown to have great respect for all of her siblings. Much like her counterpart in Ami, she is also a strategist and is incredibly talented at chess.
Her attack is Dark Water, which is a stream of freezing water which surrounded her and was then blasted towards the enemy.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>144736.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2139" picture="25822.jpg">Kasahara Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7977" type="appears in" update="2013-10-24">
<rating votes="11">4.29</rating>
<name>Calaveras</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Calaveras is the second oldest of the sisters and has the ability, much like Tuxedo Mask, of communing with spirits of the dead. She is named for the mineral calaverite, and is a counterpart of Aino Minako.
Calaveras is shown to be a petty woman who indulges in relentlessly teasing her other siblings, especially Petz. She also appears unwilling to do anything for herself. She never accepts a single mission and instead tags along on several of Petz`s missions.
She lacks any psychic power in the anime unlike in manga, and her attack is the Dark Beaut whip.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>144737.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2205" picture="186188.jpg">Hanba Tomoe</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7978" type="appears in" update="2013-10-24">
<rating votes="11">3.15</rating>
<name>Petz</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Petz is the oldest of the four sisters. She is named for the mineral petzite and is the counterpart of Kino Makoto.
Petz often clashes with Calaveras, but the majority of both women`s operations end up with them working together. She is very proud and is willing to step on others to achieve personal glory and power. She also appears bitter over a past relationship and reacts strongly when Calaveras teases her about it.
Her attack is Dark Thunder, in which she threw a blast of black lightning toward her target.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>144739.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2413" picture="22272.jpg">Mizuta Wasabi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7979" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-01-26">
<rating votes="10">2.55</rating>
<name>Kurenai no Rubeus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kurenai no Rubeusu, known simply as Rubeus is the first member of the Black Moon Clan to appear in the 20th century. He is charged with finding a person codenamed Rabbit, who had fled into the Tokyo of the past. Besides following the orders of Prince Demand and Wiseman, he leads his own set of minions, the Ayakashi Sisters.
Rubeus arrives in the present in his spaceship to look for Chibiusa. He is the love interest to Kooan, the youngest, though the majority of the sisters are in love with him. However, he does not return their feelings, and is in fact, using them as pawns.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>167979.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52" picture="19811.jpg">Takahashi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8028" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-01-26">
<rating votes="11">4.80</rating>
<name>Midori no Esmeraude</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Midori no Esmeraude is the second of the Black Moon Clan to appear. She is a selfish and vain woman who tries to emanate a goddess-like appearance by wearing an elegant, tight-fitting dress along with opera-length gloves and knee-high stiletto boots. She has a distinctive laugh, loud and piercing, and is the most comedic member of the Black Moon. She is infatuated with Prince Demand, who is obsessed with Sailor Moon.
Souce: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>167980.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8044" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-01-26">
<rating votes="9">5.53</rating>
<name>Ao no Saphire</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ao no Saphire, Blue Saphire, is the alchemist of the Black Moon Clan, and the younger brother of Prince Demand. He is more cautious and rational than his companions. He is the only member of the Clan that does not wear earrings made from Black Crystal, despite having invented them.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>167978.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="586" picture="171556.jpg">Yonaga Tsubasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8177" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-01-26">
<rating votes="9">6.70</rating>
<name>Prince Demand</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Prince Demand is the leader of all of Planet Nemesis in the 30th century.</description>
<picture>167977.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="255" picture="40713.jpg">Miyano Mamoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8244" type="appears in" update="2014-02-11">
<rating votes="7">2.10</rating>
<name>Wiseman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Death Phantom, who calls himself Wiseman, is an immortal form of Chaos from the future. He approached Prince Demand and Saphire when they were younger and manipulated them into gathering power for him, with the ultimate goal being the opening of the Dark Gate. He promised he could give them the power and ability to go to Earth and appeal to Neo-Queen Serenity for amnesty for the citizens of Nemesis, who had committed no crimes themselves.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>150105.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4841" picture="55063.jpg">Iwasaki Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8481" type="appears in" update="2009-06-05">
<rating votes="20">4.50</rating>
<name>Diana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27627.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3929" picture="25678.jpg">Nakagawa Shouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8693" type="appears in" update="2018-08-24">
<rating votes="40">6.07</rating>
<name>Oosaka Naru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222692.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="162" picture="23208.jpg">Satou Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8694" type="appears in" update="2018-09-02">
<rating votes="29">5.82</rating>
<name>Umino Gurio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Umino Gurio is Usagi`s classmate. His defining characteristic is his glasses, which have odd swirls in them, denoting their thickness.
He is a know-it-all, and he keeps Usagi informed on current events, new students, gossip, and any other information she might appreciate.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>223098.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34784" picture="129957.jpg">Yamashita Daiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8772" type="appears in" update="2018-08-25">
<rating votes="25">5.56</rating>
<name>Furuhata Motoki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222716.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4032" picture="77662.jpg">Okamoto Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9006" type="appears in" update="2018-08-25">
<rating votes="12">6.10</rating>
<name>Sakurada Haruna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haruna Sakurada is the junior high school teacher of Usagi Tsukino.
She acts very young for her age, however her personality does change slightly. She has long, brown hair, and can be quite strict, especially when it comes to Usagi mucking things up with her laziness. However, she is also lovesick and obsessed with finding a husband, which makes her an easy target for the Dark Kingdom during the first series.</description>
<picture>222737.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="349" picture="79057.jpg">Kanda Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9013" type="appears in" update="2018-08-30">
<rating votes="4">3.17</rating>
<name>Kuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222966.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38300" picture="236362.jpg">Morishita Yukiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9014" type="appears in" update="2009-06-11">
<rating votes="4">2.65</rating>
<name>Yumiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28488.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28674" picture="77522.jpg">Kim Hyang-Lee</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9220" type="appears in" update="2018-09-16">
<rating votes="3">5.36</rating>
<name>Princess D</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223880.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="210" picture="71057.jpg">Ueda Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9250" type="appears in" update="2014-12-30">
<rating votes="9">4.09</rating>
<name>Nishimura Reika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>166854.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9313" type="appears in" update="2009-06-14">
<rating votes="12">5.06</rating>
<name>Prince Endymion</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28826.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9709" type="appears in" update="2009-06-20">
<rating votes="2">3.33</rating>
<name>Chiral</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29474.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9710" type="appears in" update="2009-06-20">
<rating votes="2">3.33</rating>
<name>Achiral</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29475.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2976" picture="234380.jpg">Tanaka Kazunari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55327" type="appears in" update="2013-04-23">
<rating votes="5">6.01</rating>
<name>Tsukino Usagi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>"Moon Power! Change me into a doctor who works at a university hospital!"
This is a magic disguise form.</description>
<picture>135738.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55347" type="appears in" update="2013-04-23">
<rating votes="5">4.69</rating>
<name>Tsukino Usagi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>"Moon Power! Change me into a cool bus attendant!"
This is a magic disguise form.</description>
<picture>135769.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60737" type="appears in" update="2013-10-24">
<rating votes="4">3.82</rating>
<name>Mamoru (Shounen Jidai)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144746.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="68433" type="appears in" update="2014-08-11">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Naru-chan no Mama</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A youma that disguised herself as Naru`s mother.</description>
<picture>157627.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69374" type="appears in" update="2014-08-11">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Onna Koushi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A youma that disguised herself as a lecturer.</description>
<picture>159515.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3398" picture="224826.jpg">Kingetsu Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69375" type="appears in" update="2014-08-11">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Onna Koushi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The true form of youma.</description>
<picture>159516.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3398" picture="224826.jpg">Kingetsu Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69376" type="appears in" update="2014-08-11">
<name>Naru-chan no Mama</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The true form of youma.</description>
<picture>159518.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69377" type="appears in" update="2014-08-11">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Mii</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159525.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69378" type="appears in" update="2014-08-11">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Mii no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159526.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2801" picture="23195.jpg">Komatsu Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69863" type="appears in" update="2014-09-07">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Senpai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An older boy (senpai) who Mako loved.</description>
<picture>160547.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2487" picture="23183.jpg">Akabane Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69864" type="appears in" update="2014-09-07">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Hanayome</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A mannequin from Wedding shop which was possesed by Nephrite`s youma.</description>
<picture>160546.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70146" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Izono Kyouju</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Doctor Izono is a researcher specializing in the Phantom Silver Crystal.
Izono is actually http://anidb.net/ch7702 [Zoisite] in disguise.</description>
<picture>161371.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1900" picture="156922.jpg">Yamaguchi Yuriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72446" type="appears in" update="2014-12-30">
<name>Endou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Endou is Motoki`s friend.</description>
<picture>166855.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="552" picture="23199.jpg">Miura Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73130" type="appears in" update="2015-02-07">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Sarashina Kotono</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62506.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="349" picture="79057.jpg">Kanda Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73757" type="appears in" update="2015-03-12">
<name>Asanuma Ittou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>169981.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="336" picture="17172.jpg">Sakaguchi Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="159582" update="2014-07-10">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-30</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">うさぎ -SAILOR MOON-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Usagi: Sailor Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Usagi -Sailor Moon-</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Usagi -Sailor Moon-</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Усаги — Сейлор Мун</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Usagi: Sailor Moon</title>
<summary>Usagi Tsukino is a bit of a clumsy and a crybaby in the 8th grade. Luna, a black cat with a crescent moon on her forehead, gives Usagi a miracle brooch.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656623</identifier>
<identifier>sailor-moon-crystal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160380" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-06-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>655889</identifier>
<identifier>sailor-moon-crystal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160719" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">PV Extended (BGM Ver.)</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>655889</identifier>
<identifier>sailor-moon-crystal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160973" update="2014-08-19">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-16</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Masquerade -仮面舞踏会-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Masquerade Dance Party</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Maskenball</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Masquerade -Le bal masqué-</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Бал-маскарад</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Masquerade: Kamenbutoukai</title>
<summary>Usagi has learned Princess D from the Kingdom of D, biggest resource-producing country of precious stones, will exhibit her legendary secret treasure. Suspecting it might be the "Legendary Silver Crystal", Usagi sneaks into the embassy of Kingdom of D.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>657713</identifier>
<identifier>sailor-moon-crystal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160974" update="2014-08-02">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-02</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">レイ -SAILOR MARS-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rei: Sailor Mars</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Rei -Sailor Mars-</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rei -Sailor Mars-</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Рэй — Сейлор Марс</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rei: Sailor Mars</title>
<summary>Disturbing rumors about the Sendaizakaue bus swirl all around Usagi. Amid the rumors, Usagi meets a beautiful shrine maiden with black hair named Rei Hino.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>657711</identifier>
<identifier>sailor-moon-crystal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160975" update="2014-07-22">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-19</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">亜美 -SAILOR MERCURY-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ami: Sailor Mercury</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ami -Sailor Mercury-</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ami -Sailor Mercury-</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Ами — Сейлор Меркурий</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ami: Sailor Mercury</title>
<summary>Through an unexpected turn of events, Usagi becomes close with Ami Mizuno, a genius girl with an IQ of 300. But there`s something odd about the students at Ami`s seminar...</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>657709</identifier>
<identifier>sailor-moon-crystal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="161028" update="2014-07-05">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-06-30</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161029" update="2014-07-05">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-06-30</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161729" update="2014-09-15">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-09-06</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">まこと -SAILOR JUPITER-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Makoto: Sailor Jupiter</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Makoto -Sailor Jupiter-</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Makoto -Sailor Jupiter-</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Макото — Сейлор Юпитер</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Makoto: Sailor Jupiter</title>
<summary>All of Juban Middle School is talking about the "cursed bridal shop", where every men who visits is said to disappear. Just then, a tall girl with superhuman strength, Makoto Kino, transfers to the school!</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659771</identifier>
<identifier>sailor-moon-crystal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="161792" update="2014-09-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">タキシード仮面 -TUXEDO MASK-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tuxedo Mask</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Tuxedo Mask</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`homme masqué - Tuxedo Mask</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Таксидо Камэн</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tuxedo Kamen: Tuxedo Mask</title>
<summary>Tuxedo Mask has been reported to have committed many crimes to obtain the "Legendary Silver Crystal". Luna and others are convinced he`s the enemy, but Usagi can`t believe it...</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659773</identifier>
<identifier>sailor-moon-crystal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162080" update="2014-10-04">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地場衛 -TUXEDO MASK-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mamoru Chiba: Tuxedo Mask</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Mamoru Chiba -Tuxedo Mask-</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mamoru Chiba - Tuxedo Mask -</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Тиба Мамору — Таксидо Камэн</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chiba Mamoru: Tuxedo Mask</title>
<summary>Usagi learns Tuxedo Mask`s identity is actually Mamoru Chiba. Meanwhile, brainwashed people in Usagi`s town wander around looking for Sailor Moon.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659775</identifier>
<identifier>sailor-moon-crystal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162299" update="2014-11-08">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">美奈子 -SAILOR V-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Minako: Sailor V</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Minako -Sailor V-</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Minako - Sailor V -</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Минако — Сейлор Ви</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Minako: Sailor V</title>
<summary>The one who saved Sailor Moon was actually Sailor V. Sailor V aka Minako Aino heads to the Tokyo Tower to settle things with Kunzite but…</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659777</identifier>
<identifier>sailor-moon-crystal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162648" update="2014-11-15">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-11-15</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Moon -月-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Mond</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Moon - Lune -</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Луна</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moon: Tsuki</title>
<summary>Sailor Moon and the others have landed on the Moon to solve the mystery of the Legendary Silver Crystal. There they meet Usagi`s mother from a previous life, Queen Serenity.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662729</identifier>
<identifier>sailor-moon-crystal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162649" update="2014-11-08">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-11-01</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">セレニティ -PRINCESS-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Serenity: Princess</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Prinzessin Serenity</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Serenity - Princess -</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Принцесса Серенити</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Serenity: Princess</title>
<summary>While trying to protect Sailor Moon, Tuxedo Mask loses consciousness. Out of sorrow, Sailor Moon awakens as Princess Serenity.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659779</identifier>
<identifier>sailor-moon-crystal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="163646" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-12-20</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">敵 -QUEEN METARIA-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Enemy: Queen Metalia</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Queen Metalia -Der Feind-</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Противник — Королева Металия</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Teki: Queen Metaria</title>
<summary>Sailor Moon learns that Mamoru has become a soldier of the Dark Kingdom. She decides to take on Queen Beryl in an effort to get Mamoru back, but…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662733</identifier>
<identifier>sailor-moon-crystal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="163647" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-12-06</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">再会 -ENDYMION-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reunion: Endymion</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Endymion -Wiedersehen-</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Новая встреча, Эндимион</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikai: Endymion</title>
<summary>Appearing before a devastated Usagi is a man who looks just like Mamoru but goes by "Endo". Usagi sees traces of Mamoru and thus approaches him…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662731</identifier>
<identifier>sailor-moon-crystal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="163648" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-12-27</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦 -REINCARNATION-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Final Battle: Reincarnation</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Entscheidungskampf -Reincarnation-</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen: Reincarnation</title>
<summary>To end the painful journey, Sailor Moon stabs Mamoru with the holy sword before turning it on herself.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662735</identifier>
<identifier>sailor-moon-crystal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="163649" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-12-27</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">終結 そして 始まり -PETITE ÉTRANGÉRE-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Conclusion and Commencement: Petite Etrangere</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein Ende und ein Anfang -Petite Ètrangère-</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuuketsu Soshite Hajimari: Petite Etrangere</title>
<summary>Sailor Moon stands up to destroy Queen Metalia, who radiates a tremendously dark energy. The power of the "Legendary Silver Crystal" is finally released.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662737</identifier>
<identifier>sailor-moon-crystal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="164761" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-02-07</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">侵入 -SAILOR MARS-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Infiltration: Sailor Mars</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Invasion -Sailor Mars-</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinnyuu: Sailor Mars</title>
<summary>Usagi and the others try to figure out the identity of Chibi-Usa, the mysterious girl who fell from the sky. Meanwhile, at Rei`s school where the school fair is taking place, a new enemy has crept in.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662739</identifier>
<identifier>sailor-moon-crystal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="165433" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-02-21</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">誘拐 -SAILOR MERCURY-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Abduction: Sailor Mercury</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Entführung -Sailor Mars-</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuukai: Sailor Mercury</title>
<summary>When Rei is abducted, Usagi begins to doubt the identity of Chibi-Usa. Meanwhile, Ami is challenAged by a mysterious woman at the World Chess Conference.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662741</identifier>
<identifier>sailor-moon-crystal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="166347" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-04-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クリスタル・トーキョー -KING ENDYMION-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crystal Tokyo: King Endymion</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Crystal Tokio -King Endymion-</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Crystal Tokyo: King Endymion</title>
<summary>Mamoru`s future self, King Endymion, appears before Sailor Moon and her friends. He reveals a shocking fact about Planet Earth in the future.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>677505</identifier>
<identifier>sailor-moon-crystal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="166348" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-04-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">タイム・ワープ -SAILOR PLUTO-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Time Warp: Sailor Pluto</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Time Warp -Sailor Pluto-</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Time Warp: Sailor Pluto</title>
<summary>Usagi and the others decide to go to the 30th century, where Chibi-Usa came from.  Waiting for them there is the solitary Guardian Sailor Pluto.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>677503</identifier>
<identifier>sailor-moon-crystal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="166349" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-03-21</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">侵略 -SAILOR VENUS-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Invasion: Sailor Venus</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Invasion -Sailor Venus-</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinryaku: Sailor Venus</title>
<summary>Minako sneaks into a channeling session to communicate with people in other dimensions. There, she learns the channeler is Calaveras the Medium of the four Spectre Sisters!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>677501</identifier>
<identifier>sailor-moon-crystal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="166350" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-03-07</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">秘密 -SAILOR JUPITER-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Secret: Sailor Jupiter</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Geheimnis -Sailor Jupiter-</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Himitsu: Sailor Jupiter</title>
<summary>Usagi and the others try to locate Ami and Rei. Seeing this, Mamoru`s underclassman Ittou Asanuma demands to know Makoto`s identity.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662743</identifier>
<identifier>sailor-moon-crystal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="167541" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-05-02</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">錯綜 -NEMESIS-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Complication: Nemesis</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Komplikation -Nemesis-</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakusou: Nemesis</title>
<summary>Captured by Demande, Usagi loses her transformation powers. Meanwhile, Chibi-Usa feels helpless and goes to see Sailor Pluto.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>677507</identifier>
<identifier>sailor-moon-crystal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="167569" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-05-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">思惑 -NEMESIS-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hidden Agenda: Nemesis</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Verborgenes Motiv -Nemesis-</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omowaku: Nemesis</title>
<summary>Usagi tries to escape the Black Moon Castle. She arrives at the "Malefic Black Crystal" reactor, where she finds Demande`s younger brother Saphir.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>677509</identifier>
<identifier>sailor-moon-crystal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="167973" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-06-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">攻撃 -BLACK LADY-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Attack: Black Lady</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Angriff -Black Lady-</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kougeki: Black Lady</title>
<summary>Sailor Moon and the others are stunned to learn Chibi-Usa`s real identity is Black Lady. And finally, Wiseman`s own identity is revealed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>677513</identifier>
<identifier>sailor-moon-crystal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="167974" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-06-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暗躍 -WISEMAN-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Covert Maneuvers: Wiseman</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Manipulation -Wiseman-</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">An`yaku: Wiseman</title>
<summary>Sailor Moon and the others continue their search for Tuxedo Mask and Chibi-Usa. But Wiseman`s covert maneuvers had already begun…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>677511</identifier>
<identifier>sailor-moon-crystal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="168353" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">再生 -NEVER ENDING-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Replay: Never Ending</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wiedergeburt -Never Ending-</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saisei: Never Ending</title>
<summary>Death Phantom radiates an enormous dark power. Sailor Moon and Sailor Chibi Moon take a stand and release the power of the "Legendary Silver Crystal".
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>677517</identifier>
<identifier>sailor-moon-crystal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="168354" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-07-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">対決 -DEATH PHANTOM-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Showdown: Death Phantom</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Konfrontation -Death Phantom-</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiketsu: Death Phantom</title>
<summary>Upon contact with the "Legendary Silver Crystals", it was Sailor Pluto who saved the world from destruction. As Black Lady watches Sailor Pluto lose her life…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>677515</identifier>
<identifier>sailor-moon-crystal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
