<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="931" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>19</episodecount>
<startdate>1999-03-30</startdate>
<enddate>1999-04-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Taiho Shichau zo Special</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">You`re Under Arrest! TV Special</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">YUA Special</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">YUA! Special</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">逮捕しちゃうぞ Special</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">You`re Under Arrest! Mini Specials</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="438" type="Parent Story">Taiho Shichau zo: You`re Under Arrest (1996)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="386728">Giving it a solid 6 only because of the original art style and animation. 
Other than that, the same stories but in shorter format. For fans only.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20050205084545/http://www.tbs.co.jp/w_anime/wtaiho/index-j.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="817" type="Original Work">Fujishima Kousuke</name>
<name id="1419" type="Character Design">Nakajima Atsuko</name>
<name id="2241" type="Direction">Nishimura Junji</name>
<name id="4144" type="Music">Ootani Kou</name>
<name id="1551" type="Music">Iwasaki Yasunori</name>
</creators>
<description>The mean streets of Tokyo are that much safer when the ladies of Bokuto Police Station are on patrol! When the fun-loving and free-wheeling http://anidb.net/ch11779 [Natsumi] teams up with the mechanical wizard http://anidb.net/ch11848 [Miyuki], criminals do not stand a chance.
From booby-trapped handbags to exhibitionists from beyond the grave to geriatric gearheads, there is never a dull moment. But will they be able to protect their undergarments and co-workers from the depredations of an army of Tokyo`s oversexed peeping Toms? Can Natsumi`s finances hold out until her next pay cheque clears? Chaos ensues and neither speeders nor sneaks stand a chance as Miyuki and Natsumi show that crime does not pay!</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="483">6.33</permanent>
<temporary count="485">7.24</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>84014.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>623</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4162</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>2011</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>833</identifier>
<identifier>gebwbt</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20050205084545/http://www.tbs.co.jp/w_anime/wtaiho/index-j.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>125554</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="618" parentid="2565" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>trap</name>
<description>A trap is a plot device where a male character is mistaken for a female, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the male (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the male, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the male character as a female; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through his behaviour, and/or language. A male character misinterpreted by others as female, without action from the male (explicitly feminine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t1637 [reverse trap].
Note: the tag image is from http://anidb.net/a10475 [Himegoto].</description>
<picurl>161537.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2697" parentid="2848" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-05">
<name>voyeurism</name>
<description>Voyeurism is the sexual interest in or practice of spying on people engaged in intimate behaviors, such as undressing, sexual activity, or other actions usually considered to be of a private nature. The principal characteristic of voyeurism is that the voyeur does not normally interact directly with the subject of his/her interest, who is often unaware of being observed. The essence of voyeurism is the observing but may also involve the making of a secret photograph or video of the subject during an intimate activity. When the interest in a particular subject is obsessive, the behavior may be described as stalking.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162189.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2756" parentid="2881" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>board games</name>
<description>People here play a board game. It can vary from chess and Go, to Monopoly, to Dungeons and Dragons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2759" parentid="2881" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>motorsport</name>
<description>Driving involves driving in a competitive manner. Note that just driving to get groceries does not suffice, unless one does it like Takumi Fujiwara in Initial D.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2816" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sexual fantasies</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime let their imaginations run wild thinking about another character.
Yes, they are thinking about sex, and in an ecchi anime these thoughts are often perverted, leading to a nosebleed. But it may also be romanticising simply being husband and wife, and everything that implies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2820" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>wardrobe malfunction</name>
<description>A euphemistic term for an embarrassing display of a body part when clothing droops, falls, or is torn. Wikipedia: "Super Bowl XXXVIII half-time show" for more details.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2840" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>mafia</name>
<description>A mafia is a type of organized crime syndicate whose primary activities are protection racketeering, the arbitration of disputes between criminals, and the organizing and oversight of illegal agreements and transactions. Secondary activities may be practiced such as gambling, drug trafficking, loan sharking, and fraud. The term was originally applied to the Sicilian mafia, but has since expanded to encompass other organizations of similar methods and purpose, such as in "the Russian mafia" or "the Japanese mafia", and is applied informally by the press and public, but the criminal organizations themselves have their own terms; for example, the original Sicilian and Italian-American mafia call themselves "cosa nostra", while the Japanese mafia calls itself "yakuza".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>211289.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2917" parentid="2756" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>chess</name>
<description>Chess is a game for two players. It is played on a square board, made of 64 smaller squares, with eight squares on each side. Each player starts with sixteen pieces (eight pawns, two each of knights, bishops, and rooks, and one king and queen). One player`s pieces are a light color, he is called "White", and the other player`s pieces are a dark color, he is called "Black".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3489" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>car chases</name>
<description>Car chases occur as part of the action setting in this anime.</description>
<picurl>211263.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3667" parentid="2676" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo Tower</name>
<description>Tokyo Tower is a communications and observation tower in the Shiba-koen district of Minato, Tokyo, Japan. At 332.9 metres, it is the second-tallest structure in Japan. The structure is an Eiffel Tower-inspired lattice tower that is painted white and international orange to comply with air safety regulations.
Source: Wikipedia
Note: Not to be confused with the very much younger http://anidb.net/t3037 [Tokyo Skytree].</description>
<picurl>161123.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3959" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-07">
<name>TBS Wonderful</name>
<description>A late-night slot on TBS that ran from 29-Sep-1997 to 26-Sep-2002.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4606" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>slide show animation</name>
<description>The entire anime or parts of it show sequences of still images. Sometimes used in low budged animations for action scenes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6021" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>gender bender</name>
<description>Term used to refer to a person who takes on the role of their opposite gender. This often only reaches to the extent of cross-dressing (involving physical appearance and clothing only), but in rarer cases, involves a total gender swap (which seems to be more common in anime) - where the willing or unwilling victim receives a body opposite of their original gender (either permanently or temporarily), with all natural parts per their new body fully (or just all-out amply) included.
Example of cross-dressing gender bender: "Maria+Holic"
Examples of body-swap gender bender: "Kashimashi: Girl meets Girl", "Birdy the Mighty Decode"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6248" parentid="2872" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>thievery</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6399" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-25">
<name>episodic</name>
<description>An episodic anime consists of many successive short arcs that are generally 1-2 episodes in length, with strong plot continuity within each arc but generally little continuity from one arc to the next. For long shows (well upwards of 50 episodes), the episode count constraint is less tight; for example, a show with close to 250 episodes would also be considered episodic if it consisted of a majority of arcs of up to 3 or maybe 4 episodes and possibly also very few slightly longer arcs.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="11779" type="main character in" update="2010-08-15">
<rating votes="159">8.73</rating>
<name>Tsujimoto Natsumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Natsumi is an officer stationed at the fictional Bokuto Station in Tokyo`s Sumida Ward. She is very outgoing as well as very laid back. She often demonstrates superhuman strength second only to Shoji Tokairin and is a motorcycle enthusiast, capable of high-risk maneuvers on both bikes and mopeds. Natsumi has a prodigious appetite for food and alcohol, and has been known to show up at work with a hangover. She is also a chronic late sleeper. Despite having many bad habits, she is a very capable police officer and does her job seriously when needed. She keeps a mini-moped, a Honda Motocompo (JR-2) in Miyuki`s Honda Today squad car and uses it when a flanking strategy is required. It is prominently labeled "NATUMI" (in the Nihon-shiki transliteration system) before her first day at Bokuto in the beginning of the first anime, later re-coloured and re-labeled "POLICE" in the later appearances and on the Bandai Model kit of the Honda Today. When off-duty, she operates a Yamaha RZV motorbike until it is damaged beyond repair during later part of the first season. She is subsequently tricked into buying a Subaru R-2, which is in a near-non-functioning state. This car is then thoroughly renovated and heavily modified by Miyuki into a patrol car. She uses the wrecked motorbike`s engine, modifying the car to make its operation follow closely to that of a motorbike. In the manga version, this car operates with double engines.
Natsumi is also familiar with judo and kendo, being able to defeat her opponents during training sessions. Her strength and her familiarity with hand-to-hand combat complement Miyuki`s brilliant mind in creating devices or modifying known vehicles very well, making her and Miyuki famous throughout Bokuto Station. She is also the only person in this series able to consistently defeat Strikeman`s fastballs and is called Home-Run Woman by Strikeman for this very reason.</description>
<picture>35664.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="471" picture="242052.jpg">Tamagawa Sakiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11848" type="main character in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="170">8.45</rating>
<name>Kobayakawa Miyuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miyuki is Natsumi`s partner and roommate. Miyuki is not as physically tough as Natsumi, but she is much smarter and more polite. A technical genius, Miyuki frequently performs custom vehicle modifications for various people at the precinct, as well as being an expert with computers. Miyuki is a superb driver, almost as daring as Natsumi, and very difficult to shake in a pursuit. She is also punctual, shy and diligent - in contrast to Natsumi, who is tardy, brash and frequently lazy. Her mini patrol car, a Honda Today, is a heavily modified version for patrol duties. Normally the engine is a 554cc, but Miyuki has stroked it out to 700cc(although still having a yellow number plate for K-cars) and added twin cams, a turbo-charger, and nitrous oxide boost. Such a car could theoretically be built given current technology, but would be impractical at best in reality. She also has a blue Toyota Sports 800 as her personal car.
Unlike Natsumi`s infatuation towards the chief (Kachou) of Traffic Division, Miyuki admires and respects him because of his dedication in working with the division. During situations where force was the only solution, Miyuki uses airsoft guns with paintball bullets in order to incapacitate or to leave a homing beacon on the opponents. Her love interest happens to be with the "White Hawk" Ken Nakajima but has initial difficulty in telling him until the end of the series. Her feelings for Ken were driven to the point when she pointed an air gun on Natsumi`s head when she joked that she would have to marry Ken in the future.
Miyuki is fearful of anything that cannot be explained by science, such as the Paranormal, Supernatural or anything that was similar to science fiction. She is also afraid of reptiles.
Her character design was also used as the template for a goddess whom the characters prayed to in a four panel gag strip added to a version of YUA who eventually became Belldandy when the strip proved popular and was developed into Oh! My Goddess.</description>
<picture>35890.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="692" picture="188445.jpg">Hiramatsu Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16044" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="88">7.26</rating>
<name>Aoi Futaba</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An officer who joined Bokuto Station in the first season, Aoi is originally mistaken for a woman. In fact, Aoi is a man. He had cross dressed to go undercover as a decoy to catch a serial rapist in the vice unit and, in the process, "went native". Now, Aoi is more feminine in appearance and personality than any of the women in the station. Aoi`s romantic gender preferences are often speculated on by the Bokutou police, but in the end it is discovered that Aoi prefers men.</description>
<picture>45063.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1682" picture="41033.jpg">Matsumoto Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18842" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="27">5.65</rating>
<name>Kachou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The section chief of Bokuto Station`s Traffic Control Department is usually referred to simply as "chief" (課長, kachou). His name was first revealed to indeed spell "Kachou" (花蝶, kachou, lit. "Flower butterfly") in the second season by his monk uncle (a.k.a. FOX). He is a stern, but fair leader who uses a relaxed touch to keep his team of misfit officers in line. Natsumi had a long-standing crush on him before she met Toukairin. Though he allows his subordinates to do as they normally please in the station, he reminds them of their priorities as police officers.
In the movie, he got in trouble with Superintendent Arizuka when he was linked to Emoto, who was suspected of starting the Hachi-Ichi-Go (Bee Number 1) crisis in the Greater Tokyo Area. First stripped off his command and thrown into a cell by Arizuka due to suspicion of coercing with Emoto, he eventually disclosed details regarding both Emoto and Project "Hachi-Ichi-Go", as well as the fact that Emoto severed connections with him as well. During the final confrontation in Tokyo Tower, Emoto shot him in the leg, reinforcing the fact that he was not Emoto`s accomplice.
He uses a Honda NSX as his personal car when doing police work in the OVA. In the rest of the series, he uses a Honda Legend.</description>
<picture>49714.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3248" picture="157354.jpg">Masamune Issei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18860" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-15">
<rating votes="65">2.85</rating>
<name>Nakajima Ken</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A motorcycle patrol officer stationed in Bokuto Precinct who is such a gifted rider that he might have a successful racing career if he wanted it. Ken is strong, tough and handsome but at the same time, was terribly shy. He and Miyuki share strong feelings for each other, but have difficulties expressing them. He is the only son of Daimaru Nakajima, managing a motorbike shop called ZAPPER, and the stepson of his teenaged stepmom Sena Wakabayashi. Details on his mother was not revealed, but it is known that his father became a widower before the OVA and first season series started. His peers call him "White Hawk" for his skills as a motorbike officer in chasing down various offenders. His family was from the Mie Prefecture.</description>
<picture>49744.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="199" picture="23218.jpg">Shimada Bin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18862" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-08">
<rating votes="82">5.50</rating>
<name>Nikaidou Yoriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A dispatcher at Bokuto Station who later becomes a patrol officer and partner of Aoi Futaba, Yoriko is an incorrigible gossip who pokes her nose into everything that happens at the precinct. Unfortunately, she frequently misinterprets things she sees and hears about, resulting in embarrassment and complications. She keeps an especially close eye on Miyuki and Ken. Yoriko also enjoys heckling her colleagues, especially when she talks about anything supernatural or paranormal.
She is also clumsy in anything she does but always can somehow cover the trouble created with her luck, which made her the top in class during her years in the Metropolitan Police Department Academy and earned the ire of her classmate Chie Sagamiono, who had aspired to become valedictorian back in their academy days. She is also insecure about her job for a short period of time when she saved an elementary student from Yakuza thugs.</description>
<picture>49747.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2046" picture="186581.jpg">Kozakura Etsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18868" type="appears in" update="2010-06-15">
<rating votes="4">10.00</rating>
<name>Maho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49753.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="18869" type="appears in" update="2010-06-15">
<rating votes="4">4.13</rating>
<name>Yuuta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49754.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="18870" type="appears in" update="2010-06-15">
<rating votes="4">4.13</rating>
<name>Shou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49755.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="19617" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-07-13">
<name>Kurouda Youko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51223.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="19640" type="appears in" update="2010-07-15">
<name>Takako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51301.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="9674" update="2005-06-12">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>1999-03-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">違反切符は破らないで!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">File 1.1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ihan Kippu wa Yaburanaide!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9675" update="2005-06-12">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>1999-04-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">とんで火にいる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">File 1.3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tonde Hi ni Iru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9676" update="2005-06-12">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>1999-04-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シルキー・パンティー・コレクター</title>
<title xml:lang="en">File 2.1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Silky Panty Collector</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9677" update="2005-06-12">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>1999-03-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">きっぱりと交通安全講習会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">File 1.2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kippari to Koutsuuanzen Koushuu Kai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9678" update="2005-06-12">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>1999-04-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悩殺・マウスtoマウス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">File 1.4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nousatsu Mouth to Mouth</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37750" update="2014-04-26">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>1999-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦うショルダーバッグ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">File 3.4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tatakau Shoulder Bag</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37751" update="2005-06-12">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>1999-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">きわどいのがお好き</title>
<title xml:lang="en">File 2.4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiwadoi no ga Osuki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37752" update="2005-06-12">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>1999-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">華麗なる対決</title>
<title xml:lang="en">File 3.3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Karei Naru Taiketsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37753" update="2014-04-26">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>1999-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天国がくれた一万円</title>
<title xml:lang="en">File 4.1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tengoku ga Kureta Ichiman En</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37754" update="2005-06-12">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>1999-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">チューンナップレストラン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">File 3.2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tune Up Restaurant</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37755" update="2017-04-27">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">渚の交通誘導</title>
<title xml:lang="en">File 6: Diverting Traffic at the Beach</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nagisa no Koutsuu Yuudou</title>
<summary>Summer arrives to Bokuto Station. Miyuki and Natsumi have to work on a beach road protecting the safety of the civilians that are enjoying their summer vacations. Suffering because of the heat, the two officers are having problems remaining calm when a pickpocket appears on the beach and causes a ruckus. The girls must do their best to catch the thief, control the traffic, and enjoy their summer day.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="37756" update="2005-06-12">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>1999-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天使をつかまえろ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">File 2.2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenshi o Tsukamaero</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37757" update="2005-06-12">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>1999-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">見つめてあげたい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">File 3.1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mitsumete Agetai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37758" update="2014-04-26">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>1999-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">春の夜の夢</title>
<title xml:lang="en">File 4.4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haru no Yoru no Yume</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37759" update="2005-06-12">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>1999-04-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ホラーナイト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">File 2.3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Horror Night</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37760" update="2014-04-26">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>1999-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">炎のシルバーチェイサー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">File 5.2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Honoo no Silver Chaser</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37761" update="2014-04-26">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>1999-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">この胸のときめきを</title>
<title xml:lang="en">File 5.3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kono Mune no Tokimeki o</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37762" update="2016-02-18">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>1999-04-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アクションしちゃうぞ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">File 5.4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Action Shichauzo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37763" update="2014-04-26">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>1999-04-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コンビニパニック</title>
<title xml:lang="en">File 5.1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Konbini Panic</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37764" update="2014-04-26">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>1999-04-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">怪奇!裸女が漂うトンネル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">File 4.2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaiki! Hadaka Onna ga Tadayou Tunnel</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37765" update="2014-04-26">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>1999-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コンクリートで抱きしめて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">File 4.3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Concrete de Dakishimete</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
