<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9323" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-01-12</startdate>
<enddate>2013-01-12</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gekijouban Hunter x Hunter: Phantom Rouge</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Hunter x Hunter movie</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">hxh movie</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Ловец срещу Ловец: Кървавият фантом</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">劇場版 HUNTERxHUNTER 緋色の幻影[ファントム・ルージュ]</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Hunter x Hunter: Phantom Rouge</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8550" type="Parent Story">Hunter x Hunter (2011)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://hxh-movie.jp</url>
<creators>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="3630" type="Character Design">Yoshimatsu Takahiro</name>
<name id="8259" type="Character Design">Takada Haruhito</name>
<name id="7839" type="Character Design">Tasaki Satoshi</name>
<name id="874" type="Original Work">Togashi Yoshihiro</name>
<name id="4790" type="Direction">Satou Yuuzou</name>
<name id="8259" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takada Haruhito</name>
<name id="6655" type="Chief Animation Direction">Umehara Takahiro</name>
<name id="7839" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tasaki Satoshi</name>
<name id="4393" type="Music">Hirano Yoshihisa</name>
</creators>
<description>Kurapika became a Hunter to take vengeance on the Phantom Troupe, a gang of thieves who massacred his clan. The Phantom Troupe sought out the Kurta Clan for their eyes, which turn scarlet when they get agitated. An unknown party has stolen Kurapika`s "scarlet eyes," but Kurapika`s life is saved with the help of Gon, Killua, and Leorio. The Phantom Troupe stands before Kurapika and the others, who are about to discover the true identity of the person with the No.4 spider tattoo.
Note: The premise of the movie is based off a manuscript of the Yorknew City arc written by http://anidb.net/cr874 [Togashi Yoshihiro] that he eventually ended up scrapping.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="986">5.03</permanent>
<temporary count="989">6.61</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>92710.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14152</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13271</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5303</identifier>
<identifier>rtrtow</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3658</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>343413</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15647</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>hunter_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="4976" type="appears in" update="2019-03-22">
<rating votes="747">9.10</rating>
<name>Hisoka Morow</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hisoka is a magician, as well as a serial killer. Hisoka is deceitful, playful, and narcissistic by nature; he acts only according to self-interest. Hisoka combines his magic tricks with violence, and delights in battling against those he considers strong to the point of sexual arousal. In the manga, his sentences within speech balloons typically end with a suit symbol. Hisoka takes an interest in Gon and his friends after encountering them during the Hunter Exam; although he initially is posited as an antagonist due to affinity towards murder, he spends much of the series acting as both an adversary and comrade to Gon.
Nen type: Transmutation
In Hunter`s Character &amp; World Official Databook his height is 187 cm and in manga ch. 377 his height is 190+ cm.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>46438.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7192" type="main character in" update="2013-09-01">
<rating votes="500">5.41</rating>
<name>Gon Freecss</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gon Freecss is the son of the legendary Hunter Ging Freecss and the protagonist of the series Hunter × Hunter by Yoshihiro Togashi.
Gon was left in the care of his aunt Mito on Whale Island as an infant by his father Ging, and never saw his father since. Holding great disdain for Ging`s constant travels and putting Gon in danger, she forced Ging to give his son up so he could live normally. Mito told him as a child that his parents were deceased, but Gon eventually figured out the truth and chose the path of a Hunter to meet his father once again.</description>
<picture>46413.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27977" picture="76416.jpg">Han Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7273" type="main character in" update="2019-03-22">
<rating votes="672">8.87</rating>
<name>Killua Zaoldyeck</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Killua was born as the middle child to a family of renowned assassins, the Zoldyck family. Showing great promise from birth, Killua has already mastered many killing techniques at a tender age, and is set to be one of the best assassins the family has ever produced. Bored and tired of killing, Killua unexpectedly rebelled against his family, injuring both his mother and brother, and ran away to join the Hunter exam. He met Gon during the first portion of the Hunter Exam and became great friends.</description>
<picture>46430.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="101" picture="16709.jpg">Ise Mariya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7274" type="main character in" update="2019-03-22">
<rating votes="382">7.18</rating>
<name>Kurapika</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>46434.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7275" type="main character in" update="2019-03-22">
<rating votes="174">5.66</rating>
<name>Leorio Paradinight</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leorio meets Gon just as Gon leaves Whale Island to take the Hunter Exam. Much is unknown about Leorio. What we do know is that he once lost a close friend, Pietro, to a debilitating illness. Leorio feels deeply remorseful about being unable to save his friend, as the illness was entirely curable, but required a surgery he could not afford. Thus, he aspires to become a doctor--one that not only cures the ill of their disease, but also waives the fee for the poor. In this light, his outwardly superficial reason to join the Hunter Exams in the pursuit of great wealth has a more noble justification--the money he gains is used not only to fund for his medical school fees, but also to pay for the medicine and other miscellaneous expenditures when treating those who can`t afford it.</description>
<picture>46435.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39390" type="appears in" update="2018-09-28">
<rating votes="104">6.49</rating>
<name>Feitan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Feitan is one of the original members hailing from Meteor City and currently the de facto leader of the Phantom Troupe. He is attired in what one would expect from a bandit — dark clothes partnered with a skullhead scarf that covers his mouth. He seldom speaks, but when he does, it is full of grammatical errors, giving the impression that he is not speaking in his native tongue. During the Phantom Troupe`s fight with Chimera Ants, Feitan reverts to his native language, which was shown with Chinese characters. After Feitan`s victory over Zazan in Meteor City, he is crowned temporary leader of the Phantom Troupe. Feitan`s movements are incredibly fast, being able to leave afterimages of his body. He wields an umbrella that conceals both a sword and a gun that fires out of the tip.
His Nen ability is called "Pain Packer: Unforgiven" which transforms the injuries he has received from his enemy into an attack. The more pain he receives, the stronger his attack is. Currently, only "Rising Sun: Burnt by the Sun" has been revealed, a miniature sun that burns anyone around him disregarding even allies, as shown by the rest of the Phantom Troupe fleeing from the scene when he uses this ability. Only Feitan is unaffected by the attack, presumably because of the armor that is formed on him. Nen type: Transmutation
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>90754.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43495" type="appears in" update="2019-03-22">
<rating votes="94">8.04</rating>
<name>Chrollo Lucilfer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chrollo Lucilfer is the founder and leader of the Phantom Troupe. He forms the group with six other homeless children in Meteor City in his youth, thereafter leaving it. The Troupe was joined by more members, in accordance with Chrollo`s idea of a group with exactly thirteen members, including himself. He organizes the Phantom Troupe mainly to commit acts of theft, though it is unknown what the group does with the stolen objects. His Nen ability also allows him to directly steal the abilities of other users of Nen. He led the genocide on Kurapika`s clan, the latter thereafter stalking Chrollo and neutralizing his Nen ability as punishment. Nen type: Specialization
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>90764.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="255" picture="40713.jpg">Miyano Mamoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43496" type="appears in" update="2012-10-26">
<rating votes="12">8.65</rating>
<name>Phantom Troupe</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>127247.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="43498" type="appears in" update="2019-03-22">
<rating votes="10">5.79</rating>
<name>Franklin Bordeau</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Franklin is very large, with multiple facial scars similar to that of a Frankenstein. His ability is called "Dual Machine Gun", and is capable of shooting countless bullets composed of Nen from his fingers (which he himself modified). Franklin ranks fourth in physical power among the Troupe, and he is among the original members hailing from Meteor City.
Nen type: Emission
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>90755.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="280" picture="170840.jpg">Kiuchi Hidenobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43500" type="appears in" update="2019-03-22">
<rating votes="66">7.30</rating>
<name>Machi Komachine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Machi is incredibly loyal to Chrollo, and is one of the original Phantom Troupe members from Meteor City. Hisoka seems to have an occasional interest in her, although it is hard to see whether it is genuine. Her ability is to form aura into thread, the strength of which is inversely proportional to its length: a thread as long as the diameter of the Earth would be as strong as cotton, but a one meter-long thread can lift a ton. Besides attacking it can be used to track people, but was also shown used to stitch severed limbs back on. Physically, she is the strongest woman in the Troupe and the sixth strongest overall. She also has an extremely keen intuition (the other members of the Troupe say that she has never been wrong about her intuitions).
Nen type: Transmutation
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>90757.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29667" picture="223460.jpg">Maeda Rena</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43501" type="appears in" update="2019-03-22">
<rating votes="9">7.73</rating>
<name>Nobunaga Hazama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nobunaga Hazama has a similar appearance to ronin warriors in Edo period Japan, complete with a long katana that he uses with great finesse and skill. Nobunaga specializes in combining Nen with the use of his katana in executing enemies. His best friend is Uvogin, and the two bring out the best of each other during combat. Seeing some of Uvogin`s personality in Gon, he expresses interest in having Gon join the Troupe, though Gon adamantly refuses. Nobunaga ranks ninth in physical power among the Troupe, and is one of the original members from Meteor City. Nen type: Enhancement
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>90758.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="266" picture="17091.jpg">Uchida Naoya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43502" type="appears in" update="2019-03-22">
<rating votes="17">4.86</rating>
<name>Phinks Magcub</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Phinxs uses his hands in battle, which has been shown to be extremely powerful. He is one of the original Phantom Troupe members from Meteor City and wears an Egyptian Pharaoh-like outfit in battle. Phinxs seems to get along best with Feitan, and is almost always seen partnered with him both in and out of combat. His Nen ability is called "Ripper Cyclotron", the strength of which is dependent upon how many times he rotates his arm; the more rotations, the more powerful his attack will be. In terms of physical strength, Phinxs is ranked second among the Troupe members. His name is an anagram for "Sphinx".
Nen type: Enhancement
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>90760.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="367" picture="17213.jpg">Kenn</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43503" type="appears in" update="2019-03-22">
<rating votes="21">6.69</rating>
<name>Shalnark Ryuusei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shalnark is member number six of the Phantom Troupe, and from his appearance, he seems to be a normal boy. However, he is one of the most intelligent and quick-thinking members in the group, being highly adept at using computers and information gathering. Shalnark is also a licensed Hunter, so he has access to certain information that could be potentially useful to the Phantom Troupe. His main ability revolves around remotely manipulating the actions of others using his cell phone by sticking a specialized antenna into their bodies. His secondary ability involves applying the antenna upon himself and putting his body on autopilot, resulting in an enhanced state with enough power to devastate most opponents. However, he dislikes this ability because he is subject to immense muscle pain for several days after its use, and as he has no control over the process and retains no memory over what has transpired he can`t derive any pleasure or satisfaction when he uses it to win a fight. Shalnark ranks tenth in physical power among the Troupe.
Nen type: Manipulation
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>90761.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="268" picture="17093.jpg">Hidaka Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43504" type="appears in" update="2019-03-22">
<rating votes="36">7.24</rating>
<name>Shizuku Murasaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shizuku is extremely forgetful and can be an airhead at times which, along with her unassuming appearance, can cause opponents to underestimate her combat abilities. Shizuku uses her Nen vacuum "Blinky" ("Deme-chan" in the original Japanese version) in combat, which is able to suck up anything that is not nen created or that she considers living. It is also able to regurgitate the last thing sucked up. She is left-handed, and the twelfth strongest physically out of the thirteen members of the Troupe. Shizuku is member number eight, a replacement for the last member since the Troupe came together. Nen type: Conjuration
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>90762.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27221" picture="131964.jpg">Arakawa Miho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43505" type="appears in" update="2019-03-22">
<rating votes="31">7.17</rating>
<name>Pakunoda</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pakunoda is an original member of the Phantom Troupe from Meteor City. She is fully loyal to Chrollo, even going against the Troupe in order to help him. She is killed by Kurapika`s Judgement Chain in the climax of the Phantom Troupe arc by violating the restrictions placed upon her. Her main nen ability is to read the memories of people she touches by making specific questions. Her secondary ability allows her to transform these memories into the shape of a bullet which she fires into the heads of her companions from a gun, thereby giving them that information. Pakunoda is buried in the Troupe`s Yorknew hideout. She is eleventh in physical strength. Nen type: Specialization
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>90759.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43506" type="appears in" update="2019-03-22">
<rating votes="18">6.91</rating>
<name>Uvogin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Uvogin was one of the original members of the Troupe from Meteor City. Out of all of the Phantom Troupe, he was the strongest in terms of raw physical power. Uvogin was so strong, that direct hits from bullets, sniper bullets, and even anti-tank rockets don`t do visible damage to him. Like all of the Troupe, he never hesitates to kill, and particularly enjoys combat against skilled opponents. Although he prefers to fight alone, Uvogin becomes stronger when fighting with a partner, usually Nobunaga, because he fights better when there is someone else to protect (although he never admits this). Seeking revenge on Kurapika for capturing him after his battle with the Shadow Beasts, Uvogin tracks him to the hotel where Neon Nostrade and the rest of her bodyguards are staying. They fight one-on-one in a small canyon on the outskirts of Yorknew City. Kurapika eventually captures Uvogin with his Chain Jail, and questions him about the location and abilities of the other Phantom Troupe members. Uvogin refuses to answer any questions, responding only with "Kill me." Kurapika then pierces Uvogin`s chest with the Judgement Chain ability, giving Uvogin the condition that he must answer all questions truthfully. Kurapika once again asks him the location of the other Troupe members, to which Uvogin only smiles and says to Kurapika "Go to hell, you bastard." Kurapika`s Judgement Chain pierces Uvogin`s heart, instantly killing him. Uvogin is buried by Kurapika at the site of their battle. He was the eleventh member of the Troupe. Nen type: Enhancement
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>90763.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50108" type="appears in" update="2012-11-02">
<rating votes="1">1.92</rating>
<name>Omokage</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>127584.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38424" picture="141804.jpg">Fujiki Naohito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50297" type="appears in" update="2012-11-02">
<name>Pyro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>127585.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24037" picture="67420.jpg">Kawashima Umika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50298" type="appears in" update="2014-02-01">
<rating votes="2">5.55</rating>
<name>Retz</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>127586.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4" picture="177060.jpg">Hirano Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50299" type="appears in" update="2012-11-02">
<rating votes="3">6.91</rating>
<name>Illumi Zaoldyeck</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>127587.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="263" picture="186711.jpg">Matsukaze Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="141043" update="2013-01-28">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>100</length>
<airdate>2013-01-12</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="143748" update="2012-09-05">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
