<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9324" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>2012-10-18</startdate>
<enddate>2012-12-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kami nomi zo Shiru Sekai: Tenri Hen</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The World God Only Knows - Tenri`s Chapter</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">twgok ova 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">神のみぞ知るセカイ 天理篇</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The World God Only Knows OVA: Tenri Arc</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9553" type="Sequel">Kami nomi zo Shiru Sekai: Megami Hen</anime>
<anime id="8490" type="Prequel">Kami nomi zo Shiru Sekai: 4-nin to Idol</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://kaminomi.jp/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="986" type="Animation Work">Manglobe</name>
<name id="3529" type="Character Design">Watanabe Akio</name>
<name id="18553" type="Original Work">Wakaki Tamiki</name>
<name id="12168" type="Direction">Oosedo Satoshi</name>
<name id="2529" type="Music">Matsuo Hayato</name>
<name id="3328" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kawamura Toshie</name>
</creators>
<description>It is summer break and http://anidb.net/ch18463 [Katsuragi Keima] intends to spend all his time on video games. An old acquaintance, the timid girl http://anidb.net/ch34021 [Ayukawa Tenri], returns to the neighbourhood — and apparently carries a lost soul inside of her. It is up to Keima and http://anidb.net/ch18462 [Elysia de Lute Ima] to unravel the secrets of her heart.
Source: ANN
Note: Bundled with the 19th and 20th volumes of the manga.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1814">6.66</permanent>
<temporary count="1822">7.33</temporary>
<review count="1">7.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>126983.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14907</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15117</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5212</identifier>
<identifier>nlqsbw</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://kaminomi.jp/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5496</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>345764</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15340</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3132" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-08-11">
<name>helpful couple</name>
<description>This is a very low key type of romance in which the main two characters spend a great deal of time hanging out together just helping other people solve problems. The couple`s personal interaction tends to be subtle.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5984" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-09-10">
<name>girly tears</name>
<description>Usually girly tears are the ones not shed by men (duh). 
Like when a (stereotypical) girl watches something and cries her makeup out, a (stereotypical) dude just says, proclaiming his masculinity: "Meh, yet another soap opera bulls..t, I`ll be in my garage fixing my ride while playing heavy metal on a burning guitar ...with my teeth! And where`s my beer, woman?".
So that`s how it goes: girly tears are for girls and sissies! Chuck Norris forbid a guy would weep watching something that has this tag! Now 20 push-ups!
P.S. The opposite of "manly tears". Or is it? Let`s face it - it`s all subjective (and relative, and context-dependent).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6078" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-23">
<name>gotta catch them all</name>
<description>A typical plot or sub-plot for many shows. Either the cast or somebody else, that being often the main antagonist, embarks on a quest to collect things, shiny things. Things that are said to grant simple wishes or even do miracles like bringing people back to life, destroying the whole world, galaxy, universe and in rare cases turning the hero into the greatest Pokemon Master. Those things can be weapons, lost technology, magical artefacts, pieces of a giant magical artefact and in some cases even people or little critters.
The point is, there`s stuff to collect!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="18462" type="main character in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="342">7.50</rating>
<name>Elysia de Lute Ima</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Elucia or Elsie as she is commonly known, is a demon who was assigned to capture evil spirits that have escaped from hell. Her feather cloth (the floating scarf she is always seen with) can change the appearance of an object, create disguises to aid the mission or it can hide people in plain sight. She is left-handed and is rarely seen without her broom, as it was from her original role as a cleaner for hell. To stay close to Keima, she tells Mari, Keima`s mother, that she is an illegitimate child of Keima`s father, and ends up living in the Katsuragi household as well as attending the same class in school. Elsie is often made fun of by the other demons because of the poor grades she had in the demon academy. However, after partnering with Keima, they were able to capture 9 escaped spirits within half a year`s time, which earned her the Section Chief`s Award.
Elsie is also a member of Chihiro`s band in which she plays a left handed bass. She has also developed an interest in fire trucks. She literally idolises Keima, often referring to him as "Kami-sama" or "Kami-nii-sama" in her role as his sister.</description>
<picture>55510.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18463" type="main character in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="620">8.23</rating>
<name>Katsuragi Keima</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Katsuragi Keima is the primary protagonist of the story, a 17-year-old high school student attending Maijima High School Academy. He is known as "The Capturing God (落とし神, Otoshi-gami)" in the gaming world for his legendary skills in "capturing" any girls in dating sims. But ironically, he is called otamegane (a derogatory portmanteau of the two words otaku and megane-"glasses"). At the start of the series, Keima becomes a collaborator for catching runaway spirits when he replies to an e-mail requesting his help to "capture" girls without knowing it was a contract from Hell, to which Elsee appeared and asked for his aid to "capture" girls in real-life. For each individual of the "Capture Targets"—a girl with the runaway spirit in her—Keima utilizes his analytical skills and experiences from dating sims to capture them. Whenever he isn`t capturing runaway spirits, he is almost always seen playing video games on his PFP (a parody of Sony`s PSP). Also, despite the fact he even plays video games in class, he is still at the top of class in every subject. As the story progresses, his perspective of the "real world" girls becomes different.</description>
<picture>55509.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23425" type="appears in" update="2020-04-13">
<rating votes="56">8.23</rating>
<name>Katsuragi Mari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Keima`s mother resembles a typical shoujo manga-style mother; optimistic, ditsy, and loving. However, when she is angry, Mari removes her glasses and lets her hair down and changes her personality completely. Keima claims that she used to be a part of a biker gang, and has shown violent tendencies that reflect this.</description>
<picture>246186.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32944" type="appears in" update="2011-05-31">
<rating votes="15">6.48</rating>
<name>Sugimoto Yotsuba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sugimoto Yotsuba, also known as Yokkyun, is Keima`s most favourite game girl. She is drawn in a parody style of the famed visual novel Kanon.</description>
<picture>72601.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="483" picture="27541.jpg">Tange Sakura</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34021" type="main character in" update="2012-10-12">
<rating votes="64">7.38</rating>
<name>Ayukawa Tenri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ayukawa Tenri is a shy 17 year old girl from Maijima Municipal Misato East High School. A reticent childhood friend of Keima`s, she was his neighbor before his family moved seven years ago. In the present, she and her mother visit the Katsuragi`s where Keima does not remember her well. Unknown to Keima at first, he believes Tenri has a spirit inside of her but in reality it is a Goddess name Diana. Ten years ago during a school trip, both Keima and Tenri got lost in an underground cave where they both witness the Weiss (what evil spirits where called before) escaping from Hell and were saved by Diana who agreed to take over Tenri`s body. In order to save Diana, who is being chased by Nora who believes Tenri has a spirit inside of her, Keima pretends to capture Tenri`s heart and kiss her and have Elsie release a weak spirit in order to fool Nora. After that incident, Tenri`s family soon moves next door to Keima home.
Tenri has been love with Keima since they were children as she admired his ability to remain calm and collected no matter the situation. Despite Diana suggesting that Tenri should do more to make Keima fall for her, Tenri is just fine with their current relationship of being friends. She also enjoys doing magic tricks and playing with bubble wrap.
As Diana`s host, whenever Diana takes over Tenri`s body, she is able to perform and do amazing feats that Tenri is unable to. While she usually does nothing when Diana takes over, Tenri will sometimes interfere if Diana does something she disapproves especially when it comes to Diana`s attempts to make her and Keima closer. While not taking over, Diana can communicate and see others via a reflective surface like glass or mirrors. Because of Diana`s knowledge about Heavens involvement with the New Hell regime, Keima usually meets Tenri to discuss with Diana about these topics. With recent events of Keima trying to find Diana`s other Goddesses sisters, Keima has warned Tenri to be careful as to not catch the attention of those targeting the Goddesses.
Tenri`s name is derived from Tenri Station (天理駅, Tenri-eki) and her character design is modeled after Diana Barry, from Anne of Green Gables.</description>
<picture>126782.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34022" type="main character in" update="2013-09-03">
<rating votes="61">7.99</rating>
<name>Diana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Diana is the goddess of "the hunt and the moon", as well as the first goddess Keima encounters who resides in Tenri`s body. Keima first meets Diana when he assumes she is a Weiss, but Tenri manages to convince him otherwise after she tells Keima about how she first met Diana, who saved them both ten years ago from the Weiss. Because of her knowledge which Elsie and Haqua aren`t aware of, Keima visits her when he wants to know more about the relationship between Heaven and the Underworld. When Diana takes over Tenri`s body, she appears with slanted eyes in contrast to Tenri`s rounded eyes. Diana acts cold, selfish and thoughtless most of the time which tends to irk some people, yet she is very supportive of Tenri`s love for Keima. She wishes for Tenri and Keima to be a couple as it would restore her powers, despite being disgusted that Keima has managed to make other girls fall in love with him as well. Diana is also the one who originally requested that Keima should find her sisters, in exchange for helping him seal back the Weiss. Later on in the series, after Keima apologises to her for his indecisiveness, Diana regains more of her powers and now has the ability to use her angel wings.</description>
<picture>126783.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47891" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-12">
<rating votes="25">4.74</rating>
<name>Nola Florian Reolia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nola is a Spirit Hunter who is introduced during their biannual assembly; she is ten years older than Elsie and Haqua. She is arrogant and disdainful; she looks down on younger demons. Although she has a human partner, Asama Ryou, she sometimes tries to force Loose Spirits out without his help. Her preferred method of capturing Loose Spirits is to fulfill the target`s desire: (e.g. riches for those who want money, suitable partners for those who desire love, death to her enemies for those who desire revenge). Due to her impulsive nature, she sometimes assumes the target`s strong emotion to be hate instead of love, and attacks the target`s person of affection.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>139960.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48506" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-12-26">
<rating votes="14">2.45</rating>
<name>Asama Ryou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129983.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="202" picture="25743.jpg">Terashima Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49979" type="appears in" update="2012-12-26">
<rating votes="5">4.65</rating>
<name>Tenri no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tenri`s mother.</description>
<picture>129985.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="203" picture="38566.jpg">Matsuki Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51672" type="appears in" update="2012-12-31">
<rating votes="6">5.05</rating>
<name>Katsuragi Keima</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Katsuragi Keima as a child.</description>
<picture>130193.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51798" type="appears in" update="2012-12-31">
<rating votes="2">3.18</rating>
<name>Kaketama</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130195.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18360" picture="48491.jpg">Yamazaki Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="141044" update="2012-12-28">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">再会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Reunion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144835" update="2012-12-28">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-12-18</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">邂逅</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Encounter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaikou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144840" update="2012-10-20">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146168" update="2012-12-26">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-12-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
