<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9339" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>20</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-01-25</startdate>
<enddate>2013-06-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hetalia: The Beautiful World</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ヘタリア The Beautiful World</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Hetalia: The Beautiful World</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="10947" type="Sequel">Hetalia: The World Twinkle</anime>
<anime id="7448" type="Prequel">Hetalia World Series</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="750045">I`m not a fan of history in general, but yet I have a huge amount of useless yet fun facts thanks to this anime. May not suit everyone, but it`s very funny and short so why not give it a shot ?</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://hetalia.com/bw/</url>
<creators>
<name id="730" type="Animation Work">Studio Deen</name>
<name id="3918" type="Character Design">Oka Mariko</name>
<name id="3724" type="Series Composition">Fudeyasu Kazuyuki</name>
<name id="2744" type="Direction">Watanabe Hiroshi</name>
<name id="4220" type="Original Work">Himaruya Hidekazu</name>
<name id="3918" type="Chief Animation Direction">Oka Mariko</name>
<name id="4221" type="Music">Conisch</name>
</creators>
<description>Forget what you learned in history class, and imagine all the nations of the world as guys on an inappropriate reality show. Pledge allegiance to your favorite superpower in Hetalia Axis Powers!
Source: crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="263">5.94</permanent>
<temporary count="264">6.70</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>131351.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14925</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15195</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>17273</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>21075</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://hetalia.com/bw/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3856</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>344529</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15948</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>HetaliaOfficial</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3955" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>DESCRIPTION MISSING</name>
<description>The description for this entry is missing. e.g plot, biography...
Please help by adding it, and remove this tag afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="5841" type="main character in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="61">6.40</rating>
<name>Italia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A bright and energetic nation that progressed from being the kin of Roma Antiqua, widely recognised as the strongest nation in the world, to being clumsy and irresponsible. Personified as being carefree, cowardly and lackadaisical (noted by his collection of white flags he uses to surrender), he often depends on Germany to resolve issues. Nods to Italian culture include his artistry and recurrent portrayal of pasta and pizza. He has an older brother, who represents southern Italy and who is commonly known as Italy Romano.</description>
<picture>59514.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5842" type="main character in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="57">7.82</rating>
<name>Doitsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A hard worker and lover of rules. He sticks to them rigidly and trains his troops to do the same. Despite this, he has formed a close relationship with the carefree Northern Italy. He notes at one point that he has a crazy boss.</description>
<picture>59516.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5843" type="main character in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="45">6.92</rating>
<name>Nihon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hard-working, serious, skilled with his hands, and needs time to adjust to other people. He is inexperienced in the outside world, but does his best to learn all he can. Generally quiet, he sometimes seems to have the attitude of an old man.</description>
<picture>59515.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="52" picture="19811.jpg">Takahashi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5844" type="main character in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="33">5.06</rating>
<name>America</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Raised by England and having fought for his independence, America became a country of pioneers. He is an energetic country who loves sticking his nose into other people`s business. He sees everything in a positive light, is quick to take action, and he always has his own idea of doing things. He also has immense physical strength and courage, although he has a crippling fear of ghosts, particularly when they are vague blobs of light in pictures. Strangely, a grey named Tony appears in his house from time to time without him minding it at all. America is frequently seen clutching a hamburger and flashing a thumbs up. America also has a penchant for coming up with elaborate inventions that never go anywhere.</description>
<picture>59509.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5845" type="main character in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="48">7.85</rating>
<name>Igirisu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A nation that was once a pirate and tormented Spain, the United Kingdom is a gentleman who is known for having terrible cooking skills (although America enjoys his food), a foul mouth, and huge eyebrows. He does not get along well with France or Russia, and can sometimes be cynical, particularly towards his somewhat estranged sibling America. Despite being mocked by the other nations for it, England is a strong believer of unicorns, faeries, and magic, going so far as to literally curse his enemies. England cannot hold his liquor well and is a very unhappy sort of drunk. He once formed an alliance with Japan because he felt lonely. He is classified as a tsundere character.</description>
<picture>59510.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="221" picture="17039.jpg">Sugiyama Noriaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5846" type="main character in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="36">6.71</rating>
<name>France</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Once a large nation, but after Napoleon Bonaparte had died, he was no longer good in war and instead attracted tourists to his country with his wine. He has an intense rivalry with England, and loves to argue with him over trivial topics. France is infatuated with most of the nations, often touching them inappropriately. He has been known to streak naked and makes blatant sexual comments at every opportunity. France maintains a bit of facial hair because he feels it makes him look like a big brother. He is constantly pictured with a rose, whether he is carrying it or using it as a censor.</description>
<picture>59511.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="183" picture="16992.jpg">Onosaka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5847" type="main character in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="78">8.26</rating>
<name>Russia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Despite having the cruelty of a child, Russia is the tallest of all the nations. He adores vodka and sunflowers. His primary hate is "General Winter", despite using the cold to his advantage in war. Russia has a kind and gentle face, but has mentally cracked from the strain of his bloody history. The other nations are mortified by him, particularly Lithuania, whom he loves to both physically and emotionally abuse. Occasionally, he stalks others while in a panda costume. Russia promises that eventually "everyone will become one with Russia". He also frequently says "KolKolKolKol" to nations he is threatening. Russia is almost always seen carrying a section of pipe. He is classified as a yandere character.</description>
<picture>59512.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1663" picture="23213.jpg">Takato Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5848" type="main character in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="34">5.27</rating>
<name>Chuugoku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the oldest nations and is regarded as the eldest brother among the East Asian nations. He is extremely superstitious and religious. Slightly disturbed of Russia. He has certain tastes for things and gets irritated if a food has a certain pattern of tastes. He is also a big fan of Hello Kitty and tends to end his sentences with the Japanese suffix -aru.</description>
<picture>59513.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1442" picture="18829.jpg">Kaida Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5849" type="appears in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="21">6.35</rating>
<name>Austria</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>22928.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="5850" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-25">
<rating votes="8">3.32</rating>
<name>Spain</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59959.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="5851" type="appears in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="11">7.83</rating>
<name>Poland</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>22930.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2883" picture="23111.jpg">Tanaka Kokoro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5852" type="appears in" update="2009-04-09">
<rating votes="10">2.91</rating>
<name>Greece</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>22931.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="5854" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-11">
<rating votes="9">6.45</rating>
<name>Estonia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Estonia is described as "The wisest of the Baltic brothers and the most lucky as well." He is very high-tech, and is the owner of the strange "mochis", which are small, round, white creatures; each of them is like a certain country, with the four that are usually shown being America, Italy, Canada, and England. Of the three, it is he who tends to stand up to Russia the most.</description>
<picture>22933.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="10476" type="main character in" update="2010-02-16">
<rating votes="7">6.28</rating>
<name>Canada</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An easygoing, softhearted and gentle young man.
The polar bear Kumajirou is always with him. They`ve been together for so long without even knowing about each other, so he can`t remember his name.
He hates being mistaken for America, so he tries to show the appeal for Canada in various ways, but...
He hates fighting, but his neighbor is his neighbor, so when will he be able to live in peace...?</description>
<picture>43101.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14093" type="appears in" update="2010-01-13">
<rating votes="18">7.66</rating>
<name>Hungary</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41460.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="14095" type="appears in" update="2010-01-13">
<rating votes="12">5.73</rating>
<name>Swiss</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41462.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="14096" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-25">
<rating votes="15">5.83</rating>
<name>Romano</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59960.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="14101" type="appears in" update="2013-03-11">
<rating votes="4">8.82</rating>
<name>Sweden</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sweden appears to be scary and often intimidates those around him, although he is actually friendly. He has a tendency to leave vowels out of his statements, making what he says difficult to decipher. He has a fondness for Finland, calling him "m` wife".</description>
<picture>41468.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="14102" type="appears in" update="2013-03-11">
<rating votes="4">5.18</rating>
<name>Finland</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Finland is a cheerful nation who has a particular fondness for Christmas because of the belief that Santa Claus lives in Lapland, which is a major region in northern Finland. He and Sweden escaped from Denmark`s house together, traveling back to their homes together as well. He considers all the Nordics to be brothers, and he and Sweden are shown to be the peacekeepers between them.</description>
<picture>41469.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="14103" type="appears in" update="2013-11-05">
<rating votes="3">7.92</rating>
<name>Sealand</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sealand is unofficially the smallest nation in the world. Dressed in a sailor suit, Sealand is the youngest and smallest character in the series. He was created after England made him, but left him in the middle of the sea and forgot about him. However, nobody recognizes Sealand as a nation in his own right. As a result, he has to try other ways of getting noticed. For example, he once went to a meeting disguised as Canada. In the film Paint it, White, Sealand is shown that he has the ability to run across water and jump great heights, being able to jump from sea-level to his platform in a single leap. He refers to England as jerk England or British jerk.</description>
<picture>41472.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="16298" type="appears in" update="2010-04-01">
<rating votes="4">5.69</rating>
<name>Ukraine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>45501.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="18035" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-25">
<rating votes="24">8.38</rating>
<name>Preussen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59961.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="57562" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-29">
<rating votes="16">7.44</rating>
<name>Turkey</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Formerly known as the Ottoman Empire, he has a big rivalry with Greece after he invaded the country, but Russia also is another biggest enemy of him from history of the Russo-Turkish War. Turkey is described as being, "unnecessarily passionate and uncomfortably friendly". However, despite his jovial personality, Turkey can be stubborn about trivial things.</description>
<picture>60713.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3998" picture="33313.jpg">Fujimoto Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61134" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-05">
<rating votes="4">4.27</rating>
<name>Oranda</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is the older brother of Belgium and Luxembourg. Initial notes described him as a tsundere who is xenophobic and thinks little of using drugs, which may be referencing to the semi-legality of soft-drug consumption in the Netherlands, and is hinted to have a lolicon fetish. Current notes describe him as neurotic and solemn, obsessed with cleanliness and money and doesn`t like to be tied up. He has a pet bunny and beat up Finland and Sweden and drove them out of the New World. He has disliked Spain since the 80 years war although he mostly appears in the group formed by Spain, South Italy, Belgium and himself.</description>
<picture>145342.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12624" picture="79638.jpg">Mine Nobuya</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="146982" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-01-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">それぞれの戦場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sorezore no Senjou</title>
<summary>In this episode: throwing stars, sharpened chopsticks, steel tanks, and other super-mega-manly stuff - like, for instance, Germany squatting in a dandelion patch. Also, YOU GUYS, HETALIA’S BACK!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="147146" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-02-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">学園ヘタリア 進め! 新聞部! 前半戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gakuen Hetalia: Susume! Shinbun-bu! Zenhansen</title>
<summary>The Axis boys investigate W Academy’s various clubs, including the Gourmet Club, the Witchcraft Club, and the Man, France is Looking REALLY Good Lately Club. Okay, that last one’s not a real thing. But, seriously, France is looking REALLY good lately.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="147443" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-02-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロシアとおともだち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Russia to Otomodachi</title>
<summary>Poor Russia. He had a pretty rough childhood. Everyone picked on him. Even random hamsters totally hated him. Stupid hamsters. Oh, and it turns out that Prussia has always, even as a little kid, been a total di… uh, handful. Come on, you know how he is.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="147444" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-02-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">学園ヘタリア 進め! 新聞部! 後半戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gakuen Hetalia: Susume! Shinbun-bu! Kouhansen</title>
<summary>It seems W Academy’s most ridiculous clubs each share the same single member. This member’s identity should not surprise you. Also, HUGE news! A NEVER-BEFORE-SEEN character shows up around two minutes into the episode!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="147564" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-03-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロマーノにっき</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Romano Nikki</title>
<summary>This episode explores the intricacies of Romano and Spain’s adorably dysfunctional relationship. Also, somebody keeps peeing in Romano’s bed. He blames a rogue squirrel. But I ain’t buying it.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="147565" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-02-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">私が去ろうとも貴方は残る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi ga Sarou to mo Anata wa Nokoru</title>
<summary>This episode about France is heavy. It’s deep. There’s a wistful old man and two uncertain young lovers. Right in the middle of it all: ageless France. Is it a blessing or a curse that he stays forever yum? Wait, I meant YOUNG. FOREVER YOUNG. DAT HAIR.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="147878" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-03-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とること!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toru Koto!</title>
<summary>Young Greece waxes philosophical about his love of cats, his desire to pet cats, and his hunger for sweets. Then he takes a bath with Turkey. Turkey is super cool. And strong.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="147879" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-03-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">オランダさんち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Holland-san Chi</title>
<summary>Belgium wants to throw a waffle party, but the only things her big bro Netherlands cares about are pickled fish, clean kitchens, and cold hard cash! He so blunt - and dreamy!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="147880" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-03-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロシアさんと僕のゆるやかな喧嘩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Russia-san to Boku no Yuruyaka na Kenka</title>
<summary>The blog-o-sphere erupts into flames when Estonia’s website gets hacked! With Russia as the main suspect, America attem-///error…(0
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="147881" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-03-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アメリカ人と暮らしてるとよくあること</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">America-jin to Kurashiteru to Yoku Aru Koto</title>
<summary>In today’s episode: Quality time in the bathtub. Also, America’s got some pretty sweet dance moves. Japan’s got some pretty sweet abs. And why am I just now hearing about this cat that apparently likes to sit in pots?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="148661" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふぁいんでぃんぐ・サンタ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 13</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Finding Santa</title>
<summary>It’s a super squee Christmas season except for one teeny problem – Santa’s gone missing! Luckily, France is still a dreamboat, and Canada has a Polar Bear! What does that mean!? Who cares! Polar Bears 4 Eva!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="148662" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-04-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">めりーはろうぃーん!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Merry Halloween!</title>
<summary>Japan’s peaceful soak in a nice, hot tub is ruined when America kicks in the window and invites him to a Halloween party – in his room! Also, England summons an old fairy to scare the pants off America. Scary no pants time!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="148663" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-04-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">僕たちの失敗</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bokutachi no Shippai</title>
<summary>It’s April Fools’ Day and someone is forcing all the countries to dress up in embarrassing costumes! France is suddenly super small, and everyone is up in arms! Except that one guy who lives upstairs from America. I can never remember his name.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="150165" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-05-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">HETALIA OF THE DEAD/前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 17</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hetalia of the Dead: Zenpen</title>
<summary>When the countries gather to show off their favorite horror movies, it’s nothing but boobs, bloody entrails, Japanese ghosts, creepy naked Santas, and mental stabbings! OMG WHAT WAS THAT NOISE!?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="150166" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-05-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">イタリアの忘れ物</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 16</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Italia no Wasuremono</title>
<summary>You guys, there’s a royal wedding and afterward England’s Prince IS VISITING SEYCHELLES!!! Oh, wait, that’s supposed to be a big secret. Pretend you never read that. Just think of studly archangels and cardboard hats instead.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="150167" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-05-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">A bientot!また会いましょう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 15</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">A Bientot! Mata Aimashou</title>
<summary>France looks dashing whilst discoursing on the Hundred Years War and Joan of Arc’s tragic, yet beautiful, life. Did I mention how dreamy France’s hair looks when he twirls in the breeze? Well, it does. It really, really does.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="150168" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-05-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">兄弟よ!俺たちは...!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 14</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoudai yo! Oretachi wa...!</title>
<summary>Today’s agenda consists of cool diplomatic poses, brothers pumping iron, sneaking into the American camp – and a shared love of hamburgers! BEEFCAKES BEEFCAKES BEEFCAKES!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="150911" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">一周年だよ!三国同盟</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 20</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Isshuunen Da yo! Sankoku Doumei</title>
<summary>Japan throws a swanky party to celebrate his alliance with Germany and Italy. Germany wants to get down to business, but Italy is looking forward to snacks, calico kittens, and bath time!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="150912" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-06-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">もっともっと!!進めシーランド!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 19</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Motto Motto!! Susume Sealand!</title>
<summary>Seborga hangs upside down from a tree and drips ketchup all over Wy’s yard. Meanwhile, Ukraine and Hungary dish on super cute costumes from throughout the ages! Get a load of Crete!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="150913" update="2018-03-30">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-06-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">HETALIA OF THE DEAD/後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 18</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hetalia of the Dead: Kouhen</title>
<summary>The dreamy boys of Hetalia love horror films! Canada’s opus features a cage full of pancakes and bears, Germany shows off its jugs and vampires, and America proves that a good cook can kill any zombie! Hold up – who in the eff is this Canada dude!?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="151396" update="2014-10-22">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-10-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">リヒテンシュタインとハリネズミ国家</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Liechtenstein and the Hedgehog Country</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Liechtenstein to Harinezumi Kokka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151397" update="2014-10-22">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-08-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">百年ごとの贈り物</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Centennial Gift</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hyakunen Goto no Okurimono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151398" update="2014-10-22">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-06-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヴァレンティーノ/後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Buon San Valentino, Second Part</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Valentino Kouhen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151399" update="2014-10-22">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-04-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヴァレンティーノ/前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Buon San Valentino, First Part</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Valentino Zenpen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159834" update="2014-10-23">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2014-02-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">僕がヒロインに囲まれ過ぎて世</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Was Overwhelmed by Heroines</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boku ga Heroin ni Kakomare Sugite yo</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
