<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9342" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-01-11</startdate>
<enddate>2013-03-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Boku wa Tomodachi ga Sukunai Next</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">나는 친구가 적다 2기 NEXT</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Haganai Next</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Haganai 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">僕は友達が少ないNEXT</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Haganai Next</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">我的朋友很少NEXT</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8419" type="Prequel">Boku wa Tomodachi ga Sukunai</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="8">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="21092">While the first season started quite well, re: "a boy and his harem of weird girls", the 2nd season, which I did not anticipate would arise (but did), [b]did not betray my expectations of how this would turn out:-[/b]
It devolved into [b]just another banal harem show.[/b]
Actual comic moments are far and few between in this 2nd season, instead focussing on all the more harem-oriented elements. So even though the Audio-Visual components of this show are still good by today`s standards, that alone will probably determine whether one might consider this an enjoyable 6 hour diversion.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="473211">As good as the first one. More focus on Sena and worser position for Yozora(which disappointed me). But a lot of Rika and good new secondary characters. The only bad thing that they adapted all 8 present volumes of the LN and till the author herself finds out how to conclude the story we won`t see more of it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="382805">more good stuff, characters become a little thiner or animation quality dropped, but still very good funny</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="51585">Awesome continuation for awesome series.

Pigs that can`t fly are serious business. At least in Mazui`s translation. I haven`t laughed this hard for a long time.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="454583">a must see for me because i love this anime so much, fits the comedy and romance. If you`re a romance lover then you must watch this. Season 1 is more to comedy than romance and Season 2 is the other way around</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/haganai/</url>
<creators>
<name id="27061" type="Original Work">Hirasaka Yomi</name>
<name id="1645" type="Direction">Kitahata Tooru</name>
<name id="28474" type="Animation Work">AIC Build</name>
<name id="15901" type="Character Design">Watanabe Yoshihiro</name>
<name id="27061" type="Series Composition">Hirasaka Yomi</name>
<name id="3405" type="Series Composition">Urahata Tatsuhiko</name>
<name id="2431" type="Music">Tom-H@ck</name>
<name id="15901" type="Chief Animation Direction">Watanabe Yoshihiro</name>
<name id="22641" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takashina Yuka</name>
<name id="17220" type="Chief Animation Direction">Shen Hong</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a light novel series by http://anidb.net/cr27061 [Hirasaka Yomi] with illustrations by http://anidb.net/cr24691 [Buriki].
The Neighbours Club — a club with the objective of making friends, populated by girls and boys undertaking interesting activities.
Despite the incident which happened at the end of summer, the atmosphere at the Neighbours Club continues as before. With the appearance of a strange nun and a student council committee member, http://anidb.net/ch32433 [Hasegawa Kodaka]`s days become even more lively.
Exciting times lie ahead as the club makes a trip to an amusement park, plays games, holds a birthday party, takes part in a school festival, and many other events. Eventually, the relationship of the members greatly changes...
~ translated and adapted from official site by Cranston</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="3537">6.19</permanent>
<temporary count="3559">7.27</temporary>
<review count="1">7.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>95013.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14827</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14967</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5166</identifier>
<identifier>tsvkiq</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/haganai/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Boku_wa_Tomodachi_ga_Sukunai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>僕は友達が少ない</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2817</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>344512</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15642</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=qRGxtqDj9Wg</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=-5MFjf7EGM0</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=msCDgDkn8Jo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B00KATU4WU</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1065" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-05">
<name>heterochromatic eyes</name>
<description>Heterochromia Iridis is a condition where one eye is a different color from the other, or one eye is more than one color.
Characters with different eye-colour may not necessarily have the medical condition itself, as the state of different-coloured eyes can be caused by various other reasons such as possession by spiritual entities, indication of special powers or artificial changes.</description>
<picurl>63229.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1133" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>otaku</name>
<description>Otaku, derived from a Japanese term for another`s house or family (お宅, otaku), appeared in the 1980s. In the anime http://anidb.net/a77 [Macross], first aired in 1982, the term was used by http://anidb.net/ch7418 [Lynn Minmay] as an honorific term.
In modern Japanese slang, the term otaku refers to a fan of any particular theme, topic, or hobby. Common uses are anime otaku (a fan of anime), cosplay otaku and manga otaku (a fan of Japanese comic books), pasokon otaku (personal computer geeks), geemu otaku (playing video games), and wota (pronounced ota, previously referred to as idol otaku) that are extreme fans of http://anidb.net/t2438 [idols], heavily promoted singing girls. There are also tetsudou otaku or denshamania (railfans) or gunji otaku (military geeks).
While these are the most common uses, the word can be applied to anything (music otaku, martial arts otaku, cooking otaku, etc).
Some of Japan`s otaku use the term to describe themselves and their friends semi-humorously, accepting their position as fans, and some even use the term proudly, attempting to reclaim it from its negative connotations. In general colloquial usage however, most Japanese would consider it undesirable to be described in a serious fashion as otaku; many even consider it to be a genuine insult.
The negativity which modern society shows towards otaku and otaku culture is historically partly attributed to Miyazaki Tsutomu, who became known as The Otaku Murderer in 1989. His bizarre murders fueled a moral panic against otaku. However, the public appearance of most otaku is the major reason for them to be shunned by society today.</description>
<picurl>52482.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1403" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-10">
<name>nun</name>
<description>A nun is a member of a religious community of women, typically one living under vows of poverty, chastity, and obedience. She may have decided to dedicate her life to serving all other living beings, or she might be an ascetic who voluntarily chose to leave mainstream society and live her life in prayer and contemplation in a monastery or convent. The term "nun" is applicable to Catholics (eastern and western traditions), Orthodox Christians, Anglicans, Lutherans, Jains, Buddhists, Taoists, Hindus and some other religious traditions.
Source: Wiktionary</description>
<picurl>165755.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2072" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>maid</name>
<description>A maid is a female employed in domestic service. They usually wear uniforms. Since their nature is to be obedient and serve their goshujin-sama (master), they are one of the most desired types of women in Japan, a dream of every Japanese man, particularly http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku]. Often seen in so-called Maid Cafes in Akihabara, where male customers can for a little time enjoy the feeling of being served by a woman. The male gender opposite is the butler.</description>
<picurl>4954.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2894" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>female student</name>
<description>Pretty much exclusive to hentai shows only unless an ecchi show has implied sex and/or a strong indicator of nudity. A character is considered a student if she goes to school, doesn`t matter if it`s high school, college or homeschooling, but she should be of appropriate age for a student; a housewife going to college should not get this category.</description>
<picurl>210611.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3107" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-10-12">
<name>unfoundedly feared character</name>
<description>Due to some strange misunderstanding, or some other unfounded reason the character in the anime is feared by his contemporaries.
Example: A male student with an "evil eye" is mistaken for a delinquent, and thus feared by the students in his class.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3108" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-20">
<name>catastrophic gadgets</name>
<description>Comedy element: One of the characters in the anime tends to "invent", "create", or "call into existence" all sorts of wacky gadgets. The intent is to help the other protagonists in some way. Only that this fails every single time, ending in a catastrophe.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3395" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-18">
<name>promise</name>
<description>A dramatically-made promise that serves as foreshadowing. The promise will eventually be called in and action will be required.
Whether they succeed, fail or refuse to keep their promise depends almost entirely on the idealism-level of the story. Other factors, such as whether they were told what they had to do, or if it was a Leonine Contract, may come into play. Even Releasing from the Promise is usually a scene of high drama.
Source: TVTropes</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3751" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-02">
<name>grandiose displays of wealth</name>
<description>Some of the characters in this anime come from very wealthy families. A huge estate with large mansion or castle, a flotilla of expensive cars, private jets or islands, and many servants will impress the viewer profoundly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3946" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-04-16">
<name>filmmaking</name>
<description>Filmmaking is the process of making a film. This may be tied to studios with very large budgets or to inexpensive independent products alike, and even to amateur films; modern technology allows people to film events of significance in their lives, such as their marriages. Anime in school settings may have a film club, which sometimes produce their own films for e.g. the school culture festival.</description>
<picurl>68842.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4116" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-13">
<name>eternal blush</name>
<description>It is no ordinary blush it is a blush that does not disappear.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4246" parentid="3395" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-01">
<name>childhood promise</name>
<description>Sweet childhood promises... who remembers them other than the Japanese anime characters?
It keeps the main characters obsessed with promises that they made when they were children, mostly related to love, with lines like "I will always protect you" or "I will marry you when we grow up".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5188" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-02-08">
<name>inconclusive romantic plot</name>
<description>This tag refers to unresolved romance in a series. It`s common in harem anime, but may also appear in normal romance series (especially if they are incomplete adaptations of novels or manga).
The protagonist doesn`t choose any of his love interests in the end and doesn`t dump any of them either. This tag does not refer to those (few) series where protagonist actually chooses all the girls on his own accord (i.e. Sekirei).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5527" parentid="2729" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-07-17">
<name>spanking</name>
<description>Spanking someone`s butt as torture or for sexual pleasure.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5834" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>show within a show</name>
<description>A fictional TV (or radio, or stage) show that takes place within an actual TV show; or, occasionally, a fictional instalment or incarnation of an actual show. Many comedies have short one-off gags where they parody existing shows.
Example: A large part of Martian Successor Nadesico is centred around the fictional popular anime Gekigangar III, which is being watched by several characters of the Nadesico crew.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="32428" type="main character in" update="2017-05-11">
<rating votes="440">5.69</rating>
<name>Mikazuki Yozora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A cruel and selfish black-haired girl who says she understands and respects bullying but resents being called a bully herself, Yozora`s difficult personality drives away anyone who might wish to make friends with her before she meets http://anidb.net/ch32433 [Kodaka]. She is physically abusive towards, and often argues with, http://anidb.net/ch32430 [Sena] and manipulative towards http://anidb.net/ch32434 [Maria], who she cons into giving up an empty room for the use of the http://anidb.net/ch37939 [Neighbor`s Club], and http://anidb.net/ch32431 [Yukimura], who she fools into working for the club as a cross-dressing cosplay maid. The only person she can`t insult is http://anidb.net/ch32429 [Rika], as Rika takes whatever insult she gives her and deflects it back with a dirty joke that leaves her tired - to the point where she just does what Rika says (like cross-dress for example) rather than argue.
She is Kodaka`s childhood friend, though at the time, he believed that she was a boy, calling her "Sora"; her nickname for him was "Taka." On the day that Kodaka moved, she intended to wear a skirt and reveal her gender to him but was too embarrassed to do so. Kodaka eventually recognized her after she had to cut her hair short due to it catching on fire. She seems to have feelings for Kodaka.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>76319.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32429" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-26">
<rating votes="361">7.36</rating>
<name>Shiguma Rika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A freshman and highly capable mad scientist. She was saved by http://anidb.net/ch32433 [Kodaka] when she fell unconscious during a disastrous lab experiment, and begs to repay his kindness with sex; she joined the http://anidb.net/ch37939 [Neighbor`s Club] just to get closer to him.
Although there are many adult themes in the series, she is the most sexually forward member. This was clearly highlighted in her first speaking appearance, when she described the attractions of rape to Kodaka in the middle of a stunned class. She has a habit of inserting any sexual innuendo possible in her sentences, to the point where she finds it normal to convert any innocent thought into something perverted. As a fujoshi, she is a passionate consumer of BL doujinshi and magazines, is comically aroused by intercourse between mecha, and is delighted when http://anidb.net/ch32431 [Yukimura] offers to have sex with Kodaka. Rika is proud of her perverseness, as she says that she would be a boring person if people only thought of her as a genius girl. To compound her eccentricity, she speaks in the third person.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>76322.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="304" picture="17139.jpg">Fukuen Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32430" type="main character in" update="2017-05-11">
<rating votes="513">7.77</rating>
<name>Kashiwazaki Sena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The wealthy blonde daughter of the school`s headteacher, Sena shows a dislike of all things "ordinary". She is both attractive and academically successful, but her resulting arrogance leads her to be disliked by her female peers. Their admiration eludes her, much as she desires it; she treats her male classmates only as servants to be used, although many of them would like to be her boyfriend. Nonetheless, she holds http://anidb.net/ch32433 [Kodaka] to a higher standard. Kodaka concludes that she is the weirdest member of the club, as she is able to warrant weird and disgusted looks not only from http://anidb.net/ch32428 [Yozora] and http://anidb.net/ch32432 [Kobato], but also from http://anidb.net/ch32431 [Yukimura] and http://anidb.net/ch32429 [Rika].
She enjoys playing video games, including dating sims and eroge, partially because they allow her to make female (if virtual) friends. She is generally fascinated by the girls in these games and has also taken a liking to Kobato. Yozora calls her "Meat" (肉 Niku - due to her large breasts?), an insulting nickname which she secretly likes because it was the first she had ever received.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>76320.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32431" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-26">
<rating votes="233">5.56</rating>
<name>Kusunoki Yukimura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>First introduced as a stalker of http://anidb.net/ch32433 [Kodaka]. "His" first meeting with the http://anidb.net/ch37939 [Neighbor`s Club] resulted in gender confusion, as "his" appearance is decidedly feminine despite "his" assertions of male hood (which are ultimately shown to be false, when her true biological gender is finally revealed).
A gullible student with low self-esteem, she admiringly believes Kodaka to be a romantic and masculine criminal who lives life the way he wants to, and eagerly pledges to become his underling on the basis that she can learn to become less effeminate through him; however, she also appears to harbor a crush on Kodaka. She fittingly refers to Kodaka as "aniki". She tends to do everything Kodaka says to the extreme; when Kodaka asked her to bring http://anidb.net/ch32434 [Maria] something healthy to eat, Yukimura brought a protein shake and tried to force it down her throat until she finished it all.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>76321.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25804" picture="71817.jpg">Yamamoto Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32432" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-22">
<rating votes="409">7.65</rating>
<name>Hasegawa Kobato</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch32433 [Kodaka]`s younger sister; she is a student in middle school, but nonetheless joins the http://anidb.net/ch37939 [club]. She is very close to her brother, who she calls "An-Chan", and behaves in a jealous and clingy way whenever she feels that he is not giving her the attention she deserves, to the point where it is obvious that she has a brother complex. She sees http://anidb.net/ch32434 [Maria] as a rival for Kodaka`s brotherly affections and so often gets into fights with the latter. Despite being older than Maria she has smaller breasts than her, which Maria is always eager to point out.
She has a penchant for darkness, vampires and the macabre ever since she started watching an anime called Full Metal Necromancer. As a result she often speaks in an affected fashion, and claims to be known as "Reisys VI Felicity Sumeragi", an ancient vampire who has lived for ten thousand years, and wears a gothic dress and red contacts, but this facade quickly breaks down when she gets emotionally worked up and she speaks in a strong Kyushu accent. Indeed, her behavior does not for the most part differ from that of a regular girl (procrastinating with her homework, staying inside when it is hot, etc.) which Kodaka points out, causing her to be embarrassed and slightly lose character.
Moreover, she is not very good at mathematics, taking a long time to solve a question Kodaka posed to her, and displays rather limited vocabulary, frequently getting words wrong.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>76323.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32433" type="main character in" update="2017-05-11">
<rating votes="275">5.14</rating>
<name>Hasegawa Kodaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The protagonist, a transfer student who has not been able to make friends in his first month at St. Chronica`s. Of all of the members of the club, he is the most gentle, balanced and socially competent in personality; but his unusual hair color, inherited from his late English mother, leads classmates to assume he is a violent and abusive delinquent and spread defamatory rumors about him. Because of his long experience of antagonism, Kodaka has become accustomed to fighting and can defend himself quite well.
His father is working in the United States, and so he takes care of his younger sister alone at home, which has also made him a good cook. His childhood was characterized by frequent movement, and as a result he has few memories related to home life and close friendships; however, though he does not realize it at first, he and http://anidb.net/ch32428 [Yozora] were childhood friends before his family moved.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>76318.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2225" picture="192115.jpg">Kimura Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32434" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-26">
<rating votes="214">4.13</rating>
<name>Takayama Maria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Maria is the supervising teacher of the http://anidb.net/ch37939 [Neighbors Club]; she is a ten-year old nun. While she`s a child genius she is also very rude and immature, and often uses a variety of expletives when annoyed. She develops a sibling-like relationship with http://anidb.net/ch32433 [Kodaka], who regularly makes her packed lunches, and is affectionate with him, much to http://anidb.net/ch32432 [Kobato`s] annoyance. She is also gullible, which http://anidb.net/ch32428 [Yozora] uses to her advantage, and at some point, Kobato uses it to win an argument.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>76324.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37931" type="appears in" update="2017-05-11">
<rating votes="8">5.46</rating>
<name>Sora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71161.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37932" type="appears in" update="2011-10-21">
<rating votes="7">5.79</rating>
<name>Lace</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71162.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3202" picture="24193.jpg">Nakamura Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37933" type="appears in" update="2011-11-24">
<rating votes="7">5.03</rating>
<name>Guernica</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77534.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5023" picture="62245.jpg">Obata Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37939" type="appears in" update="2011-10-22">
<rating votes="4">9.65</rating>
<name>Rinjinbu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Rinjinbu is a club at St. Chronica`s Academy founded by Mikazuki Yozora specifically designed for people who don`t have very many friends. They try to learn how to build friendships through cooking together, playing games, and other group activities.</description>
</character>
<character id="38589" type="appears in" update="2017-05-11">
<rating votes="8">7.27</rating>
<name>Taka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76946.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28861" picture="65897.jpg">Seri Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38590" type="appears in" update="2012-01-26">
<rating votes="19">6.55</rating>
<name>Kashiwazaki Pegasus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is http://anidb.net/ch32430 [Sena`s] father and the chairman of St. Chronica`s. He is a friend of Kodaka`s father, and pulled strings so that http://anidb.net/ch32433 [Kodaka] could attend the school. He`s embarrassed by the unusual pronunciation of his first name (which normally would be pronounced "Tenba"). He constantly badmouths Kodaka`s father, but only because he truly values him as a best friend. He seems intent to betroth Sena to Kodaka, often saying that he considers Kodaka to be "a man I can entrust Sena to". He`s a wealthy man always seen wearing traditional clothing, and is quite weak to alcohol.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>76948.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38591" type="appears in" update="2017-05-11">
<rating votes="34">6.55</rating>
<name>Stella</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76949.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51989" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-08">
<rating votes="23">5.27</rating>
<name>Hidaka Hinata</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133343.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51990" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-08">
<rating votes="30">5.01</rating>
<name>Yusa Aoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133344.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="101" picture="16709.jpg">Ise Mariya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51991" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-22">
<rating votes="66">5.89</rating>
<name>Takayama Kate</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130544.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52166" type="appears in" update="2013-01-20">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Shenhua</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>131088.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32750" picture="227075.jpg">Taneda Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52167" type="appears in" update="2013-01-20">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Lloyd El Doran</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>131087.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28471" picture="57632.jpg">Yamamoto Itaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52168" type="appears in" update="2013-01-20">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Kusakabe Fumio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>131085.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="60" picture="171602.jpg">Kawada Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52169" type="appears in" update="2013-01-20">
<rating votes="2">2.58</rating>
<name>Asakura Misao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>131086.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="68" picture="16675.jpg">Yasumura Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52170" type="appears in" update="2013-01-20">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Fujioka Koyomi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>131084.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52275" type="appears in" update="2013-01-20">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Kyoushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>131083.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2501" picture="191381.jpg">Yoshikai Kiyohito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52415" type="appears in" update="2014-02-04">
<rating votes="2">5.12</rating>
<name>Hasegawa Hayato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149541.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52554" type="appears in" update="2013-02-01">
<rating votes="2">4.56</rating>
<name>Onee-san</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>131671.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12323" picture="171959.jpg">Takayama Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52555" type="appears in" update="2013-02-01">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Astaroth</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>131672.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28872" picture="66014.jpg">Kitamura Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52747" type="appears in" update="2017-05-11">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Mikazuki Yozora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>131959.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23686" picture="224554.jpg">Uchiyama Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52748" type="appears in" update="2013-02-08">
<rating votes="2">4.56</rating>
<name>Fuyuki Youko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>131958.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17149" picture="174125.jpg">Yamamura Hibiku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52749" type="appears in" update="2013-02-08">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Nagatani Eiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>131955.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52750" type="appears in" update="2013-02-08">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Suzutsuki Touma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>131956.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29979" picture="223317.jpg">Oosaka Ryouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52751" type="appears in" update="2013-02-08">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Shinomori Ouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>131957.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4821" picture="186259.jpg">Fukushima Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52974" type="appears in" update="2013-02-16">
<rating votes="3">5.06</rating>
<name>Nami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132239.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34426" picture="128153.jpg">Suzaki Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53326" type="appears in" update="2013-03-01">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>France Eiga no Onna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132974.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34544" picture="171992.jpg">Iida Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53327" type="appears in" update="2013-03-01">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>France Eiga no Otoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132973.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28471" picture="57632.jpg">Yamamoto Itaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53620" type="appears in" update="2013-03-10">
<rating votes="2">4.56</rating>
<name>Yayoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133443.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4780" picture="28006.jpg">Fujita Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53621" type="appears in" update="2013-03-10">
<rating votes="2">6.23</rating>
<name>Rui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133444.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34544" picture="171992.jpg">Iida Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53871" type="appears in" update="2013-03-15">
<name>Takeo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="13866" picture="43577.jpg">Shiibashi Kazuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53872" type="appears in" update="2014-09-23">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Haruko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>161531.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37003" picture="171788.jpg">Kawakami Chihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53873" type="appears in" update="2013-03-15">
<name>Miki</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="12352" picture="130106.jpg">Hirata Mana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54149" type="appears in" update="2013-03-22">
<rating votes="2">5.07</rating>
<name>Gal</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134057.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34426" picture="128153.jpg">Suzaki Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="146362" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-11</airdate>
<rating votes="16">6.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">やはり俺の青春はまちがっている</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yeah, My Youth Is Seriously Wrong</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yahari Ore no Seishun wa Machigatte Iru</title>
<summary>As we rejoin the Neighbors, we find that, no, they still don`t have any friends. Sena decides to follow Yozora`s lead with a stylish new haircut! Kodaka doesn`t get much studying done during his visit to the Kashiwazaki manor, but he does manage to learn some disturbing facts about Sena…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="146694" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-18</airdate>
<rating votes="14">4.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ホモゲ部</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Homo Game Club</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Homo Ge Bu</title>
<summary>Rika draws from her extensive knowledge of gay erotica to give the Neighbors a crash course on male friendship. Later, Kodaka runs into an oddly familiar-looking lavender-haired nun…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="146718" update="2015-10-25">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-01-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146719" update="2015-10-25">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-01-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146830" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="16">8.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺の妹達がこんなに可愛い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Little Sisters Are This Cute</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore no Imouto-tachi ga Konna ni Kawaii</title>
<summary>Maria runs away from home (with her big sister`s help) and winds up at Kodaka`s place. Later, the Neighbors celebrate the end of finals the only way they know how: awkwardly, with lots of public humiliation!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="146835" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-01</airdate>
<rating votes="15">8.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">この中に1人男がいる!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Man Is Among Them!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kono Naka ni Hitori Otoko ga Iru!</title>
<summary>Yozora and Sena face off in a race to conquer the Black Dragon at Yokoshima Wonderland. Who will prevail?! Later, Yukimura`s shocking secret is revealed!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="147062" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-01</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺の幼なじみが修羅場すぎる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Childhoold Friend Is Too Much of a Battleground</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore no Osananajimi ga Shuraba Sugiru</title>
<summary>The Neighbors Club will be presenting a movie for the school festival, and Yozora`s writing the script! What can we expect? High drama! Steamy boy-on-boy action! Meat! A samurai? Probably a lot of repressed feelings of isolation and self doubt, too!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="147063" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-22</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お兄ちゃんだけど愛さえあれば妹が増えても関係ないよねっ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">He`s My Brother, but As Long As There`s Love, It Doesn`t Matter If He Gets More Sisters, Right?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onii-chan Dakedo Ai Sae Areba Imouto ga Fuete mo Kankeinai yo ne!</title>
<summary>Kobato`s birthday is coming up, and the Neighbors need to get her some presents. Kodaka and Sena find themselves shopping together! Will Sena be able to break down the wall of Kodaka`s obliviousness? Do you really have to ask?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="147064" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-15</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">奇行少女は傷つかない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unbreakable Strange-Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikou Shoujo wa Kizutsukanai</title>
<summary>The school festival is approaching, and the Neighbors will be taking part! Can our intrepid band of oddballs find a way to attract normal people to their booth? Can they stop Rika from scaring away customers?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="147065" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-08</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そんな遊びはいけません!~君がいると世界観が乱れる~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">That Kind of Play Is Not Allowed! My Worldview Is Disturbed When You Are Around</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sonna Asobi wa Ikemasen! Kimi ga Iru to Sekaikan ga Midareru</title>
<summary>Yozora tries her hand at one of Rika`s dating sims, and quickly learns that she doesn`t like virtual people any better than real people. Then, Kodaka tests out Rika`s new time machine!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="147501" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-15</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">残念王と笑えない話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sad-Case King and the Stone-Cold Story</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zannen Ou to Waraenai Hanashi</title>
<summary>Sena refuses to be seen in Yozora`s plagiarized movie, so the Neighbors have to do it over again. High drama! Steamy boy-on-boy action! Meat! A samurai! No, for real this time!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="147502" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-08</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">迷い猫オーバーヒート</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stray Cats Overheat</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mayoi Neko Overheat</title>
<summary>Kodaka meets Yusa Aoi, Sena`s classmate and perpetual runner-up. Someone has tricked this girl into thinking that Kodaka and Sena are happy and well-balanced individuals -- in a committed relationship! Who is responsible? Will this scandal undermine the Neighbors Club`s founding principles of social ineptitude and mutual schmuckery?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="147743" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-29</airdate>
<rating votes="14">5.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">僕は友達が......</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I... Many Friends</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boku wa Tomodachi ga...</title>
<summary>Kodaka`s cowardly flight from the club room has left the Neighbors on the brink of collapse. Will he be lured away by the world of normal kids with real lives, or can Rika save the club with the help of her deadly new weapon?! Hold onto your yaoi holes, it`s time for the final showdown!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="147744" update="2018-01-18">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-22</airdate>
<rating votes="15">7.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">迷えるチキンな俺</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dismay of I, the Chicken</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mayoeru Chicken na Ore</title>
<summary>This week is full of lessons for the Neighbors: There`s no such thing as a "yaoi hole"; little girls can`t actually be nuns; Kodaka really is that much of a putz.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="148664" update="2015-10-25">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-03-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148665" update="2015-10-25">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-03-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148712" update="2013-03-31">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-06-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148713" update="2013-03-31">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-05-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148714" update="2017-11-02">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブラックドラゴン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Black Dragon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148715" update="2018-04-18">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-03-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148871" update="2013-04-04">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148872" update="2013-04-04">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150384" update="2013-05-05">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-12-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">プロモーション映像第2弾!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Promotion Eizou Dai 2 Dan!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150385" update="2013-05-05">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-12-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">番宣CM映像</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 30s</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bansen CM Eizou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150386" update="2018-04-18">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-08-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">プロモーション映像</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Promotion Eizou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155772" update="2013-11-03">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155773" update="2013-11-03">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155774" update="2013-11-03">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155775" update="2013-11-03">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194059" update="2017-12-19">
<epno type="4">T10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194060" update="2017-12-19">
<epno type="4">T17</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 14</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194061" update="2017-12-19">
<epno type="4">T16</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 13</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194062" update="2017-12-19">
<epno type="4">T15</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194063" update="2017-12-19">
<epno type="4">T14</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194064" update="2017-12-19">
<epno type="4">T13</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194065" update="2017-12-19">
<epno type="4">T12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194066" update="2017-12-19">
<epno type="4">T11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194067" update="2018-04-18">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 5</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
