<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9351" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>4</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-07-24</startdate>
<enddate>2013-07-24</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Corpse Party: Tortured Souls - Bougyaku Sareta Tamashii no Jukyou</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">コープスパーティー トーチャードソウルズ -ぼうぎゃくされたたましいのじゅっきょう-</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Вечеринка мёртвых: Плач замученных душ</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Вечеринка мёртвых: Замученные души</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">コープスパーティー Tortured Souls -暴虐された魂の呪叫-</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Corpse Party: Tortured Souls</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9157" type="Prequel">Corpse Party: Missing Footage</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="435866">Bloody hell , and bloody indeed!!
It was interesting , it didn`t have that horror feel , but it had a nice story.
It is good if you don`t have anything else to do or watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="173054">MUST SEE for gore fans. This was quite a display of violence, entrails, and gore. There are no other redeeming qualities of this anime. Watch for the gore. That`s it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="307450">End was good :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="60976">Since game was great I was afraid, that anime may be just poor-made adaptation. It`s not. It has great story based on game, yet so different, so if you played game before you still will be surprised. Only minus - it has only 4 eps...</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://corpse.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="7264" type="Character Design">Tanaka Masaki</name>
<name id="7264" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tanaka Masaki</name>
<name id="34756" type="Original Work">Kedouin Makoto</name>
<name id="9674" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kojima Chika</name>
<name id="1012" type="Animation Work">Asread</name>
<name id="8022" type="Direction">Iwanaga Akira</name>
<name id="30325" type="Music">Hamada Takashi</name>
<name id="34758" type="Music">Hamamoto Mao</name>
</creators>
<description>One rainy night after a school festival, a group of students from Kisaragi Academy decide to perform the Sachiko Ever After charm, which will unite them forever as friends. Once the ritual is done, a sudden earthquake transports them to Heavenly Host, a torn down elementary school. Unbeknownst to Satoshi and his friends, however, is the horrific past behind it which culminated in its demolition. As they look for each other and try to escape from Heavenly Host, they soon find out their lives are at the mercy of those affected by that same bloodied past.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1186">4.46</permanent>
<temporary count="1200">6.24</temporary>
<review count="1">6.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>93956.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14993</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15037</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://corpse.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Corpse_Party</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>コープスパーティー#.E3.82.B3.E3.83.BC.E3.83.97.E3.82.B9.E3.83.91.E3.83.BC.E3.83.86.E3.82.A3.E3.83.BC_Tortured_Souls_-.E6.9A.B4.E8.99.90.E3.81.95.E3.82.8C.E3.81.9F.E9.AD.82.E3.81.AE.E5.91.AA.E5.8F.AB-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>345732</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15844</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2535" parentid="1152" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-18">
<name>ghost</name>
<description>In traditional belief, a ghost is the soul or spirit of a deceased person or animal that can appear, in visible form or other manifestation, to the living. Descriptions of the apparition of ghosts vary widely: The mode of manifestation can range from an invisible presence to translucent or wispy shapes, to realistic, life-like visions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2852" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>thriller</name>
<description>The thriller is a genre of fiction in which tough, resourceful, but essentially ordinary heroes are pitted against villains determined to destroy them, their country, or the stability of the free world. The hero of a typical thriller faces danger alone or in the company of a small band of companions. The protagonist may be a law enforcement agent, a journalist, or a soldier, but typically he or she is cut off from the resources of "their" organization. More often the hero is an ordinary citizen drawn into danger and intrigue by circumstances beyond their control.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214683.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4113" parentid="6347" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-20">
<name>body exchange</name>
<description>Two or more characters swap bodies (or, equally, swap minds).
When this plot is done, usually the voices also switch as narrative cheat to help viewers keep track of who`s who. More subtly, it`s just the eyes. More serious/action-oriented shows might not do this. The Flip often involves characters of different ages, genders, races, or social classes. Another variation is a protagonist and antagonist switching, which usually involves each trying to undermine the other`s organization while simultaneously trying to switch back. If one or both of the characters have superpowers or other special abilities, they`ll have a lot of trouble figuring their new powers out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4257" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>survival</name>
<description>The theme/genre of survival typically depicts the act or process of continuing to live, generally in a hostile, possibly post-apocalyptic environment. Survival-centered media tends to be dark, set most commonly in a contemporary context, and generally leads either to small groups of people forming closely knit and functional units or to individuals turning against their fellows in a return to the survival of the fittest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6347" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>body and host</name>
<description>When a foreign entity like that of a symbiote, body snatcher, puppeteer parasite, or even a hacker (when regarding machines like robots and computers) enters/outright hijacks a body, the possessed subject becomes what is usually called: the host.
The basic purpose of the host varies on what the point was for it to have been hijacked in the first place. Sometimes it`s used as a disguise, other times it`s used as a decoy and destraction, even simply being used as a weapon and piece of armor that the possessor uses to cause sheer chaos and destruction, but sometimes... a host can be used for fetish fuel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7075" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-05-07">
<name>adapted into Japanese movie</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a Japanese movie.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="47949" type="appears in" update="2019-10-21">
<rating votes="2">5.86</rating>
<name>Yoshizawa Ryou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yoshizawa Ryou is one of the three children spirits who roam Heavenly Host Elementary School and the first victim of the murder case that took place in it.</description>
<picture>141685.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7789" picture="34523.jpg">Moriya Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47950" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-21">
<rating votes="15">3.52</rating>
<name>Kishinuma Yoshiki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92691.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47951" type="main character in" update="2019-10-21">
<rating votes="16">6.02</rating>
<name>Nakashima Naomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92690.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47952" type="main character in" update="2019-10-21">
<rating votes="11">6.32</rating>
<name>Mochida Satoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92687.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47953" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-21">
<rating votes="12">4.24</rating>
<name>Mochida Yuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92696.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47954" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-21">
<rating votes="9">2.43</rating>
<name>Morishige Sakutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92695.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="174" picture="41158.jpg">Kakihara Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47955" type="appears in" update="2019-10-21">
<rating votes="6">3.93</rating>
<name>Kanno Yuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kanno Yuki is one of the three children spirits who roam Heavenly Host Elementary School and the third victim of the murder case that took place in it.</description>
<picture>141687.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5663" picture="228631.jpg">Igarashi Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47956" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-21">
<rating votes="18">6.38</rating>
<name>Shinohara Seiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92693.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47957" type="main character in" update="2019-10-21">
<rating votes="18">6.06</rating>
<name>Shinozaki Ayumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92692.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4715" picture="223209.jpg">Imai Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47958" type="appears in" update="2019-10-21">
<rating votes="4">2.86</rating>
<name>Tsuji Tokiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsuji Tokiko is one of the three children spirits who roam Heavenly Host Elementary School and the second victim of the murder case that took place in it.</description>
<picture>141686.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1437" picture="18823.jpg">Oohara Momoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47959" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-21">
<rating votes="11">4.47</rating>
<name>Suzumoto Mayu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92694.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="83" picture="38901.jpg">Nanri Yuuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47973" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-21">
<rating votes="16">6.15</rating>
<name>Shishido Yui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92699.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47975" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-21">
<rating votes="15">4.63</rating>
<name>Shinozaki Sachiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92702.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7" picture="186500.jpg">Ootani Ikue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55182" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-21">
<rating votes="4">5.56</rating>
<name>Kizami Yuuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141464.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58904" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-21">
<rating votes="5">3.97</rating>
<name>Saenoki Naho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141465.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17860" picture="57847.jpg">Yamamoto Ayano</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58905" type="appears in" update="2019-10-21">
<name>Shinozaki Yoshie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shinozaki Yoshie is Sachiko`s mother. She was an Infirmary doctor at Heavenly Host Elementary School.</description>
<picture>142446.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7" picture="186500.jpg">Ootani Ikue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59154" type="appears in" update="2019-10-21">
<name>Yanagihori Yoshikazu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141877.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3797" picture="65487.jpg">Matsuo Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59155" type="appears in" update="2019-10-21">
<name>Nakashima Natsumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mother of Nakashima Naomi.</description>
<picture>142444.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38432" picture="141978.jpg">Oshiyama Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59454" type="appears in" update="2019-10-21">
<name>Yanagihori Takamine</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yanagihori Takamine was the principal of Heavenly Host Elementary School before its demolition.</description>
<picture>142445.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9114" picture="201075.jpg">Kikumoto Taira</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="146856" update="2013-01-19">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-12-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="149809" update="2013-08-04">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2013-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">多重的別離</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Multiple Separation</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Всеобщая разлука</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tajuuteki Betsuri</title>
</episode>
<episode id="149992" update="2013-08-04">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2013-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">哀しき真実</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sorrowful Truth</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Горькая правда</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanashiki Shinjitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="149993" update="2013-08-04">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2013-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">届かぬ想い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unreachable Feelings</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Недостижимые чувства</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Todokanu Omoi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="149994" update="2013-08-04">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2013-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">壊れる蝶番</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hinged Break</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Сорванные петли</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kowareru Choutsugai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152489" update="2013-08-13">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-07-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
