<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9356" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-08-31</startdate>
<enddate>2013-08-31</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gekijouban Ano Hi Mita Hana no Namae o Bokutachi wa Mada Shiranai.</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Anohana Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Gekijouban Anohana</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">劇場版あの日見た花の名前を僕達はまだ知らない.</title>
<title xml:lang="zh" type="official">劇場版 我們仍未知道那天所看見的花名</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">AnoHana: The Flower We Saw That Day: The Movie</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8181" type="Prequel">Ano Hi Mita Hana no Namae o Bokutachi wa Mada Shiranai.</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="6">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="396857">Too much of the movie is recap, and I kind of feel like it doesn`t really deserve anything more than a 6, but I`ll give it a 7 just because it was really nice to finally get to see the gang hang out and just be happy, smile and be good friends again. Their friendship is completely restored at this point, and their depression is cured too. Very heartwarming. Worth the watch just for that alone imo. So the new scenes are definitely great. Just wish the whole movie was new stuff like that, instead of only half of it. Nevertheless, if you`re a fan of the series, you should watch this. It`ll put a smile on your face for sure.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="591695">It has almost been two years since I first watched the series (watched it twice). And I gotta say this made me cry as much as it first did. However I was pretty disappointed that so much of the movie is filled with recap materials. None the less it brought back lots of memories. It is worth watching definitely!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="35309">Worth watching the movie, if you want to know what happened one year after the original series. But much of the material (about 40 minutes) is recap of the original series.
It is also worth to recall what happened in the series. Otherwise, no change. No surprise.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="367685">The movie is half recap of the show and half new material, mostly set after the events of the show. The recap is rather brief and doesn`t quite convey the same emotion the show did, so it doesn`t work so well as a standalone movie, but rather as a sequel. Either way, it still managed to make me cry. Just a little...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="475247">I watched this move day after original series. This is something like backstage of the main story. Great recap with new scenes and shows what happend after 11 episode. Worth watching.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.anohana.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="2210" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tanaka Masayoshi</name>
<name id="24701" type="Music">Remedios</name>
<name id="2188" type="Direction">Nagai Tatsuyuki</name>
<name id="1303" type="Animation Work">A-1 Pictures</name>
<name id="2210" type="Character Design">Tanaka Masayoshi</name>
<name id="51037" type="Original Work">Chou Heiwa Busters</name>
</creators>
<description>Set one year after the events of http://anidb.net/a8181 [Anohana], this film follows each of the protagonists as they meet up once more to reflect upon those events and find the resolve to move on.
Note: The film retells the key events of the Anohana story through flashbacks.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1192">6.99</permanent>
<temporary count="1197">7.36</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>156837.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15154</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15039</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5176</identifier>
<identifier>avuwxe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.anohana.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Anohana:_The_Flower_We_Saw_That_Day</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>あの日見た花の名前を僕達はまだ知らない。</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4672</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>345373</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16240</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18005</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="55" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-11">
<name>awards</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2090" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-17">
<name>trauma</name>
<description>Character with emotional or psychological injury, caused by single or multiple events/experiences in the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2535" parentid="1152" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-18">
<name>ghost</name>
<description>In traditional belief, a ghost is the soul or spirit of a deceased person or animal that can appear, in visible form or other manifestation, to the living. Descriptions of the apparition of ghosts vary widely: The mode of manifestation can range from an invisible presence to translucent or wispy shapes, to realistic, life-like visions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2909" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>karaoke</name>
<description>Obligatory national pastime for students in any anime with school setting. Amateur singing to subtitled music videos.
The word itself is a compound of the Japanese words for "empty orchestra".</description>
<picurl>160894.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3013" parentid="55" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-10">
<name>Newtype Anime Award</name>
<description>This anime has won 1 or more Newtype Anime Award(s)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3992" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-08-17">
<name>nostalgia</name>
<description>A bitter-sweet longing for things, persons, or situations from the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4327" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-18">
<name>be careful what you wish for</name>
<description>Be careful what you wish for... your wish may actually come true. This is an age-old philosophical problem of what human beings think they want and what is actually good for them. The power to wish for anything can be very dangerous and usually — as a moral lesson — yields unexpected / unwanted results.
A contract with the devil is a specific case of this; receiving great power, especially from a devil, is usually a double edged sword.</description>
<picurl>230309.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4477" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-02">
<name>communication with the dead</name>
<description>This character is able of some manner of communication with the dead, or at least with one dead person. This includes talking to the dead, seeing the dead, outright mediumship, or any form of unidirectional or bidirectional form of communication that ordinary characters are not generally able to achieve.
This does not apply in environments where characters are expected to be dead, or where nobody is alive to begin with.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5790" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-30">
<name>family without mother</name>
<description>For some reason, the protagonist`s mother is no longer among the living. The much-too-early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime, and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family. For example: the grief-stricken father and children barely function as humans; the oldest daughter has an extra burden of raising the other children, additional emphasis is given to the only female child in the family, i.e. with bishounen brother and dad in a shoujo setting.
In rare cases the mother may still be alive, just not living with the rest of the family presently, i.e. on some quest or job and gone for a long time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5875" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>jealousy</name>
<description>A character is jealous of another character either due to love, or power, or wealth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5881" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-07">
<name>childhood memory</name>
<description>The childhood memory of one of the protagonists plays an important part as plot device in this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="11140" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-07-12">
<rating votes="267">8.09</rating>
<name>Sebastian Michaelis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sebastian appears to be a youthful male with red-orange eyes and dark brown hair (black in the anime). He is typically dressed in a distinguished outfit consisting of black trousers, tailcoat, vest, tie and shoes with a white botton-down shirt. He wears white gloves that cover up the sign of his Faustian contract with Ciel Phantomhive, which is on his left hand. When they are off, it is shown that he has black fingernails, although it is unknown if this is their natural colour. He frequently carries a pocket watch as well. When in tutor mode, he also wears glasses, although it`s unknown if he actually needs them or not. He slightly resembles Ciel`s father, and has had his attractiveness commented on before.
Sebastian`s demonic form has never fully been shown. Details including high-heeled boots, longer fingernails, slitted pupils and sharper, longer teeth are all that have been revealed. In the anime, he has the ability to transform into a crow, although this has never been said or implied in the manga.
Source: kuroshitsuji.wikia.com</description>
<picture>157980.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="11141" type="cameo appearance in" update="2017-12-31">
<rating votes="109">7.16</rating>
<name>Ciel Phantomhive</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ciel is a young male, whose age is from 12 to 13 throughout the series, with blue eyes and black hair. As the head of the noble Phantomhive family, he typically dresses in a way that suits his standing, including a long jacket, button-down shirt, tie, shorts, knee-high socks and boots. Occasionally, he carries other accessories such as a top hat, white or black gloves and a cane. He also has his ears pierced and frequently wears a one-of-a kind family ring that has been passed down through his family for generations. He nearly always wears an eye patch over his left eye, not because he is missing it, but because that`s where the sign of his Faustian contract with Sebastian Michaelis is hidden.
Occasionally, he wears other outfits, typically because he is undercover, investigating something at Queen Victoria`s request. These outfits have included a dress, when he invaded Aleister Chamber`s home, and pauper`s clothes, when he posed as a servant when joining the Noah`s Ark Circus.
Source: kuroshitsuji.wikia.com</description>
<picture>33143.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="11361" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="99">6.56</rating>
<name>Musubi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Musubi (Sekirei #88) is the main heroine of the series. She met Minato when she literally fell out of the sky while being chases by other Sekirei.
Musubi specializes in hand-to-hand combat which utilizes her greatly enhanced strength, enforced by the heavy combat gloves she always wears. Musubi`s `uniform` consists of a short red skirt and her upper clothes resemble those traditionally worn by a Miko. During periods of anger or jealousy, an image of a ferocious bear appears behind her, which is a result of her being Miya`s disciple. She is quite naive, often saying things she doesn`t understand and is the most "childish" of Minato`s Sekirei, even more so than Kusano, yet at times can be insightful. Musubi is the most "competitive" of Minato`s Sekirei, often showing great eagerness to fight other Sekirei, but never fails to be polite as she would usually ask for permission first before fighting them. She eats a lot and is a fairly decent cook, but she can only cook curry in large amounts. Musubi`s known attacks are the Kuma-ken (Bear Fist) and Kuma-ryusei (Bear Meteor).</description>
<picture>34379.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="11496" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-08-18">
<rating votes="165">8.14</rating>
<name>Tsukiumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsukiumi (Sekirei #09) is a Sekirei with a tsundere personality. She refers to herself as Minato`s "legal wife" and is very possessive of him. The most aggressive of Minato`s Sekirei, Tsukiumi has a very short temper and rarely smiles. She does, however, have an honorable side, and is a strong adherent to the fundamental rule that Sekirei combat is one-on-one. She also goes to great lengths to prevent innocent civilians or bystanders from getting caught up in Sekirei fights.
Tsukiumi has the ability to control and manipulate water, as well as the ability to gather large quantities of water out of the air. Her name literally means "Moon Sea".</description>
<picture>34385.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13559" type="cameo appearance in" update="2017-09-13">
<rating votes="118">6.26</rating>
<name>Takanashi Souta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takanashi Souta is a high school student who was pressed into service at Wagnaria by Taneshima Poplar. Poplar keeps mispronouncing his name as `Katanashi`, and can never seem to say it properly. He is a self-described `minicon`, a person with an obsession with small, cute things such as children, kittens, hamsters, and water fleas, and as such is immediately charmed by the diminutive Taneshima.
Since he is the only boy in a family of five, he wound up wearing many of his sisters` old clothes as a child, and as such harbors deep insecurities about his masculinity. He arguably allows Inami Mahiru to keep hitting him as this works as affirmation for his manhood.</description>
<picture>39732.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13560" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-09-30">
<rating votes="188">7.50</rating>
<name>Taneshima Popura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Taneshima Popura is a waitress at Wagnaria, and the first employee of the odd restaurant that Takanashi meets. While she is a year older than Takanashi (who calls her `senpai`, as she is his upperclassman at the same school), she is very small for her age, and is too weak to perform some of the menial tasks at the restaurant. She does not take kindly to remarks about her small size, even when they are meant to be complimentary.</description>
<picture>39733.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13561" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-06-28">
<rating votes="215">6.19</rating>
<name>Inami Mahiru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Inami Mahiru is a waitress at Wagnaria, who harbors a deep fear of men, and will involuntary hit any man who comes too close to her. She is also freakishly strong despite her willowy appearance. Since Takanashi Souta started working at Wagnaria, she has been hitting him more frequently than others, a risk he takes so he can cure her androphobia.
[SPOILER]It turns out that Inami`s father is to blame for her behavior, since he brainwashed her into fearing all men and placed extra weights in her schoolbags which gradually increased her strength.[/SPOILER]</description>
<picture>39734.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13562" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-07-02">
<rating votes="129">6.53</rating>
<name>Todoroki Yachiyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Todoroki Yachiyo is a waitress at Wagnaria. She has a strange obsession with Kyouko that began when they were children, and will do anything she asks, which usually means making her a parfait or some other food. She will not tolerate anyone who even seems to make advances that may take Kyouko away from her, and will readily threaten someone inopportune enough to do so with her katana, which she carries at all times.
Satou Jun seems to like her, and she seems to like him best among all of her male co-workers, but her obsession with Kyouko makes any progress between them unlikely.</description>
<picture>39735.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13563" type="cameo appearance in" update="2017-09-13">
<rating votes="109">5.91</rating>
<name>Shirafuji Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shirafuji Kyouko is the restaurant manager of Wagnaria. She is almost never seen doing any useful work, except to call on some mysterious people to shake down ruffians who foolishly attempt to leave the restaurant without paying. She is a childhood friend of Todoroki, whom she once saved from bullying, but that seems to have mutated into a strange obsession, but Kyouko seems as oblivious to this as with almost everything else, content to receive Todoroki`s service as it is given.</description>
<picture>39736.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13564" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-07-01">
<rating votes="119">8.31</rating>
<name>Satou Jun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Satou Jun is one of the cooks at Wagnaria. He is usually silent but can be very blunt when he is forced to speak. He has an unrequited love for Todoroki Yachiyo, and is frustrated by the fact that she seems to be warming up to him but will not let go of her obsession with Shirafuji Kyouko. He is also a heavy smoker.</description>
<picture>39737.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13565" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-07-01">
<rating votes="78">4.97</rating>
<name>Souma Hiroomi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Souma Hiroomi works as a cook at Wagnaria. He attempts to find the secrets of everyone he comes into contact with, and does not seem comfortable associating with anyone he cannot dig enough dirt on to blackmail. He has occasionally used his knowledge of many of his co-workers` most intimate secrets to get out of unpleasant chores at the restaurant.</description>
<picture>39738.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="15958" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-07-01">
<rating votes="189">7.88</rating>
<name>Yamada Aoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yamada Aoi is a girl Otoo picked up one day in his travels, and recruited to work at Wagnaria. Not much is known for certain about her, not even that `Yamada Aoi` is actually her real name, which makes Souma nervous. She lives in the attic of the restaurant.</description>
<picture>44881.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="17524" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="354">4.17</rating>
<name>Kousaka Kyousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kousaka Kyousuke is the main protagonist of the series, and acts as the narrator. He is a fairly ordinary second-year high school student who wishes for nothing more than a peaceful life until he accidentally discovers his little sister Kirino`s otaku hobbies. Even though Kirino is mean and disrespectful to him, he tries to be a good elder brother to her, giving her advice as best he can, and helping her to continue in her hobbies and make new friends. He is a responsible and reliable person who cares deeply about the welfare of his sister and of his friends.</description>
<picture>55755.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="17525" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-12-17">
<rating votes="921">4.94</rating>
<name>Kousaka Kirino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kousaka Kirino is the main heroine of the series. She is a 14-year old girl who seems normal on the outside, but is in secret a hardcore otaku obsessed with anime and visual novel eroges, especially those involving little sisters. She works part-time as a model, which is how she managed to purchase her most impressive collection of figurines, visual novels, and anime DVDs. She has a talent for writing, and loves track and field.
She is initially cold and disrespectful towards her brother Kyousuke, but after he discovers her secret hobby and he supports her in it, they gradually grow closer.</description>
<picture>53292.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="17526" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-04-21">
<rating votes="1020">8.54</rating>
<name>Gokou Ruri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kuroneko (a.k.a. Gokou Ruri) was one of the anime otaku girls Kirino had met in a gathering organized by Saori. Though their tastes in anime and games greatly differ, they nevertheless began to be good friends. She also became a good friend to Kyousuke, and it is hinted that she may have feelings for him. As befits the Kuroneko epithet, she is usually seen wearing a black Gothic Lolita-style dress, and is sharp-tongued and antisocial.
She enters Kyousuke`s high school later in the series, and joins the Game Club at his urging, displaying her considerable talents at writing and graphic design.</description>
<picture>55756.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="18152" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-07-13">
<rating votes="22">4.67</rating>
<name>Alois Trancy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2897.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="18153" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-07-13">
<rating votes="14">2.42</rating>
<name>Claude Faustus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2917.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="28414" type="main character in" update="2014-06-18">
<rating votes="58">6.93</rating>
<name>Hisakawa Tetsudou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hisakawa Tetsudou, nicknamed Poppo, is the first friend that Jinta reconnects with. As a child, Poppo was uncontrollably energetic and friendly. These traits have not changed. Presently, Jinta reunited with him when he was searching for Menma. He visited their old clubhouse and found that Poppo was living there. Poppo explains that he works part-time jobs to earn money. When he makes enough, he goes on trips around the world. Because of this, Poppo does not attend high school.
Poppo seems to have questionable interests: Jinta found several pornographic magazines upon entering the clubhouse. Poppo also seems to have an obsession for foreign girls, especially Vietnamese girls. Overall, he has a lewd personality.</description>
<picture>66681.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="465" picture="56019.jpg">Kondou Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28415" type="main character in" update="2014-06-18">
<rating votes="132">7.36</rating>
<name>Anjou Naruko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Anjou Naruko is a childhood friend of Jinta and Menma. While she displays a cold attitude towards Jinta, she is secretly concerned for him. She is perhaps the closest to him at present and is enrolled the same school (although Jinta stopped attending school). Chiriko comments that Naruko has not changed over the years: she is still easily persuaded by everyone around her. Naruko seems to be popular in high school and gets along well with girls that Chiriko deems "sluts."
While they have grown apart, Naruko seems cares deeply about her childhood friends. She works at a video game store and has a large collection of manga and video games herself. Because of this collection, she started reconnecting with Jinta and Poppo.</description>
<picture>66590.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28416" type="main character in" update="2014-06-18">
<rating votes="75">5.63</rating>
<name>Yadomi Jinta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yadomi Jinta is the main character of the series. In the past, Jinta was an energetic, young boy and the leader of his group, the Super Peace Busters. When Naruko asked him if he had a crush on Menma, he said, "Why would I be in love with such an ugly—?" He had plans to apologize to her the next day, but she died later that night in a drowning accident.
Unable to forgive himself, Jinta spent the next years of his life in a constant state of gloominess. He became withdrawn and eventually became a hikikomori, or a shut-in. He currently lives with his father. While he is enrolled at the same high school as Naruko, he stopped attending.</description>
<picture>66591.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="470" picture="17419.jpg">Irino Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28417" type="main character in" update="2015-01-05">
<rating votes="159">6.20</rating>
<name>Honma Meiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Honma Meiko, nicknamed Menma, is a ghost girl who suddenly appears to Jinta several years after her death. Menma asks him to reunite their group of friends so her wish can be granted. She does not seem to remember what is her wish, but she knows she has to reunite her friends in order to remember.
It is hinted that she has feelings for Jinta, and that only Jinta is able to see her.</description>
<picture>66592.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28418" type="main character in" update="2014-06-18">
<rating votes="61">3.13</rating>
<name>Matsuyuki Atsumu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Matsuyuki Atsumu is a childhood friend of Jinta and Menma. In the present, Atsumu holds a condescending attitude towards Jinta. He becomes agitated when Menma is mentioned and is still distraught over her death. He, together with Chiriko, attend the same high school, which Jinta failed the entrance exams to enter. It appears that he is dating Chiriko.</description>
<picture>66589.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28419" type="main character in" update="2014-06-18">
<rating votes="60">5.25</rating>
<name>Tsurumi Chiriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>As a child, Tsurumi Chiriko was a shy girl and a member of the Super Peace Busters. Now, she is enrolled at an elite school with Matsuyuki. She is serious, stoic, and cocky. Upon meeting with Naruko, Chiriko insults both her and her friends. While the other members of the Super Peace Busters have fallen apart, Chiriko and Matsuyuki have remained friends after Menma`s death.</description>
<picture>66588.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30633" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-18">
<rating votes="13">6.78</rating>
<name>Yadomi Jinta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70174.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3712" picture="240126.jpg">Tamura Mutsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30634" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-18">
<rating votes="10">5.17</rating>
<name>Hisakawa Tetsudou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70176.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30635" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-18">
<rating votes="13">5.05</rating>
<name>Matsuyuki Atsumu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70172.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21733" picture="152476.jpg">Seto Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30637" type="appears in" update="2014-06-19">
<rating votes="19">4.93</rating>
<name>Yadomi Atsushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yadomi Atsushi is Jintan`s father.</description>
<picture>70385.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="264" picture="228626.jpg">Ogata Mitsuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30646" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-18">
<rating votes="14">6.09</rating>
<name>Tsurumi Chiriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70173.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30648" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-18">
<rating votes="62">7.29</rating>
<name>Honma Meiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70175.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30652" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-18">
<rating votes="15">6.84</rating>
<name>Anjou Naruko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70171.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31465" type="appears in" update="2014-06-19">
<rating votes="5">3.93</rating>
<name>Naruko no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Naruko`s mother.</description>
<picture>70379.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="31467" type="appears in" update="2014-06-19">
<rating votes="10">3.67</rating>
<name>Honma Irene</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Honma Irene is Menma`s mother.</description>
<picture>70383.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="142" picture="68482.jpg">Ooura Fuyuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31468" type="appears in" update="2014-06-19">
<rating votes="7">6.33</rating>
<name>Honma Satoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Honma Satoshi is Menma`s younger brother.</description>
<picture>70384.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1609" picture="19579.jpg">Mizuhara Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31664" type="appears in" update="2014-06-19">
<rating votes="6">5.24</rating>
<name>Yadomi Touko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yadomi Touko is Jintan`s mother.</description>
<picture>70677.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32806" type="appears in" update="2011-05-27">
<rating votes="2">2.37</rating>
<name>Yama-san</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72378.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="34049" type="appears in" update="2014-06-18">
<rating votes="5">8.27</rating>
<name>Chou Heiwa Busters</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The group Jinta and his friends created together when they were kids.</description>
<picture>156838.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="55012" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-07-19">
<rating votes="79">8.41</rating>
<name>Hachiken Yuugo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hachiken Yuugo is a city boy from Sapporo. After failing to pass the entrance exams for the high school of his preference, Yuugo decided to enroll at Yezo instead, believing that easier academic course would leave him with more time to prepare for college exams. However, the agricultural courses` demand for hard labor proved his assumptions wrong. Due to his father`s strict upbringing, he is somehow unable to refuse when someone needs his help. Despite complaining a lot when he feels people are abusing of his generosity, Yuugo quickly earns the friendship and respect of his peers. Just after enrolling, he joins the Equestrian Club along his classmate Aki, soon rising to the position of vice-president due to his reliable nature. Yuugo is usually anxious about his future as, unlike his classmates who already have set their goals in life, he is still wondering about what career he should choose.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>135315.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="55013" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-07-19">
<rating votes="25">7.91</rating>
<name>Komaba Ichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Komaba Ichirou is one of Yuugo`s close friends and a skilled baseball player, Komaba dreams of becoming a professional ball player so he can use the money he earns in the league to improve his family`s dairy farm. He is also Aki`s childhood friend and neighbour, and their closeness is a constant source of jealousy for Yuugo. However, once Komaba`s family goes bankrupt and their farm is sold to pay their debt, he is forced to quit Yezo and look for a job to make ends meet.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>135317.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="55015" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-07-19">
<rating votes="31">6.63</rating>
<name>Inada Tamako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Inada Tamako is a rich classmate of Yuugo whose family runs a huge industrial farm. Usually an obese girl, under the extra fat she hides a quite beautiful figure that reveals itself occasionally when she works too hard or gets herself into a quick diet. However she feels too weak when she is thinner thus it does not take much time for her to regain all the weight she had previously lost.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>135319.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="55017" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-07-19">
<rating votes="66">5.74</rating>
<name>Mikage Aki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mikage Aki is a first year who is also a member of the Equestrian Club and Yuugo`s love interest. She is studying to inherit her family business, a cow and horse farm specialising in raising Ban`ei race horses. Aki usually has a cheerful and positive attitude and she eventually develops feelings for Yuugo, leading to them start dating. Her father is very protective and was wary of her relationship with Yuugo at first, but some time later starts seeing him as a man worthy of becoming her husband, just like the rest of her family. Once her family goes into difficulties and is forced to sell all their horses, Aki, encouraged by Yuugo, expresses her will to not inherit the farm and become a professional jockey instead. Thus she starts studying to enter college with his help. Another curious trait of Aki`s is that she is so enthusiastic about horses that she can easily memorise every fact related to them, thus Yuugo makes use of it to help with her studies.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>135316.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="56105" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-06-21">
<rating votes="23">7.34</rating>
<name>Yoshino Mayumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138822.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="148608" update="2013-10-25">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>100</length>
<airdate>2013-08-31</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156635" update="2013-12-10">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158927" update="2014-04-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-08-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160351" update="2014-06-04">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-03-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ノンクレジットオープニング(スペシャルO.A ver.)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Non-credit Opening (Special O.A Ver.)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Non-credit Opening (Special O.A Ver.)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160352" update="2014-06-04">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM (13 min)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
