<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9358" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-01-07</startdate>
<enddate>2013-03-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Amnesia</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">アムネシア</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Амнезия</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">AMNESIA</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Amnesia</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">암네시아</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">失忆症</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9186" approval="4" total="4">Karneval (2013)</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="99271">A very, very confusing story. I still have to say it was great and interesting, I couldn`t stop watching until the end. Not everyone can stand the thought of not knowing things until the end though, so if you`re one of those people then it`s probably not for you. ;)</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.anime-amnesia.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="982" type="Animation Work">Brain`s Base</name>
<name id="17732" type="Character Design">Yoshikawa Maho</name>
<name id="1921" type="Direction">Oohashi Yoshimitsu</name>
<name id="24131" type="Original Work">Otomate</name>
<name id="8977" type="Music">Dewa Yoshiaki</name>
<name id="17732" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yoshikawa Maho</name>
<name id="677" type="Series Composition">Machida Touko</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a romance adventure game by the same name for female players .
August 1st. The http://anidb.net/ch50665 [Shujinkou] regains consciousness in an unfamiliar cafe, with no memories of her past. Where is this place? What was she doing here? Who and what kind of life did she live?
A boy named http://anidb.net/ch50287 [Orion] appears before her, calling himself a fairy. Under his direction, Shujinkou gropingly searches for clues about her past self. She eventually meets people that know her: a childhood friend, a senior, and a lover.
~ translated and adapted from official site by Cranston</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="988">2.36</permanent>
<temporary count="1005">5.17</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>130397.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14811</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20655</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>15085</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5229</identifier>
<identifier>ttpvpz</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.anime-amnesia.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Amnesia_(visual_novel)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>AMNESIA</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2861</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>344533</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15689</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7803</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>amnesia</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="780" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-23">
<name>fairy</name>
<description>A fairy is a type of mythical being or legendary creature in European folklore, a form of spirit, often described as metaphysical, supernatural, or preternatural.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>206567.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1179" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-21">
<name>indecisive</name>
<description>This character has trouble taking their own decisions, and may rely on others to do that instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2072" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>maid</name>
<description>A maid is a female employed in domestic service. They usually wear uniforms. Since their nature is to be obedient and serve their goshujin-sama (master), they are one of the most desired types of women in Japan, a dream of every Japanese man, particularly http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku]. Often seen in so-called Maid Cafes in Akihabara, where male customers can for a little time enjoy the feeling of being served by a woman. The male gender opposite is the butler.</description>
<picurl>4954.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2488" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>multiple personality disorder</name>
<description>Multiple personality disorder is a psychiatric diagnosis that describes a condition in which a single person displays multiple distinct identities or personalities (known as alter egos or alters), each with its own pattern of perceiving and interacting with the environment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2667" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>university</name>
<description>Since college/university students are typically at least eighteen years old, with stories covering mature everyday life topics, you will find the college setting quite often in seinen and josei anime.
Topics that can now be covered - as compared to High School settings - are higher education (i.e. coping with higher intellectual stress), the more adult party life (i.e. alcohol, smoking, sex), the issues of daily life vs. studying - especially when having to work to pay for bills, and finally the possible friction between those in and out of college.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2788" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-21">
<name>confession</name>
<description>Someone confesses his/her love to someone else.</description>
<picurl>160903.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2792" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>reverse harem</name>
<description>Reverse harem, or sometimes also male harem, is the common name for the gender-reversed version of the usual http://anidb.net/t2859 [harem genre]. In a reverse harem, instead of the usual situation with several female characters focused on one male character, the viewer sees several male characters surrounding a single female character. Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. The most notable exception is that, due to the most relevant characteristics of the trope`s fan base, reverse harem authors tend to go for http://anidb.net/t1760 [bishounen] looks. Though they are also exceptions to the common harem genre, harems with homosexual relationships are not covered by reverse harem.</description>
<picurl>126787.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3265" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-09">
<name>death is cheap</name>
<description>Important characters will have a terrible tendency to die dramatically, but will not, under any circumstances, stay dead. This tends to cheapen the dramatic death of a character to the point of being little more than a flesh wound if overused. If you ever hear passing mention of any form of afterlife in a series, be warned that the value of "dead" has become a whole lot less all of a sudden. Similarly, if the entire supporting cast is being killed off left and right, expect a resurrection by the end of the current arc. This trope became so common in some series that most people are more likely to be shocked if a character does not come back from the dead than when it does.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4009" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-20">
<name>unresolved romance</name>
<description>At the end of the series the main character — even though involved in one or more romances — does not choose and thus resolve the situation.
Usually emotionally very disappointing for the viewer.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4499" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-07-28">
<name>some weird shit goin` on</name>
<description>Scenes of this show point to insanely strange events which seem to be taking place; throughout its episodes, the show may or may not explain what is going on. Either way, many viewers will find that a succinct and accurate way to describe the show is "WTF?", and the show`s explanations (or lack thereof) to the events will often be subject of heated debate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5188" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-02-08">
<name>inconclusive romantic plot</name>
<description>This tag refers to unresolved romance in a series. It`s common in harem anime, but may also appear in normal romance series (especially if they are incomplete adaptations of novels or manga).
The protagonist doesn`t choose any of his love interests in the end and doesn`t dump any of them either. This tag does not refer to those (few) series where protagonist actually chooses all the girls on his own accord (i.e. Sekirei).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5593" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-13">
<name>branching story</name>
<description>The whole series consists of alternative stories, starting at the same point, branching off to different endings. It is like a normal dating sim, where you have different choices to meet different girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5789" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-05-02">
<name>back to square one</name>
<description>The story returns to its starting point (or another situation) once or even multiple times. Possible causes for this might be amnesia or time travel.
This sometimes leads to the repetition of certain events (like in the "Endless Eight" episodes in Suzumiya Haruhi no Yuutsu (2009)).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5882" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>secret identity</name>
<description>The (usually main) protagonist has a secret identity that he or she desperately tries to keep secret.
This can lead to all sorts of amusing misunderstandings, thus is used as comedy element in some anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6115" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-02">
<name>omimai</name>
<description>Visiting a sick person (as in a hospital or at home).
The protagonist or any other character caught a cold so his friends go visit him. In a school setting this is used as a plot device to allow fellow students to show their concern, and it is also a pertinent excuse to get out of school.</description>
<picurl>160896.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="49087" type="main character in" update="2012-11-02">
<rating votes="14">3.84</rating>
<name>Shin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>127566.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="174" picture="41158.jpg">Kakihara Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49088" type="main character in" update="2012-11-02">
<rating votes="12">2.50</rating>
<name>Toma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>127567.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49089" type="main character in" update="2012-11-02">
<rating votes="14">2.59</rating>
<name>Ikki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>127564.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="181" picture="171560.jpg">Taniyama Kishou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49090" type="main character in" update="2012-11-02">
<rating votes="12">3.32</rating>
<name>Ukyou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>127568.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="689" picture="170354.jpg">Miyata Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49091" type="main character in" update="2012-11-02">
<rating votes="13">3.52</rating>
<name>Kent</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>127565.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50287" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-11-02">
<rating votes="7">2.20</rating>
<name>Orion</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>127569.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5663" picture="228631.jpg">Igarashi Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50665" type="main character in" update="2012-11-30">
<rating votes="19">2.43</rating>
<name>Shujinkou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128804.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50969" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-11-30">
<rating votes="6">3.58</rating>
<name>Mine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128806.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5605" picture="29786.jpg">Akutsu Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50970" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-11-30">
<rating votes="4">4.07</rating>
<name>Waka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128808.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12637" picture="130507.jpg">Takahashi Hidenori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50971" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-11-30">
<rating votes="5">4.20</rating>
<name>Sawa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128805.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7789" picture="34523.jpg">Moriya Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50972" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-11-30">
<rating votes="6">2.18</rating>
<name>Rika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128807.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5641" picture="228630.jpg">Yoshida Seiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53566" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-08">
<rating votes="6">1.41</rating>
<name>Ikki Fan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Three crazy girls from Ikki`s fanclub. They are constanly angry becase the heroine is close to Ikki so they are doing various horrible things to her.
Seiyuu:
Ikki`s Fan 1 (イッキファン1):http://anidb.net/cr34225 [Narumi Kyouko]
Ikki`s Fan 2 (イッキファン2):http://anidb.net/cr34875 [Iizuka Mayu]
Ikki`s Fan 3 (イッキファン3):http://anidb.net/cr31783 [Marutsuka Kana]</description>
<picture>133313.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31783" picture="157185.jpg">Marutsuka Kana</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="34875" picture="157016.jpg">Iizuka Mayu</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="34225" picture="127053.jpg">Narumi Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="146356" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-07</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
<summary>The Heroine wakes up on august 1st, with no memories of who she is or where she`s been.  A mysterious boy named "Orion" appears before her, calling himself a "Spirit."  With his help, she starts to put back together the pieces of her life and keep the people around her from finding out that she`s lost her memories."
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617437</identifier>
<identifier>amnesia</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146641" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-28</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
<summary>The staff of Meido no Hitsuji decides to have a fireworks party, during which Shin finally tells Heroine the truth of her accident. He also reveals a story of his own past that she was not expecting.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617443</identifier>
<identifier>amnesia</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146642" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-21</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
<summary>Shin has figured out that Heroine has lost her memory.  He attempts to jog her memory by taking her to familiar places and talking about their relationship.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617441</identifier>
<identifier>amnesia</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146643" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-14</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
<summary>Orion tells Heroine to keep her memory lost a secret as she doesn’t know who to trust.  At the restaurant a firework, sparks part of her memory with some disturbing news.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617439</identifier>
<identifier>amnesia</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146644" update="2013-01-08">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-01-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146645" update="2013-01-08">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-01-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147093" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
<summary>Toma has been taking care of Heroine after she has passed out.  Toma has continued to take care of her after a series of unknown threats.  To lighten the mood they go shopping together and not long Heroine is approached by three angered girls.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617451</identifier>
<identifier>amnesia</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147094" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
<summary>Heroine suddenly appears outside her apartment, and receives a text message from Kent, who says to meet up at the café. Heroine is confused by the conversation she has with Kent but plays along the best she can.  Later at the café Kent figures out she has lost her memory.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617449</identifier>
<identifier>amnesia</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147095" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-11</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
<summary>Heroine doesn`t know which Ikki’s personality is real, and she meets a man that advises her watch her back.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617447</identifier>
<identifier>amnesia</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147096" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-04</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
<summary>Heroine is confused on why she was sent back in time.  Orion appears before trying to explain but disappears before she is able to understand.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617445</identifier>
<identifier>amnesia</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147471" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12</title>
<summary>The evil Ukyo goal is to kill Heroine, as she runs for her life a battle wages inside of Ukyo.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617459</identifier>
<identifier>amnesia</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147472" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-18</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11</title>
<summary>Ukyo is claiming to be Heroine’s lover, and he warns her that the world is trying to kill her.   But can Ukyo be trusted when he is…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617457</identifier>
<identifier>amnesia</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147473" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-11</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
<summary>The Heroine makes it home; she opens her diary to read…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617455</identifier>
<identifier>amnesia</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147474" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-04</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
<summary>The Heroine makes it home; she opens her diary to read…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617453</identifier>
<identifier>amnesia</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148623" update="2013-03-26">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending - ep12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155244" update="2014-05-28">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
<episode id="182241" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617847</identifier>
<identifier>amnesia</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
