<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9376" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-10-28</startdate>
<enddate>2016-10-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kono Sekai no Katasumi ni</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">In a Corner of This World</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">To All the Corners of the World</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="synonym">V koutě našeho světa</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">この世界の片隅に</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">In This Corner of the World</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">In this Corner of the World</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Dans un recoin de ce monde</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">In questo angolo di mondo</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">En este rincón del mundo</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="official">Dünyanın Bu Köşesinde</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14233" type="Alternative Setting">Kono Sekai no (Sara ni Ikutsumo no) Katasumi ni</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="332" approval="16" total="16">Hotaru no Haka</anime>
<anime id="3630" approval="4" total="4">Ushiro no Shoumen Daare</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://www.konosekai.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="31375" type="Animation Work">MAPPA</name>
<name id="219" type="Direction">Katabuchi Sunao</name>
<name id="39868" type="Original Work">Kouno Fumiyo</name>
<name id="1466" type="Character Design">Matsubara Hidenori</name>
<name id="39547" type="Music">Kotringo</name>
</creators>
<description>Newly-wed http://anidb.net/ch84018 [Urano Suzu] moves to her new life in Kure City on the coast of Hiroshima Prefecture, where she perseveres through World War II with pluck and determination.
Note: The movie premiered at Tokyo International Film Festival 2016. Regular cinematic release started on November 12.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="610">8.97</permanent>
<temporary count="613">8.13</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221325.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17177</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15227</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.konosekai.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.inthiscornermovie.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>In_This_Corner_of_the_World_(film)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>この世界の片隅に_(映画)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4859</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>348641</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19867</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>konosekai_movie</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20439</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="55" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-11">
<name>awards</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2691" parentid="2641" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-12-21">
<name>World War II</name>
<description>World War II, or the Second World War (often abbreviated WWII or WW2), was a global military conflict which involved most of the world`s nations, including all great powers, organised into two opposing military alliances: the Allies and the Axis. The war involved the mobilisation of over 100 million military personnel, making it the most widespread war in history. In a state of "total war," the major participants placed their entire economic, industrial, and scientific capabilities at the service of the war effort, erasing the distinction between civilian and military resources. Over seventy million people, the majority civilians, were killed, making it the deadliest conflict in human history.
The start of the war is generally held to be September 1, 1939, with the invasion of Poland by Nazi Germany and subsequent declarations of war on Germany by most of the countries in the British Empire and Commonwealth, and by France. Many countries were already at war before this date, such as Ethiopia and Italy in the Second Italo-Abyssinian War and China and Japan in the Second Sino-Japanese War. Many who were not initially involved joined the war later, as a result of events such as the German invasion of the Soviet Union, the attacks on Pearl Harbor and British colonies, and subsequent declarations of war on Japan by the United States, the Netherlands, and British Commonwealth.
In 1945, the war ended in a victory for the Allies. The Soviet Union and the United States subsequently emerged as the world`s superpowers, setting the stage for the Cold War which continued for the next 46 years. The United Nations was formed in the hope of preventing another world conflict. The acceptance of the principle of self-determination accelerated decolonization movements in Asia and Africa, while Western Europe itself began moving toward integration.
------
About the picture
Top left: Battle of Wuhan
Top right: Second Battle of El Alamein
Middle left: Battle of Stalingrad
Middle right: German dive bombers over Eastern Front winter 1943-1944
Bottom left: Wilhelm Keitel signing German Instrument of Surrender
Bottom right: Invasion of Lingayen Gulf</description>
<picurl>40430.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3013" parentid="55" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-10">
<name>Newtype Anime Award</name>
<description>This anime has won 1 or more Newtype Anime Award(s)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4224" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into JDrama</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a JDrama.
A JDrama (Japanese drama), also called "terebi dorama" ("television drama") or "dorama" for short, is a Japanese live action television series.
Japan produces many drama series every year, from a huge variety of genres. Like anime, they generally air in three-month seasons or multiples thereof, with new shows airing every season. Some kinds of drama, especially the morning or afternoon ones, tend to be broadcast daily, while evening ones tend to be broadcast weekly, also like anime.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4277" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-30">
<name>nuclear weapons</name>
<description>A nuclear weapon is an explosive device that derives its destructive force from nuclear reactions, which release vast quantities of energy from relatively small amounts of matter. Nuclear weapons are considered weapons of mass destruction, and their use and control have been a major focus of international relations policy since their debut.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5111" parentid="2672" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Hiroshima</name>
<description>Hiroshima Prefecture is a prefecture of Japan located in the Chuugoku region on Honshu island. The capital is the city of Hiroshima.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214291.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6350" parentid="55" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-21">
<name>Oofuji Noburou Award</name>
<description>The Oofuji Noburou Award is an animation award given to a group or individual at the Mainichi Film Awards to recognise animation excellence. It is named after Japanese animator http://anidb.net/cr5602 [Oofuji Noburou].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6358" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-03-18">
<name>crowdfunded</name>
<description>This anime was funded, at least partially, through a campaign on a crowdfunding website (e.g. Kickstarter, Makuake).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="84018" type="main character in" update="2017-06-08">
<rating votes="7">10.00</rating>
<name>Houjou Suzu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203721.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46702" picture="190397.jpg">Non</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84019" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-06-08">
<name>Urano Sumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203729.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27977" picture="76416.jpg">Han Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84020" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-06-08">
<name>Houjou San</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203726.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="485" picture="223410.jpg">Shintani Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84021" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-06-08">
<name>Houjou Entarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203725.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4185" picture="224827.jpg">Ushiyama Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84022" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-06-08">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Houjou Shuusaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203722.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3709" picture="84359.jpg">Hosoya Yoshimasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84023" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-06-08">
<name>Mizuhara Tetsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203727.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84024" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-06-08">
<name>Shiraki Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203728.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40608" picture="159215.jpg">Iwai Nanase</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84025" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-06-08">
<name>Kuromura Harumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203724.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41452" picture="164784.jpg">Inaba Natsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89837" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-06-08">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Kuromura Keiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203723.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46703" picture="190398.jpg">Omi Minori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89838" type="appears in" update="2017-06-08">
<name>Urano Juurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203730.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="267" picture="25729.jpg">Koyama Tsuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89839" type="appears in" update="2017-06-08">
<name>Urano Kiseno</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203731.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23492" picture="64272.jpg">Tsuda Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89840" type="appears in" update="2017-06-08">
<name>Morita Ito</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203732.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34" picture="240893.jpg">Kyouda Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89841" type="appears in" update="2017-06-08">
<name>Kobayashi no Oji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203733.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="270" picture="25681.jpg">Sasaki Nozomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89842" type="appears in" update="2017-06-08">
<name>Kobayashi no Oba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203734.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17052" picture="234928.jpg">Shiota Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89843" type="appears in" update="2017-06-08">
<name>Chita-san</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203735.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38809" picture="146234.jpg">Seta Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89844" type="appears in" update="2017-06-08">
<name>Kariya-san</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203736.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="50509" picture="203738.jpg">Tachibana Kotone</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89845" type="appears in" update="2017-06-08">
<name>Doumoto-san</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203737.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42130" picture="167355.jpg">Semi Kikuyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106953" type="appears in" update="2019-11-12">
<name>Bakemon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241149.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106954" type="appears in" update="2019-11-12">
<name>Marina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241150.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31968" picture="85813.jpg">Meguro Mina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106955" type="appears in" update="2019-11-12">
<name>Chizuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241157.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55768" picture="228598.jpg">Ikeda Yuine</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106956" type="appears in" update="2019-11-12">
<name>Urano Youichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241151.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55766" picture="220696.jpg">Oomori Kanata</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="179386" update="2018-11-07">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>130</length>
<airdate>2016-10-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="192626" update="2017-11-05">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2016-10-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="192627" update="2017-11-05">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">パイロットフィルム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pilot Film</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pilot Film</title>
</episode>
<episode id="192628" update="2017-11-05">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>6</length>
<rating votes="1">3.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">冬の記憶</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Memory of Winter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuyu no Kioku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208482" update="2018-09-23">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">『この世界の片隅に』観客180万人を超えて主人公・すずさんからのありがとう.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Suzu-san`s Thanks</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Kono Sekai no Katasumi ni" Kankyaku 180-mannin o Koete Shujinkou Suzu-san kara no Arigatou.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208483" update="2018-09-23">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">劇場予告編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Theatre Trailer (1:57)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekijou Yokokuhen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208484" update="2018-09-23">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">特報</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV (1:25)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokuhou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208485" update="2018-09-23">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Spot 1 (0:15)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208486" update="2018-09-23">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Spot 2 (0:30)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208487" update="2018-09-23">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Spot 3 (0:15)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208492" update="2018-09-23">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2017-09-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アニメーション映画『この世界の片隅に』制作風景 原画篇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Making of: Key Animation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Animation Eiga "Kono Sekai no Katasumi ni" Seisaku Fuukei: Genga Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208493" update="2018-09-23">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2017-09-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アニメーション映画『この世界の片隅に』制作風景 背景篇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Making of: Photography</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Animation Eiga "Kono Sekai no Katasumi ni" Seisaku Fuukei: Haikei Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208494" update="2018-09-23">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>2017-09-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">旅のはじまり ~映画『この世界の片隅に』制作準備の日々~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Making of: Beginning of the Journey</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tabi no Hajimari: Eiga "Kono Sekai no Katasumi ni" Seisaku Junbi no Hibi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208495" update="2018-09-23">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2017-09-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">練馬アニメカーニバル2015 映画『この世界の片隅に』公開まであと1年! 記念トークイベント</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nerima Anime Carnival 2015 One Year Till Premiere Talk Event</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nerima Anime Carnival 2015 Eiga "Kono Sekai no Katasumi ni" Koukai made Ato Ichinen! Kinen Talk Event</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208496" update="2018-09-23">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-09-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">『この世界の片隅に』息を吹き込むアフレコの現場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Making of: Dubbing</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Kono Sekai no Katasumi ni" Iki o Fukikomu Af-Reco no Genba</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208497" update="2018-09-23">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>2017-09-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">『この世界の片隅に』公開記念! ネタバレ爆発とことんトーク!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Premiere Commemoration Spoiler-Filled Talk Show</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Kono Sekai no Katasumi ni" Koukai Kinen! Netabare Bakuhatsu Tokuton Talk!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208498" update="2018-09-23">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">呉市立美術館 マンガとアニメで見る こうの史代この世界の片隅に展</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kure Municipal Art Museum Exhibition</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kure Shiritsu Bijutsukan Manga to Anime de Miru: Kouno Fumiyo Kono Sekai no Katasumi ni Ten</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208499" update="2018-09-23">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2017-09-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">劇場舞台挨拶集 公開初日舞台挨拶 / 公開二日目舞台挨拶 / 100万人突破ありがとう! 大ヒット御礼舞台挨拶 / 祝! 日本アカデミー賞最優秀アニメーション作品賞受賞 大ヒット御礼舞台挨拶</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Theatre Stage Thank You Compilation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekijou Butai Aisatsu Shuu: Koukai Shonichi Butai Aisatsu / Koukai Futsuka Me Butai Aisatsu / 100-mannin Toppa Arigatou! Dai Hit Orei Butai Aisatsu / Iwai! Nihon Academy Shou Saiyuushuu Animation Sakuhin Shou Shushou Dai Hit Orei Butai Aisatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208500" update="2018-09-23">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-09-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">『この世界の片隅に』ライブ付プレミア試写会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Live Premiere Screening Event</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Kono Sekai no Katasumi ni" Live-zuke Premiere Shishakai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208501" update="2018-09-23">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>2017-09-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アニメーション映画『この世界の片隅に』オリジナルサウンドトラック発売記念 スペシャルライブ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Original Soundtrack Release Commemoration Special Live Concert</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Animation Eiga "Kono Sekai no Katasumi ni" Original Soundtrack Hatsubai Kinen Special Live</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208502" update="2018-09-23">
<epno type="2">S14</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2017-09-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">のん, すずさんになる.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Interviewing Non</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Non, Suzu-san ni Naru.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209543" update="2018-10-22">
<epno type="2">S15</epno>
<length>6</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Untypeset Scene Collection</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209544" update="2018-10-22">
<epno type="2">S16</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-10-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening Scenes</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209545" update="2018-10-24">
<epno type="2">S17</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2016-10-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Crowdfunding Backer Credits</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
