<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9384" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-07-06</startdate>
<enddate>2013-07-06</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gekijouban Gintama Kanketsuhen: Yorozuya yo Eien Nare</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Gintama: The Movie: The Final Chapter: Be Forever Odd Jobs</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="synonym">Gintama Movie 2</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Сребърна душа: Краят - Йородзуя завинаги</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Gintama: Kanketsu-hen - Yorozuya yo Eien Nare</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">劇場版 銀魂 完結篇 万事屋よ永遠なれ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Gintama: The Movie: The Final Chapter: Be Forever Yorozuya</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Gintama - The Movie 2 - Das letzte Kapitel: Für immer die Alles-Agentur</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Гинтама: Финальная глава - Йородзуя навсегда</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">银魂剧场版 完结篇 永远的万事屋</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="11249" type="Side Story">Gintama x Mameshiba</anime>
<anime id="9427" type="Parent Story">Gintama` (2012)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="17">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="126877">Great "conclusion" for an anime that i have been watching for years. Makes me sad that it is done (yes i believe this is not a troll, been waiting for more than half a year for a new episode) but at least they still have the manga. A must watch for fans. As for non-fans, start with the anime season first to see if this anime is for you, if you`re Japanese or into Japanese culture you will find it entertaining.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="732962">loved it...it`s funny.sad and exciting a must watch..but see the series before you watch this movie..one of my favorite animes..</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="30718">a must see</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="241883">A good movie, pushes the right `Gintama` buttons without trolling us altogether...!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="471779">Three words for this movie: BEST ENDING EVER</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="319919">I refuse to accept this as an ending. WE WANT MORE GINTAMA MOREEEEEE</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="328481">This is not happening...I`m not gonna accept this is over NO!!!!!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="325320">absolute perfect mixture of humor, randomness AND epic characters, GINTAMA FOREVERRRRRRR</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="471611">well do i even need to say anything stop wasting time here and go watch it</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="371670">As expected, Gintama movie did not disappoint - pure awesomeness. :D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="501819">Pure Epicness, Gintama for Eternity</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="572928">this is Gintama for damn sake!!! 
you dont need any reason to watch its already the awesomess anime ever created!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="615924">the best anime ever!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://wwws.warnerbros.co.jp/gintama/</url>
<creators>
<name id="6124" type="Original Work">Sorachi Hideaki</name>
<name id="24337" type="Direction">Fujita Youichi</name>
<name id="726" type="Animation Work">Sunrise</name>
<name id="1911" type="Character Design">Takeuchi Shinji</name>
<name id="1911" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takeuchi Shinji</name>
<name id="10808" type="Music">Audio Highs</name>
</creators>
<description>While watching a movie, http://anidb.net/ch1162 [Gintoki] comes upon a "http://anidb.net/ch62582 [movie thief]," a figure in Japanese culture often depicted as a man with a video camera as a head. After scolding the movie thief for his actions, he finds himself warped into another world via the camera lens. In this world, 5 years have passed, and not only has the land of Edo changed into an apocalyptic wasteland, but http://anidb.net/ch56491 [Kagura] has changed into a beautiful woman with no Chinese speech pattern, http://anidb.net/ch56490 [Shinpachi] has turned into a cool samurai who is not a tsukkomi anymore, and the Gintoki of this time has gone missing, though he is assumed to be dead. http://anidb.net/ch89655 [Gintoki] is determined to find out the truth of the deadly sickness that is ravaging Edo, and also to understand the feelings of Kagura and Shinpachi, who have been trying to deal with their leader`s disappearance.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1519">9.32</permanent>
<temporary count="1540">8.56</temporary>
<review count="2">9.83</review>
</ratings>
<picture>226660.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14996</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15335</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://wwws.warnerbros.co.jp/gintama/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Gintama:_The_Movie:_The_Final_Chapter:_Be_Forever_Yorozuya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>劇場版_銀魂_完結篇_万事屋よ永遠なれ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>345075</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16225</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1589" parentid="2622" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-08">
<name>samurai</name>
<picurl>244341.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2906" parentid="2846" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>nanomachines</name>
<description>The anime features sub-microscopic (nano = 10E-9 = one billionth) machines, machines that float in the bloodstream and affect the human body. They can be used both for good (repairing human cells in situ) or for evil (nano-machine warfare, attacking human cells in situ).</description>
<picurl>183210.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5863" parentid="2798" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-06">
<name>Weekly Shounen Jump</name>
<description>The Weekly Shounen Jump is a Japanese manga magazine released on a weekly basis. Its main target audience consists of young males and it features several manga titles. The magazine was created by http://anidb.net/cr780 [Shueisha] in July, 1968, and was originally only called Shounen Jump, because it was not published every week at the time. A number of very famous shounen manga were or are published in it, such as http://anidb.net/a386 [Hokuto no Ken], http://anidb.net/a231 [Dragon Ball], http://anidb.net/a942 [City Hunter], http://anidb.net/a826 [Saint Seiya], http://anidb.net/a590 [Slam Dunk], http://anidb.net/a312 [Yuu Yuu Hakushou], http://anidb.net/a69 [One Piece], http://anidb.net/a239 [Naruto], http://anidb.net/a2369 [Bleach], http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], http://anidb.net/a3468 [Gintama], to name a few of the most well-known.</description>
<picurl>66685.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1162" type="main character in" update="2013-06-01">
<rating votes="1891">9.23</rating>
<name>Sakata Gintoki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakata Gintoki is the main character of the story. He has naturally permed hair, which he blames for his lack of a love-life. He rides a motor scooter and wields a bokuto, which has "Lake Touya" inscribed on it. His job, as is written on his business card, is a "free-lancer", meaning he`ll take any job for nearly any price. He enjoys reading http://anidb.net/cr5372 [Shounen Jump] comics and he has a sweet tooth and will go into crazed combat if he does not have his sweets (he has glycosuria).
In the past, he was a Joui (someone who attempted to overthrow Amanto to protect the government). The reason Gintoki does not join http://anidb.net/ch1165 [Katsura Kotarou] again to fight the aliens is that he does not like to fight alongside "gloomy terrorists".</description>
<picture>137509.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1165" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-08">
<rating votes="389">8.67</rating>
<name>Katsura Kotarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Katsura is Gintoki`s former comrade during the Joi war. Even after the Amanto take-over of Japan, Katsura continues to resist the Amanto, and has amassed a band of followers. His weapon of choice is a metallic grenade. He is a wanted man due to his involvement in terrorist activities against the Bakufu, and is constantly on the run from the Shinsengumi.
[spoiler="Very late Gintama spoiler."]Although his initial methods were originally more violent in nature (for instance, sending a bomb to an Amanto embassy), Katsura has gradually grown to believe that there are people important to him in Edo, and decides that he no longer wants to destroy the country, but believes there should be a way to change it without causing sacrifices.[/spoiler]</description>
<picture>29351.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1166" type="appears in" update="2012-08-31">
<rating votes="130">7.53</rating>
<name>Elizabeth</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Elizabeth resembles a giant white duck or a giant penguin and is Katsura`s companion. Elizabeth was a present from Tatsuma Sakamoto, who presumably picked it up on his travels around space. Although many people consider Elizabeth to be insane and extraneous, Katsura has named the ambiguous avian "Elizabeth" and dotes on it. While it appears to be just one being, Shinpachi purchased a doll named Space Alien Stefan to which looks perfectly similar to Elizabeth. Elizabeth is something of a painter, and is surprisingly dexterous. Also, Elizabeth resorts to using signboards to "communicate", as well as an occasional means of attack. Elizabeth is also a skilled fighter, able to use signboards to fight off swordsmen.</description>
<picture>29348.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1168" type="appears in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="325">8.66</rating>
<name>Okita Sougo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Okita is the best swordsman in the Shinsengumi. Personality-wise, he tends to be light-hearted and somewhat childish, not entirely unlike Kagura, though his speech is heavily deadpan. The rest of his character can be inferred from the following conversation between Kondou and Hijikata: Kondou asks Hijikata to stop Okita "before he becomes a sadist", Hijikata responds with "No, it`s too late. He`s the King of the Planet of Sadists".</description>
<picture>29352.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="191" picture="17006.jpg">Suzumura Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1169" type="appears in" update="2010-04-20">
<rating votes="192">5.76</rating>
<name>Shimura Tae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Despite her sweet face, she is one of the most violent characters in Gin Tama (and arguably strongest too). She mercilessly beats up Kondo Isao and Gintoki whenever they anger her; in episode 19, she mercilessly kicks the men out onto the road (namely her brother, Gintoki, Hasegawa and Sadaharu) so as to stop a car for a hitch ride. She often displays her trademark sweet-looking smile with her eyes closed before engaging in her violent activities. Her killer intent is so strong that on one occasion, a stare from her brings the entire Shinsengumi on their knees begging for mercy. Her weapon of choice seems to be a naginata, a Japanese spear.</description>
<picture>29354.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="271" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1650" type="appears in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="160">6.49</rating>
<name>Sarutobi Ayame</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A female ninja nicknamed Sacchan, supposedly from the Oniwabanshuu. She is severely short-sighted and often loses her glasses to hilarious - or disastrous - effect. She met Gintoki when she fell through his roof. When she tried to convince him that he had inappropriate relations with her, he briefly played along despite knowing that she was lying to get his help. Ever since that incident, she has become infatuated with him, much to his exasperation. Her feelings for him seem to be encouraged, as she enjoys being put down and threatened by him, due to her extreme masochism. Her attacks are mostly based on natto and bondage. She often follows Gintoki and the rest of Yorozuya around much to his knowledge, throwing objects at her to come out when he needs her help. She cannot stand Zenzo Hattori, her former Oniwaban comrade, and has "attacked" him at his "weak point" (his haemorrhoids) by shoving in an enormous syringe, wooden barbecue stick and a candle.</description>
<picture>16192.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1653" type="appears in" update="2008-12-28">
<rating votes="113">6.02</rating>
<name>Otose</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gintoki`s landlady. He swore to protect her when he ate food offerings to her dead husband. Her real name is Ayano Terada, Ms. Otose being a "genji" alias. She was very pretty when she was young and worked at a restaurant. She secretly fed poor children dumplings for free, and was fired. She is a smoker. Despite constant arguments over Gintoki`s general inability to pay his rent, she is confident in his defence of her.</description>
<picture>16195.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3368" picture="132584.jpg">Kujira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1654" type="appears in" update="2008-12-27">
<rating votes="66">1.93</rating>
<name>Catherine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An amanto who resembles a cat. At first, she seems to be a diligent worker at Otose`s snack shop who is trying to support her family, but soon reveals herself to be a thief.</description>
<picture>16196.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="372" picture="141584.jpg">Sugimoto Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1655" type="appears in" update="2008-12-28">
<rating votes="259">8.17</rating>
<name>Hasegawa Taizou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hasegawa used to be an official working for the Bakufu, but after an unfortunate incident with Amanto dignitary Prince Hata, whom he was assigned to serve and protect, his superior asked him to succumb to his shame and commit seppuku, hearing which he ran away from his quarters. He initially believed that humans should focus on appeasing the Amanto, but after his encounter with Gintoki, his mindset changed, which led to him punching Hata out, thus getting fired. Since then, he has been living a life of somewhat like a loser, getting fired almost every time he gets a new job, mostly due to the unfavourable look his sunglasses and goatee give him. No matter what, he refuses to remove his sunglasses because it`s the only thing he had left to remind him of his successful past. Although he does exchange the sunglasses for a decent pair of half-moon spectacles at one point, he goes back to wearing them after he decides that he is going to live out his life in the best way he can. He is constantly seen working various part-time jobs.</description>
<picture>16197.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32" picture="16618.jpg">Tachiki Fumihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1656" type="appears in" update="2008-12-28">
<rating votes="110">8.47</rating>
<name>Sadaharu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sadaharu has the outward appearance of a giant dog, but is actually an inugami. He was originally owned by a pair of miko sisters (Ane and Mone). His inugami powers are awakened if he consumes both strawberries and milk at the same time. He was named by Kagura, after her first pet, a rabbit which she accidentally killed while having a nightmare. When sitting on his haunches, he is taller than most humans. He was left in front of Gintoki`s apartment in a box that had "To Mr. Freelancer" written on it. Sadaharu chomps on anything smaller than itself, such as Gintoki`s and other people`s heads. Kagura seems to be the only one who can control him, for she has immense strength, though he chomps on her occasionally. Though he was dangerous when Gintoki first received him, he has become quite tame in the later episodes. He even obeys Gintoki at certain points, and has helped the main characters in many occasions. After a certain period of time, even Gintoki (who originally did not want Sadaharu around) refused to abandon Sadaharu or give him back to the miko sisters.
Recently, Sadaharu has impressed a yakuza`s boss and receives permission to date his dog (whom Sadaharu himself has fallen in love for).</description>
<picture>16198.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="216" picture="171983.jpg">Takahashi Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1658" type="appears in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="70">7.07</rating>
<name>Yamazaki Sagaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yamazaki is a spy, whose speciality is naturally gathering intelligence. Yamazaki is often caught by Hijikata playing badminton by himself, and he is subsequently beaten. He is often seen cosplaying as a badminton-playing version of Echizen Ryoma from The Prince of Tennis.</description>
<picture>16200.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="378" picture="46436.jpg">Oota Tetsuharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1662" type="appears in" update="2008-12-28">
<rating votes="121">7.38</rating>
<name>Takasugi Shinsuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A former comrade of Gintoki and Katsura, and a major antagonist. He now leads a radical Joui faction called the Kiheitai and is known amongst the Shinsengumi as `the most dangerous man in both the Joui faction and amongst the radicals`. He is easily recognisable through his bandaged left eye, his colourful kimono, his eerie smile, and the pipe he is often seen smoking.
He, Gintoki, and Katsura studied in the same temple elementary school when they were children, and he fought with them against the Amanto invasion during the latter part of the Joui war. After the war ended, he vanished, and has since gained a dangerous reputation due to his assassination of many of the Bakufu`s main officers and his planning of a large-scale coup d`état. Before his first appearance in both the anime and the manga, he was mentioned to have fled Edo and to have been hiding in Kyoto, although it is unclear how long before this was.</description>
<picture>16204.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1667" type="appears in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="132">6.58</rating>
<name>Yagyuu Kyuubee</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kyuubee is an aristocratic young lady who was brought up as a male in order to succeed her family`s clan. She dresses and behaves like a boy due to her upbringing, but occasionally shows her more feminine side. She was close friends with Otae when they were children (and is in fact in love with her), and lost her left eye protecting her when they were young. As a result of this incident, Kyuubee now wears an eye-patch across her left eye. The incident also left her with the determination to make herself stronger, and for many years she was training hard to improve her skills.</description>
<picture>16210.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1668" type="appears in" update="2010-05-03">
<rating votes="35">3.51</rating>
<name>Toujou Ayumu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Toujou Ayumu is http://anidb.net/ch1667 [Kyuubee]`s servant, who is extremely dedicated, if not obsessive, in his concern for his young master. He generally speaks in a very polite (original Japanese dub) manner, using -masu and -desu instead of the short dictionary forms usually employed in a normal male-speech. He addresses http://anidb.net/ch1667 [Kyuubee] as waka, which means young master, and has for years kept a diary recording http://anidb.net/ch1667 [Kyuubee]`s activities. http://anidb.net/ch1667 [Kyuubee] is usually indifferent to Toujou`s excessive attention, although she did kick him when he commented that gothic lolita clothes would suit her. Toujou`s eyes are normally closed unless he is surprised or under emotional distress. If his eyes do open, the whites of his eyes are actually black, and his pupils either glow with an unearthly green, blue or red. He has an obsession with beating a raw, unbroken egg yolk on his rice for meals (as shown when the egg yolk broke, and him going into a berserk rage quite uncharacteristic with his usual demeanour).</description>
<picture>16211.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1674" type="appears in" update="2008-12-28">
<rating votes="68">6.30</rating>
<name>Sakamoto Tatsuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakamoto is a former member of the Joi. He is a good-natured man and optimistic to the point of being ridiculous, even in the most dangerous situations. His favorite phrase is "AHAHA! It must be _____". He also has a tendency to misspell names; he calls Gintoki "Kintoki". Gintoki often corrects him, citing that if he were named Kintoki, kin means gold (because `Kin` from `Kintoki` instead of `Gin` would make the title `Kintama`, which means `testicles` instead of `Gin Tama`, which means `silver soul`).
Despite his goofy nature, Sakamoto is actually a successful businessman in the galaxy. He believes that business is a way of protecting his country. He has a private, well-equipped defensive business fleet. He believes that sacrifices should be made for the good of the community, which is why he chose to abandon his comrades on Earth to travel into space. Sakamoto is shown to be skilled with a pistol in an anime episode. His name is based on the historical character Sakamoto Ryoma.</description>
<picture>16216.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1678" type="appears in" update="2019-12-14">
<rating votes="51">2.74</rating>
<name>Hiraga Gengai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiraga Gengai is Kabuki District`s greatest mechanic. He is a grey-bearded almost-bald person who wears goggles.
His son`s death left him with a deep emotional scar, and Takasugi took advantage of that and used him. He makes ugly and crude machines and has a bad habit of telling important parts-of-a-messages later, which usually gets Gintoki mutilated. Now he is seen making machines and fixing Gintoki`s bike.</description>
<picture>16220.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="199" picture="23218.jpg">Shimada Bin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7827" type="appears in" update="2012-01-26">
<rating votes="123">7.69</rating>
<name>Tama</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>80557.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="186" picture="16999.jpg">Minami Omi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10426" type="appears in" update="2012-01-26">
<rating votes="3">7.19</rating>
<name>Musashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A homeless man who wears large glasses and an orange cap without pants. He seems to have many talents, including badminton. He`s very similar to Hasegawa in that they are both often seen doing various oddjobs. Musashi has the eyes of a Samurai. Despite looking completely different otherwise, he is sometimes mistaken for Gintoki due to their similar hairstyles. In the credits, he`s usually listed as "Musashi-like" person.</description>
<picture>80593.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="377" picture="17223.jpg">Sakaguchi Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11731" type="appears in" update="2012-01-26">
<rating votes="467">8.76</rating>
<name>Tsukuyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>80564.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="160" picture="30490.jpg">Kaida Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19496" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-06-14">
<rating votes="72">7.09</rating>
<name>Toriko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Gourmet Hunter with an abnormally large appetite (A food serving for 500 people could only get him 1/10 full). He is known as one of the "Four Heavenly Kings", and his nickname is "The Glutton". Despite having a huge appetite and massive power, he doesn`t indiscriminately kill and eat any animal; he only kills those animals he decides to eat. He has immunity to seventy different poisons, created by injecting himself with a near fatal dose of each poison and causing his body to create antibodies. He also has an animal-like sense of smell. He has adopted the Battle Wolf`s new born pup and named it Terry Cloth. Like the other Kings, Toriko started of as a chain animal.</description>
<picture>73363.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="56490" type="main character in" update="2013-06-01">
<rating votes="3">8.03</rating>
<name>Shimura Shinpachi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>137508.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="336" picture="17172.jpg">Sakaguchi Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56491" type="main character in" update="2013-06-01">
<rating votes="21">8.14</rating>
<name>Kagura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>137510.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57112" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-11">
<rating votes="3">8.66</rating>
<name>Katsura Kotarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138363.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57113" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-11">
<rating votes="6">8.20</rating>
<name>Hijikata Toushirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138364.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="259" picture="17082.jpg">Nakai Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57114" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-11">
<rating votes="1">7.75</rating>
<name>Kondou Isao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138365.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="375" picture="17221.jpg">Chiba Susumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57116" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-11">
<rating votes="5">7.31</rating>
<name>Okita Sougo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138367.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="191" picture="17006.jpg">Suzumura Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62581" type="appears in" update="2013-12-24">
<name>Enmi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="560" picture="41051.jpg">Isobe Tsutomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62582" type="appears in" update="2017-05-30">
<rating votes="1">2.14</rating>
<name>Jikan Dorobou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The time bandit, responsible to take Gintoki into the future.</description>
<picture>203211.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="380" picture="158572.jpg">Yamadera Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87829" type="appears in" update="2017-02-20">
<name>Catherine</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Male version of http://anidb.net/ch1654 [Catherine] in Dekobokko Arc.</description>
<picture>198580.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="372" picture="141584.jpg">Sugimoto Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89653" type="appears in" update="2017-05-30">
<name>Elizabeth</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Elizabeth from the alternate timeline where Gintoki had died five years prior.</description>
<picture>203207.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="406" picture="186436.jpg">Kamiya Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89654" type="appears in" update="2017-05-30">
<name>Catherine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Catherine from the alternate timeline in which Gintoki died five years prior.</description>
<picture>203208.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="372" picture="141584.jpg">Sugimoto Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89655" type="main character in" update="2017-05-30">
<rating votes="2">9.32</rating>
<name>Chinpou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Due to time travelling rules, Gintoki cannot appear as himself. The time bandit is taking care of this by providing this appearance, Chinpou - or Chin-san.</description>
<picture>203209.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="148870" update="2015-02-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>110</length>
<airdate>2013-07-06</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156025" update="2013-11-16">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="166563" update="2015-02-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>55</length>
<airdate>2013-07-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="166564" update="2015-02-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>55</length>
<airdate>2013-07-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="179367" update="2016-08-07">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>95</length>
<airdate>2013-07-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">「劇場版銀魂 完結篇 万事屋よ永遠なれ」公開直前スペシャル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special Movie Report</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Gekijouban Gintama Kanketsuhen Yorozuya yo Eien Nare" Koukai Chokuzen Special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="179370" update="2016-08-07">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>150</length>
<airdate>2013-06-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">劇場版 銀魂 銀幕前夜祭り 2013</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gintama the Movie: Silver Screen Eve Festival (2013)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekijouban Gintama: Ginmaku Zenya Matsuri (2013)</title>
<summary>Features clip where Yorozuya discusses 8 years of Gintama, live dubbing performance by the series` seiyuu to clips from Gintama (2006) and Gintama`: Enchousen (2012), live band performances and more.</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
