<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9390" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>5</episodecount>
<startdate>2012-08-31</startdate>
<enddate>2012-12-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kyousougiga (2012)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Capital Craze Comic (2012)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Kyousogiga (2012)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">京騒戯画 (2012)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Kyousougiga (2012)</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8300" type="Sequel">Kyousougiga</anime>
<anime id="9992" type="Full Story">Kyousougiga (2013)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="306093">It`s a shame that the episodes are only 10 min long . nevertheless i enjoys every second of it ..
recommend to try it</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="493280">Recomened show off of an anime</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.kyousogiga.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="10890" type="Character Design">Hayashi Yuuki</name>
<name id="1834" type="Animation Work">Toei Animation</name>
<name id="2808" type="Original Work">Toudou Izumi</name>
<name id="27956" type="Music">Shiina Gou</name>
<name id="19313" type="Direction">Matsumoto Rie</name>
</creators>
<description>Three kids are stuck in a strange city causing massive mayhem through the land. They are searching for an atypical rabbit in order to return home. Koto, the eldest of the three, seems to have some sort of connection to this weird place ruled by a monk, a demon, and a priest.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="645">5.81</permanent>
<temporary count="645">6.70</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>93019.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14964</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15359</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5238</identifier>
<identifier>wnejwj</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/sp/kyousogiga/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>京騒戯画</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2384</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>347161</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="204" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-06-19">
<name>violent</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2769" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>hyperspace mallet</name>
<description>It comes from nowhere, it strikes without mercy, and disappears again. It`s a mallet the size of a circus sledgehammer, and it`s evidence that anime characters watch too many Bugs Bunny cartoons or Three Stooges shorts. An angry character — usually but not restricted to short-tempered schoolgirls — can often whip out a massive hammer with which to slam the target (and cause) of her ire.
In Fan Fic circles, the notional storage place for mallets when not in use is known as hammerspace or malletspace.
A recent variation is to have the character pull out a http://anidb.net/t1662 [harisen], a huge folded fan made out of paper or metal, a.k.a. the Paper Fan of Doom, and smack them with that. This is usually less painful-looking than the mallet, unless she uses it to deliver a Megaton Punch.
Ironically, this is now a Dead Horse Trope in the West, where it originated; modern Western examples are typically from shows invoking anime, which has added its own touches to the mix, or from homages to Warner Brothers cartoons.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>10253.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3934" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-10">
<name>non-linear</name>
<description>The story is told achronologically.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4280" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-02">
<name>surreal</name>
<description>Refers to things or occurrences that are generally bizarre or dreamlike, with the relentless capability of replacing reality through the eyes of the beholder. Surrealism is boundless, limited only by thought itself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="36009" type="main character in" update="2011-08-27">
<rating votes="39">8.20</rating>
<name>Koto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49693.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36010" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-27">
<rating votes="36">8.32</rating>
<name>Koto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49705.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36011" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-27">
<rating votes="13">5.93</rating>
<name>Myoue</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49710.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="191" picture="17006.jpg">Suzumura Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36012" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-27">
<rating votes="19">5.39</rating>
<name>Shouko Hakase</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49711.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36013" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-27">
<rating votes="17">5.60</rating>
<name>Yase</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49692.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36014" type="appears in" update="2011-08-27">
<rating votes="2">3.09</rating>
<name>Bishamaru</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49712.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="36016" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-10-07">
<rating votes="13">4.41</rating>
<name>Kurama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49734.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2218" picture="226178.jpg">Nakahara Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36115" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-19">
<rating votes="10">4.64</rating>
<name>A</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A is Koto`s little brother and Un`s twin brother.</description>
<picture>80209.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="268" picture="17093.jpg">Hidaka Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36116" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-19">
<rating votes="10">4.06</rating>
<name>Un</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Un is Koto`s little brother and A`s twin brother.</description>
<picture>80210.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="208" picture="20458.jpg">Shiraishi Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39507" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-19">
<rating votes="6">3.11</rating>
<name>Gejigeji</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Stuffed orange thing hanging on Koto`s hammer.</description>
<picture>80212.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="283" picture="17113.jpg">Yao Kazuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39508" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-19">
<rating votes="10">4.05</rating>
<name>Fushimi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>80205.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2796" picture="23212.jpg">Takemoto Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39509" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-19">
<rating votes="4">2.46</rating>
<name>Pakupaku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Stuffed pink rabbit hanging on Koto`s hammer.</description>
<picture>80213.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23500" picture="237150.jpg">Harashima Akari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48308" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-09-05">
<rating votes="9">4.18</rating>
<name>Inari</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142503.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58148" type="appears in" update="2013-12-14">
<rating votes="2">5.06</rating>
<name>Guuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147142.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="62311" type="appears in" update="2013-12-14">
<rating votes="2">5.06</rating>
<name>Guuji no Sokkin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147147.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="62318" type="appears in" update="2013-12-14">
<rating votes="2">8.13</rating>
<name>Yakushimaru (Myoue Youshou)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147139.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="142281" update="2012-10-30">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2012-08-31</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コト, 主人公かく語りき</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Koto, Our Heroine, Spake Thusly</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koto, Shujinkou Kaku Katariki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="142282" update="2015-08-29">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2012-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ショーコ, 科学者慌て窮す</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shouko, the Scientist, Raves and Panics</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shouko, Kagakusha Awate Kyuusu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="142283" update="2015-08-29">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2012-11-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">八瀬, 妖怪鏡都通信</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yase, the Youkai Looking Glass Report</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yase, Youkai Kyouto Tsuushin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="142284" update="2015-08-29">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2012-12-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">明恵, 坊主かく語りき</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Myoue, The Monk, Spake Thusly</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Myoue, Bouzu Kaku Katariki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="142285" update="2015-08-29">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2012-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">古都, 黒兎回想録</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Koto, The Black Rabbit, Reflects</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koto, Kuro Usagi Kaisouroku</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
