<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9398" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-04-05</startdate>
<enddate>2013-06-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hyakka Ryouran: Samurai Bride</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Samurai Girls 2</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="synonym">Samurai Girls 2: Samurai Bride</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">백화요란 사무라이 브라이드</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Hyakka Ryouran 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">百花繚乱 サムライブライド</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Samurai Bride</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">百花缭乱 SAMURAI BRIDE</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="10765" type="Sequel">Hyakka Ryouran: Samurai After</anime>
<anime id="7440" type="Prequel">Hyakka Ryouran: Samurai Girls</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="733904">Hell yeah, samurai and ecchi.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.hyakka-ryoran.tv/</url>
<creators>
<name id="10106" type="Music">Katou Tatsuya</name>
<name id="3072" type="Character Design">Miyazawa Tsutomu</name>
<name id="3661" type="Series Composition">Nishizono Satoru</name>
<name id="771" type="Work">Arms</name>
<name id="16109" type="Original Work">Suzuki Akira</name>
<name id="35417" type="Direction">Kobun</name>
<name id="3072" type="Chief Animation Direction">Miyazawa Tsutomu</name>
</creators>
<description>A malevolent being resurrects four warriors to do his bidding: the Dark Samurai. http://anidb.net/ch19205 [Yagyuu Muneakira] returns to the Yagyuu Dojo to find it has been turned into a maid cafe to pay the bills.
The Dark Samurai arrive at the dojo, defeat everyone, and seal Muneakira`s abilities. They vow to return in a month to fight http://anidb.net/ch19204 [Yagyuu Juubee] in her top condition.
The girls of Yagyuu Dojo investigate the legendary Samurai Bride, which they believe can defeat the Dark Samurai.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1070">3.38</permanent>
<temporary count="1084">5.96</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>131272.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14997</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15377</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>19255</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.hyakka-ryoran.tv/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Hyakka_Ryōran_Samurai_Girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>百花繚乱_SAMURAI_GIRLS</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2930</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>345309</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15927</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>samurai-bride</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="382" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-11">
<name>warrior</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2072" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>maid</name>
<description>A maid is a female employed in domestic service. They usually wear uniforms. Since their nature is to be obedient and serve their goshujin-sama (master), they are one of the most desired types of women in Japan, a dream of every Japanese man, particularly http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku]. Often seen in so-called Maid Cafes in Akihabara, where male customers can for a little time enjoy the feeling of being served by a woman. The male gender opposite is the butler.</description>
<picurl>4954.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2467" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-22">
<name>sword</name>
<description>A sword is a long, edged piece of metal, used as a cutting, thrusting, and clubbing weapon in many civilizations throughout the world. Before firearms became commonplace, and fast enough to render other weapons pointless in the battlefield, they were the main kind of weapon for war and duels alike. A sword fundamentally consists of a blade and a hilt, typically with one or two edges for striking and cutting, and a point for thrusting. That aside, however, they may come in all sorts of designs: the medieval European swords used to be big, heavy weapons that did not actually cut but instead broke the enemy`s bones under their armor; conversely, the Chinese jian sword (called "ken" in Japanese) attempted to exploit the armor`s joints and perforate the enemy`s flesh in those places, but was useless against the armor itself, and did not take the strikes, preferring to redirect them, to this day being considered a highly "circular" weapon and associated to taijiquan; on the other hand, the Japanese katana was a balanced all-purposes weapon that could be used even in an axe-like way, but which a master swordsman could use in many other, more elaborate manners.</description>
<picurl>127113.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2828" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-26">
<name>borderline porn</name>
<description>Breaks the bounds of "excessive fanservice".
While the physical interactions and dialogue between characters may be extremely sexual, the most sexual situations do *not* have sex itself take place.
Specifically descriptive of containing all the plentiful features of (excessive) fanservice in addition to the interactions between characters being quite sexual — at most, sexual in NATURE only. This means physical touching such as groping, molesting, or bondage will focus primarily on the revealed (i.e. nude) upper portion of the body or through/over clothing on the lower half of the body. This is all WITHOUT actual sex acts (penetration, etc.) taking place.</description>
<picurl>214855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3750" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-08">
<name>thick line animation</name>
<description>The characters are drawn with a thicker outline than is usually seen in anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3981" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-11-27">
<name>ninja maid</name>
<description>This is an old tag for anime which had characters that were maids and also ninjas, or at least able to use ninjutsu. The tag will be removed once all maids in question are properly tagged. See also the http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=animelist&amp;do.search=Search&amp;ctags.include=ninja,maid [list of anime with characters tagged ninja and maid] and the http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=animelist&amp;do.search=Search&amp;ctags.include=ninjutsu,maid [list of anime with characters tagged ninjutsu and maid].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4348" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-04">
<name>wafuku -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is set to be split and deleted. Please tag all relevant characters from the tagged shows with http://anidb.net/t7076 [the appropriate wafuku tags] and then delete this tag from the corresponding anime. Thank you very much.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4564" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-06-01">
<name>spirits</name>
<description>Spirits will appear throughout this anime. These will often be depicted as small orbs of glowing light, or transparent images of the deceased.
Not to be mistaken with "I see dead people", these spirits will usually appear at the location of their departure when the characters have gotten close to the truth surrounding their death. Or as plot element, when a spirit will often stay close to a character as a sort of "Guardian Angel". Although they are never actually seen, their presence is sometimes felt.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5943" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-14">
<name>misunderstanding</name>
<description>Suggests that a large portion of storyline revolves around a rather large misunderstanding between two or more characters, usually forming long lasting situations of separation or hostility between all those involved.
A large portion of the story may be dedicated to gradually working all parties into a mutual understanding to true intentions or changes of heart.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6083" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>master-servant relationship</name>
<description>To some genres, this would suggest a genuine pairing where one person exists to serve another person, such as in some action/dramas where the pair becomes united by destiny as partners — fighting or battles between different pairs/partners will usually be a dominant part of the story.
In other genres, this suggests a relationship where one person may be occupied as or even forcefully treated as a servant or slave to the other who designates themself the master — these services usually apply anywhere from tsundere/romantic-comedies to ecchi or to the more extreme in hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="19199" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="59">6.34</rating>
<name>Charles de d`Artagnan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl who came from France and wields two enormous double-edged swords (claymores) to fight.
She`s bound to the student council president Tokugawa Yoshihiko by a half-forced master and servant relationship.
As an assassin on Tokugawa`s side and unable to disobey him, she challenges Muneakira and his friends to fight.</description>
<picture>131576.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19200" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="77">7.08</rating>
<name>Gotou Matabee</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A beautiful and tall girl, follower of Yukimura. Being a master of the spear, she`s nicknamed "Matabei of the Spear".
She swings a long spear bigger than her own height in a splendid fighting performance, but she`s usually a silent person and doesn`t start conversations.
For some reason, she seems to have a special disposition.</description>
<picture>131577.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19201" type="main character in" update="2011-11-29">
<rating votes="78">7.78</rating>
<name>Tokugawa Sen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The vice president of the student council and the younger sister of http://anidb.net/ch19202 [Tokugawa Yoshihiko], the student council president who supervises the "Buou Private Academy". Although she`s the daughter of the Tokugawa family because she`s a master with the naginata she often goes off to the battle. She also feels interested in http://anidb.net/ch19205 [Muneakira], her childhood friend, but she`s in the age where she can`t be honest with herself.</description>
<picture>2697.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1798" picture="20493.jpg">Kotobuki Minako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19202" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-29">
<rating votes="23">1.68</rating>
<name>Tokugawa Yoshihiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch19201 [Sen]`s older brother, president of the Student Council, and head of the Tokugawa Shogunate. He believes that he is doing the best for his country, while in reality he is a ruthless tyrant with a tendency to use and discard people, including his own sister.</description>
<picture>2690.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19203" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="60">6.13</rating>
<name>Hattori Hanzou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The member of the discipline committee of the student council. http://anidb.net/ch19205 [Muneakira]`s classmate, she`s also the class representative and scolds a lot. She a kunoichi who wears a combat uniform similar to maid clothes and leads the discipline committee battle unit "Hattori Shinobi Troops" consisting only of females.
She serves http://anidb.net/ch19201 [Senhime] but seems to harbor a dubious feeling for her that goes over the master and servant relationship...</description>
<picture>2698.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="355" picture="71573.jpg">Gotou Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19204" type="main character in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="91">8.39</rating>
<name>Yagyuu Juubee</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Suddenly, a beautiful girl came falling naked from the sky. Without previous memory and calling herself "Yagyuu Jubei", still naked approached http://anidb.net/ch19205 [Muneakira] calling him "Onii-chan" (Big brother) with spontaneous Imouto-chara (little sister characterization). However, triggered by a certain event, another "Jubei" personality awakened releasing innumerable dreadful secret techniques. Her outward appearance is (around) of a high school student.</description>
<picture>2696.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19205" type="main character in" update="2011-11-29">
<rating votes="53">3.08</rating>
<name>Yagyuu Muneakira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The protagonist of the story.
A high school student enrolled in the "Buou Private Academy".
As the successor for the Yagyuu family that has been serving as sword instructor for the family of Tokugawa Shoguns for over 400 years, he is the assistant instructor of the "Yagyuu Training Hall" with more than 100 disciples.
Indecisive but gentle with anyone and sometimes carries the strength to fear nothing. Sixteen years old.</description>
<picture>2693.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="99" picture="139554.jpg">Hirakawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19206" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-01">
<rating votes="61">6.81</rating>
<name>Yagyuu Gisen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A mysterious girl who transferred to http://anidb.net/ch19205 [Muneakira]`s class.
On their first meeting, she proposed to Muneakira: "Make me... Muneakira-sama`s slave." After that, she tries to seduce Muneakira by every means and her extremely dangerous behaviour stands out.
She seems to know Muneakira very well but Muneakira is disturbed for not remembering anything about her.</description>
<picture>2689.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1609" picture="19579.jpg">Mizuhara Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19207" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="78">7.34</rating>
<name>Naoe Kanetsugu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A transfer student in the first grade of the Buou Private Academy`s Middle School section. "To believe in love and fight for love`s sake...", she seems to be a self-appointed Warrior of Love. However, her clumsiness stands out. Unaware of the plot from the chief secretary Matsudaira Takamori, she challenges Muneakira who was branded as a villain.
She can swing a large hammer bigger than her own height to fight and is a user of the "Naoe-style hammer fighting techniques", that despite how it looks, it`s an extremely bold fighting style.
She`s a childhood friend of Yukimura and they seem to have a very close connection.</description>
<picture>131575.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19208" type="main character in" update="2019-11-05">
<rating votes="86">6.49</rating>
<name>Sanada Yukimura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The child strategist with both wisdom and courage who carries the name of the ancient swordsman and general and is the leader of the Toyotomi Faction with http://anidb.net/ch19200 [Gotou Matabei], the beautiful girl who uses spears.
In battle, swings the huge iron-ribbed fans for both attack and defense.
Loli, tsundere, tsurupeta, sukumizu, etc. In a way, a thirteen year old middle school student equipped with the strongest weapons without regrets.</description>
<picture>2700.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51642" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="8">5.36</rating>
<name>Sarutobi Sasuke</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sasuke is Yukimura`s pet monkey. She is very fond of Jubei who can speak Monkey. She gains the ability to become human when she accidentally kisses Muneakira and becomes his Fourth Master Samurai. In human form she has long blonde hair and is partially covered in fur. She changes back into a monkey when she is tired. Despite her rivalry with Kanetsugu, she is shown to care deeply for Kanetsugu to the point of sacrificing herself to protect Kanetsugu.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>131569.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18198" picture="228672.jpg">Akasaki Chinatsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51643" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="13">6.61</rating>
<name>Miyamoto Musashi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>131565.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51644" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="12">5.41</rating>
<name>Sasaki Kojirou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>131566.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="252" picture="149852.jpg">Shindou Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51645" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="14">6.07</rating>
<name>Araki Mataemon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>131567.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51646" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-31">
<rating votes="17">6.35</rating>
<name>Houzouin Inshun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>131568.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="162" picture="23208.jpg">Satou Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51647" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="42">6.11</rating>
<name>Maeda Keiji</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Maeda Keiji is a wandering samurai who hates men. She is a master of Qi, a master of disguise and also wields an umbrella in battle. As a childhood friend of Kanetsugu, Keiji has taken her appearance to initially teach the girls how to use Qi. She likes to touch other girls breasts to compare their size and to determine who has the greatest. Her method of choice for long-distance transport is by motorcycle. She was nicknamed "Maedake" by Jubei.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>131564.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55069" type="appears in" update="2015-09-07">
<rating votes="9">6.00</rating>
<name>Sarutobi Sasuke</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>[B]Sasuke[/b] is Yukimura`s pet monkey. She is very fond of Jubei who can speak Monkey. She gains the ability to become human when she accidentally kisses Muneakira and becomes his Fourth Master Samurai. In human form she has long blonde hair and is partially covered in fur. She changes back into a monkey when she is tired. Despite her rivalry with Kanetsugu, she is shown to care deeply for Kanetsugu to the point of sacrificing herself to protect Kanetsugu.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>135340.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18198" picture="228672.jpg">Akasaki Chinatsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57418" type="appears in" update="2013-06-23">
<rating votes="10">6.11</rating>
<name>Yagyuu Juubee</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138928.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="148774" update="2019-05-26">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-04-26</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">将の花嫁</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Samurai Bride</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shou no Hanayome</title>
<summary>Gisen returns looking for work, at least in appearance only. Her true plan gets underway immediately as she pits the girls against each other to see who will become the Samurai Bride.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622403</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-bride</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148775" update="2019-05-26">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-04-19</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛と忠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love and Kiss</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai to Chuu</title>
<summary>Investigation time! After a heated battle with one of the resurrected samurai, Kanetsugu goes on a fact finding mission of utmost importance.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622401</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-bride</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148776" update="2019-05-26">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-04-12</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">忠, ふたたび</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kiss Again</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chuu, Futatabi</title>
<summary>There`s a panties thief on the loose! Yukimura suspects Muneakira of stealing her panties, and Sen bets a naked dance to prove that he isn`t the culprit. If not him, then who...or what?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622399</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-bride</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148777" update="2019-05-26">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-04-05</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真陰, 開幕</title>
<title xml:lang="en">True Shadow, Now Open</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinkage, Kaimaku</title>
<summary>With Muneakira now home, Yukimura unveils her latest endeavor: a maid cafe? It`s too bad their very first customers happen to be another group of samurai girls intent on taking them all down!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622397</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-bride</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148891" update="2013-04-06">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-04-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148892" update="2015-02-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-04-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150072" update="2019-05-26">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">謎の影</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mysterious Shadow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nazo no Kage</title>
<summary>A new presence makes itself known to the Master Samurai, someone unexpected and completely in the shadows. What are they to make of this new development?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622411</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-bride</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150073" update="2019-05-26">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-17</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">解除不能!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unable to Unlock!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaijo Funou!</title>
<summary>Shizuka is constantly calling and texting Hachiman while he tries to relax during summer vacation.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622409</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-bride</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150074" update="2019-05-26">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-10</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">噂の傾奇者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Reputed Dandy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uwasa no Kabukimono</title>
<summary>Shizuka announces that Hachiman and Yui must go on a recruitment drive to find more members, and they know exactly who to target.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622407</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-bride</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150075" update="2019-05-26">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-03</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">冥土争覇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Supremacy of the Underwold</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meido Souha</title>
<summary>The resurrected samurai have finally begun their assault on Muneakira and his master samurai...only to find out that there are certain stipulations they must follow to engage in battle.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622405</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-bride</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150550" update="2019-05-26">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">剣妃, 誕生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Samurai Bride Is Born</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Samurai Bride, Tanjou</title>
<summary>The cursed spirit is loose and Sen is hot on its trails. As the others continue the fight, Hanzo has designs of her own, vowing to let no harm come to her dear Princess Sen.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622419</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-bride</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150551" update="2019-05-26">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">対決の刻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Showdown</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiketsu no Toki</title>
<summary>Muneakira and his Master Samurai attempt to create the Samurai Bride using information gathered by Yukimura. However, Musashi`s sealing is making it difficult.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622417</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-bride</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150552" update="2019-05-26">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鎮護石の秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Secret of the Chingo Stone</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chingoseki no Himitsu</title>
<summary>The whereabouts and the mystery surrounding the Chingo Stone are finally revealed!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622415</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-bride</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150553" update="2019-05-26">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-31</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新たな剣姫</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The New Master Samurai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arata na Master Samurai</title>
<summary>There’s going to be a new Master Samurai in town!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622413</identifier>
<identifier>samurai-bride</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151232" update="2019-06-29">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2013-11-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">真陰[トゥルーシャドー]へようこそ! 百花繚乱ガールズトーク! 6</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girls` Talk 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">True Shadow e Youkoso! Hyakka Ryouran Girls` Talk! 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151233" update="2015-02-07">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2013-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">砂浜の乙女たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Girls on the Beach</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sunahama no Otome-tachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151234" update="2019-06-29">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2013-10-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">真陰[トゥルーシャドー]へようこそ! 百花繚乱ガールズトーク! 5</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girls` Talk 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">True Shadow e Youkoso! Hyakka Ryouran Girls` Talk! 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151235" update="2015-02-07">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2013-10-30</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダルタニアンレポート</title>
<title xml:lang="en">d`Artagnan Report</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">d`Artagnan Report</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151236" update="2019-06-29">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2013-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">真陰[トゥルーシャドー]へようこそ! 百花繚乱ガールズトーク! 4</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girls` Talk 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">True Shadow e Youkoso! Hyakka Ryouran Girls` Talk! 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151237" update="2015-02-07">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2013-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">豊乳計画</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Juicy Boobs Project</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hounyuu Keikaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151238" update="2019-06-29">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2013-08-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">真陰[トゥルーシャドー]へようこそ! 百花繚乱ガールズトーク! 3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girls` Talk 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">True Shadow e Youkoso! Hyakka Ryouran Girls` Talk! 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151239" update="2015-02-07">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2013-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最高の水着</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ultimate Swimsuit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikou no Mizugi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151240" update="2019-06-29">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2013-07-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">真陰[トゥルーシャドー]へようこそ! 百花繚乱ガールズトーク! 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girls` Talk 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">True Shadow e Youkoso! Hyakka Ryouran Girls` Talk! 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151241" update="2015-02-07">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2013-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">小次郎のメイド修行</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kojiro`s Maid Training</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kojirou no Maid Shugyou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151242" update="2019-06-29">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2013-06-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真陰[トゥルーシャドー]へようこそ! 百花繚乱ガールズトーク! 1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girls` Talk 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">True Shadow e Youkoso! Hyakka Ryouran Girls` Talk! 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151243" update="2014-06-10">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2013-06-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">佐助と武蔵が銭湯で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sasuke and Musashi at a Public Bath</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sasuke to Musashi ga Sentou de</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151244" update="2013-06-22">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">PV第一弾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">PV Daiichidan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158223" update="2014-02-22">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-04-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158224" update="2014-02-22">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-04-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158468" update="2014-03-15">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1g</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158469" update="2014-03-15">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1f</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158470" update="2014-03-15">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158471" update="2014-03-15">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158472" update="2014-03-15">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158473" update="2015-02-06">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162353" update="2014-08-23">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">AD2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162354" update="2014-08-23">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">AD1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
