<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9406" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>10</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-01-16</startdate>
<enddate>2014-03-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Maken-ki! Two</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Maken-Ki! Second Season</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Maken-Ki! 2nd Season</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">マケン姫っ! 通</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Maken-Ki! Two</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">魔具少女！通</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="10191" type="Prequel">Maken-ki! Two: Takeru Nyotaika!? Minami no Shima de Supoon</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="610995">Only for Boob and Ecchi fans thats like saying air is only for people who like to live.

Why else would anyone watch anime?</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="600311">only for boob and ecchi fans. Don`t expect to see any serious plot or something. The first season was much better</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="491381">plotless ecchi season of maken-ki. they dont even bother to use their maken for fights instead they are usin makens for punishment for male characters. so if you want to watch a plain ecchi anime this anime is for you.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://maken-ki-two.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3544" type="Character Design">Takami Akio</name>
<name id="3097" type="Direction">Kaneko Hiraku</name>
<name id="719" type="Animation Work">Xebec</name>
<name id="23640" type="Original Work">Takeda Hiromitsu</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a manga by http://anidb.net/cr23640 [Takeda Hiromitsu] formerly serialised in Dragon Age Pure, but moved to http://anidb.net/cr12273 [Gekkan Dragon Age] when the magazine was cancelled.
http://anidb.net/ch36167 [Takeru] continues his education at Tenbi Academy as part of the newly formed Security Committee. As a team with the other members they battle unscrupulous individuals who use their Maken for evil purposes. In the meantime, his libido and the conflicting romantic interests of the girls surrounding him complicate matters considerably.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="714">2.39</permanent>
<temporary count="725">5.42</temporary>
<review count="2">4.08</review>
</ratings>
<picture>148392.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15335</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15565</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>23989</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://maken-ki-two.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Maken-ki!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>マケン姫っ!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3249</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>347813</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16706</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1774" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-05">
<name>gigantic breasts</name>
<description>Gigantic breasts are unnaturally large breasts, even by anime standards; they are true gargantuan monstrosities, either because of sheer size or through the combination of size and exceedingly unnatural shape. Essentially, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are gigantic; smaller breasts are the more common http://anidb.net/t2741 [large breasts], even if they`re as big as the character`s head.</description>
<picurl>160446.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2343" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-17">
<name>ojou-sama laugh</name>
<description>A type of haughty laughter typical of rich young girls, as well as older rich women. Generally sounds like a high-pitched "OHOHOHOHOHOHO".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2631" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-11">
<name>island</name>
<description>Part of this anime takes place on an island, a small landmass that is surrounded by the sea. Generally, an island setting involves interaction with "island" elements. Such elements could include (but is not limited towards): riding on a boat, fishing, foraging/hunting, beach scene, "peaceful island life", being "shipwrecked", island fever, lamenting isolation from the mainland, etc.
An island or isle is any piece of sub-continental land that is surrounded by water. Very small islands such as emergent land features on atolls can be called islets, cays or keys. An island in a river or lake may be called an eyot (also ait), or holm. A grouping of geographically or geologically related islands is called an archipelago.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2658" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>toilet humour</name>
<description>Everything leads back to poo.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2787" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-28">
<name>teacher x student</name>
<description>Suggests a relationship involving a teacher and their student, often times sexual in nature.</description>
<picurl>206646.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2816" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sexual fantasies</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime let their imaginations run wild thinking about another character.
Yes, they are thinking about sex, and in an ecchi anime these thoughts are often perverted, leading to a nosebleed. But it may also be romanticising simply being husband and wife, and everything that implies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2821" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sudden naked girl appearance</name>
<description>A character or group of characters are simply minding their own business, when suddenly, a naked girl appears. It does not matter how or why, but a naked someone is there. Sometimes the naked girl is not happy about this. 
Usually this is a fanservice element, but not always.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2823" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>paper clothes</name>
<description>Worn clothing appears paper-thin and takes little abuse to be shredded or torn from the body. This is common in ecchi anime where the main storyline involves some type of fighting but consists primarily of dialogue and fanservice (Ikkitousen and Platonic Heart). Various girls’ clothing exploding as if made of rice paper is a very enticing prospect.</description>
<picurl>150776.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2828" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-26">
<name>borderline porn</name>
<description>Breaks the bounds of "excessive fanservice".
While the physical interactions and dialogue between characters may be extremely sexual, the most sexual situations do *not* have sex itself take place.
Specifically descriptive of containing all the plentiful features of (excessive) fanservice in addition to the interactions between characters being quite sexual — at most, sexual in NATURE only. This means physical touching such as groping, molesting, or bondage will focus primarily on the revealed (i.e. nude) upper portion of the body or through/over clothing on the lower half of the body. This is all WITHOUT actual sex acts (penetration, etc.) taking place.</description>
<picurl>214855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2830" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>furo scene</name>
<description>Furo (polite: Ofuro) is Japanese for bath, specifically a type of bath which originated as a short, steep-sided wooden bathtub. Baths of this type are found all over Japan in houses, apartments and traditional Japanese inns (Ryokans).
Furo are part of the Japanese ritual of bathing, not used for washing but for relaxing and warming oneself. Washing is carried out separately outside the furo, and only when completely clean does the bather enter the water. Generally Japanese bathrooms are small, so the bathroom is set up much like a walk-in shower area but containing the ofuro.
The cheapest and shortest way to show naked skin on TV, at least as much as allowed. It usually only takes up few minutes at most and as such it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales while still maintaining a "non-filler" episode.
Compare to the big brothers http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode] and http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160785.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2893" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>female teacher</name>
<description>Any kind of female teacher will do, even if she only does home visits. Female teachers imply mature women (even if they sometimes look like schoolgirls) dressed in what women would typically wear when doing official business (like a blouse, pinstripe dress with side front slit), but of course, not limited to that. Furthermore, school nurses also count as female teachers unless they`re actually wearing a nurse outfit, which they almost never are.
Almost completely exclusive to hentai animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2894" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>female student</name>
<description>Pretty much exclusive to hentai shows only unless an ecchi show has implied sex and/or a strong indicator of nudity. A character is considered a student if she goes to school, doesn`t matter if it`s high school, college or homeschooling, but she should be of appropriate age for a student; a housewife going to college should not get this category.</description>
<picurl>210611.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2895" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>dark-skinned girl</name>
<description>The anime features a girl with dark skin. A fetish of sorts, since the other protagonists are usually as white-skinned as porcelain dolls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3831" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-13">
<name>training</name>
<description>Training is extensive, serious practising a person undergoes in order to develop skills and abilities, such as handling weapons, playing instruments, playing sports, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3872" parentid="2869" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>formerly one-gender school</name>
<description>This anime takes place at a school that was formerly one-gender, but has recently begun to admit the opposite sex. This can be a set-up for harem situations stemming from a still-skewed gender ratio.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4182" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-01-22">
<name>hidden power</name>
<description>For some reason or another a character has powers (or potential) he or she can`t access and may not even know about. 
In some anime these hidden powers are used quite frequently to overcome an enemy or threat (e.g. Naruto, Bleach).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4431" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-06">
<name>love at first sight</name>
<description>Plot device: When two characters meet for the first time, at least one party, supposedly, immediately falls in love with the other party, and from then on tries to get to know that party better.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="36165" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-12-04">
<rating votes="78">8.11</rating>
<name>Nijou Aki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She`s the school nurse and also the staff-advisor of Maken-ki, She was in the Maken-ki before it became an all-girls academy.
Like many other females, she has a gorgeous body, but also has absurdly huge breasts, which attracts the attention of all male students and the envy of girls around her.</description>
<picture>227408.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5878" picture="45926.jpg">Harada Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36166" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-06">
<rating votes="49">6.07</rating>
<name>Rokujou Minori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Minori is the Principal and P.E teacher of the Tenbi Academy. She`s the one that allowed Inaho, Kodama, and Haruno to all live under the same roof with Takeru.
She brandishes incredible power and control over Element, and she can break through amazingly powerful barriers with her bare hands thanks to nothing more than, in her own words, her "fighting spirit". She was in the Maken-ki of the school before it became an all-girls academy.
She refers to herself as "Minori-chan" most of the time. Her Maken is a pair of gauntlets called "Dragon Ace".</description>
<picture>53685.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5889" picture="30436.jpg">Mina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36167" type="main character in" update="2011-09-08">
<rating votes="64">2.18</rating>
<name>Ooyama Takeru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A perverted high school student. He hates his father believing him to be the reason his mother died. He wields a power known as "blood pointer" which allows him to drain "element" from the people around him through his mouth. He has periodically used this ability throughout the series without knowing it. After the battle with the Venus unit he has begun to undergo training to understand this power and use it. He is the childhood friend of Ayama Haruko.
His maken is known as "Overblow", which lets him cause his opponent`s maken to gain incredible power and overflow with element causing it to go out of control and force the user to not be able to use it. However, when his opponent is able to contain the overflow of element or has perfect control over his maken, it would only provide his opponent greater power or even make the maken evolve into something greater.</description>
<picture>53669.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="612" picture="79531.jpg">Maeno Tomoaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36168" type="main character in" update="2011-09-10">
<rating votes="85">6.13</rating>
<name>Amaya Haruko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Called the strongest maiden in Tenbi by Himegami Kodama and the Vice-President of the student council. She is the childhood friend of Ooyama Takeru and has romantic feelings for him often not caring when her body is revealed in front of him. She shares a room with Ooyama Takeru, Himegami Kodama and Kushiya Inaho.
She wields one of the eight legendary maken, "Murakumo" meaning "Gathering Clouds". Her maken allows her to turn her element into photons around the blade. Murakumo`s seal cannot be broken unless it reacts to opponents on par with its power. However, Haruko was able to unleash a little of the maken`s power through her anger.</description>
<picture>53670.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="232" picture="148706.jpg">Shitaya Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36169" type="main character in" update="2011-09-08">
<rating votes="102">7.22</rating>
<name>Himegami Kodama</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wields shikigami that follow her around and call her ojou-sama. She needs element to survive, it has not fully been stated what exactly she is. But she has said to herself that she can`t leave the tenbi area because the element doesn`t flow as fully elsewhere. Which is why she went out to get a stone full of element so she could travel to the training grounds for the summer vacation. She stated that Ooyama Takeru is her mortal enemy after she saw the mark on his chest. Although its has yet to be confirmed if she still feels that way as she has kissed him on a few occasions leaving the cast a bit bewildered and annoyed. She can give her shikigami life and bring them into the real world so everyone can see them, giving them a human body in which they can fight with. It is hinted that she has a weakness for cute things, specifically rare and inexpensive stuff animal toys when she forgave the Finians when they tricked her because if she forgave them, she can have the rare king penguin stuffed toy. She is also deathly afraid of ghosts and other supernatural beings. Even becoming scared of a scary story that the story-teller openly admit that he made up the half rest of the story.</description>
<picture>53673.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="89" picture="148709.jpg">Yahagi Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36170" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-06">
<rating votes="49">5.40</rating>
<name>Shinatsu Azuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She`s a strong fighter that Takeru has had problems with like visiting the shop she works at which was a maid cafe named Macaroon. She has threatened him with death if he ever tells someone else about it.
Her Maken is "Hawk" which looks like a mechanical boot when activated. Her Maken`s ability boosts her already superior agility and speed, as well as her physical power.</description>
<picture>53684.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9512" picture="35180.jpg">Togashi Misuzu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36171" type="main character in" update="2011-09-08">
<rating votes="73">5.49</rating>
<name>Kushiya Inaho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Self proclaimed fiancée of Ooyama Takeru. She feels strongly for Takeru, and although he doesn`t remember her much she has decided to wait until he fully does.
Her maken, "Kamudo", takes the shape of a gauntlet that when brandished, greatly increases her strength and speed as demonstrated in chapter 7 when she used it to protect Takeru and the cat (later named Monji) he had saved by breaking a huge rock falling on them and then rushing in front of them to deflect the broken fragments. However, overusing it puts enough stress on her to knock her unconscious.</description>
<picture>53672.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5886" picture="30429.jpg">Nomizu Iori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36172" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-06">
<rating votes="28">2.78</rating>
<name>Usui Kengo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He has open feelings for Himegami Kodama and is supposedly in her fan club. He often, like Takeru, peeks on girls when they are in the shower, changing, etc. Much like Takeru, Kengo has a strong sense of justice.
His Maken lets him exchange himself or other people with an item in their place.</description>
<picture>70330.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3141" picture="65575.jpg">Tsuruoka Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37860" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-09-13">
<rating votes="53">4.12</rating>
<name>Takaki Furan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The President of the student council. Furan is very strict when it comes to Maken-ki`s duties that need to be carried out. She often scolds Haruko for coming late (mostly because of Takeru), providing a bad role-model for the other students as Vice-President of the student council.
Despite her shyness around boys she`s very attracted to Akaya from Venus, whom she falls for at their first meeting because unlike the peeping squads around he appears like a gentleman.</description>
<picture>70312.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9865" picture="37436.jpg">Gouda Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37861" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-18">
<rating votes="15">5.14</rating>
<name>Amato Tomika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70314.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="392" picture="17237.jpg">Matsuoka Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37862" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-18">
<rating votes="7">3.56</rating>
<name>Tagayashi Gen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70333.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19" picture="50583.jpg">Imaruoka Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38505" type="appears in" update="2017-09-13">
<rating votes="2">4.52</rating>
<name>Kagutsuchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207035.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3141" picture="65575.jpg">Tsuruoka Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38506" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-06">
<rating votes="61">6.03</rating>
<name>Akaza Chacha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A 2nd year student at Tenbi Academy. Her Maken is "Maken Scale Compressor" the ability to change the shape and density of objects.</description>
<picture>127081.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10391" picture="38277.jpg">Zougou Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38507" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-09-13">
<rating votes="30">4.58</rating>
<name>Satou Kimi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148721.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27341" picture="74876.jpg">Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38508" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-26">
<rating votes="30">2.45</rating>
<name>Minaya Uruchi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90153.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24092" picture="148715.jpg">Furuya Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38509" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-06">
<rating votes="43">6.35</rating>
<name>Amato Yuuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuuka is a close friend of Furan (who she likes to tease), and the Bookkeeper of the student council. She`s also the younger sister of Takeru`s homeroom teacher Amato Tomika.
Yuuka appears to be carefree most of the time. However, she is very cunning mostly encouraging activities of the Maken-ki that involve some kind of other work that needs to be done.</description>
<picture>130399.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23312" picture="205591.jpg">Takamori Natsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38510" type="appears in" update="2017-09-13">
<name>Kuragasa Kai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207036.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2888" picture="200816.jpg">Inoue Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38840" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-06">
<rating votes="40">5.33</rating>
<name>Syria Ootsuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is an American idol superstar and is shown as someone with amazing strength and is well-known through her singing/dancing career as well as a professional wrestler.
Her Jingu is an internal type named "Inverse". Its ability is to "reverse" situations at his/her will and her ability is not limited to reversing forces but could even reverse the will of her opponents.
Originally a male character who can use his/her Jingu`s "Inverse" ability is to change gender and physical appearance .</description>
<picture>77316.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="101" picture="16709.jpg">Ise Mariya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38876" type="appears in" update="2011-11-19">
<name>Kobayashi Ei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77370.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2888" picture="200816.jpg">Inoue Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38877" type="appears in" update="2011-11-19">
<rating votes="1">1.01</rating>
<name>Yamada Shisuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77369.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36048" picture="208013.jpg">Sunseki Kazuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38878" type="appears in" update="2011-11-19">
<name>Tanaka Biyou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77371.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="434" picture="41082.jpg">Shiraishi Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39874" type="appears in" update="2011-12-24">
<rating votes="3">2.32</rating>
<name>Nozuchi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78849.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23312" picture="205591.jpg">Takamori Natsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66833" type="appears in" update="2014-04-19">
<name>Rudolf</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An "interesting" Teddy bear, that Kodama noticed and bought from a shop.</description>
<picture>154226.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73736" type="appears in" update="2015-03-11">
<name>Bra Doro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>169943.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10772" picture="38752.jpg">Shirakawa Shuusaku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73740" type="appears in" update="2015-03-12">
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<name>Kinoshita Yumika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>169956.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27068" picture="73524.jpg">Tsumita Kayoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73770" type="appears in" update="2015-03-13">
<rating votes="2">1.59</rating>
<name>Shimoyanagi Mahiru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>170024.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34234" picture="228806.jpg">Bridcutt Sarah Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73775" type="appears in" update="2015-03-13">
<name>Monji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>170032.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4616" picture="170439.jpg">Nishi Asuka</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="157251" update="2017-05-26">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-02-06</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">まん♡コス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Man Cos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Man-Cos</title>
<summary>When the school holds a manga festival, a couple of hornballs use Maken to shrink the costumes right off the curvy contestants in the masquerade contest! Can anyone save the day - or will the student body bare all!?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="157252" update="2017-05-26">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-01-30</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ニャケン姫っ?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Meowken-ki?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nyaken-ki?</title>
<summary>When Inaho brings her pet to school, the kitten displays an amazing Element power—and turns the girls of Makenki into sexy human-feline hybrids! Can Takeru get things back to normal before the situation devolves into one epic catfight?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="157253" update="2017-05-26">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-01-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">タケル君が好き☆</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Love Takeru-kun!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Takeru-kun ga Suki</title>
<summary>A graduate of the academy returns and uses her clothes-shredding powers to steal Haruko’s memories and Maken! The security team tries desperately to track down the thief, while Inaho and amnesiac Haruko fight over Takeru’s affections.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="157254" update="2017-05-26">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-01-16</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔導検警機構</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Magical Security Organization</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Madou Kenkei Kikou</title>
<summary>Hijinks and wardrobe malfunctions abound at Tenbi Academy as Takeru and the rest of the school’s security force try to track down a perv who’s been taking lewd photos of female students and posting them on the school bulletin board—along with their bras!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="157399" update="2014-01-15">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-01-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157400" update="2014-01-15">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-01-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157768" update="2017-05-26">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-03-06</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">学園ハーレム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Academy Harem</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gakuen Harem</title>
<summary>When the principal at Tenbi gets fed up with the school, she does the only logical thing and puts one of the male students in charge. Pretty soon the academy turns into one big harem full of erotica readings, bouncy exercises, and chest inspections.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="157769" update="2017-05-26">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-02-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">その名はルドル!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">His Name Is Rudolf!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sono Na wa Rudol!</title>
<summary>Kodama goes underwear shopping, but ends up blowing all her money on an adorable fluffy teddy bear! Naturally, though, the bear ends up being a complete perv with a mind of his own, and is bursting at the seams to get his paws on every girl in sight.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="157770" update="2017-05-26">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-02-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">極悪統生会っ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Villainous Leadership Committee</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gokuaku Touseikai!</title>
<summary>In order to prove herself worthy of joining the Leadership Committee, Uruchi must complete a series of complicated trials—which somehow involve learning absolutely everything there is to know about Haruko’s body and bathing habits!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="157771" update="2017-05-26">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-02-13</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おねだり☆ティーチャー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Begging Teacher</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onedari Teacher</title>
<summary>Aki, the buxom school nurse, needs someone to pretend to be her boyfriend—so who better than Takeru, one of her students? When the two faux lovebirds end up handcuffed together on a romantic deserted island, things get really, really hard for Takeru.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="158305" update="2017-05-26">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-03-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そして, マケンキへ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">And So, Toward Makenki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soshite, Maken-ki e</title>
<summary>Someone`s broken into the principal’s room in search of files that could put the whole school at risk. In order to track down the culprit, the Leadership Committee will use all their resources—including a new student, fireworks, and skimpy costumes!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="158306" update="2017-05-26">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-03-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">君は薔薇より男らしい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You Are More Manly Than Roses</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi wa Bara yori Otokorashii</title>
<summary>The Leadership Committee president falls for a dashing boy. One problem: he’s actually Azuki dressed in guys’ clothing! Rather than come clean about the mistaken identity, the other girls make Azuki pretend to be a dude and go on a hot date with the pres.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="159803" update="2014-11-17">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2014-03-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">P~私事♡ 春恋編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">P~Watakushigoto Haruko Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160008" update="2014-11-17">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2014-06-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">P~私事♡ コダマ編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">P Watakushigoto Kodama Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160009" update="2014-11-17">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2014-05-30</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">P~私事♡ 秋編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">P Watakushigoto Aki Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160010" update="2014-11-17">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2014-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">P~私事♡ イナホ編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">P Watakushigoto Inaho Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162615" update="2014-11-17">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2014-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">P~私事♡季美編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">P Watakushigoto Kimi Hen</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
