<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9421" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-01-08</startdate>
<enddate>2013-03-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Courtesy of Zettai Karen Children: The Unlimited - Hyoubu Kyousuke</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The Unlimited Hyobu Kyosuke</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">Courtesy of ZETTAI KAREN CHILDREN THE UNLIMITED 兵部京介</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Unlimited Psychic Squad</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">THE UNLIMITED 兵部京介</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5674" type="Parent Story">Zettai Karen Children</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="1140" approval="3" total="3">Psychic Force</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="30310">Really interesting show until about the halfway point. Then we get a half-baked flashback arc and it becomes clear they need to rush things along. The ending is facepalm material.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="554531">Wish there was more to this</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="674243">This anime is good but please watch the parent series Zettai Karen Children first—ignore the bs that  say it`s not needed: it really is needed(you will miss a lot of stuff and you won`t truly appreciate how good unlimited is).</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://unlimited-zc.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="7880" type="Series Composition">Inotsume Shin`ichi</name>
<name id="7262" type="Original Work">Shiina Takashi</name>
<name id="20577" type="Direction">Igarashi Shishou</name>
<name id="1573" type="Music">Nakagawa Koutarou</name>
<name id="986" type="Animation Work">Manglobe</name>
<name id="34230" type="Character Design">Takagi Jun</name>
<name id="34230" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takagi Jun</name>
<name id="2308" type="Work">Geneon Universal Entertainment Japan</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a manga by http://anidb.net/cr7262 [Shiina Takashi], serialised in http://anidb.net/cr23232 [Shounen Sunday].
Spin-off series featuring http://anidb.net/ch4741 [Hyoubu Kyousuke], the leader of the criminal esper organization http://anidb.net/ch16201 [Pandra]. For the sake of his fellow espers, he is determined to bring about a revolution.
~ translated and adapted from official site by Cranston</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="954">6.18</permanent>
<temporary count="960">7.11</temporary>
<review count="1">5.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>130441.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14857</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16005</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5278</identifier>
<identifier>fdbmev</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://unlimited-zc.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/unlimited-zc/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Zettai_Karen_Children#The_Unlimited_-_Hy.C5.8Dbu_Ky.C5.8Dsuke</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>絶対可憐チルドレン_(アニメ)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2860</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>344507</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15688</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>the-unlimited-hyobu-kyosuke</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1438" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-18">
<name>ruthless</name>
<description>This character will stop at nothing to achieve their goals and will be unbound by any constraints</description>
<picurl>214979.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1864" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-14">
<name>extrasensory perception</name>
<description>Extrasensory perception (ESP), involves reception of information not gained through the recognized physical senses but sensed with the mind. The term was coined by Sir Richard Burton, and adopted by Duke University psychologist J. B. Rhine to denote psychic abilities such as telepathy and clairvoyance, and their trans-temporal operation as precognition or retrocognition. ESP is also sometimes casually referred to as a sixth sense, gut instinct or hunch, which are historical English idioms. The term implies acquisition of information by means external to the basic limiting assumptions of science, such as that organisms can only receive information from the past to the present.
In Japanese usage the term is often misappropriated to refer to any supernatural, non-magical, super power. Users of such powers are called `esper` in Japanese. The term `esper` is not normally in use outside of Japan but is slowly being introduced due to its usage in anime and manga.
In anime/manga the following powers, among others, are described as ESP:
- telepathy
- precognition
- clairvoyance
- retrocognition
- remote viewing
- aura reading
- out-of-body experiences (OBE)
- psychokinesis</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2633" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>prison</name>
<description>A building used to house convicted criminals and accused persons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2684" parentid="2812" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>New York</name>
<description>The City of New York, often called New York City or simply New York, is the most populous city in the United States. New York City is also the most densely populated major city in the United States. Located at the southern tip of the state of New York, the city is the center of the New York metropolitan area, one of the most populous urban agglomerations in the world.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214276.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2810" parentid="2831" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Italy</name>
<description>Italy, officially the Italian Republic, is a unitary parliamentary republic in Europe. Located in the heart of the Mediterranean Sea, Italy shares open land borders with France, Switzerland, Austria, Slovenia, San Marino and Vatican City.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214347.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2812" parentid="2832" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>United States</name>
<description>The United States of America (commonly referred to as the United States, the U.S., the USA, or America) is a federal constitutional republic comprising fifty states and a federal district. The country is situated mostly in central North America, where its forty-eight contiguous states and Washington, D.C., the capital district, lie between the Pacific and Atlantic Oceans, bordered by Canada to the north and Mexico to the south. The state of Alaska is in the north-west of the continent, with Canada to the east and Russia to the west across the Bering Strait. The state of Hawaii is an archipelago in the mid-Pacific. The country also possesses several territories in the Caribbean and Pacific.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>45504.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2832" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Americas</name>
<description>The Americas, also collectively called America, encompass the totality of the continents of North America and South America. Together they make up most of Earth`s western hemisphere and comprise the New World.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192247.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2877" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>revenge</name>
<description>A primary factor that drives the plot forward, is the almost obsessive desire of one of the characters to get back at someone else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2907" parentid="2636" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>genetic modification</name>
<description>Story-wise, genetic modification is usually centred on humans, probably the most subtle and creepy way of messing with mankind. Playing with the fear of the unknown, genetically altered humans are technically a new species, that may not only surpass but actually replace unaltered humans. The level of modification will vary from subtle changes in "look" (e.g. super-human beauty), to mental enhancements (PSI powers), to more or less atrocious adaptations to extreme environments (breath under water, radiation resistance). Note that changes in Aliens would be difficult to pinpoint, after all they are alien.</description>
<picurl>223941.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2964" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>OP variety</name>
<description>Several OP sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique OP for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3245" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-05">
<name>strategy</name>
<description>Instead of blindly running into a battle or trap, at least one of the protagonists devises a clever strategy to significantly improve the odds of victory.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3317" parentid="2810" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Venice</name>
<description>Venice is a city in northeastern Italy and the capital of the Veneto region. It is situated across a group of 118 small islands that are separated by canals and linked by bridges, of which there are 400. The islands are located in the shallow Venetian Lagoon, an enclosed bay that lies between the mouths of the Po and the Piave Rivers. Parts of Venice are renowned for the beauty of their settings, their architecture, and artwork. The lagoon and a part of the city are listed as a World Heritage Site.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3536" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-05-20">
<name>undercover</name>
<description>Be it the spy, the criminal or the police, someone pretends to be a person they aren`t in order to obtain information or something of value.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3909" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>talking is a free action</name>
<description>Time in comics is flexible. Each panel shows a single event, which is usually accompanied by a length of dialog, which must take some time to say. This disparity is usually accepted if it isn`t taken to extremes.
But often, characters will exposit when it`s most needed: at the story`s climax, when both the intricacies of the plot and the intensity of action hit their highest.
While the Heroes Outrun the Fireball, Mr. Exposition might explain why the Evil Overlord`s death caused the explosion. The Action Girl can deliver impressive lectures on why the monster`s Achilles` Heel will work, while still engaging in Waif-Fu. The Superhero can quip to his heart`s content and explain his abilities while dueling one insignificant mobster, or deliver a Kirk Summation during the course of a single Finishing Move. Sometimes even apparent mere mortals can give a lecture on what is happening when it would be a much better idea to simply run like hell.
Without stopping to breathe, apparently.
Source: TvTrope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3953" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-06">
<name>in medias res</name>
<description>In medias res, also medias in res (Latin for "into the midst of affairs (lit. into mid-affairs)"), refers to a literary and artistic technique where the narrative starts in the middle of the story instead of from its beginning. It is generally a plot-driven concept rather than a character-driven one; though characters are commonly used to provide the backstory. The characters, setting, and conflict are often introduced through a series of flashbacks or through characters relating past events to each other.
Probably originating from an oral tradition, the technique is a convention of epic poetry, one of the earliest and most prominent examples in Western literature being Homer`s Odyssey and Iliad. Virgil`s Aeneid began the tradition in literature of imitating Homer, continued in Torquato Tasso`s Jerusalem Delivered, John Milton`s Paradise Lost and "Inferno" from Dante`s Divine Comedy. George Lucas`s Star Wars saga was told using in medias res.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3993" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-28">
<name>kidnapping</name>
<description>In criminal law, kidnapping is the taking away or transportation of a person against that person`s will, usually to hold the person in false imprisonment, a confinement without legal authority. This may be done for ransom or in furtherance of another crime, or in connection with a child custody dispute.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10583.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4167" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-08-24">
<name>air combat</name>
<description>Dogfight refers to combat engagement between aircraft (or space craft), often one on one. So in short: jets, planes, missiles, machine guns and maybe a kamikaze or two.
Not to be confused with the `bark-bark` or `woof-woof` sort of dogfight.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4398" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-23">
<name>antihero</name>
<description>An antihero is a main character in a story who lacks conventional heroic qualities and attributes such as idealism, courage and morality. Although antiheroes may sometimes perform actions that are morally correct, it is not always for the right reasons, often acting primarily out of self-interest or in ways that defy conventional ethical codes.
A villain protagonist is where the leading character of the story (the protagonist) is also a villain; this is a fairly rare occurrence.</description>
<picurl>70856.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4499" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-07-28">
<name>some weird shit goin` on</name>
<description>Scenes of this show point to insanely strange events which seem to be taking place; throughout its episodes, the show may or may not explain what is going on. Either way, many viewers will find that a succinct and accurate way to describe the show is "WTF?", and the show`s explanations (or lack thereof) to the events will often be subject of heated debate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4520" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>betrayal</name>
<description>Friends become enemies.
Strong bonds of trust receive violations of confidence while friendships are faithlessly given up or revealed to have been false from the start.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6019" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-20">
<name>brainwashing</name>
<description>Brainwashing, the application of coercive techniques to change the values and beliefs, perceptions and judgements, and subsequent mindsets and behaviours of one or more people, usually for political, financial, personal, or religious purposes. Often features in dark anime or pornography.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6186" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>spring</name>
<description>During spring, the axis of the Earth is increasing its tilt relative to the Sun, and the length of daylight rapidly increases for the relevant hemisphere. The hemisphere begins to warm significantly causing new plant growth to spring forth, giving the season its name. Snow, if a normal part of winter, begins to melt, and streams swell with runoff. Frosts, if a normal part of winter, become less severe. In climates that have no snow and rare frosts, the air and ground temperatures increase more rapidly. Many flowering plants bloom this time of year, in a long succession sometimes beginning when snow is still on the ground, continuing into early summer. In normally snowless areas spring may begin as early as February (Northern Hemisphere) heralded by the blooming of deciduous magnolias, cherries and quince, or August (Southern Hemisphere) in the same way. Many temperate areas have a dry spring, and wet autumn (fall), which brings about flowering in this season more consistent with the need for water as well as warmth. Subarctic areas may not experience spring at all until May or even June.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161969.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="4730" type="appears in" update="2013-03-25">
<rating votes="45">7.05</rating>
<name>Akashi Kaoru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A ten-year-old Level 7 psychokinetic (the maximum esper potency designation), Kaoru is the reckless and zealous member of "The Children" Special Esper Team alongside Shiho and Aoi that often goes overkill with her psychic powers.</description>
<picture>20851.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4" picture="177060.jpg">Hirano Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4731" type="appears in" update="2013-03-25">
<rating votes="26">6.46</rating>
<name>Nogami Aoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A ten-year-old esper with Level 7 teleportation capability, Aoi is the rational member of "The Children" Special Esper Team alongside Kaoru and Shiho that likes playing video games in her spare time. Like her teammates, Aoi is introduced at series inception as behaving in a somewhat cavalier manner that annoys her adult superiors.</description>
<picture>20852.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="208" picture="20458.jpg">Shiraishi Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4732" type="appears in" update="2013-03-25">
<rating votes="31">6.55</rating>
<name>Sannomiya Shiho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A ten-year-old esper with Level 7 psychometry, Shiho is the sarcastic, sharp-tongued and often childishly sadistic member of "The Children" Special Esper Team alongside Kaoru and Aoi. While initially not able to do much during missions aside from gathering information that is not immediately obvious from the environment, Shiho still supports her teammates by doing whatever she can.</description>
<picture>20853.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4733" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-11">
<rating votes="37">4.45</rating>
<name>Minamoto Kouichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The first lieutenant workaholic field leader of "The Children" Special Esper Team, he is tasked with overseeing their day-to-day care and making sure they do not get too carried away when they are doing their jobs. Even as they mistreat him and generally give him super fits, the girls highly esteem Minamoto enough to ask the B.A.B.E.L. chief to be allowed to reside with him after he leads them in their introductory mission and protects Kaoru from her own out-of-control telekinesis. While he is quite courageous and sincere in his belief that Kaoru/Shiho/Aoi are little girls to be protected and cherished before they are Level 7 espers (which Shiho says are treated the same as mass-destruction weapons) and has grown to be very fond of them enough to spend time with them on diurnal outings, Minamoto has a hard time applying those life-equality ideals to Momotarou (who wrecks his apartment when Kaoru decides to nurse him back to health) and refraining from behaving toward his esper charges as if they are a bunch of brats (an accurate but counterproductive assessment). Minamoto generates quite a convoy of female admirers during the course of the Zettai Karen Children series as he works to pre-empt the precognition of a mortal showdown with Kaoru in a war-torn city during Kyousuke`s esper-led war against humans a decade in the future.</description>
<picture>20854.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4734" type="appears in" update="2009-03-10">
<rating votes="27">6.37</rating>
<name>Kashiwagi Oboro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Even if her job title is simply being Taizou`s secretary or personal assistant, Kashiwagi is no exception to the sidekick/alter ego dynamic and is generally very handy to have around. Kashiwagi performs many roles as she accompanies Taizou which include assisting with visual aids during mission briefings and preventing Taizou from giving an order or making a decision whose aftermath would most likely be rather messy.</description>
<picture>20855.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4740" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-11">
<rating votes="32">3.57</rating>
<name>Sakaki Shuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dr. Sakaki Shuuji is the old-enough-to-know-better playboy psychometric physician of B.A.B.E.L. whose job it is to inspect espers at the conclusion of every mission as well as to take care of general medical needs. Before meeting Minamoto (who is originally a medical researcher before enrolling in an overseas supervisor course), Sakaki did not have anybody to understand him as a person and advocate for him. To compensate for this, he behaved like the typical sports jock - popular in school but dangerous if obstructed. Given how he had beaten up several people and how injured they were, it is not that unreasonable to speculate that Sakaki is very well-practised in the martial arts and that it was probably in that forum that he discovered his psychometry and taught himself how to use it to his advantage. Fortunately, Sakaki saw fit to clean up his act after his Level 6 psychometry imports an admonishment to grow up from Minamoto even as he behaves as quite a lady`s man.</description>
<picture>20861.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="181" picture="171560.jpg">Taniyama Kishou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4741" type="main character in" update="2012-08-11">
<rating votes="72">7.75</rating>
<name>Hyoubu Kyousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A misanthropic former major-rank military esper with eight decades of life under his belt, Kyousuke is one tough adversary with an abundant anthology of different esper capabilities. As is the case with Kaoru`s berserk runaway telekinesis, Kyousuke has the capability to defy fully powered-up ESP Counter Measure generators but does so as "the rule". Kyousuke has a lengthy history of teleporting out of his subterranean holding cell, walking around for a breath of fresh air, and teleporting back in without anybody detecting and challenging him. Given that there are few efficacious avenues for damaging him (never mind the subjugation and confinement), Kyousuke believes that he do whatever he wishes and it would not be that outrageous to suspect that Kyousuke is either one of the alpha adversaries or the alpha adversary. He delights in giving B.A.B.E.L. fits as he foils their attempts to apprehend him and using his hypnosis to especially manipulate Minamoto for his own amusement (such as creating the illusion that Kaoru, Shiho, and Aoi are physically older than in reality). Kyousuke`s misanthropy also extends to other espers if they defy him (although he will offer them a chance to serve him first). He views Kaoru as his queen and soul mate due to her ability to defy the fully powered-up ESP Counter Measure generator and wishes for her to grow up quickly not caring anything that Kaoru is much more like a child than she initially appears as Minamoto is forced to endure on a daily basis. He and Momotarou have a social dynamic where they always see the worst of normal people and behave as if the word of an esper always takes precedence over the word of a normal person—with which they both have had several dysphoric experiences.</description>
<picture>20862.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4742" type="appears in" update="2009-03-10">
<rating votes="7">4.18</rating>
<name>Muscle Ookama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Muscle is introduced as the criminal quarry The Children have been charged with apprehending that behaves as if he were a 1960/1970s disco party-goer and has an affinity for muscular male bodies, hence the aspiration for a gold statue fashioned as such. His esper capability is using his telekinesis to burrow through the ground and to petrify people using a gemstone on his belt. A running gag involves one or more of his female opponents striking his genitals in combat.</description>
<picture>20863.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12809" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-07">
<rating votes="25">4.30</rating>
<name>Momotarou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Being the sole surviving wartime experimentation specimen to manufacture an esper animal, Momotarou is Kyousuke`s squirrel companion that sometimes behaves quite cluelessly as to Kyousuke`s modus operandi as he adds his commentary to whatever Kyousuke does or is deciding. Momotarou`s strongly- and frequently-demonstrated affinity for sunflower seeds one night causes him to be sucked into the slipstream of a passing truck and electrocuted by live power lines for no other reason than his obdurate refusal to let go of the seeds. If pushed into combat, Momotarou has the capability to compress the air around him into acoustic concussion missiles that he launches at his adversaries as well as an intense but transient siren that scrambles and encrypts the brain waves of anybody in the vicinity. When Kaoru tries to nurse him back to health, Momotarou has psychotic episodes as he recalls all the experimentation he has undergone that cause him to lash out to tremendous effect but fortunately sees that Kaoru and her teammates are kindred spirits even if he has not yet resolved his hatred for humans as a whole.</description>
<picture>38453.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15679" type="appears in" update="2010-03-09">
<rating votes="12">4.45</rating>
<name>Inugami Hatsune</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fourteen-year-old Hatsune avails her Level 4 metamorphosis as a member of The Hound Special Esper Team alongside of her partner Akira. Much to Akira`s chagrined frustration, Hatsune demonstrates the proclivity to behave her default lupine alternate manifestation which is only at its greatest efficacy when she is hungry—hungry as in `have not eaten for days` ravenous rather than merely being peckish. Unfortunately, Hatsune`s voracious appetite does have the tendency to displace the mission at hand. Even as this flaw is somewhat diminished as Minamoto trains her, Hatsune still has to overcome the fact that she computes and conducts in lupine/canine maneuvering rather than anthropoid action. Even with her canine conduct and gluttony set aside for the moment, Hatsune demonstrates a proclivity to become enthralled with anyone that sees past her exterior to interact with her as a human being and twice tries to claim Minamoto for herself. As Kaoru emphatically and vigorously demonstrates at her natural potency designation during an exercise regarding Minamoto and his affiliation, whoever is decided upon to supervise Hatsune will have to establish and maintain dominance right from the start without being cruel or despotic.</description>
<picture>44378.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12624" picture="79638.jpg">Mine Nobuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15743" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-25">
<rating votes="19">5.89</rating>
<name>Magi Shirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A senior member of PANDRA.</description>
<picture>44504.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="156" picture="227713.jpg">Ochiai Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15859" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-25">
<rating votes="15">3.99</rating>
<name>Fujiura You</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of PANDRA.</description>
<picture>44731.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15861" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-25">
<rating votes="20">5.27</rating>
<name>Kanou Momiji</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A tall woman with long blue hair and (usually) sunglasses. She is a member of PANDRA. Her power is based on teleportation and allows her to manipulate air.</description>
<picture>44733.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15862" type="appears in" update="2010-03-16">
<rating votes="4">4.15</rating>
<name>I Kyuu Gou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A dolphin with level 7 ESP precognition powers. His predictions always come true. He was the result of animal experiments during the war, much like Momotarou.</description>
<picture>44734.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28878" picture="188708.jpg">Fusegawa Kazuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15863" type="appears in" update="2013-03-25">
<rating votes="23">8.10</rating>
<name>Tsubomi Fujiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girlish and playful energy vampire with eight decades of life under her belt and the capability to practice the same powers as Kaoru and her teammates. She outranks Taizou who has established B.A.B.E.L. under her guidance.</description>
<picture>44735.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16194" type="appears in" update="2010-03-29">
<rating votes="13">2.79</rating>
<name>Patty Crew</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An unwilling member of Black Phantom. She can transform her entire body into black smoke and recreate herself at any location the black smoke occupies. Physical attacks have no effect on her.</description>
<picture>45347.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50094" type="main character in" update="2013-03-25">
<rating votes="13">5.49</rating>
<name>Andy Hinomiya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59968.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50095" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-25">
<rating votes="15">5.89</rating>
<name>Yuugiri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59969.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52197" type="appears in" update="2013-03-25">
<rating votes="2">3.46</rating>
<name>Alan Walsh</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59972.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2231" picture="235895.jpg">Kusunoki Taiten</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52198" type="appears in" update="2013-01-19">
<rating votes="1">3.91</rating>
<name>Chin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2090" picture="151718.jpg">Toochika Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52199" type="appears in" update="2013-04-06">
<rating votes="2">2.85</rating>
<name>Khan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60133.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="4688" picture="29259.jpg">Hirota Kousei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52200" type="appears in" update="2013-01-19">
<rating votes="1">3.91</rating>
<name>Hazem</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="369" picture="223406.jpg">Aoyama Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52201" type="appears in" update="2013-04-06">
<rating votes="2">2.85</rating>
<name>Maldini</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60134.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="4494" picture="245665.jpg">Yamaji Kazuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52843" type="appears in" update="2014-02-04">
<rating votes="2">3.46</rating>
<name>Sisley</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149559.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2281" picture="171603.jpg">Katou Masayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52844" type="appears in" update="2013-04-06">
<rating votes="2">1.65</rating>
<name>Sophie Grace</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Princess.</description>
<picture>60135.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52845" type="appears in" update="2013-02-11">
<rating votes="1">3.91</rating>
<name>Doga</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53515" type="cameo appearance in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Angry Video Game Nerd</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133247.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="53516" type="cameo appearance in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<name>The Nostalgia Critic</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133246.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="53580" type="appears in" update="2013-03-09">
<rating votes="1">5.46</rating>
<name>Magi Shirou (Kodomo Jidai)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="690" picture="187038.jpg">Higa Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53581" type="appears in" update="2013-04-06">
<rating votes="2">3.46</rating>
<name>Ikuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60136.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="34901" picture="130616.jpg">Lynn</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53582" type="appears in" update="2014-02-01">
<rating votes="2">6.10</rating>
<name>Utsumi Seishirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59975.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1441" picture="18827.jpg">Tsuboi Tomohiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53583" type="appears in" update="2013-03-25">
<rating votes="1">3.91</rating>
<name>Natsumi Iwao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59973.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2067" picture="186243.jpg">Hoshino Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53584" type="appears in" update="2013-03-09">
<rating votes="4">5.89</rating>
<name>Kyousuke (Kodomo Jidai)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133350.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4" picture="177060.jpg">Hirano Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53585" type="appears in" update="2013-04-06">
<rating votes="2">1.95</rating>
<name>Hyoubu Hakase</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60138.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53586" type="appears in" update="2013-03-25">
<rating votes="2">3.46</rating>
<name>Yadorigi Akio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59970.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="12387" picture="223823.jpg">Yanai Hitoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53587" type="appears in" update="2013-03-25">
<rating votes="2">4.15</rating>
<name>Shiga Tadashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59976.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="6976" picture="158591.jpg">Komatsu Fuminori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53588" type="appears in" update="2013-03-25">
<rating votes="2">2.35</rating>
<name>Saotome Eiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59977.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1816" picture="20691.jpg">Mori Katsuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53589" type="appears in" update="2013-03-09">
<rating votes="1">5.46</rating>
<name>Minamoto Kouichi (Yokoku)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53590" type="appears in" update="2013-03-25">
<rating votes="2">3.46</rating>
<name>Akuta Ryuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59971.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="267" picture="25729.jpg">Koyama Tsuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53591" type="appears in" update="2013-03-25">
<rating votes="2">3.46</rating>
<name>Kikuchi Kanji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59974.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="20385" picture="53603.jpg">Sato Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53593" type="appears in" update="2013-04-06">
<rating votes="2">4.15</rating>
<name>I Hachi Gou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60142.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2575" picture="139952.jpg">Eguchi Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54796" type="appears in" update="2013-04-06">
<rating votes="2">3.46</rating>
<name>Tsubomi Danshaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60139.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2067" picture="186243.jpg">Hoshino Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54798" type="appears in" update="2013-04-06">
<rating votes="5">5.30</rating>
<name>Tsubomi Fujiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Young Tsubomi Fujiko.</description>
<picture>60141.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54847" type="appears in" update="2013-04-08">
<rating votes="1">3.91</rating>
<name>Norman Green</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3965" picture="25836.jpg">Souya Shigenori</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="146357" update="2013-02-19">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">超常脱獄 -Schooler of deadlock-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Paranormal Jailbreak: Schooler of Deadlock</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Choujou Datsugoku: Schooler of Deadlock</title>
<summary>The leader of the criminal esper organisation P.A.N.D.R.A is imprisoned in the jail for espers, Deadlock. There he meets a man with unusually coloured eyes who catches his interest, Andy Hinomiya.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617363</identifier>
<identifier>the-unlimited-hyobu-kyosuke</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146620" update="2013-05-17">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146621" update="2013-01-07">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146622" update="2013-02-19">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶対領域 -Children Territory-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Absolute Domain: Children Territory</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zettai Ryouiki: Children Territory</title>
<summary>Hyobu Kyosuke has ordered the Catastrophe back to Japan where they are met with a warm welcome from old friends.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617369</identifier>
<identifier>the-unlimited-hyobu-kyosuke</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146623" update="2013-02-19">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">清楚と汚濁 -Queen not a Princess-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cleanliness and Pollution: Queen Not a Princess</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seiso to Odaku: Queen Not a Princess</title>
<summary>P.A.N.D.R.A has kidnapped Princess Sophie a Pro-Esper activist. The plan to do so was formulated by non-other than Yugiri.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617367</identifier>
<identifier>the-unlimited-hyobu-kyosuke</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146624" update="2013-02-19">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暗殺のメロディ -Ghost of WW2-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Melody of Assassination: Ghost of WW2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ansatsu no Melody: Ghost of WW2</title>
<summary>As Andy begins to familiarise himself within P.A.N.D.R.A, he is given his first mission to assassinate a mafia leader.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617365</identifier>
<identifier>the-unlimited-hyobu-kyosuke</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147133" update="2013-02-19">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ストレンジャーズ -Portrait of the family-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Strangers: Portrait of the Family</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Strangers: Portrait of the Family</title>
<summary>The crew enjoys some free time shopping. Andy treats Yugiri to a special treat but it is cut short when he is visited by B.A.B.E.L with some important information.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617371</identifier>
<identifier>the-unlimited-hyobu-kyosuke</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147247" update="2013-02-19">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">闇, 走る -As true as a lie-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Darkness, Run: As True as a Lie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yami, Hashiru: As True as a Lie</title>
<summary>Not only is the secret of the Catastrophe revealed but so has Andy`s hidden agenda. Does he have the power to stand against the Major?</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617373</identifier>
<identifier>the-unlimited-hyobu-kyosuke</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147411" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">遠い楽園 -Original Sin-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Distant Paradise: Original Sin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tooi Rakuen: Original Sin</title>
<summary>Old foes thought long gone, have been exposed as the mastermind behind the plans to sink the Catastrophe is taking Yugiri.  This new information re-ignites the fire in Kyosuke as he shakes off death to get his revenge.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617381</identifier>
<identifier>the-unlimited-hyobu-kyosuke</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147412" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カタストロフ -Pandora`s box opens-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Catastrophe: Pandora`s Box Opens</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Catastrophe: Pandora`s Box Opens</title>
<summary>The American government has made their move with a full on assault against the Catastrophe, but their real intentions are unknown even to their spy; History will repeat itself.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617379</identifier>
<identifier>the-unlimited-hyobu-kyosuke</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147413" update="2013-02-26">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">超能部隊・後編 -Generation ZERO PART II-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">ESP Unit Part Two: Generation Zero Part II</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chounou Butai Kouhen: Generation Zero Part II</title>
<summary>Kyousuke has been chosen to represent the E.S.P unit in the Navy war games. The Unit`s future lies on his shoulders.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617377</identifier>
<identifier>the-unlimited-hyobu-kyosuke</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147414" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">超能部隊・前編 -Generation ZERO PART I-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">ESP Unit Part One: Generation Zero Part I</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chounou Butai Zenpen: Generation Zero Part I</title>
<summary>After his father’s death, Baron Tsubomi took in Kyosuke and raised him with his daughter Fujuko, a sensory user. Together with other sensory users they help form Japans first Special ESP Unit.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617375</identifier>
<identifier>the-unlimited-hyobu-kyosuke</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148028" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">未来へ -LΛST RESOLUTION-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the Future: Last Resolution</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mirai e: Last Resolution</title>
<summary>Saotome plan is finally coming to fruition and with no one powerful enough to stop it, the world will be saved from Hyobu Kyoskue.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617385</identifier>
<identifier>the-unlimited-hyobu-kyosuke</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148029" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-19</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">嵐の中のふたり -OUTLAWS-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Two Within the Storm: Outlaws</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arashi no Naka no Futari: Outlaws</title>
<summary>New York has a new Mayor that is in support of esper relationships, at the same time Hyobu and Andy work their way into the USEI facility only to discover…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617383</identifier>
<identifier>the-unlimited-hyobu-kyosuke</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148123" update="2013-05-17">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-03-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148213" update="2013-05-17">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-03-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150592" update="2013-05-17">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-03-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150593" update="2013-05-17">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-03-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150594" update="2013-05-17">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-02-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150595" update="2013-05-17">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-02-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150596" update="2013-05-17">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-02-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150597" update="2013-05-17">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-01-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150598" update="2013-05-17">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-01-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="182212" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617259</identifier>
<identifier>the-unlimited-hyobu-kyosuke</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
