<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9436" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-07-02</startdate>
<enddate>2013-09-17</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Brothers Conflict</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Братско съперничество</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">BroCon</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">BROTHERS CONFLICT</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Brothers Conflict</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">兄弟战争</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="10809" type="Other">Brothers Conflict (2014)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9717" approval="3" total="4">Diabolik Lovers</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://www.bc-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1465" type="Series Composition">Takahashi Natsuko</name>
<name id="1420" type="Direction">Matsumoto Atsushi</name>
<name id="982" type="Animation Work">Brain`s Base</name>
<name id="38006" type="Original Work">Udajo</name>
<name id="38007" type="Original Work">Kanase Atsuko</name>
<name id="4418" type="Character Design">Ishii Kumi</name>
<name id="13809" type="Music">Nakatsuka Takeshi</name>
<name id="4418" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ishii Kumi</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch55281 [Hinata Ema] is the only daughter of a famous adventurer, Hinata Rintarou. One day, Ema learns that Rintarou is going to remarry with a successful apparel maker named Asahina Miwa. Since she doesn`t want to disturb them, Ema decides to move out and live with her 13 new brothers in a mansion called Sunrise Residence. As they live under the same roof, romance is starting to grow between Ema and the Asahina brothers.
Source: Love-colored Sky</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="490">2.64</permanent>
<temporary count="495">5.21</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>135728.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14865</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15605</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>22745</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.bc-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Brothers_Conflict</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>BROTHERS_CONFLICT</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3055</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>345837</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16081</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="618" parentid="2565" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>trap</name>
<description>A trap is a plot device where a male character is mistaken for a female, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the male (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the male, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the male character as a female; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through his behaviour, and/or language. A male character misinterpreted by others as female, without action from the male (explicitly feminine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t1637 [reverse trap].
Note: the tag image is from http://anidb.net/a10475 [Himegoto].</description>
<picurl>161537.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2792" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>reverse harem</name>
<description>Reverse harem, or sometimes also male harem, is the common name for the gender-reversed version of the usual http://anidb.net/t2859 [harem genre]. In a reverse harem, instead of the usual situation with several female characters focused on one male character, the viewer sees several male characters surrounding a single female character. Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. The most notable exception is that, due to the most relevant characteristics of the trope`s fan base, reverse harem authors tend to go for http://anidb.net/t1760 [bishounen] looks. Though they are also exceptions to the common harem genre, harems with homosexual relationships are not covered by reverse harem.</description>
<picurl>126787.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4176" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-05-14">
<name>OP and ED sung by characters</name>
<description>OP and/or ED in this anime is sung by the characters and animation shows them singing.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5805" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-06-11">
<name>post-credits scene</name>
<description>A little bit of the story is found after the credit titles. A little bonus for those patient enough!
This applies regardless of if the credits play over an ED sequence, or over the "regular episode" that continues to air into the credits.
A sequence at the end of an episode, showing what will happen in the next episode, is NOT a post-credits scene; that is a preview.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="51041" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-14">
<rating votes="4">2.56</rating>
<name>Juli</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138532.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51042" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-14">
<rating votes="3">2.95</rating>
<name>Asahina Masaomi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138547.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1692" picture="224934.jpg">Okitsu Kazuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51043" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-14">
<rating votes="3">3.63</rating>
<name>Asahina Ukyou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138548.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="99" picture="139554.jpg">Hirakawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51044" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-14">
<rating votes="3">3.84</rating>
<name>Asahina Kaname</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138549.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51045" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-14">
<rating votes="3">1.95</rating>
<name>Asahina Hikaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138550.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51046" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-14">
<rating votes="4">4.80</rating>
<name>Asahina Tsubaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138551.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="191" picture="17006.jpg">Suzumura Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51047" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-14">
<rating votes="4">3.13</rating>
<name>Asahina Azusa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138552.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51048" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-14">
<rating votes="5">6.35</rating>
<name>Asahina Natsume</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138553.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="612" picture="79531.jpg">Maeno Tomoaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51049" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-14">
<rating votes="2">1.80</rating>
<name>Asahina Louis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138554.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="589" picture="186167.jpg">Takeuchi Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51050" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-14">
<rating votes="3">3.63</rating>
<name>Asahina Subaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138555.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51051" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-14">
<rating votes="4">6.82</rating>
<name>Asahina Iori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138556.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51052" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-14">
<rating votes="3">3.80</rating>
<name>Asahina Yuusuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138557.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3709" picture="84359.jpg">Hosoya Yoshimasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51053" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-14">
<rating votes="3">1.46</rating>
<name>Asahina Fuuto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138558.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="367" picture="17213.jpg">Kenn</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51054" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-14">
<rating votes="2">2.65</rating>
<name>Asahina Wataru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138559.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55281" type="main character in" update="2013-06-14">
<rating votes="6">4.57</rating>
<name>Hinata Ema</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138546.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81734" type="appears in" update="2016-04-15">
<name>Hinata Rintarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>185778.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3185" picture="171529.jpg">Terasoma Masaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81736" type="appears in" update="2016-04-15">
<name>Asahina Miwa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>185782.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="151538" update="2017-08-03">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">兄弟</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Brothers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoudai</title>
<summary>Ema`s father remarries and she suddenly finds herself with thirteen new brothers. Today, she`s moving in with them and meeting them all for the first time, so she`s in for quite a day.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="151583" update="2017-08-03">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-07-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">嫉妬</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jealousy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shitto</title>
<summary>Now a couple months into her new living arrangement, Ema`s relationships with some of her brothers are growing and changing.  As she roots for Tsubaki to get his dream voice acting gig, she also bonds with Natsume over video games.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="151584" update="2017-08-03">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">約束</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Promise</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yakusoku</title>
<summary>Ema finds out what Futo wants from her.  And with her father`s wedding coming up, she finally meets the last of the thirteen brothers.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="151585" update="2017-08-03">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">混乱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Confusion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Konran</title>
<summary>After spending a lot of time alone with her father away overseas for work all the time, Ema is enjoying being part of a big family. But she also has some interesting run-ins with Futo, the family`s pop star with an attitude.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="152233" update="2017-08-03">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-07-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">浸水</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Submersion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinsui</title>
<summary>A lack of dinner ingredients leads to a picnic under the cherry blossoms. And Ema finally has a chance to see Subaru play basketball.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="152290" update="2017-08-03">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-08-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢幻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Visions</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mugen</title>
<summary>Ema is troubled and hurt by the revelation she finds in the official copy of her family register. As she works through it, she gets to know a little more about Natsume, Louis, and the Asahina family.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="152291" update="2017-08-03">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-08-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪夢</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nightmare</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akumu</title>
<summary>With Azusa falling ill, Tsubaki struggles with how their fight resulted in Azusa`s collapse. And in the meantime, Ema does her best to help out wherever she can.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="152292" update="2017-08-03">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-08-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">限界</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Breaking Point</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Genkai</title>
<summary>Ema, Yusuke, and Futo have their school`s Culture Fest coming up, where Futo gets up to his usual mischief. And at home, Azusa seems to be starting to crack under the pressure of the role he won away from Tsubaki.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="152293" update="2017-08-03">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-08-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">写真</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Photos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shashin</title>
<summary>Ema and Yusuke are in for a surprise at school, courtesy of Futo. And the snapshots Ema has been taking garner some attention since none of the brothers ever think to take photos.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="152677" update="2017-08-03">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-09-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋愛</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Romance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ren`ai</title>
<summary>Now that the college entrance exams are over, Ema thinks carefully about what her brothers mean to her and goes through with her earlier decision to be more open with them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="152678" update="2017-08-03">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-09-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛憎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love-Hate</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aizou</title>
<summary>The college entrance exams are coming up fast and Ema learns how nice it can be to have the support of her siblings. But on the romantic front, many of them are also hoping for a response from her after the exams.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="152679" update="2017-08-03">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-09-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">彼岸</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Enlightenment</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Higan</title>
<summary>With everything that has happened, the Asahina family`s plan for a vacation overseas has been scrapped, so instead, they decide to go on a short trip closer to home and enjoy a little summer festival.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="158216" update="2014-05-01">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2014-02-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">切望</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Desperate Desire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Setsubou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176839" update="2016-04-11">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-07-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176840" update="2016-04-11">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-07-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
