<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9473" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-01-10</startdate>
<enddate>2013-03-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gudaguda Fairies 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">gdgd妖精s 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">gdgd妖精s[ぐだぐだフェアリーーズ]</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">gdgd Fairies 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">GDGD 요정 S 2기</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="10621" type="Sequel">Gekijouban Gudaguda Fairiestte Iu Eiga wa Dou kana...?</anime>
<anime id="8661" type="Prequel">Gudaguda Fairies</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://gdgdfairy.com/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="29708" type="Direction">Sugahara Souta</name>
<name id="29707" type="Music">Inoue Jun`ichi</name>
<name id="29708" type="Character Design">Sugahara Souta</name>
</creators>
<description>Direct continuation of the previous season. Full CG series about a 3 fairies who ramble over about random subjects in 3 locations.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="90">5.37</permanent>
<temporary count="90">6.22</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>126753.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14973</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16726</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>16912</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://gdgdfairy.com/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Gdgd_Fairies</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Gdgd妖精s</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2848</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>344087</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>gdgd-fairies</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="28" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-16">
<name>baseball</name>
<description>Baseball is like a complicated version of Rounders. It involves hitting a ball with a stick, then running around several bases placed in the form of a diamond on a field. Big in the US, and also in Japan.</description>
<picurl>29801.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="780" parentid="2849" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-23">
<name>fairy</name>
<description>A fairy is a type of mythical being or legendary creature in European folklore, a form of spirit, often described as metaphysical, supernatural, or preternatural.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>206567.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1032" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-08-10">
<name>fishing</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3721" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-07">
<name>RPG elements</name>
<description>The anime shows elements of a `R`ole `P`laying `G`ame, either as part of a parody or because the anime is actually based on an RPG.
Typical elements: When collecting items, beating opponents, or levelling up a distinct (often childishly sounding) sound cue is played. A HUD (`H`eads `U`p `D`isplay) may also be presenting in combat, showing vital player and "enemy" statistics.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4131" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-11">
<name>cultural references</name>
<description>The plot of this anime shows signs of cultural references, these are often jokes that make reference to a certain custom, habit or history that is specifically attributed to that culture. Knowledge of the culture itself is needed in order to properly understand these jokes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4228" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-09">
<name>subtle OP ED sequence change</name>
<description>A (small) part of the opening or ending sequence changes after a certain episode, usually to reflect a plot milestone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4280" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-02">
<name>surreal</name>
<description>Refers to things or occurrences that are generally bizarre or dreamlike, with the relentless capability of replacing reality through the eyes of the beholder. Surrealism is boundless, limited only by thought itself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4499" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-07-28">
<name>some weird shit goin` on</name>
<description>Scenes of this show point to insanely strange events which seem to be taking place; throughout its episodes, the show may or may not explain what is going on. Either way, many viewers will find that a succinct and accurate way to describe the show is "WTF?", and the show`s explanations (or lack thereof) to the events will often be subject of heated debate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6494" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>half-length episodes</name>
<description>Half-length episodes are regular episodes that are somewhat shorter than the standard length. This includes episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length; shows with episodes up to and including 10 minutes are http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes] instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6717" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-07-26">
<name>improvised dialogue</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="8456" type="cameo appearance in" update="2015-08-14">
<rating votes="868">7.66</rating>
<name>Doraemon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Doraemon is the titular robotic cat sent back in time by Sewashi to aid Nobita. He possesses a fourth-dimensional pocket from which he can acquire various kinds of futuristic tools, gadgets, and playthings from a future department store. Doraemon originally had ears but they were bitten off by a robotic mouse in the 22nd century. As a result, he developed a morbid fear of mice despite being a robotic cat. He also has the tendency to panic during emergencies, characterized by him frantically trying to pull out a very much-needed tool from his pocket, only to produce a huge assortment of unrelated household items.
Doraemon`s physical appearance changed as the manga progressed. At first, he was predominantly blue, with a blue tail, a white stomach, and flesh-coloured hands and feet. He also stooped, and had a body much larger than his head. In later issues, he sported a smaller body, white hands and feet, and a red tail--the appearance most identify him with today.
In "The Doraemons" story arc, it is revealed that Doraemon`s original paint color was yellow. After getting his ears gnawed off by a robot mouse, he slipped into depression on top of a tower, where he drank a potion labeled "sadness". As he wept, the yellow color washed off and his voice changed due to the potion.
Doraemon weighs 129.3 kg (285 lbs) and measures at 129.3 cm (4`3") tall. He is able to run at 129.3 km/h (80.3 mph) when scared and jump 129.3 m (424.2 ft) when threatened. His maximum power is 129.3 bhp. His wrist, head, and chest circumference are all 129.3 cm. His feet is 129.3 mm in diameter. He is manufactured on September 3, 2112 (12/9/3), at the Matsushiba Robot Factory. Doraemon is considered a substandard product because many of his robotic features (ie. radar whiskers and cat-calling bell) malfunctioned after production. One can turn off Doraemon by pulling his balloon tail.
Doraemon`s favourite food is dorayaki, a Japanese treat filled with red bean paste. Speculations led to dorayaki being the origin of his name. However, it was revealed in one of the manga chapters that his name originates from the Japanese word nora neko for "stray cat", and the -emon ending which is part of traditional Japanese names, as seen also in, for example, Ishikawa Goemon.
In the 2007 birthday episode, `MS-903` is used to call Doraemon by the factory owner where Doraemon is produced.
Doraemon usually uses the phrase "nanoda".</description>
<picture>2237.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="11210" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-01-04">
<rating votes="40">8.23</rating>
<name>Kiki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kiki is a 13-year-old witch-in-training, living in a small rural village where http://anidb.net/ch40118 [her mother] is the resident herbalist. According to witches` tradition she has to leave her home at the age of 13 and find a place in http://anidb.net/ch40121 [another town] where she can stand on her own feet even though flying on her broom is the only skill she can master so far.</description>
<picture>79435.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="33162" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-08-28">
<rating votes="2">4.49</rating>
<name>Fuguta Sazae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>1281.gif</picture>
</character>
<character id="36797" type="main character in" update="2011-09-17">
<rating votes="5">6.95</rating>
<name>Korokoro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>56326.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1511" picture="173601.jpg">Akesaka Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36798" type="main character in" update="2011-09-17">
<rating votes="2">2.14</rating>
<name>Shirushiru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>56319.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1609" picture="19579.jpg">Mizuhara Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36799" type="main character in" update="2011-09-17">
<rating votes="2">2.14</rating>
<name>Pikupiku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>56320.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20025" picture="132938.jpg">Mimori Suzuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40322" type="appears in" update="2012-01-09">
<rating votes="2">8.54</rating>
<name>Mochida Fusako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Woman from another world.</description>
<picture>79710.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1511" picture="173601.jpg">Akesaka Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53847" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-05-17">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Sarsar</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173575.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20025" picture="132938.jpg">Mimori Suzuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53848" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-05-17">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Kurkur</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173576.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1511" picture="173601.jpg">Akesaka Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53849" type="appears in" update="2015-05-19">
<rating votes="1">2.08</rating>
<name>Jasmine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173649.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1511" picture="173601.jpg">Akesaka Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53850" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-05-17">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Furfur</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173574.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1609" picture="19579.jpg">Mizuhara Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="146202" update="2012-12-28">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2012-12-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">お便り紹介コーナー / 第2期を一緒にのぞいちゃおう!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 0</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otayori Shoukai Corner / Dai 2 Ki o Issho ni Nozoi Chaou!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146203" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2013-03-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">gdgd学園</title>
<title xml:lang="en">pkpk, shrshr, krkr appear!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gdgd Gakuen</title>
<summary>Picking the right club is very important!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617411</identifier>
<identifier>gdgd-fairies</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146204" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2013-03-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">名言</title>
<title xml:lang="en">nmnm Appears!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meigen</title>
<summary>shr-chan wants to leave behind a memorable quote. And everyone comes out for a game of baseball.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617409</identifier>
<identifier>gdgd-fairies</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146205" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2013-03-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">キャンプ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">usus Appears</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Camp</title>
<summary>The gdgd Fairies along with their new friends go on a magical camping trip.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617407</identifier>
<identifier>gdgd-fairies</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146206" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2013-03-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢</title>
<title xml:lang="en">mkmk appears!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume</title>
<summary>shr-chan starts the story, kr-chan builds up the story, and it`s up to pk-chan to finish it.  But her dad might cause problems.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617405</identifier>
<identifier>gdgd-fairies</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146207" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2013-02-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">引っ越し</title>
<title xml:lang="en">umum Appears!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hikkoshi</title>
<summary>Three new fairies have moved in and try to figure out how to introduce themselves to their neighbors.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617403</identifier>
<identifier>gdgd-fairies</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146208" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2013-02-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">入れ替わり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">trtr appears!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Irekawari</title>
<summary>A nasty impact has caused the fairies to switch bodies and later pkpk meets her father.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617401</identifier>
<identifier>gdgd-fairies</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146209" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2013-02-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">gdgdトラベル妖精s</title>
<title xml:lang="en">tgtg Appears!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gdgd Trouble Yousei S</title>
<summary>The Fairies take a holiday to a hot spring and play a very interesting game.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617399</identifier>
<identifier>gdgd-fairies</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146210" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2013-02-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">タイムマシン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">lplp appears!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Time Machine</title>
<summary>The Fairies go back in time and everything makes starts to make sense.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617397</identifier>
<identifier>gdgd-fairies</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146211" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2013-01-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジャムの瓶のフタ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">gdgd and Magic are Real</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jamu no Bin no Futa</title>
<summary>What’s the difference between a witch and a magical girl? This time the fairies play, What’s in the box?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617395</identifier>
<identifier>gdgd-fairies</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146212" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2013-01-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぐだぐだ電話相談室</title>
<title xml:lang="en">gdgd Advice Hotline</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gudaguda Denwa Soudanshitsu</title>
<summary>Viewers have a chance to call in and get helpful advice from the Fairies. 
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617393</identifier>
<identifier>gdgd-fairies</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146213" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2013-01-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">天気</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Weather</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenki</title>
<summary>The fairies discuss the weather, heroes, and the dubbing lake returns. 
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617391</identifier>
<identifier>gdgd-fairies</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146214" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2013-01-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">デジャブ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Deja Vu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Deja Vu</title>
<summary>Join krkr, pkpk, and shrshr for Tea Time, the Magic Room, and the all new Magic Speaker.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>617389</identifier>
<identifier>gdgd-fairies</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
