<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9484" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-04-12</startdate>
<enddate>2013-09-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Toaru Kagaku no Railgun S</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">とある科学の超電磁砲S</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Toaru Kagaku no Choudenjihou S</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">railgun s</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">To Aru Kagaku no Railgun S</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">某科学的超电磁炮 S</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">toaru s</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">とある科学の超電磁砲[レールガン]S</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">A Certain Scientific Railgun S</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">어떤 과학의 초전자포 S</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">科學超電磁砲S</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">科学的超电磁炮S</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="official">یک ریلگان علمی خاص اس</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14441" type="Sequel">Toaru Kagaku no Railgun T</anime>
<anime id="6460" type="Prequel">Toaru Kagaku no Railgun</anime>
<anime id="10453" type="Side Story">Toaru Kagaku no Railgun S: Daiji na Koto wa Zenbu Sentou ni Osowatta</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="10">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="361472">This Sequel is more awesome than i was expecting it to be, the drama halfway through the series is amazing.  Ofcourse fans i would advise that you take time to watch " To Aru Majutsu no Index " to give you a more broader knowledge of the "To Aru" story.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="110081">If you`ve seen the original "Index" show, you know about the storyline that develops throughout this season - yes, we get to see the "Sisters" story-arc from Misaka`s point of view and fill in the blanks left by "Index" season 1.
If you haven`t seen "Index", be prepared for a much darker set of episodes compared to "Railgun`s" previous story-arcs.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="416687">Much of Railgun S is just a retelling of an early Index arc: same story, cast, composer, studio.  Nothing new here...except Nagai Tatsuyuki.  That Railgun S blows away the original so thoroughly is a testament to Nagai`s directorial brilliance.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="396857">After rewatching both seasons of Index, and both seasons of Railgun, in preparation for season 3 of Index, I figured for this particular season I`d write a recommendation. It really is striking to me how the first two thirds of Railgun S somehow manages to be heads and shoulders above any of the previous seasons of both Railgun and Index (the last third though, which is an anime original story, is bland and boring). The action is way cooler. The story is great. Characters are better too. And although not all that important, it`s visually the prettiest looking season so far. But what really matters is the vastly superior directing and music. There are a few select scenes that might really strike a nerve, touch your heart, and move you. This is definitely the darkest adaptation yet, with a few scenes of bloody violence, and there is tragedy, but there is also wonderful resolution of those tragedies. Do yourself a favour and watch this one.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="84998">If you are a fan of the Index franchise then this is very watchable. It`s MUCH better than its prequel series. It has its flaws but it`s very watchable if you are already familiar with the characters and setting.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="469382">The Index franchise`s best arc (LN`s included) from Misaka`s point of view. As long as you ignore the second arc, this is a must watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="106569">Electrifying!
Best anime of 2013!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="260717">Absolutely amazing. The To Aru series have come a long way.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="478777">Truly magnificent! Nothing compared to the first season and I can definitely see why:
Character development!

Not only does this season take a significantly darker tone that really does Mikoto justice as a heroine, it truly manages to deliver a stunning, absolutely emotional retelling of the sisters arc from Toaru Majutsu no Index S1 . Mikoto`s interaction with Touma receives a beautiful and emotional makeover compared to the latter and you get to see the Mikoto`s sweet, vulnerable side. After that it is IMPOSSIBLE not to fall in love with her character and appreciate her as a heroine.

Unfortunately I cannot give this more than 8 because FRANKLY I didn`t care about anything that happened after episode 17. I guess the one thing I enjoyed during those last episodes was seeing Mikoto ``grow up``  as a person. 

Definitely, DEFINITELY a must see! ONCE again watch this according to "Full chronological order" available on reddit!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>https://toaru-project.com/railgun_s/</url>
<creators>
<name id="4344" type="Series Composition">Minakami Seishi</name>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="2188" type="Direction">Nagai Tatsuyuki</name>
<name id="6874" type="Character Design">Haimura Kiyotaka</name>
<name id="6888" type="Original Work">Fuyukawa Motoi</name>
<name id="6886" type="Original Work">Kamachi Kazuma</name>
<name id="3896" type="Music">I`ve Sound</name>
<name id="4112" type="Music">Iuchi Maiko</name>
<name id="3082" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tomioka Hiroshi</name>
<name id="9564" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yamashita Yuu</name>
<name id="1795" type="Animation Character Design">Tanaka Yuuichi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the Toaru Kagaku no Railgun manga written by http://anidb.net/cr6886 [Kamachi Kazuma] and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr6888 [Fuyukawa Motoi], which in itself is a spin-off of the light novel, manga and anime series http://anidb.net/a5975 [Toaru Majutsu no Index].
Academy City is the home to circa 2.3 million citizens, about 80% of whom are students working to develop psychic powers and advanced technology. Students are ranked according to levels corresponding to their psychic powers: those without any are ranked at Level 0, and those with some manner of powers progress from Level 1, the weakest, to Level 5, the strongest. Only seven students in the whole city are ranked Level 5, and these seven are ranked among themselves as well.
Electro-master http://anidb.net/ch2469 [Misaka Mikoto] is a headstrong Level 5 esper, ranked third in the city. Her perverted and passionate roommate, http://anidb.net/ch2470 [Shirai Kuroko], is a Level 4 Teleporter and a member of law enforcement and public safety corps http://anidb.net/ch14760 [Judgment]. http://anidb.net/ch10392 [Uiharu Kazari] is Kuroko`s shy Level 1 partner at Judgment and a specialist at hacking and information gathering. http://anidb.net/ch10391 [Saten Ruiko] is Kazari`s mischievous friend who has a habit of flipping the latter`s skirt to find out what color of underwear she is currently wearing, much to her chagrin, and a Level 0.
In this city where supernatural powers abound and urban legends are an integral part of daily life, there is never a dull day, and things are about to get more exciting again, not necessarily in a desirable way. The latest and greatest urban legends talk about money cards hidden all over the city and some mysterious project that involves clones. Having once agreed to cede her DNA map to a research that aimed to cure a form of muscular dystrophy, Mikoto isn`t any pleased to hear about that project, fearing that these clones may be hers.
She sets out to investigate the case, and her preliminary results show that she was indeed considered for the project, but the city`s supercomputer, Tree Diagram, indicated that her clones would be far weaker than herself. Mikoto is relieved, but not for long, as she is about to discover many sleep-depriving truths about the cloning project. Meanwhile, just what are those money cards about, and, more importantly, are they anyhow related to the clones?
— written by Hinoe</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2666">7.52</permanent>
<temporary count="2690">7.74</temporary>
<review count="2">8.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>233287.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14853</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19697</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>16049</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5244</identifier>
<identifier>uqokfg</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://toaru-project.com/railgun_s/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>A_Certain_Scientific_Railgun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>とある科学の超電磁砲</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2937</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>345236</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15946</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/3941</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2013/toarukagakunorailgun_s</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=yRVqp0B5QOc</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=Bd-LBH1iQOs</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=I1Yef5i7oDI</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=FlTz_yrqZaM</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=TYipT9lbLuU</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=y6zgm2scKIE</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>a-certain-scientific-railgun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19832</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>18324</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1018" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-25">
<name>middle school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1279" parentid="2869" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-18">
<name>all-girls school</name>
<description>This school is only for female students. There may be a few male teachers though.</description>
<picurl>70853.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1864" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-14">
<name>extrasensory perception</name>
<description>Extrasensory perception (ESP), involves reception of information not gained through the recognized physical senses but sensed with the mind. The term was coined by Sir Richard Burton, and adopted by Duke University psychologist J. B. Rhine to denote psychic abilities such as telepathy and clairvoyance, and their trans-temporal operation as precognition or retrocognition. ESP is also sometimes casually referred to as a sixth sense, gut instinct or hunch, which are historical English idioms. The term implies acquisition of information by means external to the basic limiting assumptions of science, such as that organisms can only receive information from the past to the present.
In Japanese usage the term is often misappropriated to refer to any supernatural, non-magical, super power. Users of such powers are called `esper` in Japanese. The term `esper` is not normally in use outside of Japan but is slowly being introduced due to its usage in anime and manga.
In anime/manga the following powers, among others, are described as ESP:
- telepathy
- precognition
- clairvoyance
- retrocognition
- remote viewing
- aura reading
- out-of-body experiences (OBE)
- psychokinesis</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2072" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>maid</name>
<description>A maid is a female employed in domestic service. They usually wear uniforms. Since their nature is to be obedient and serve their goshujin-sama (master), they are one of the most desired types of women in Japan, a dream of every Japanese man, particularly http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku]. Often seen in so-called Maid Cafes in Akihabara, where male customers can for a little time enjoy the feeling of being served by a woman. The male gender opposite is the butler.</description>
<picurl>4954.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2671" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>school dormitory</name>
<description>A school dormitory or residence hall is the student living quarters at an elite academy, boarding school, or military school. The main characters may live or work at the dormitory, and it often becomes the backdrop for a reoccurring part of the story.</description>
<picurl>223167.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2769" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>hyperspace mallet</name>
<description>It comes from nowhere, it strikes without mercy, and disappears again. It`s a mallet the size of a circus sledgehammer, and it`s evidence that anime characters watch too many Bugs Bunny cartoons or Three Stooges shorts. An angry character — usually but not restricted to short-tempered schoolgirls — can often whip out a massive hammer with which to slam the target (and cause) of her ire.
In Fan Fic circles, the notional storage place for mallets when not in use is known as hammerspace or malletspace.
A recent variation is to have the character pull out a http://anidb.net/t1662 [harisen], a huge folded fan made out of paper or metal, a.k.a. the Paper Fan of Doom, and smack them with that. This is usually less painful-looking than the mallet, unless she uses it to deliver a Megaton Punch.
Ironically, this is now a Dead Horse Trope in the West, where it originated; modern Western examples are typically from shows invoking anime, which has added its own touches to the mix, or from homages to Warner Brothers cartoons.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>10253.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2822" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>skirt flipping</name>
<description>Naughty characters — usually boys — flip the skirts of female protagonists to ascertain what panties they are wearing (also see Pantsu category).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2907" parentid="2636" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>genetic modification</name>
<description>Story-wise, genetic modification is usually centred on humans, probably the most subtle and creepy way of messing with mankind. Playing with the fear of the unknown, genetically altered humans are technically a new species, that may not only surpass but actually replace unaltered humans. The level of modification will vary from subtle changes in "look" (e.g. super-human beauty), to mental enhancements (PSI powers), to more or less atrocious adaptations to extreme environments (breath under water, radiation resistance). Note that changes in Aliens would be difficult to pinpoint, after all they are alien.</description>
<picurl>223941.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3316" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-08-10">
<name>despair</name>
<description>Involves characters that may be lost in negatively emotional atmospheres created through feelings of hopelessness and suffering.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3529" parentid="2627" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>space elevator</name>
<description>A needle-like structure placed on the equator of a planet connecting the surface with a low planetary orbit in about 200-300km height (it may even reach out into a geostationary orbit). Very efficient way to move mass "out of" a planet`s gravity well — much more efficient than e.g. chemical rockets.
Alas it is not yet possible to build a space elevator, because all know materials would be crushed under their own weight. There is a faint hope that carbon-based nano-tubes may be a usable material in the future though.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5816" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-10-03">
<name>massacre</name>
<description>Mass murder.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6062" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-05">
<name>heroic sacrifice</name>
<description>"In order to save the many, the few will need to sacrifice their lives..." or so this character may think. 
In a seemingly hopeless situation, against impossible odds, the character does not choose the path of the coward and run, he or she chooses to bravely face the enemy, fully aware that this will mean death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6088" parentid="2785" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-01-29">
<name>unrequited shoujo ai</name>
<description>At least one female character has a romantic or sexual interest in another female character, but the feelings are not returned.
This can be because the recipient is oblivious, straight, or simply not interested.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="870" type="appears in" update="2019-04-07">
<rating votes="457">3.24</rating>
<name>Index</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Index, also known by her full name, Index Librorum Prohibitorum, is the series` co-heroine, a young nun from Necessarius ("Church of Necessary Evil"), a branch of the Church of England. Her mind has been implanted with the 103,000 magical texts of the Index-Librorum-Prohibitorum as she possess Photographic memory at the cost of her own memories, or so the church authorities say. Her sorcery name is Dedicatus545. She is said to have 15% of memory space left to use in daily activities, which allows her to live normally for less than a year. However, all of this is a lie and are the church`s plan to make her unable to betray, by "maintenance" her once the memory has come to its limit.</description>
<picture>232175.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2342" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-07">
<rating votes="795">6.50</rating>
<name>Kamijou Touma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kamijou Touma is the main protagonist of Toaru Majutsu no Index and a recurring character in its spin-off Railgun.
He has the lowest psychic rank possible at Level 0— largely because the people testing psychic abilities cannot detect or classify his abilities. Due to this, the founder of Academy City considers him neither a Psychic nor a Magician but rather a normal person with a unique ability.
Actually his power is Imagine Breaker (幻想殺し, Gensou Goroshi, "Imagine Killer"), a power which negates all magic, psychic, or divine powers but also his own good luck. He tends to stay away from trouble but possesses a strong sense of justice, albeit somewhat shallow and dogmatic. In order to save Index from the need of a memory reset, he had activated her self-protection system and destroyed the spell responsible for her mind strain but ended up losing all of his past memories, including everything about Index, when he came in contact with Feather of Light (光の羽, Hikari no Hane); this remains a secret to everyone except himself, the doctor that takes care of him (who is, unknown to Touma, the Heaven Canceler) and later Mikoto in the sixteenth novel. Though he no longer remembers the past, he has not completely forgotten the people he cares about.
Throughout the series, he tries to live his life normally while still facing against the many adversaries from the worlds of science and most of the magic and the conflicts that follow. Despite his very bad luck, he has managed to get the interests and hearts of many ladies who are infatuated with him, which Aisa jokes about, that his life is like a dating sim where he is bound to unlock more paths to more girls.</description>
<picture>232176.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="545" picture="188506.jpg">Abe Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2469" type="main character in" update="2019-04-11">
<rating votes="2418">8.60</rating>
<name>Misaka Mikoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Misaka Mikoto is one of the series` main heroines, as well as the main protagonist of the side story, A Certain Scientific Railgun. Her parents are Tabigake and Misuzu Misaka, which her father is a prominent businessman and millionaire. Despite her rich background, she grew up in a normal typical childhood.
At a young age, she was discovered to be a Level 1 Electromaster, espers who have the ability to generate and control electricity. She enrolled into Academy City to train her powers and worked very hard until her powers were ranked Level 5, the highest esper ranking, with her being the third strongest of the seven espers with this rank. As an electromaster, she can generate and manipulate electricity which she can use to shock opponents, hack into electronics like computer networks and security systems, and use electromagnetism to cling to surfaces or manipulate iron particles into a chain-sword whip. Mikoto`s signature move is her ability to shoot metal projectiles such as coins at high destructive speeds, hence her nickname, The Railgun. If she is in a bad mood, she will sometimes let out bursts of electricity describing her emotional stress, usually resulting in power failures or even citywide blackouts.
Mikoto attends Tokiwadai Middle School, a famous girls` school for the rich and elite psychics and one of the five elite schools of Academy City. To most people, she is considered a proper lady, but in reality, she has a short-tempered, prideful, and improper attitude with some tomboyish tendencies and insecurities, a fact few other characters know. She is fond of cute, childish things, such as flowery pajamas and Gekota, the popular frog mascot franchise. Contrary to what she claims, she has a strong sense of morals and hates injustice. Mikoto has a one-sided rivalry with Touma, who nicknamed her Biri Biri (ビリビリ, relating to the sound of an electric shock), ever since their first meeting before the events of the first novel when he first dissipated her electricity after he unsuccessfully tried to rescue her. Since that incident, she is always trying to have a proper match with Touma and defeat him despite his many attempts to avoid conflict with her.
When Mikoto was young, she was tricked into giving the city`s scientist her DNA under the pretense of finding the cure for Duchenne muscular dystrophy; their actual goal to create military-grade combat clones of her. When it was discovered that the clones did not have the same power level as Mikoto, they were instead used in an Project called Level 6 Shift, intended to make Accelerator the first level 6 esper by having him kill 20,000 clones. The events of how Mikoto tried to stop the project are briefly mentioned in the third novel and expanded upon in the Railgun manga. When all of her attempts failed, she contemplates letting herself be killed by Accelerator, as an unexpected variable to destroy Tree Diagram`s calculations. However, it is not until Touma intervenes and beats Accelerator, proving him to be really weak, that the project is canceled and the remaining 9969 surviving Sisters are spared.
After those events, she eventually develops strong romantic feelings towards Touma but is unable to express them due to her insecurities and the fact other girls are also interested in him. Even though she and Touma tend to bicker and argue with each other, they share a somewhat friendly relationship.</description>
<picture>232410.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2470" type="main character in" update="2019-04-11">
<rating votes="973">6.22</rating>
<name>Shirai Kuroko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shirai Kuroko is a level 4 psychic, and member of Judgement, a special public committee group, whose duty it is to maintain peace and order in Academy City. She is in love with Misaka, who she calls "Onee-sama" (sister) and tends to get jealous if someone else gets her attention. This unfortunately happens to be Touma, since he has caught the attention of Misaka for various reasons. Her special power is instant teleportation, which allows her to teleport herself and anything in her possession - as long as it weighs around 130-137 kilograms - to anywhere in a radius of around 81-85 metres.</description>
<picture>232414.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2473" type="appears in" update="2019-04-11">
<rating votes="194">5.78</rating>
<name>Tsukuyomi Komoe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Despite her childish and very short (135 cm) appearance, she is actually an adult and one of Touma`s teachers. This is proven by her apartment being littered with beer cans and cigarettes. She also contradicts her age by acting childish to her students, having a child-like crush on Touma, and ending her sentences with desu, something a child usually does. This irony means that she is often regarded as one of the seven great mysteries of Academy City.</description>
<picture>232411.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7856" type="cameo appearance in" update="2017-10-07">
<rating votes="244">8.81</rating>
<name>Kino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kino is sort of a valiant stoic cipher almost like a seinen hero. Kino comes off as androgynous and is considered male as often as female by the people she meets. Kino never talks much and never unnecessarily. She will lend a hand to someone in need and even risk her life for another but she does not purposely get involved in the affairs of others. Kino is often cynical and skeptical but you get the feeling deep down she still believes in people and the world. If Kino has one strong driving force and personality trait it seems to be curiosity. She will always investigate something if it seems intriguing and is sometimes the only reason she will interact with anyone.
Source: Reverse Thieves</description>
<picture>187645.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="10391" type="main character in" update="2011-04-26">
<rating votes="479">7.25</rating>
<name>Saten Ruiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saten Ruiko is a Level 0, classmate and friend of Uiharu who is known for wearing a flower on the left side of her hair. She is a little shameless as she sometimes flips Uiharu`s skirt in public. When rumours of a special tool that increases psychic powers called the "Power Upper" spread, she considers obtaining it out of envy as she does not have any apparent powers. When she uses it, Ruiko consequently winds up in a coma and gradually recovers thanks to the help the creator of the Level Upper. She first appears in the To Aru Kagaku no Railgun manga and makes a cameo appearance in the To Aru Majutsu no Index light novel series and the opening of the anime and is set to appear in the animated Railgun spinoff.</description>
<picture>33388.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10392" type="main character in" update="2011-04-26">
<rating votes="321">4.79</rating>
<name>Uiharu Kazari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Uiharu Kazari is Shirai`s friend and colleague in Judgment and another protagonist in To Aru Kagaku no Railgun. Shy and humble, she goes to a different middle school from Shirai and is known for wearing a headband made of flowers on her head, and sometimes a surgical mask as she constantly suffers the flu. Her powers are currently unknown. She makes a cameo appearance in the opening of the anime and is set to appear in the animated Railgun spinoff. She has enormous eyebrows.</description>
<picture>33387.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10527" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-07">
<rating votes="341">7.63</rating>
<name>Accelerator</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Accelerator is the most powerful Psychic in Academy City. His real name is unknown, though Accelerator recalls his surname was composed of two characters and his given name consisted of three characters. First appearing as an antagonist, he later becomes a main character and the lead of the science side in the Toaru Majutsu no Index series. Because Accelerator has been this reflexively powerful since childhood, he was unstoppable even when the military was sent to kill him. However, these past influences resulted in his inability to trust others and he was left alone. After meeting Touma, he develops a sense of admiration and jealousy towards Touma`s heroism and ability to help others, contrasting with how Accelerator feels he is only able to destroy.
A sadistic boy about the same age as Touma, he has an ability called Vector Change, a form of telekinesis allowing him to change the vector values of anything he touches. This ability allows Accelerator perform feats such as reversing the blood flow inside a person`s body, increasing the wind velocity around him to create a massive plasma storm, and blocking sound. His ability is automatic, which means that he must consciously allow gravity to affect him and that his body blocks all ultraviolet radiation, resulting his albino appearance (white hair and pale skin) because his body is unable to make melanin. The automatic nature of Redirection also prevents the use of projectiles (like bullets) and explosives (like bombs) against him. After being shot by http://anidb.net/ch14551 [Amai Ao], Accelerator`s ability to use his power is hindered, but slowly recovers with the help of http://anidb.net/ch14534 [Heaven Canceller] and the http://anidb.net/ch14538 [Misaka Network]. However, he is forced to use a cane and is restricted to using his ability for only 15 minutes at a time, as well as losing more than half of his computation ability even with 10,000 sisters doing calculations for him.
Accelerator`s unique ability make him the subject of an experiment attempting to create the first Level 6 psychic; according to the city`s best supercomputer, Tree Diagram (which was unprecedentedly destroyed by Index`s Dragon Breath), this feat could only be achieved by killing 128 skilled Level 5 psychics without a single failure. Since there are only six other known Level 5s in Academy City, an alternative plan was formed to level up Accelerator by having him kill 20,000 skilled Level 2 psychics: the Misaka clones. He willingly joins the experiment to gain a reputation as the most powerful and feared psychic that no one would be foolish enough to challenge and even killed many who got in his way. The Sisters` memories of his behavior during the experiment may suggest that he is, in a way, a pacifist; since his power won`t disappear, the only way he sees to stop fighting is to be so strong and sadistic that no one would raise a finger against him. He even seems to attempt to frighten the Sisters or otherwise encourage them to refuse the battle. Mikoto tries to stop the experiment to save her sisters, but it is Touma who finally does so and defeats Accelerator after discovering his weakness: Accelerator was physically weak because of his total reliance on his powers. Overconfidence in his psychic abilities resulted in his defeat as Touma beat him with his Imagine Breaker and street-fighting skills.
After his defeat, he reappears later and takes a more heroic role protecting a girl named Last Order, the last Misaka clone. In the aftermath of the incident, Accelerator is shot in the head by Amai Ao, damaging his brain and severely limiting the use of his power.</description>
<picture>232181.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12365" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-26">
<rating votes="162">5.58</rating>
<name>Kongou Mitsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kongou Mitsuko is a Level 4, 2nd year transfer student of Tokiwadai Middle School. As Kuroko`s rival, she is confident, boastful, and desires to become a Level 5. Although she if often boastful about her abilities, she usually finds herself the victim of several attacks. Like all Tokidawai students, she lives in one of the school`s dormitories albeit her dormitory is located within the School Garden District.
Her ability is called "Aero Hand" (空力使い, Kuuriki Tsukai) which with any object she touches, a powerful gust of wind will take form, propelling it like a missile. She also owns a pet snake named Ekaterina. She originally appears in the eighth novel and makes her first animated appearance in the Toaru Kagaku no Railgun anime.</description>
<picture>37373.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1798" picture="20493.jpg">Kotobuki Minako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12366" type="appears in" update="2011-03-15">
<rating votes="35">4.31</rating>
<name>Tessou Tsuzuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tessou Tsuzuri is a grade school teacher who wears glasses with a rather panicky personality and also a member of the Anti-Skills, where she normally partners with Yomikawa. Her lack of confidence makes her prone to messing up on the field. She enjoys beat-em-up games.</description>
<picture>37374.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="424" picture="224027.jpg">Endou Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12957" type="appears in" update="2011-03-15">
<rating votes="31">4.72</rating>
<name>Wannai Kinuho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wannai Kinuho is Kuroko`s classmate who resides in the same dorms as Mitsuko. She is best friends with Awatsuki Maaya and together they are members of the swim club with Kinuho having the ability of aquakinesis, which gives her control over water. Kinuho was once saved from some thugs by Mikoto and is thankful to Mikoto on what she did. They are often seen hanging around Mitsuko.</description>
<picture>38716.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12958" type="appears in" update="2011-03-15">
<rating votes="34">5.23</rating>
<name>Awatsuki Maaya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Awatsuki Maaya is Kuroko`s classmate who resides in the same dorms as Mitsuko. She is best friends with Wannai Kinuho and together they are members of the swim club. They are often seen hanging around Mitsuko.</description>
<picture>38717.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="617" picture="65451.jpg">Nanjou Yoshino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12959" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-15">
<rating votes="84">5.97</rating>
<name>Konori Mii</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Konori Mii is a high school student and Chief of the 177th Branch of Judgment where Kazari and Kuroko work. As their sempai before becoming chief, she tries to make sure both girls do their work at Judgment seriously and at the same time wants them to be safe. She is a Level 3 esper with a power called Clairvoyance (透視系能力 (クレアボイアンス), Toushi Kei Nouryoku) which gives her X-ray vision, allowing her to spot concealed weapons. In the past, she used to be a member of a Skill-Out gang called Big Spider to find a purpose in her life. It was there where she met and fell in love with Wataru Kurozuma, the leader of the Big Spider`s. But after his supposed death two years ago, the incident made her change her ways and become the Judgment member she is now.</description>
<picture>38718.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="210" picture="71057.jpg">Ueda Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12960" type="appears in" update="2009-11-13">
<rating votes="31">5.25</rating>
<name>Ryoukan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38719.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13328" type="appears in" update="2013-05-05">
<rating votes="7">3.45</rating>
<name>Hazamaya Kana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hazamaya Kana is a girl who lost her bag and asks Judgement for help. Misaka, mistakingly thinks the bag is related to the recent graviton explosions case, leading her to a wild-goose chase.
The girl later appears once again in the Seventh Mist shopping centre, where Kaitabi Hatsuya plans to detonate his next bomb. Her, Misaka and Uiharu are saved by Touma`s Imagine Breaker in the occuring explosion.</description>
<picture>136260.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13691" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-11">
<rating votes="165">5.61</rating>
<name>Yomikawa Aiho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A teacher at Touma`s school and a friend of Komoe. She is beautiful, has glamorous proportions, and is always seen with a green jersey. She is a member of the Anti-Skills and cares deeply for her students, and is apparently an active peacekeeper within the Academic City. A favor to her old friend, Yomikawa is asked by Yoshikawa Kikyou to take care of Accelerator and Last Order after they are released from the hospital.</description>
<picture>232406.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="160" picture="30490.jpg">Kaida Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13692" type="appears in" update="2013-10-10">
<rating votes="7">1.52</rating>
<name>Kihara Gensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kihara Gensei is a senior scientist in neurology. While he may look like a kind old man, but beneath this facade lies a heartless man who has no problem of using the lives of innocent children, all in the name Science. He was http://anidb.net/ch12962 [Harumi]`s former boss who trick her and her students to partake in an experiment whose real purpose was to test Esper`s AIM fields going out of control which left her students in a coma. Later in the Toaru Kagaku no Railgun anime, it is revealed that this experiment was in fact part of a larger plan, the Level 6 Ability Crystal project which aims to create a Level 6 Esper. Gensei theorizes those who have potential to become a Level 6 when given Ability Crystals, a by product made from the essences and proteins of comatose espers as result of their AIM fields going out of control, will become a Level 6 esper . His current whereabouts are unknown. As his surname suggest, he is Amata Kihara`s father who was introduced in Volume 12 of the novels.
He is also the grandfather of http://anidb.net/ch14937 [Telestina] and used her as a test subject for the Ability Crystals.</description>
<picture>144031.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6942" picture="41078.jpg">Takaoka Binbin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14532" type="appears in" update="2019-03-27">
<rating votes="43">1.89</rating>
<name>Aogami Pierce</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>His real name is unknown. Touma`s friend and classmate. A funny individual who tends to see Touma`s bad luck, who he calls "Kami-yan" in a different way. He is a self-confessed pervert, lolicon, and masochist who enjoys being punished by his teacher, Tsukuyomi. He is always seen with Motoharu. He, Motoharu, and Touma are known as the three idiots in their class as not only do they have the lowest test scores, but they are also Level 0s (except the latter two have good reasons for being that way).</description>
<picture>231737.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5040" picture="88977.jpg">Kawahara Yoshihisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14534" type="appears in" update="2020-04-12">
<rating votes="75">5.82</rating>
<name>Kaeru Kao no Ishi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The "Heaven Canceller". Often mentioned as "the Frog-Faced Doctor" by http://anidb.net/ch2342 [Kamijou Touma], he is an exceptionally-gifted and benevolent physician who can cure any illness and heal any injury, even if it is terminal. He is only unable to heal specific brain-related injuries, such as the "Imagine-Breaker Boy`s" damaged memories and http://anidb.net/ch10527 [Accelerator]`s computation ability; however, in the latter case, he was able to configure Accelerator to control his powers with support from the Misaka Network. This medical genius also manages the life extension devices for the ruler of http://anidb.net/ch34367 [Academy City], http://anidb.net/ch2731 [Aleister Crowley], while also supporting the foundation of the city itself.</description>
<picture>232416.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="415" picture="241624.jpg">Nakano Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14536" type="appears in" update="2019-04-11">
<rating votes="64">6.17</rating>
<name>Tsuchimikado Maika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Motoharu`s younger step-sister. She wears a maid attire (as she goes to a Maid School) and rides on top of a cleaning `bot. She has a friendly relationship with Touma and knows that he has two girls (Index and Aisa) living with him but keeps the secret between her and Touma and is a good friend of Mikoto as she works at her school. Even though she lives in her school`s dormitory, she sometimes goes to live at her brother`s apartment; for instance, in episode ten, she stays at said residence because her dormitory`s air conditioner breaks down.</description>
<picture>232413.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="304" picture="17139.jpg">Fukuen Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14537" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-11">
<rating votes="206">7.77</rating>
<name>Misaka Imouto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Introduced in both the third volume of the novel and manga, respectively, and episode ten of the anime, Touma meets the younger `twin sister` of Mikoto who he calls Misaka`s sister (御坂妹, Misaka Imouto), who seems rather quiet and emotionless. Her voice is rather monotonous and computer-like. Her speech pattern is unique, for she talks in third person (adding a description of herself after she finishes talking). While both sisters may look alike from a distance, Misaka has paler eyes and wears striped panties under her skirt. Misaka also wears a special set of goggles that enables her to see electron beams and magnetic field lines for the reason that, unlike Mikoto, she does not have that ability. At the beginning of the third volume, Mikoto seems to dislike and worry about Misaka for some reason, and later events reveal why.
In reality, Misaka imouto is a clone of Mikoto; in fact, the first one Touma meets is No. 10032 out of 20,000 other clones (excluding Full-Tuning and Last Order) copied from Mikoto called `The Sisters`. Even though they have a weaker variant of Mikoto`s electric abilities (Level 3), the Sisters` minds are connected by a special psychic ability called Radio Noise (欠陥電気, Kekkan Denki?, "Flawed Electric"), which enables their brainwaves to become electric signals; this allows them to share their thoughts and memories within their communication network, also known as the Misaka Network. Being rapidly-manufactured clones, the Sisters rarely change their facial expression because they did not learn how to. Due to minds having connected to the Misaka Network, most of the Sisters never considered themselves human yet some of them had slight difference in personalities.
20,000 clones were created in total, to be used in an experiment designed to create the first Level 6 psychic ("Level 6 Shift"), Accelerator. By the time of third novel, 10,031 were killed in the experiment. After the Level 6 Shift experiment fails, all 9969 surviving Sisters are ordered back to the research center where they were created to have "readjustments" so that they will have normal life spans. The Sisters later began showing their owned unique personalities to differentiate themselves after learning how to `disconnect` from the Network and keeping their own private memories inaccessible to the others in the Network.
Misaka 10032, also known as Misaka Imouto, is the most prominent clone that is most featured in the series. She is known for having a soft spot for cats which she herself has a pet black kitten. She was the first sister clone that Touma met. Due to the many interactions she had with him, 10032 wonder why she thought about him so much. Misaka 10032 was Accelerator`s latest target in the Level 6 experiment, but Touma managed to stop him before he killed her. Confused, she asks him why he did so since she was a clone, to which he replied that even though she was a clone, she was still an individual with a life. His words (along with Mikoto`s) affect her so much that she and the Sisters decide to help Touma by controlling all of the city`s wind turbines to prevent Accelerator from creating a plasma storm.
After the Level 6 experiment was canceled, she was one of ten Sisters to stay in Academy City while the rest went overseas around the world for treatment. She later falls in love with Touma and receives a necklace from him (he bought it for her during his date with Mikoto and mistook 10032 for Mikoto) which she treasures.</description>
<picture>232463.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1992" picture="151673.jpg">Sasaki Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14538" type="appears in" update="2015-07-28">
<rating votes="12">8.16</rating>
<name>Sisters</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Introduced in both the third volume of the novel and manga, respectively, and episode ten of the anime, http://anidb.net/ch2342 [Touma] meets the younger twin sister of http://anidb.net/ch2469 [Mikoto] who he calls Misaka`s sister (御坂妹, Misaka Imouto), who seems rather quiet and emotionless. Her voice is rather monotonous and computer-like. Her speech pattern is unique, for she talks in third person (adding a description of herself after she finishes talking). While both sisters may look alike from a distance, Misaka has paler eyes and wears striped panties under her skirt. Misaka also wears a special set of goggles that enables her to see electron beams and magnetic field lines for the reason that, unlike Mikoto, she does not have that ability. At the beginning of the third volume, Mikoto seems to dislike and worry about Misaka for some reason, and later events reveal why.
In reality, Misaka Imouto is a clone of Mikoto; in fact, the first one Touma meets is No. 10032 out of 20,000 other clones (excluding Full-Tuning and http://anidb.net/ch14550 [Last Order]) copied from Mikoto called The Sisters. Even though they have a weaker variant of Mikoto`s electric abilities (Level 3), the Sisters` minds are connected by a special psychic ability called Radio Noise (欠陥電気), which enables their brainwaves to become electric signals; this allows them to share their thoughts and memories within their communication network, also known as the Misaka Network. Being rapidly-manufactured clones, the Sisters rarely change their facial expression because they did not learn how to. Due to minds having connected to the Misaka Network, most of the Sisters never considered themselves human yet some of them had slight difference in personalities.
20,000 clones were created in total, to be used in an experiment designed to create the first Level 6 psychic ("Level 6 Shift"), Accelerator. By the time of third novel, 10,031 were killed in the experiment. After the Level 6 Shift experiment fails, all 9969 surviving Sisters are ordered back to the research center where they were created to have "readjustments" so that they will have normal life spans. The Sisters later began showing their owned unique personalities to differentiate themselves after learning how to disconnect from the Network and keeping their own private memories inaccessible to the others in the Network.</description>
<picture>143487.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1992" picture="151673.jpg">Sasaki Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14550" type="appears in" update="2019-04-11">
<rating votes="216">7.69</rating>
<name>Last Order</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Last Order is the name of http://anidb.net/ch2469 [Misaka Mikoto]`s No. 20001 clone. She is the administrator of the http://anidb.net/ch14538 [Misaka Network] and the fail-safe mechanism in case the Sisters got out of control. She is not designed to function independently and survive for long outside a culture container and appears to be only about ten years old. Due to intercepting an emotion program http://anidb.net/ch55166 [Nunotaba Shinobu] intended to install into all of the clones, she is capable of showing emotions unlike the other sisters and has a close relationship with Mikoto, http://anidb.net/ch14537 [Misaka Imouto], http://anidb.net/ch10527 [Accelerator] and her adult guardians, http://anidb.net/ch13691 [Yomikawa Aiho] and http://anidb.net/ch14552 [Yoshikawa Kikyou]. Like her older clone sisters, she speaks in third person with a description, except she says "Misaka" twice. She has all of the memories of the Misaka clones and has observed Accelerator through this method, posing a theory that Accelerator did not actually want to do the Level 6 Shift experiment.
Accelerator meets Last Order when she follows him home one day after he fends off a bunch of street thugs hearing of his defeat against a Level 0. Though Accelerator tries to dissuade her from hanging around him, she persists in following him around because she wants someone to keep her company. She is later kidnapped by http://anidb.net/ch14551 [Amai Ao] so he can infect the Misaka clones to possibly go on a rampage and attack people. Accelerator manages to stop him but gets injured in the process. Last Order and Accelerator are put under the care of Aiho after the incident. Accelerator does all he can to protect her since she is the first person in his life who requested his help. Throughout the story, she remains with Accelerator and has been involved in situations relating to him. After Accelerator`s confrontation with Aiwass, she is left in critical condition. However, Accelerator brings Last Order with him to Russia in hopes of finding http://anidb.net/ch870 [Index], who may have the knowledge to cure her.</description>
<picture>232462.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="430" picture="246278.jpg">Hidaka Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14551" type="appears in" update="2010-10-17">
<rating votes="9">1.24</rating>
<name>Amai Ao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Former researcher for the "The Sisters" project. His specialty is creating personality data with self-learning capabilities. During the "Level 6 Shift" project, he was assigned to directing the experiments. After the project is put to a stop, he tries to join an organization outside Academy City by planting a virus upon Last Order and leaking information about the city.</description>
<picture>57049.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="644" picture="205640.jpg">Suzuki Tatsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14760" type="appears in" update="2011-07-09">
<rating votes="19">8.79</rating>
<name>Judgment</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The public moral committee. It is made up of students with powers from every grade level whose duty is to maintain peace and order within the school system. As most of the city population are students, it is the duty of Judgment to catch those delinquents misusing their powers along with other offenders and protect the students. Each district in Academy City has at least one Judgment branch office headed by a senior student who serves as a police chief. In the event of a situation that Judgment members cannot handle, their superiors and the city`s security forces, the Anti-Skills will take over. Overall, the role of a Judgment officer is more like a part-time civilian patrol officer as their authority is normally limited to their district area where their local Judgment branch office is located and they can only use their authority at other districts when ordered to by their superiors or in cases of emergency. Most Judgment members can be recognized by the green stripped arm band with a shield symbol they wear.</description>
<picture>6487.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="14761" type="appears in" update="2010-03-23">
<rating votes="14">6.51</rating>
<name>Anti-Skill</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Anti-Skill is the city`s police and security forces. Unlike Judgment, most members of Anti-Skills are adults who are mostly normal people and even school teachers who are trained to deal with the city`s day-to-day activities and security, in addition to dealing with rogue psychics who abuse their powers. Most members of Anti-Skills are seen with special SWAT armor that resist psychic powers along with firearms and riot gear, which shows how serious the situation has to be for them to be called out. They are also responsible in investigating and stopping the experiments that are against the law and inhumane to students but due to the interventions by the city administration, they are stopped from investigating experiments that were approved by the Board of Directors. Their symbol is a three-point spear shaped like a capital "E" turned 90 degrees to the left.</description>
<picture>4219.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="14937" type="appears in" update="2017-07-28">
<rating votes="19">4.24</rating>
<name>Telestina Kihara Lifeline</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of the Multi Active Rescue squad.</description>
<picture>65249.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14939" type="appears in" update="2013-10-10">
<rating votes="7">5.57</rating>
<name>Yanagisako Aomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144033.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14942" type="appears in" update="2010-03-02">
<rating votes="19">4.38</rating>
<name>Haruue Erii</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haruue marks her first appearance in episode 17 where she is helped in a search for her lost locket by Tsuzuri. Later she reappears as an out-of-season transfer student into Sakugawa Middle School`s 2nd year and becomes Uiharu`s roommate.
The locket actually contains a picture of Edasaki Banri. Haruue was raised at a child care institute as a child error. When she was young, she held a strong telepathic connection to Edasaki who stayed at the same institute for some time.</description>
<picture>42840.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24827" type="appears in" update="2011-07-10">
<rating votes="12">7.99</rating>
<name>Tokiwadai Chuugaku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>One of the elite five schools of Academy City, this elite girls middle school is located within District 7, the School Garden.</description>
<picture>6498.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="25329" type="appears in" update="2011-04-04">
<rating votes="31">7.30</rating>
<name>Misaka Misuzu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Misaka Misuzu is Mikoto`s mother, who is currently studying in college. Due to her youthful looks, Touma at first mistakes her as Mikoto`s older sister. She is aware that both her daughter and Index like Touma. Since the sports festival, she has become good friends with Kamijou Shiina.</description>
<picture>64682.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="295" picture="25758.jpg">Shinohara Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34367" type="appears in" update="2014-01-29">
<rating votes="20">7.51</rating>
<name>Gakuen Toshi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Gakuen Toshi, or Academy City, is a city of several schools and institutions of higher learning from kindergarten to university level that learn side-by-side along with the scientists who research on psychic powers and higher technology, the latter being one of the primary reasons for its establishment. It is the most advanced city in the world and its technology is said to be 30 years ahead of what`s `outside` of it.</description>
<picture>149221.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="34537" type="appears in" update="2011-07-14">
<rating votes="14">5.25</rating>
<name>Magical Powered Kanamin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Magical Powered Kanamin is the titular character of the eponymous Magical Powered Kanamin anime which airs in Academy City. The anime is about the adventures of a young girl with magic powers on the run from Roman Catholic Church witch hunters. Index is a big fan of it.</description>
<picture>75414.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54960" type="appears in" update="2019-11-16">
<rating votes="35">7.00</rating>
<name>Shokuhou Misaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shokuhou Misaki is a mysterious Level 5 Tokiwadai student that goes under the alias The Queen. Her ability is Mental Out, the ultimate form of telepathy which includes reading other people`s memories, changing a person`s personality by means of brainwashing, telepathy, memory elimination, amplification of will, reproduction of thought and transplantation of emotions. She appears to activate this ability using a remote control-like device. However, this power does not work on people with electromagnetic properties, such as Mikoto.
As one of the two Level 5s of Tokiwadai, her followers have a rivalry with Mikoto`s fans. Despite this, she is in good terms with Mikoto.
She rarely shows herself in public, instead using her followers or mind controlled people to act as her representatives when talking with individuals.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>68094.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1876" picture="66007.jpg">Asakura Azumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55166" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-27">
<rating votes="20">5.73</rating>
<name>Nunotaba Shinobu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nunotaba Shinobu is a student from Nagatenjouki Academy, who worked on the Sisters` Radio Noise experiment before it was shut down.
She was called again when the Sisters project was revived to be used for the Level 6 Shift program.
However, when she noticed the Sisters clones had something of a conscience, she was unable to see them as objects anymore. She attempted to stop the experiments by using envelopes containing cash cards to lure in witnesses in the unwatched alleyways, where the Sisters would fight Accelerator.
She does not appear to have any powers, but uses good acting to invoke fear into people and make them believe she has a deadly one.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>137226.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9124" picture="186845.jpg">Hayama Ikumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55167" type="appears in" update="2013-04-20">
<rating votes="29">7.92</rating>
<name>Misaka Mikoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135469.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55209" type="appears in" update="2013-04-20">
<rating votes="2">1.89</rating>
<name>Isha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135554.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="369" picture="223406.jpg">Aoyama Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55570" type="appears in" update="2013-10-11">
<rating votes="2">5.40</rating>
<name>Amami Eiga</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144074.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12266" picture="56026.jpg">Kanemoto Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55571" type="appears in" update="2013-10-11">
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<name>Kusakabe Masami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144075.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17069" picture="80944.jpg">Numakura Manami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55753" type="appears in" update="2013-05-11">
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<name>Oyaji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136558.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33894" picture="151731.jpg">Yamagishi Haruo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55899" type="appears in" update="2013-06-22">
<rating votes="8">8.97</rating>
<name>Misaka 9982</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Introduced in Toaru Kagaku no Railgun, she was the first Sister clone Mikoto met. While she was similar to the other clones, 9982 had a rather unusual personality, as she was very interested in the outside world. She was very snarky to people, often giving long detailed critiques on their taste in food. The one thing that she desired was to meet her older sister, Mikoto, the girl whom she was cloned from. Upon their first meeting, the two had an awful start due 9982`s refusal to reveal to Mikoto what the Sisters were involved in, but they both later bonded somewhat after Mikoto gave her a Gekota badge.
Sadly, the meeting would be their last as 9982 was scheduled to fight Accelerator that day. Despite being horribly beaten, including having her leg ripped off, 9982 appreciated the time she spent with Mikoto in her last moments. She died, crushed by a passenger car thrown by Accelerator, still clutching the first and only gift she received from Mikoto.</description>
<picture>136770.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1992" picture="151673.jpg">Sasaki Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56173" type="appears in" update="2013-10-11">
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<name>Minori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144077.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37985" picture="175206.jpg">Asakura Momo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56195" type="appears in" update="2013-10-11">
<rating votes="2">2.58</rating>
<name>Kites Knockraven</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144076.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6125" picture="223612.jpg">Hayashi Kazuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56196" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-09">
<rating votes="52">6.75</rating>
<name>Frenda Seivelun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Frenda Seivelun is a member of ITEM. She makes use of a tape of explosive material and an electronic device to create a fuse that can cut through various objects. Usually the fuses are connected to dolls with explosives within them.</description>
<picture>65247.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="22366" picture="217303.jpg">Uchida Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56197" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-07-28">
<rating votes="33">6.14</rating>
<name>Takitsubo Rikou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takitsubo Rikou is a member of ITEM. Her ability is called AIM Stalker (能力追跡, Nouryoku Tsuiseki) which she uses to track down espers by memorizing their AIM fields. Her ability also allows her to steal other espers` abilities by memorizing their AIM, potentially allowing her to become the eighth Level 5 esper in Academy City.</description>
<picture>65246.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="34426" picture="128153.jpg">Suzaki Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56198" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-11">
<rating votes="35">6.94</rating>
<name>Kinuhata Saiai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kinuhata Saiai is a member of ITEM. Her ability is the Level 4 Offense Armour (窒素装甲, Chisso Soukou), which she uses to control the nitrogen in the atmosphere and create a few centimeters barrier of nitrogen that she can use to attack and defend.</description>
<picture>232495.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18198" picture="228672.jpg">Akasaki Chinatsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56199" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-07-28">
<rating votes="64">4.79</rating>
<name>Mugino Shizuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mugino Shizuri is one of the seven Level 5 espers, ranking fourth after Misaka Mikoto, she is the leader of ITEM, which is at odds with SCHOOL. She looks down upon lower-level espers and does not mind eliminating people who get in her way or go against her, regardless of whether they are enemies or allies.
Her power can create multiple beams that can sear through objects, or she can defend herself by creating a shield of energy. She can also use silicon cards to split her attacks into multiple blasts.</description>
<picture>65245.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56200" type="appears in" update="2013-05-26">
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<name>Driver</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>137128.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24946" picture="200733.jpg">Tamaru Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56510" type="appears in" update="2014-01-29">
<rating votes="2">5.71</rating>
<name>Item</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>149222.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="56897" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<rating votes="16">6.90</rating>
<name>Level 5</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Within Academy City, the Level 5s are the most powerful psychics in the city. The following are the currently known Level 5s; ranked not by strength but by how useful they are to http://anidb.net/ch2731 [Aleister]`s plans.
1.) http://anidb.net/ch10527 [Accelerator]
2.) http://anidb.net/ch98257 [Kakine Teitoku]
3.) http://anidb.net/ch2469 [Misaka Mikoto]
4.) http://anidb.net/ch56199 [Mugino Shizuri]
5.) http://anidb.net/ch54960 [Shokuhou Misaki]
6.) Unknown. A possible impersonator claiming to be Aihana Etsu has appeared.
7.) http://anidb.net/ch107656 [Sogiita Gunha]</description>
<picture>243175.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="57417" type="appears in" update="2013-06-23">
<rating votes="2">2.58</rating>
<name>Sunglasses</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138927.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31390" picture="151711.jpg">Shiga Madoka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57563" type="appears in" update="2013-06-29">
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<name>Souji Kakari</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139277.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25812" picture="151726.jpg">Matsumoto Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57564" type="appears in" update="2013-06-29">
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<name>Otoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139276.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37882" picture="173035.jpg">Yamashita Seiichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57768" type="appears in" update="2013-07-07">
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<name>Keibi Robo</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139704.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25804" picture="71817.jpg">Yamamoto Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58222" type="appears in" update="2013-07-28">
<rating votes="2">4.77</rating>
<name>Imouto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140555.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32738" picture="88323.jpg">Kido Ibuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58223" type="appears in" update="2013-07-28">
<rating votes="2">5.40</rating>
<name>Ane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140554.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29353" picture="186153.jpg">Yamazaki Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58969" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-09-03">
<rating votes="10">5.09</rating>
<name>Febri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141586.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5886" picture="30429.jpg">Nomizu Iori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58970" type="appears in" update="2013-08-17">
<rating votes="2">2.58</rating>
<name>Aritomi Haruki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141588.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="400" picture="171989.jpg">Majima Junji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58971" type="appears in" update="2013-08-17">
<rating votes="4">6.47</rating>
<name>Edasaki Banri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141589.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="162" picture="23208.jpg">Satou Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58996" type="appears in" update="2013-08-24">
<rating votes="2">2.58</rating>
<name>Kosako Shun`ichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141874.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="58997" type="appears in" update="2013-08-18">
<rating votes="2">2.58</rating>
<name>Hannin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141638.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37882" picture="173035.jpg">Yamashita Seiichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59148" type="appears in" update="2013-08-24">
<rating votes="2">5.40</rating>
<name>Judgment (Onna)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141873.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23608" picture="65179.jpg">Mochizuki Rei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59149" type="appears in" update="2013-08-24">
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<name>Judgment (Otoko)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141872.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34296" picture="225238.jpg">Ishikawa Kaito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59150" type="appears in" update="2013-08-24">
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<name>Untenshu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141871.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25812" picture="151726.jpg">Matsumoto Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59403" type="appears in" update="2013-09-03">
<rating votes="3">4.33</rating>
<name>Waitress</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142334.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34407" picture="202909.jpg">Suwa Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59404" type="appears in" update="2013-09-03">
<rating votes="2">2.58</rating>
<name>Ishi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142333.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30309" picture="80361.jpg">Saitou Hironori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59405" type="appears in" update="2013-09-15">
<rating votes="2">2.58</rating>
<name>Madarame Kenji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143172.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34070" picture="130103.jpg">Furukawa Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59406" type="appears in" update="2013-09-07">
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<name>Sakurai Jun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142621.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23608" picture="65179.jpg">Mochizuki Rei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59407" type="appears in" update="2013-09-15">
<rating votes="2">2.58</rating>
<name>Sekimura Hirotada</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143173.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24093" picture="124751.jpg">Hikami Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59408" type="appears in" update="2013-09-03">
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<name>Anti-skill</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142335.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34296" picture="225238.jpg">Ishikawa Kaito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59410" type="appears in" update="2013-09-03">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>STUDY</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>142346.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="59970" type="appears in" update="2013-09-21">
<rating votes="2">4.77</rating>
<name>Kongou Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143395.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="60" picture="171602.jpg">Kawada Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59971" type="appears in" update="2013-09-21">
<rating votes="3">5.68</rating>
<name>Janie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143396.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5886" picture="30429.jpg">Nomizu Iori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60221" type="appears in" update="2013-10-11">
<rating votes="18">8.44</rating>
<name>Misaka 19090</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Misaka 19090 is one of http://anidb.net/ch2469 [Misaka Mikoto]`s http://anidb.net/ch14538 [clones]. Her personality is alike that of the other clones, with suppressed emotions, since they weren`t beneficial to the Level Six experiment. Also similarly to most of the other clones, she seems to have feelings for http://anidb.net/ch2342 [Kamijou Touma], shown when she displays envy towards the other clones. She was the first one to implement a plan to attract him over the other clones.
In http://anidb.net/a9484 [Toaru Kagaku no Railgun S], she is shown to have emotions more similar to those of regular people, thanks to the efforts of http://anidb.net/ch55166 [Nunotaba Shinobu].</description>
<picture>143885.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1992" picture="151673.jpg">Sasaki Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91639" type="appears in" update="2017-10-04">
<rating votes="4">4.50</rating>
<name>Misaka 10031</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Misaka 10031 is one of the many clones of Misaka Mikoto and the first clone that Kamijou Touma meets.</description>
<picture>207869.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1992" picture="151673.jpg">Sasaki Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91646" type="appears in" update="2017-10-05">
<name>Souji Robo</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cleaning Robots are automated cylindrical machine designed to clean the grounds of Academy City. They can be described as mobile trashbins.</description>
<picture>207890.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="91649" type="appears in" update="2017-10-05">
<name>Kihara Ichizoku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Kihara Family or Clan is one of the largest gatherings of scientists that work for Academy City`s dark side and the forerunners of the most twisted human experiments. As a result, many if not most of them are highly influential scientists with high-ranking posts over multiple organizations under Academy City. The Kihara Family serve as a recurring antagonistic force in the series.</description>
</character>
<character id="91652" type="appears in" update="2017-10-05">
<rating votes="4">4.50</rating>
<name>Misaka 13577</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207893.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1992" picture="151673.jpg">Sasaki Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91653" type="appears in" update="2017-10-05">
<rating votes="2">6.58</rating>
<name>Misaka 10039</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207894.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1992" picture="151673.jpg">Sasaki Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="148119" update="2018-02-01">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-03</airdate>
<rating votes="20">5.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妹達[シスターズ]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sisters</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sisters</title>
<summary>In high spirits, Misaka joins the other girls for a day of shopping at Seventh Mist, where she helps the others with their shopping, as well. Misaka spends another day playing with children. One of Misaka`s clones goes through the phases of her training.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727305</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-scientific-railgun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148120" update="2018-02-01">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-04-26</airdate>
<rating votes="20">5.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">超電磁砲量産計画[レディオノイズけいかく]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Project Radio Noise</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Radio Noise Keikaku</title>
<summary>Rumors swirl about that Misaka is the template for a project to produce Level 5 clones. When Nunotaba refers to her as the "Original," Misaka decides to check her out, and learns that she worked at the hospital where Misaka submitted her DNA map.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727303</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-scientific-railgun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148121" update="2018-02-01">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-04-19</airdate>
<rating votes="21">4.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">寿命中断[クリティカル]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Critical</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Critical</title>
<summary>After dreaming of her past, Misaka sets out for a day of shopping, but when Kuroko suggests a shortcut, they find an envelope with a cash card in it--one of many placed throughout town. Elsewhere, Saten thinks she sees someone who looks like Misaka.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727297</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-scientific-railgun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148122" update="2018-02-01">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-04-12</airdate>
<rating votes="22">4.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">超電磁砲[レールガン]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">"Railgun"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Railgun</title>
<summary>Haruue joins Saten and Uiharu on a trip to the Garden of Learning to see Misaka and Shirai, as well as to do some shopping. They later go to visit Edasaki in the hospital, where she is undergoing physical therapy, when things take an unexpected twist.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727295</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-scientific-railgun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148909" update="2019-05-05">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 2 (0:30)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148910" update="2019-05-05">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1 (0:15; Currently Airing Version)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148911" update="2019-05-05">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1 (0:15; Pre-Air AT-X Version)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148912" update="2019-05-05">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-03-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">放送告知</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1 (0:15; Pre-Air Version)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Housou Kokuchi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="149607" update="2013-04-13">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-04-12</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="149771" update="2019-05-05">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-04-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="149833" update="2019-05-05">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ACE番宣 90秒版</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV ACE Ver. (1:41)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">ACE Bansen 90-byou Ban</title>
</episode>
<episode id="149834" update="2019-05-05">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">番宣B TOKYO MX 事前告知</title>
<title xml:lang="en">TOKYO MX Announcement Ver. B (0:15)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bansen B Tokyo MX Jizen Kokuchi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="149835" update="2019-05-05">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">番宣A TOKYO MX 事前告知</title>
<title xml:lang="en">TOKYO MX Announcement Ver. A (0:15)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bansen A Tokyo MX Jizen Kokuchi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="149932" update="2018-02-01">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-31</airdate>
<rating votes="22">8.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Item[アイテム]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Item</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Item</title>
<summary>The members of the underworld organization ITEM finish one mission, and are called in to defend the remaining facilities. When Misaka tries to infiltrate one building, she encounters Item member Frenda. Meanwhile, Nunotaba drops in at the other facility.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727323</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-scientific-railgun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="149933" update="2018-02-01">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-24</airdate>
<rating votes="23">3.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お姉さまの力になりたいですの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I... I Want to Be of Help to You, Sissy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onee-sama no Chikara ni Naritai Desu no</title>
<summary>Misaka manages to sabotage most of the experimental facilities remotely before she is cut off, leaving her to deal with the rest in person. Shirai resolves to help Misaka by doing her part to be more vigilant at work, but risks shutting the others out.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727319</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-scientific-railgun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="149934" update="2018-02-01">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-17</airdate>
<rating votes="23">7.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あたし... みんなのこと見えてるから</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I... Can See All of You</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atashi... Minna no Koto Mieteru kara</title>
<summary>Misaka lashes out at Accelerator, but is left frustrated. She realizes the full breadth of the situation she has become involved in, and feels responsible for allowing it to happen. Nunotaba discusses the ramifacations of the clones` existence with Misaka.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727317</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-scientific-railgun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="149935" update="2018-02-01">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-10</airdate>
<rating votes="29">9.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶対能力進化計画[レベル6シフトけいかく]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Project Level 6 Shift</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Level 6 Shift Keikaku</title>
<summary>Finding herself face-to-face with a clone of herself, Misaka ends up helping her get a cat out of a tree, sharing ice cream cones, and having tea with her. It isn`t until later that Misaka discovers the true, sinister project that calls for her clones.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727311</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-scientific-railgun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150708" update="2018-02-01">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-21</airdate>
<rating votes="22">7.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">自動販売機</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Vending Machine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jidouhanbaiki</title>
<summary>Misaka and Kamijo meet again at the malfunctioning vending machine in the park, where Shirai mistakes him for being Misaka`s boyfriend. Misaka becomes shaken when she bumps into another Misaka clone, and learns that the experiments are still ongoing.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727335</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-scientific-railgun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150709" update="2018-02-01">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-14</airdate>
<rating votes="21">8.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">原子崩し[メルトダウナー]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Meltdowner</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meltdowner</title>
<summary>Having realized who Misaka is, Mugino decides to give her a run for her third-place ranking. When Frenda mistakenly leaves her doll-bombs behind while heading to the other facility, Misaka collects them and uses them to supplement her diminished powers.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727331</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-scientific-railgun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150710" update="2018-02-01">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-07</airdate>
<rating votes="22">7.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">能力追跡[AIMストーカー]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">AIM Stalker</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">AIM Stalker</title>
<summary>As Misaka continues her way into the research facility, she and Mugino play a game of cat-and-mouse. Meanwhile, at the other facility, Nunotaba sneaks into a control room, planning to disrupt the experiment by adding a new factor to the Misaka Network.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727329</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-scientific-railgun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151154" update="2018-02-01">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-07-19</airdate>
<rating votes="27">9.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最弱[かみじょうとうま]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kamijo Toma</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kamijou Touma</title>
<summary>Kamijo races to the scene of the experiment, only to find that it has already started. Kamijo calls out Accelerator, who takes him to be yet another challenger to his position, until for the first time, as Misaka watches on, he gets his nose bloodied.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727353</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-scientific-railgun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151155" update="2018-02-01">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-07-12</airdate>
<rating votes="26">9.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">約束</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Promise</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yakusoku</title>
<summary>While Shirai frets about Misaka staying out again all night, she receives a visit from Kamijo, who manages to find Misaka`s documents about the project. Kamijo catches up with Misaka on a bridge, where he tries to talk her out of doing anything rash.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727349</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-scientific-railgun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151156" update="2018-02-01">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-07-05</airdate>
<rating votes="20">7.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一方通行[アクセラレータ]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Accelerator</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Accelerator</title>
<summary>Thwarted in her attempt to sabotage Tree Diagram, Misaka takes her frustration out on a nearby lab that is part of the project. Meanwhile, Accelerator and #10031 carry out their experiment, while Kamijo searches for Misaka`s missing sister.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727345</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-scientific-railgun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151157" update="2018-02-01">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-28</airdate>
<rating votes="22">5.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">樹形図の設計者[ツリーダイアグラム]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tree Diagram</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tree Diagram</title>
<summary>Misaka sets out on one last mission to put a halt to the experiments by destroying the supercomputer Tree Diagram. Meanwhile, Kamijo runs into Misaka`s clone #10032 again, and the two of them decide what they should do about a stray kitten she has found.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727339</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-scientific-railgun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151875" update="2018-02-01">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-08-16</airdate>
<rating votes="19">3.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お引越し</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Moving</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ohikkoshi</title>
<summary>Edasaki is due to be discharged from the hospital, and it is learned that she will be living with Haru`ue. The move is bittersweet for Uiharu, who is losing her roommate, but she feels it is for the best. Meanwhile, a new movement is afoot in the city.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727365</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-scientific-railgun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151876" update="2018-02-01">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-08-02</airdate>
<rating votes="19">4.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勉強会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Study Group</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Benkyoukai</title>
<summary>With the end of summer vacation approaching, the girls plan a study session at Saten`s apartment to catch up on homework. Everyone is to bring an ingredient for a potluck stew party, but most have trouble deciding what to buy, leading to some surprises.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727361</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-scientific-railgun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151877" update="2018-02-01">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-07-26</airdate>
<rating votes="19">7.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">姉妹</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sisterhood</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shimai</title>
<summary>Misaka stands up for clone #10032, declaring that she is doing so because they are sisters. The next day, the two of them spend time in a park, where 10032 asks her for a special favor. Later, Misaka has difficulty trying to express her thanks to Kamijo.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727355</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-scientific-railgun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152133" update="2018-02-01">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-08-30</airdate>
<rating votes="16">3.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フェブリ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Febri</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Febri</title>
<summary>As Yomikawa takes over investigating the runaway security robots, Konori invites the whole gang out to take in a bath at a bathhouse. On their way home, a number of detours lead them to a confrontation with yet another, much more dangerous runaway robot.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727373</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-scientific-railgun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152134" update="2018-02-01">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-08-23</airdate>
<rating votes="17">3.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">学園都市研究発表会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Academic Reach Assembly</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gakuentoshi Kenkyuuhappyoukai</title>
<summary>Febri takes an instant liking to Saten, and is warm to everyone except for Misaka, much to her chagrin. At Judgment, Uiharu is unable to find any information on who Febri is, so arrangements are made to admit her into an orphanage as a "Child Error."
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727367</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-scientific-railgun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152315" update="2019-05-05">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-08-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152316" update="2014-01-02">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-08-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152544" update="2018-02-01">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-09-13</airdate>
<rating votes="16">5.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">STUDY</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Study</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Study</title>
<summary>Therestina reluctantly provides Misaka with the clues she needs to find the group behind Febrie`s secret. With Kongo`s help, the girls identify Aritomi as the man they are pursuing, and find out more about him and his company, the STUDY Corporation.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727381</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-scientific-railgun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152545" update="2018-02-01">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-09-06</airdate>
<rating votes="16">3.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">闇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Darkness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yami</title>
<summary>With the revelation that Febri is synthetic, Misaka is determined to find whoever built her, and have them fix her. The investigation is stalled on all fronts, even with the help of her friends running down leads, until help comes from a surprise source.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727375</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-scientific-railgun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152728" update="2013-12-08">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2013-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="10">1.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">MMR III ~もっとまるっと超電磁砲III~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Much More Railgun III</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">좀 더 있는 그대로 초전자포 III</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Motto Marutto Railgun III</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152741" update="2018-02-01">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-09-27</airdate>
<rating votes="19">8.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Eternal Party</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eternal Party</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eternal Party</title>
<summary>Shirai, Konori, Kongo and friends, and Uiharu and Saten confront the powered suits at the four Assembly sites, where they soon receive backup. Misaka and Febrie move to take on Aritomi directly, but he has one final surprise up his sleeve for them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727391</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-scientific-railgun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152742" update="2018-02-01">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="17">6.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">革命未明[Silent Party]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Silent Party</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Silent Party</title>
<summary>Aritomi reveals his motivations for STUDY`s project to Misaka. She also learns about Nunotaba`s plight, and some of the details concerning what STUDY has planned at the Reach Assembly the next day. Will she be able to escape and put a stop them?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727385</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-scientific-railgun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="156614" update="2013-12-10">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2013-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="10">2.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">MMR IV ~もっとまるっと超電磁砲IV~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Much More Railgun IV</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">좀 더 있는 그대로 초전자포 IV</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Motto Marutto Railgun IV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156770" update="2019-04-28">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156771" update="2014-02-16">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-07-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156772" update="2019-04-28">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-06-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158167" update="2019-05-05">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-07-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160256" update="2019-05-05">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2013-09-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 24 Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160257" update="2019-05-05">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-09-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 23 Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160258" update="2019-05-07">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-09-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 21 Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="216549" update="2019-05-05">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">Blu-ray&amp;DVD 発売告知CM</title>
<title xml:lang="en">BD&amp;DVD Vol. 1 CM (0:15)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Blu-ray &amp; DVD Hatsubai Kokuchi CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="216550" update="2019-05-05">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">コミケ84 PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Comiket 84 PV (2:00)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Comiket 84 PV</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
