<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="951" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1973-07-18</startdate>
<enddate>1973-07-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Mazinger Z Tai Devilman</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Mazinger-Z Vs. Devilman</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Mazinger-Z Versus Devilman</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">マジンガーZ対デビルマン</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Devilman contre Mazinger Z</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Mazinga Z contro Devilman</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="950" type="Character">Mazinger-Z</anime>
<anime id="1236" type="Character">Devilman</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="1009" type="Unknown Relation">Toei Douga</name>
<name id="868" type="Original Work">Nagai Gou</name>
<name id="3354" type="Original Work">Dynamic Production</name>
<name id="5209" type="Music">Watanabe Chuumei</name>
<name id="6709" type="Music">Misawa Gou</name>
</creators>
<description>The Evil Demon Clan is attacking!
Only the Super-Robot Mazinger Z can save us.
And here comes Devilman, the good one of the Demon Clan.
He will help you defeat Dr. Hell and Lord Zennon, the leaders of the Demon Clan!
Go, Mazinger Z!!!</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="153">3.76</permanent>
<temporary count="153">5.40</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>204454.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3556</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3898</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2391</identifier>
<identifier>jbusbn</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2706</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>144429</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="16">
<externalentity>
<identifier>m057</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3087" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>super robot</name>
<description>These robots tend to have almost semi-magical attacks, which seem impossible or non-realistic, and/or perform non-realistic transformation sequences where they seem to gain/lose mass and utterly change their form, even if it means making their super-hard armour bend like plastic sheets.</description>
<picurl>222137.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="5122" type="main character in" update="2018-04-05">
<rating votes="26">7.04</rating>
<name>Kabuto Kouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215855.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="5560" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-05">
<rating votes="18">4.13</rating>
<name>Yumi Sayaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215858.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="5562" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-12">
<rating votes="10">3.33</rating>
<name>Kabuto Shirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kabuto Shirou is Kabuto Kouji`s younger brother. Most of the time, Shirou`s role is to add some comic relief to the plot. His character acquires a bit more depth in Great Mazinger, as he becomes acquainted with his father Kenzou, who was previously thought to be dead. He pilots his own robot in Great Mazinger, the Robot Junior.</description>
<picture>22403.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="5569" type="appears in" update="2009-04-04">
<rating votes="6">9.75</rating>
<name>Mazinger Z</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>22409.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="5571" type="appears in" update="2009-04-04">
<rating votes="4">3.33</rating>
<name>Aphrodite A</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>22410.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="5582" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-04">
<rating votes="7">6.72</rating>
<name>Yumi Gennosuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>22419.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="5583" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-04">
<rating votes="42">5.73</rating>
<name>Boss</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>22420.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="5594" type="appears in" update="2009-04-05">
<rating votes="4">1.50</rating>
<name>Tetsu-Kamen Heishi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>22446.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7692" type="main character in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="43">7.47</rating>
<name>Devilman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26556.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3268" picture="24747.jpg">Tanaka Ryouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7693" type="main character in" update="2015-02-04">
<rating votes="93">6.75</rating>
<name>Fudou Akira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akira Fudou lost his birth parents at a young age to an accident while exploring the Himalayas, killing his mother and father. He was then taken in to live in the care of close family friends. He has always been timid, shy, with very little courage and was often bullied before becoming into contact with the `Demon Lord of Battles`, Amon. It is Akira`s pure soul that keeps Amon trapped within Akira; allowing him to use Amon`s power and strength to transform freely into Devilman.</description>
<picture>26558.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3268" picture="24747.jpg">Tanaka Ryouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55763" type="main character in" update="2018-04-05">
<rating votes="4">7.21</rating>
<name>Dr. Hell</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dr. Hell was the main villain of the fictional robot anime Mazinger Z, its spinoff Mazinkaiser, and its remake Shin Mazinger Shougeki! Z-Hen. He was a brilliant, cunning and evil scientist, obsessed with world domination through his creations, the armies of Mechanical Beasts. He was a colleague of Dr. Kabuto, a well-meaning scientist, and accompanied him on an archeological expedition to the Greek island of Bardos, where ruins of the ancient Mikenese Empire were found. There they discovered that the ancient Mikenese civilization had the technology to build giant robotic warriors. Hell stole that technology and used it to create an army of fighting machines with which he planned to conquer the world. Dr. Kabuto used this technology coupled with an alloy he`d created to build a robot, Mazinger Z, to halt Hell`s plans for world conquest. Time and again Dr. Hell`s robots were destroyed by Mazinger Z, sometimes due to the in-fighting between his lieutenants Baron Ashura and Count Brocken.</description>
<picture>215856.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="55764" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-12">
<rating votes="5">3.51</rating>
<name>Ashura Danshaku</name>
<gender>intersexual</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Baron Ashura is the main henchman of Dr. Hell, the antagonist of Mazinger Z. He/she is notable for being voiced by two simultaneous seiyuu as well as being a half-man, half-woman combination. Mazinger`s most persistent enemy, it makes regular appearances in the Super Robot Wars series as Dr. Hell`s loyal underling.
Baron Ashura`s origin began long ago with a man and woman who fell in love. Their love was forbidden and upon discovery, the lovers shared a terrible fate: they were mummified and buried alive. Many years later, a cave in collapsed the roof of the tomb. A huge chunk of rubble landed between the two corpses, destroying the man`s right half and the woman`s left half. The would-be world conqueror Dr. Hell stumbled upon the tomb. He sewed the two remaining halves together and then brought the composite being to life. The new being swore loyalty to Dr. Hell. Dubbing his creation Baron Ashura, Dr. Hell used it as his main henchman.

While not a pilot Itself, Ashura has commanded Dr. Hell`s Salude and Bood submarines and at one point also is appointed as the pilot of Daima U5 by Dr. Hell in episode 27 of the television series. In episode 78, Ashura fatally wounded itself crashing the Bood into Mazinger Z in a futile attempt to destroy the robot. Duke Gorgon saw the dying Baron on the sea surface and tried to save it. Baron Ashura died in the arms of its enemy, who finally acknowledged its bravery. In the next episode, Ashura was paid homage with mechanical beast Jetfire P1 resembling its face.

Baron Ashura appears in every episode of Mazinkaiser until Dr. Hell transforms it into the mechanical monster King Gordon. Baron Ashura also appears in Shin Mazinger Shougeki! Z Hen faithful to its role although its origin was given more depth as it is revealed in the series Ashura was a pair of Mikene servants name Tristian and Isolde.
[Source: Wikipedia (en)]</description>
<picture>136566.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="11939" update="2011-07-01">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1973-07-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
<summary>Mazinger Z and Devilman come together to fight the Daemon race creaturs.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="62922" update="2006-09-14">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
