<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9512" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>10</episodecount>
<startdate>2012-10-08</startdate>
<enddate>2012-12-07</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Aratanari Fukaki Ao</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">エウレカセブンAOショートアニメ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Eureka Seven Ao - Short Anime</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">新たなり深き青</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">에우레카 세븐 AO - Short Anime</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8854" type="Other">Eureka Seven Ao</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://eurekaao-prj.net/?page_id=2066</url>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch40360 [Fukai Ao], http://anidb.net/ch40359 [Arata Naru] together with http://anidb.net/ch43464 [Noah] are watching a Pied Piper! animation, and Naru becomes upset regarding the topic of portrayed bust size... Ao comments on Okinawa-specific food, which reminds Naru that he just went and left the island to have fun... Just mentioning http://anidb.net/ch41249 [Elena] makes Naru quite jealous... Naru uses "Naruware" to hack Ao`s cell phone... When http://anidb.net/ch41248 [Fleur] and Elena come to visit, Naru is less than thrilled initially...
— written by foo2</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="153">2.35</permanent>
<temporary count="153">4.92</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>128404.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15979</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://eurekaao-prj.net/?page_id=2066</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>エウレカセブンAO#.E3.82.B7.E3.83.A7.E3.83.BC.E3.83.88.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2558" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>catgirl</name>
<description>A catgirl (nekomusume, 猫娘) is a girl that has a cat`s characteristics, a form of zoomorphism.
They can appear either as normal girls without any obvious cat traits —such as eyes, ears, paws, or a tail— or as girls who have one or more of these traits. In the former case they are usually cats that have become human through the means of magic. The feline features are added for moe and/or sexiness appeal, with the most common features being cat ears and tail. Nya~, the Japanese equivalent of meow, is often used by girls acting cute and is not a trait exclusive to catgirls.
Not to be confused with characters who simply are wearing a http://anidb.net/t1622 [cat ears accessory] (nekomimi, 猫耳) as a fashion accessory. Catgirls with cat ears should also be tagged with http://anidb.net/t2541 [animal ears].</description>
<picurl>150775.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="40359" type="main character in" update="2012-04-05">
<rating votes="9">2.51</rating>
<name>Arata Naru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A childhood friend of http://anidb.net/ch40360 [Ao]`s. She has a weak and sickly body, but an indomitable spirit. As a result of a tragic accident 10 years ago, Naru experienced an awakening of her latent powers as a yuta (an Okinawan word for someone who has developed the ability to communicate with the dead and channel spiritual energy). She feels some kind of admiration for the "Umikyonchu" who has protected her during the accident.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>79794.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30554" picture="81681.jpg">Oohashi Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40360" type="main character in" update="2013-07-04">
<rating votes="11">3.61</rating>
<name>Fukai Ao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young boy who was raised by elderly doctor http://anidb.net/ch42354 [Toshio]. His father is missing and his mother also left him ten years ago, on the occasion of a certain "accident".
Due to his complex background, he used to suppress parts of his inner self for his entire life, but his encounter with http://anidb.net/ch41250 [Nirvash] will make him know his destiny and abilities, and he will take his life in own hands.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>79795.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3189" picture="81680.jpg">Honjou Yuutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41248" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-04">
<rating votes="16">6.91</rating>
<name>Fleur Blanc</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young IFO pilot for Team Pied Piper. Fleur is the only daughter of Christophe Blanc who presides over GENERATION BLUE, the organization that commands Team Pied Piper`s activities. She is jealous of http://anidb.net/ch40360 [Ao]`s natural-born IFO piloting abilities.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>81376.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30554" picture="81681.jpg">Oohashi Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41249" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-04">
<rating votes="9">5.89</rating>
<name>Elena Peoples</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An IFO pilot for Team Pied Piper. She has such a passionate love for the two-dimensional world of television and games. She watches anime even during flight operations and quoting anime dialogue all the time, which makes her behavior not understandable.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>81375.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1679" picture="38587.jpg">Omigawa Chiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43464" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-13">
<name>Noah</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>85928.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="145558" update="2012-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-10-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145559" update="2012-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-10-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145560" update="2012-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-10-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145561" update="2012-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-10-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145562" update="2016-01-01">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-11-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145563" update="2016-01-01">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-11-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145564" update="2016-01-01">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-11-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146192" update="2012-12-27">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-12-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146193" update="2016-01-01">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-11-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146194" update="2016-01-01">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-11-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
