<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9515" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-11-23</startdate>
<enddate>2013-11-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kaguya-hime no Monogatari</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The Tale of Princess Kaguya</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Сказание о принцессе Кагуя</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Приказката за принцеса Кагуя</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">かぐや姫の物語</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The Tale of the Princess Kaguya</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Die Legende der Prinzessin Kaguya</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Le Conte de la princesse Kaguya</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">La Storia della Principessa Splendente</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">El cuento de la princesa Kaguya</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">O Conto da Princesa Kaguya</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Prinsessa Kaguyan taru</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">La leyenda de la princesa Kaguya</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="6821" approval="8" total="8">Kaguya-hime</anime>
<anime id="7779" approval="5" total="6">Hello Kitty no Kaguya-hime</anime>
<anime id="7" approval="1" total="8">Mononoke-hime</anime>
<anime id="2426" approval="1" total="6">Genji Monogatari</anime>
<anime id="500" approval="1" total="3">Kaidoumaru</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="536010">Beautifully composed in all areas: Art, Animation, Music, and Storytelling. 
Art Style really evokes traditional Japanese paintings but also accompanied by very fluid animation in movement and human expression.

Highly recommended and a must see for Ghibli fans.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://kaguyahime-monogatari.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="11846" type="Work">Hoshino Kouji</name>
<name id="43" type="Original Plan">Takahata Isao</name>
<name id="1947" type="Music">Hisaishi Joe</name>
<name id="43" type="Direction">Takahata Isao</name>
<name id="729" type="Work">Studio Ghibli</name>
<name id="49305" type="Original Work">Taketori Monogatari</name>
<name id="10986" type="Animation Design">Tanabe Osamu</name>
</creators>
<description>* Adaptation of the Japanese folk tale Taketori Monogatari (Tale of the Bamboo Cutter), also known as Kaguya Hime (Princess Kaguya).
In an idyllic rural setting, http://anidb.net/ch59900 [an old bamboo cutter] and http://anidb.net/ch59901 [his wife] raise a tiny girl found nestled within a glowing bamboo stalk along with a fortune in gold. As she approaches adulthood, the bamboo cutter uses the fortune to purchase a villa in the capital, buy himself a title and employ tutors to transform the country girl, now given the name http://anidb.net/ch59898 [Kaguya], into a refined woman. News of her beauty brings powerful and wealthy suitors who compete for her hand in marriage, all the while Kaguya wishes that she and her family could return to their former life. Sooner or later, though, her true origins will make their own claim upon her.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1109">8.31</permanent>
<temporary count="1112">7.75</temporary>
<review count="4">7.49</review>
</ratings>
<picture>165889.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14976</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16664</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://kaguyahime-monogatari.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gkids.com/films/the-tale-of-the-princess-kaguya/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Kaguya-hime_no_Monogatari_(film)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>かぐや姫の物語</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>344585</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16389</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2659" parentid="2660" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Moon</name>
<description>The Moon is an astronomical body that orbits planet Earth, being Earth`s only permanent natural satellite. It is the fifth-largest natural satellite in the Solar System, and the largest among planetary satellites relative to the size of the planet that it orbits.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214385.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2685" parentid="2641" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-30">
<name>Heian period</name>
<description>Last division of classical Japanese history, covering the time period from 794 to 1185.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3869" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>mono no aware</name>
<description>Literally "the pathos of things", also translated as "an empathy toward things," or "a sensitivity of ephemera"; a Japanese term used to describe the awareness of the transience of things and a gentle sadness (or wistfulness) at their passing.
Also frequently been translated as "the `ahh-ness` of things".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3876" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>folklore</name>
<description>Folklore, or simply Lore, are the traditions of a culture, subculture, or group, in the form of legends, music, proverbs, jokes, popular beliefs, fairy tales, stories, tall tales and customs. In usage, there is a continuum between folklore and mythology.
Folklore is generally divided into four areas of study: physical artifacts, transmissible entities and stories, culture and technologies, and behaviors and rituals.
[From Wikipedia]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4048" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>Japanese mythology</name>
<description>Japanese mythology is a system of beliefs that embraces Shinto and Buddhist traditions as well as agriculture-based folk religion. The Shinto pantheon alone consists of an uncountable number of kami (Japanese for "gods" or "spirits").
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4413" parentid="6563" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-16">
<name>heaven</name>
<description>Heaven, the Heavens or Seven Heavens, is a common religious, cosmological or transcendent place from which heavenly beings (such as a God, angels, the jinn, and sky deities like King or Queen of Heaven, Heavenly Father, Heavenly Mother, Son of Heaven, heavenly saints or venerated ancestors) originate, are enthroned or inhabit.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6352" parentid="6397" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>Kaguya-hime</name>
<description>The Tale of the Bamboo Cutter (Taketori Monogatari, 竹取物語), also known as Princess Kaguya (かぐや姫 Kaguya-hime, 赫映姫 or 輝夜姫), is a 10th-century Japanese folktale. It primarily details the life of a mysterious girl called Kaguya-hime, who was discovered as a baby inside the stalk of a glowing bamboo plant by a bamboo cutter, alongside riches in gold. The thumb-sized girl grew into a beautiful woman, and this was known all over the lands. Eventually 5 princes made their way to her to ask her foster father for her hand. Each of them got tasked with something seemingly impossible to fullfil to marry her. After all of them failed, the emporer came to see her, and fell for her beauty. His proposal was denied as well, telling him that she wasn`t of this country and thus couldn`t marry him. In the summer Kaguya-hime started to cry upon seeing the full moon. Her foster parents inquired on the matter and after a while she gave in, telling them that she was actually coming from the moon, and that she needs to return there. When the day came to return, the emperor sent many guards to her home to protect her from the moon people. They came and took her with them anyway, leaving the parents in sadness and tears. The heartbroken emperor wanted to send her a message, and went on to ask where he could find the closest place to heaven. This being the Great Mountain of Suruga Provice. The tale goes on saying that the name of the mountain, which we know today as Mount Fuji, came from the word immortality (fushi, or fuji), and the Kanji from the emperor`s army ascending its slopes, meaning literally "Mountain Abounding with Warriours" (富士山).
The anime or episode either takes on the whole tale of Kaguya-hime or just parts of it.</description>
<picurl>169473.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6397" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-02">
<name>tales</name>
<description>Tales are stories told time and again and passed down from generation to generation, and some of those show up in anime not just once or twice, but several times.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6563" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-23">
<name>spirit realm</name>
<description>A spirit realm is a place where inhabited by the spirits of the dead, deities, demons, and other such entities. Examples would be Heaven and Hell in Christianity, the Elysium in Greek mythology, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7075" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-05-07">
<name>adapted into Japanese movie</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a Japanese movie.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="59898" type="main character in" update="2013-09-17">
<rating votes="10">9.01</rating>
<name>Kaguya-hime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143255.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38535" picture="143259.jpg">Asakura Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59899" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-09-17">
<rating votes="2">2.30</rating>
<name>Sutemaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143256.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38534" picture="143260.jpg">Koura Kengo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59900" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-09-17">
<rating votes="2">3.51</rating>
<name>Okina</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143257.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38533" picture="143261.jpg">Chii Takeo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59901" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-09-17">
<rating votes="2">1.89</rating>
<name>Ouna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143258.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38532" picture="143262.jpg">Miyamoto Nobuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62052" type="appears in" update="2013-12-04">
<name>Kitanokata</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="14773" picture="217774.jpg">Asaoka Yukiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62053" type="appears in" update="2013-12-04">
<name>Ootomo no Dainagon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="7273" picture="32249.jpg">Uzaki Ryuudou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62054" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-04">
<rating votes="2">1.77</rating>
<name>Menowarawa</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="38911" picture="147110.jpg">Tabata Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62055" type="appears in" update="2013-12-04">
<name>Mikado</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="38910" picture="147111.jpg">Nakamura Shichinosuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62056" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-04">
<rating votes="2">1.56</rating>
<name>Inbe no Akita</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="38909" picture="147112.jpg">Tatekawa Shinosuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62057" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-04">
<rating votes="2">2.47</rating>
<name>Sagami</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="5154" picture="236895.jpg">Takahata Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62058" type="appears in" update="2013-12-04">
<name>Isonokami no Chuunagon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="35558" picture="131522.jpg">Kojou Tamaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62059" type="appears in" update="2013-12-04">
<name>Ishitsukuri no Miko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="482" picture="17466.jpg">Kamikawa Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62060" type="appears in" update="2013-12-04">
<name>Kuramochi no Miko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="9429">Hashizume Isao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62061" type="appears in" update="2013-12-04">
<name>Abe no Udaijin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="37806" picture="138731.jpg">Ijuuin Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62062" type="appears in" update="2013-12-04">
<name>Sumiyaki no Roujin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="5231" picture="146320.jpg">Nakadai Tatsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="152599" update="2016-01-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>140</length>
<airdate>2013-11-23</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="153921" update="2013-09-07">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="179108" update="2016-07-22">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>90</length>
<airdate>2014-12-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">高畑勲, 「かぐや姫の物語」をつくる.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Isao Takahata and His Tale of the Princess Kaguya</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Takahata Isao, "Kaguya-hime no Monogatari" o Tsukuru.</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
