<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9516" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-10-25</startdate>
<enddate>2014-10-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Santa Company</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">サンタ・カンパニー</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14946" type="Alternative Setting">Santa Company: Christmas no Himitsu</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.santa-company.net</url>
<creators>
<name id="7652" type="Character Design">Harada Hiroki</name>
<name id="10909" type="Original Plan">Itoso Kenji</name>
<name id="26744" type="Direction">Kamakura Yumi</name>
<name id="10909" type="Chief Direction">Itoso Kenji</name>
<name id="22477" type="Music">Itagaki Yuusuke</name>
<name id="10909" type="Series Composition">Itoso Kenji</name>
<name id="20732" type="Series Composition">Fukushima Naohiro</name>
<name id="2216" type="Chief Animation Direction">Myouchin Usaku</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch50822 [Noel] is an 11-year-old girl who despises Christmas. She has lived with her father ever since her parents divorced three years ago, but her father ends up busy at work every Christmas and she cannot play with her friends from school.
On a lonely Christmas Eve, Noel takes her usual apartment complex elevator ride to her home, but when the doors open, she finds herself lost in a humongous factory — owned by Santa Claus. Santa Claus has gone corporate as Santa Company with the motto Swiftly, surely, secretly. The outfit takes orders and delivers top-notch presents to children in the utmost secrecy. Noel meets some new friends, and together, they take off in a sled to deliver presents.
Source: ANN
Note: The world premiere was hosted at the Tokyo International Film Festival on October 25, 2014.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="159">3.32</permanent>
<temporary count="160">5.33</temporary>
<review count="1">6.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>128563.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14919</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16381</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.santa-company.net</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.kickstarter.com/projects/itoso-tag/santa-company</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Santa_Company</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>サンタ・カンパニー</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4588" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-20">
<name>fast-paced</name>
<description>Hold onto your hats, this anime`s storyline is relentless.
The characters don`t get time to take a breath as events keep both them and the viewer on a roller coaster ride of revelation and excitement!
Hopefully it all makes sense...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6358" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-03-18">
<name>crowdfunded</name>
<description>This anime was funded, at least partially, through a campaign on a crowdfunding website (e.g. Kickstarter, Makuake).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="50822" type="main character in" update="2013-12-04">
<name>Noel White</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146691.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50823" type="main character in" update="2013-12-04">
<name>Bell Crystal</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146692.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50824" type="main character in" update="2013-12-04">
<name>Mint Rondo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146693.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50825" type="main character in" update="2013-12-04">
<name>Thomas Dou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146694.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50826" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-04">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Rudolf III</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146695.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31811" picture="85614.jpg">Karasuma Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62026" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-04">
<name>Nazo no Tenshu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146688.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2220" picture="188715.jpg">Inaba Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62027" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-04">
<name>Pedro Rondo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146689.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62028" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-04">
<name>Nicola White</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146690.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="451" picture="17347.jpg">Touchi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73726" type="appears in" update="2017-11-12">
<name>Santa Claus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>169903.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38116" picture="223784.jpg">Kitada Masamichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73727" type="appears in" update="2015-03-11">
<name>Tegami no Onnanoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>169904.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38593" picture="223625.jpg">Kokido Shiho</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="156904" update="2013-12-26">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-12-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159236" update="2014-04-13">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2014-04-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">"Santa Company" Key-frame animation / Chapter of Departure.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chapter of Departure. (Key-frame Animation)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Santa Company" Key-frame Animation / Chapter of Departure.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159237" update="2014-04-13">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2014-04-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">"Santa Company" Vertion without voice / Chapter of Departure.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chapter of Departure. (Version Without Voice)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Santa Company" Vertion Without Voice / Chapter of Departure.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159238" update="2014-04-13">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-02-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">トレーラー:2014年公開予</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer: 2014 Publication</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Trailer: 2014-nen Koukaiyo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163748" update="2014-10-25">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2014-10-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
