<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="952" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1974-07-25</startdate>
<enddate>1974-07-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Mazinger Z Tai Ankoku Daishougun</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">Mazinger Z vs Ankoku Daishougun</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Mazinger-Z vs General Dark</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Mazinger-Z vs General of Darkness</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Mazinger Z vs. The Grand General of Darkness</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">マジンガーZ対暗黒大将軍</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Mazinga Z contro il Generale Nero</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="954" type="Alternative Setting">Mazinkaiser: Shitou! Ankoku Daishougun</anime>
<anime id="950" type="Parent Story">Mazinger-Z</anime>
<anime id="10001" type="Other">Robot Girls Z</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="868" type="Original Work">Nagai Gou</name>
<name id="3354" type="Original Work">Dynamic Production</name>
</creators>
<description>During the battle between Dr.Hell and Mazinger Z, the Mikene Empire awakens again and, under the lead of Ankoku Daishogun (General of the Darkness), attack the world. Mikene`s Battle Beasts are more powerful than Dr.Hell`s Mechanical Monsters, and Mazinger Z is no match for them. Only a miracle can save the world... or a new warrior...
Note: This movie introduced the Mikene Empire and the Great Mazinger.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="117">4.54</permanent>
<temporary count="118">5.79</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>204424.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3593</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4406</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2392</identifier>
<identifier>krdzwx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2713</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>144782</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="16">
<externalentity>
<identifier>m060</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3087" parentid="2274" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>super robot</name>
<description>These robots tend to have almost semi-magical attacks, which seem impossible or non-realistic, and/or perform non-realistic transformation sequences where they seem to gain/lose mass and utterly change their form, even if it means making their super-hard armour bend like plastic sheets.</description>
<picurl>222137.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="5122" type="main character in" update="2018-04-05">
<rating votes="26">7.02</rating>
<name>Kabuto Kouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215855.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="5560" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-05">
<rating votes="18">4.12</rating>
<name>Yumi Sayaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215858.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="5562" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-12">
<rating votes="10">3.33</rating>
<name>Kabuto Shirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kabuto Shirou is Kabuto Kouji`s younger brother. Most of the time, Shirou`s role is to add some comic relief to the plot. His character acquires a bit more depth in Great Mazinger, as he becomes acquainted with his father Kenzou, who was previously thought to be dead. He pilots his own robot in Great Mazinger, the Robot Junior.</description>
<picture>22403.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="5569" type="appears in" update="2009-04-04">
<rating votes="6">9.75</rating>
<name>Mazinger Z</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>22409.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="5582" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-04">
<rating votes="7">6.73</rating>
<name>Yumi Gennosuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>22419.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="5583" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-04">
<rating votes="42">5.72</rating>
<name>Boss</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>22420.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="32237" type="appears in" update="2018-04-05">
<rating votes="8">9.63</rating>
<name>Tsurugi Tetsuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An orphan young man raised by Dr. http://anidb.net/ch32239 [Kabuto Kenzou], trained to be the pilot of Great Mazinger ever since he was young. At first shown only as a bad-tempered young man with a heart of gold under his hotheadedness, he later develops a strong jealousy against his adoptive brother http://anidb.net/ch5122 [Kabuto Kouji].
Tetsuya served as the main character in Great Mazinger and first appeared in the final episode of Mazinger Z.
He also appears in Violence Jack, where he is brutally killed by the motorcycle gang known as Hell`s Wind. This prompts his lover, http://anidb.net/ch32238 [Honoo Jun], to seek vengeance for him.</description>
<picture>215857.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="32239" type="appears in" update="2013-05-12">
<rating votes="6">6.73</rating>
<name>Kabuto Kenzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kenzou was the son of Kabuto Juuzou, the inventor of Mazinger Z, but working in secret he improved upon the original designs to create the more formidable Great Mazinger. After a laboratory experiment that went wrong, he and his wife are thought to be dead. However, he was instead turned into a cyborg by his father in order to keep him alive. To shield them from danger and psychological shock, Kenzou`s sons Kouji and Shirou are unaware of this and grow believing both of their parents are dead, and were raised by Juuzou.
Kenzou reveals the truth to both of them in the Great Mazinger series, first to Shirou, since Kouji was away for a big part of the series, and their relationship would cause conflict with his adopted son Tsurugi Tetsuya, who was raised by Kenzou together with his best friend Jun and comes to feel intensely jealous of Kenzou`s actual children, especially so of Kouji. Dr. Kabuto would eventually die in battle at the end of the series and Tetsuya and Koji fight together to avenge his death.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>10466.gif</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="21662" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1974-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="63090" update="2006-09-14">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
