<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9520" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-04-05</startdate>
<enddate>2013-06-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Photokano</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Photograph Girlfriend</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="synonym">Foto Kano</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Photo Kano</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">フォトカノ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Photo Kano</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Photo Kano</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">PhotoKano</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">写真女友</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="7506" approval="60" total="66">Amagami SS</anime>
<anime id="7656" approval="10" total="15">Yosuga no Sora: In Solitude, Where We Are Least Alone.</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="118697">I liked the idea of this anime because it did something new at least for me. The anime shows a storyline up to a certain point I think it was episode 5 where the stroyline is same for everyone of the girls. Then it branches off and shows how the life with only one girl could have been while in school in only one episode. The good part the anime avoids being about a harem again. So for the new idea it gets a lot bonus points with me</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="366520">first 6 episodes were thoroughly enjoyable, then branched off into other stories/girls, but you keep asking your self, he has a Girlfriend, is this before that or after, i don`t mind it, but does not make much of a story IMO, however for a simple anime that`s cute and can make you laugh it`s not bad</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>https://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/photokano/</url>
<creators>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="29656" type="Character Design">Shimada Sanae</name>
<name id="8547" type="Series Composition">Yokoyama Akitoshi</name>
<name id="8547" type="Direction">Yokoyama Akitoshi</name>
<name id="4441" type="Music">Kubota Mina</name>
<name id="29656" type="Chief Animation Direction">Shimada Sanae</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the PSP dating simulation game by the same name.
During http://anidb.net/ch50852 [Maeda Kazuya]`s first year of high school he felt like a nobody, just another forgotten face shuffling through the crowded hallways. Even his best friend from childhood, http://anidb.net/ch50853 [Niimi Haruka], seemed somehow more difficult to approach, since she had matured a little quicker in the unsettling way that girls have a habit of doing. However, this year, things will be different for Kazuya, and part of that change may just be because of the big new girl magnet hanging in front of him: the used digital SLR he just received from his dad! But will just having a camera be enough to make talking to girls a snap? Well, if he stays focused and has enough talent to make them look good, it might just be! And since it is digital, there are no negatives or having to wait for things to develop! Will Kazuya`s new stock in trade click with the most beautiful girls in school, or will his career as a lensman be just a flash in the pan? Find out as he goes for total exposure...
Source: Sentai Filmworks</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1243">2.81</permanent>
<temporary count="1249">5.64</temporary>
<review count="2">4.83</review>
</ratings>
<picture>231350.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14902</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16397</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/photokano/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tbscontents.com/en/program/photokano</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Photo_Kano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>フォトカノ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2934</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>345290</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15935</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/3962</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11000</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2013/photokano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>anime_photokano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=9uZq2_MO05k</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>photo-kano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18352</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="34">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xy2dr0_pv-photo-kano_fun#.UXL831erUw8</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1651" parentid="2883" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>photography</name>
<description>Photography is the art or process of producing images by the action of radiant energy and especially light on a sensitive surface (such as film or an optical sensor).
Source: Merriam-Webster</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2396" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-08">
<name>swimsuit</name>
<description>A swimsuit is one of several kinds of garments designed to be worn by people engaging in water-based activities or sports or during certain activities under sunlight. Most kinds of swimsuit reveal a large portion of the body surface area, but exceptions exist. The more revealing kinds may also be worn as undergarment in sports that require wetsuits, or when there is a need to display the body, as in the case of beauty pageants or bodybuilding contests.
There is a very wide range of styles of modern swimsuits, which vary in relation to body coverage and materials. The choice of style of swimsuit is dependent on current fashions, community standards of modesty, and plain personal preference. Swimsuits for men usually expose the chest, while those for women do not usually do so; however, many women prefer to engage in water or sun activities with their torso uncovered, in a practice commonly described as toplessness or topfreedom. Since the early twentieth century a naturist movement has developed in western countries that seeks a return to non-sexual nakedness when swimming and during other appropriate activities; in some places around the world, nude beaches have been set aside for people who choose to engage in normal beach activities in the nude, and such beaches may or may not enforce nudity onto their goers.
In anime, it is common for at least one episode to feature the characters in swimsuits, usually as an excuse for gratuitous fanservice; when that happens, the episode is usually labeled a pool or beach episode, after the place the characters went to. Swimsuits, and in particular one-piece swimsuits, are a very common fetish in Japan; while the reason for that is uncertain, a common folk explanation is the fact that boys throughout their entire adolescence are commonly exposed to their female classmates wearing them, in what might be called an experiment in sexual discovery waiting to happen.</description>
<picurl>149786.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2455" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>tsundere</name>
<description>Tsundere (ツンデレ) (pronounced /(t)sʌnˈdɪə(r)/ in English or /t͡sun.de.ɽe/ in Japanese) is a Japanese concept of a character archetype which describes a person with a conceited, irritable, and/or violent personality that suddenly becomes modest and loving when triggered by some sort of cause (such as being alone with someone). The inverse scenario, where a modest and loving person becomes conceited/irritable/violent, is also a tsundere.
The default state does not matter. The character can default to "tsuntsun" or "deredere"; the key concept is the fact that there`s a (generally very quick) flip from one mode to the other.
It can also describe a contradictory personality which is good-willed on the inside, but with a harsh attitude on the outside. Originally found in Japanese bishoujo games, the word is now part of the otaku moe phenomenon, reaching into other media such as anime, manga, novels, and even mass media.
Tsundere is a portmanteau of the two words tsuntsun (ツンツン), and deredere (デレデレ). Tsuntsun is defined as "aloof, morose, pointed", and deredere is defined as "exhausted, lovestruck". Tsunderekko (ツンデレっ娘) is a related noun, referring to a girl with a tsundere personality. Like nekomimi, tsundere is considered a moe-inspiring character trait. The concept has received increasing attention in Japan, with a tsundere cafe opened in Akihabara and tsundere-themed products released (like Tomy Co.`s portable television set), and the concept increasingly reflected in recent anime, from an extended discussion of the meaning of the concept and its origin on the internet in http://anidb.net/a4777 [Lucky Star]`s Lucky Channel segment to merchandise for http://anidb.net/a3651 [The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya] classifying the characters according to tsundere-ness. Another accepted definition of tsundere is a girl who has a combative attitude toward others but is also kind on the inside. She usually plays out as having an attitude toward the main character, usually a male, and often criticizing him in one way or another, but as the series progresses she eventually warms up to him and sometimes even falls in love with him.</description>
<picurl>30388.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2520" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>school swimsuit</name>
<description>A school swimsuit (also known as sukumizu, shorthand for school mizugi) is a standardised navy blue one-piece swimsuit worn by schoolgirls. Typically they also have a name tag on the front. Sukumizu can also be black or white.
Normally worn at schools though sometimes also worn at beaches when the character feels this to be easier, forgot to buy a normal swimsuit of their own or wants to give some fan service to those that like school swimsuits better than regular swimsuits.
In http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] anime, a swimsuit of this type sometimes serves censoring purposes when characters take a bath. If there is a group of female characters donning swimsuits, you can expect the youngest or youngest-looking girl to wear one of these.</description>
<picurl>52174.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2670" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>school festival - TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>THIS TAG NEEDS TO BE SPLIT:
into http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=tag&amp;tagid=6119&amp;reltb=eptb [school culture festival]
and http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=tag&amp;tagid=2665&amp;reltb=eptb [school sports festival]
The obligatory school festival (or cultural fair) with cosplay cafe, haunted house, theatre performance, and food booths cannot be missing in any school setting.
For good measure there may also be an athletics or sports festival in this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2781" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>first kiss</name>
<description>The first kiss plays a role in this anime. Especially for the female cast this can be quite an important moment, so that stealing ones first kiss is serious for them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2823" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>paper clothes</name>
<description>Worn clothing appears paper-thin and takes little abuse to be shredded or torn from the body. This is common in ecchi anime where the main storyline involves some type of fighting but consists primarily of dialogue and fanservice (Ikkitousen and Platonic Heart). Various girls’ clothing exploding as if made of rice paper is a very enticing prospect.</description>
<picurl>150776.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2842" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-19">
<name>incest</name>
<description>Incest is human sexual activity between family members or close relatives by consanguinity (blood relations) and sometimes by affinity (marriage or stepfamily), adoption, clan, or lineage. The incest taboo is among the most widespread cultural taboos in present and past societies. Most modern societies have laws regarding incest or social restrictions on closely consanguineous marriages, with first cousins being the closest kin that is often (but not always) considered legally acceptable.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210769.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2845" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-04-30">
<name>blackmail</name>
<description>In general usage, blackmail is a crime involving unjustified threats against a person or organization in order to make a gain or harm or cause material loss to them unless a demand is met. It may be considered similar to or a form of extortion, although some jurisdictions will consider them as separate crimes. Most often, blackmail involves the threat of revealing some secret to a given third party, which may be another person, a rival organization, or a state institution such as the police, or to the general public. In anime and related media, and more specifically in pornographic works, blackmail is also a device used to coerce people, generally female and often schoolgirls, into having sex with another or others; in such cases, it may be considered similar to or a form of rape.</description>
<picurl>136031.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3101" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-22">
<name>lottery wheel</name>
<description>One of the protagonists plays the lottery wheel in some shopping mall and — as fate will have it — wins a prize, e.g. a visit to the local hot springs or water park. Thus adding an unexpected plot twist to the story (and some ecchi potential).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3395" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-18">
<name>promise</name>
<description>A dramatically-made promise that serves as foreshadowing. The promise will eventually be called in and action will be required.
Whether they succeed, fail or refuse to keep their promise depends almost entirely on the idealism-level of the story. Other factors, such as whether they were told what they had to do, or if it was a Leonine Contract, may come into play. Even Releasing from the Promise is usually a scene of high drama.
Source: TVTropes</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4149" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>non-blood-related siblings -- DO NOT USE -- TO BE DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is set to be deleted. Please add char-char relations of the "is family of" type with the http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Content:Characters#is_family_of [appropriate relation comment] to the relevant characters and remove the tag from the corresponding anime. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4246" parentid="3395" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-01">
<name>childhood promise</name>
<description>Sweet childhood promises... who remembers them other than the Japanese anime characters?
It keeps the main characters obsessed with promises that they made when they were children, mostly related to love, with lines like "I will always protect you" or "I will marry you when we grow up".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4389" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>amusement park visit</name>
<description>Plot device: All or part of the cast visit an amusement park. 
Added to show the characters in a more leisurely environment (i.e. other than school or at home). Often used in school settings to "develop" and "further" the relations between the male and female leads in this anime. Can also set the stage for comedic misunderstandings, or private moments with possibly ecchi undertones. 
Furthermore, it gives the anime creators a chance to show off their characters in non-uniforms (e.g. school uniforms). Also see "pool episode".</description>
<picurl>160897.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4481" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>protection complex</name>
<description>A character has a protection complex if the character is overly protective of other characters, beyond what would be considered a "normal" or "expected" duty of care.
The magnitude of overprotection can vary. It can be as low as constantly nagging someone to "stay safe". It can be as extreme as the protector making it their mission in life to protect the other character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4496" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-02">
<name>public aquarium</name>
<description>A public aquarium is the aquatic counterpart of a zoo, housing living aquatic species for viewing. Most public aquariums feature tanks larger than those kept by home aquarists, as well as smaller tanks. Since the first public aquariums were built in the mid-19th century, they have become popular and their numbers have increased. Most modern accredited aquariums stress conservation issues and educating the public.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>167001.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4543" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-11-04">
<name>even the girls want her</name>
<description>A female character is presented as so uniquely spectacular that even some (or all) other female characters wouldn`t mind making her their (girl)friend-with-benefits.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5593" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-13">
<name>branching story</name>
<description>The whole series consists of alternative stories, starting at the same point, branching off to different endings. It is like a normal dating sim, where you have different choices to meet different girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5834" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>show within a show</name>
<description>A fictional TV (or radio, or stage) show that takes place within an actual TV show; or, occasionally, a fictional instalment or incarnation of an actual show. Many comedies have short one-off gags where they parody existing shows.
Example: A large part of Martian Successor Nadesico is centred around the fictional popular anime Gekigangar III, which is being watched by several characters of the Nadesico crew.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5862" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-08">
<name>melodrama</name>
<description>A melodrama is a dramatic work that exaggerates plot and characters in order to appeal to the emotions, often with strongly stereotyped characters. Language, behaviour, or events which resemble melodramas are also called melodramatic. In scholarly and historical musical contexts melodramas are dramas of the 18th and 19th centuries in which orchestral music or song was used to accompany the action.
Melodrama is a style of drama that has been applied on the stage, in movies and television, and radio formats, from the 18th century to the present. Because of the long timeframe in which the style has existed, it is difficult to derive a precise definition. The term melodrama is most often used pejoratively, to suggest that the work to which the term is applied lacks sophistication or subtlety.
The term originated from the early 19th-century French word mélodrame, which is derived from Greek melos, music, and French drame, drama (from Late Latin drāma, which in turn derives from Greek drān, to do, perform).
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5883" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-05-10">
<name>dreams</name>
<description>Waking or sleeping, the mind can go to some strange places, usually beyond the control of the dreamer. New worlds, strange creatures, unfulfilled fantasies, they are all there.
Sometimes a person`s dreams can be taken over, with catastrophic consequences for the character and sometimes the real world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6039" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-18">
<name>piggyback ride</name>
<description>One of the protagonists (usually male) gives another character (usually female) a ride on the back. Can be interpreted as a sign of closeness or endearment in a romance setting.
Reasons: The female character is exhausted from previous running, or has a fit of anaemia, or hurt herself and no longer can walk.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6577" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-17">
<name>student government</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="50852" type="main character in" update="2013-03-29">
<rating votes="14">3.86</rating>
<name>Maeda Kazuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134401.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10776" picture="77627.jpg">Shimazaki Nobunaga</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50853" type="main character in" update="2012-11-26">
<rating votes="21">6.26</rating>
<name>Niimi Haruka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128637.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50854" type="main character in" update="2013-03-29">
<rating votes="23">6.94</rating>
<name>Muroto Aki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134402.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50855" type="main character in" update="2013-03-29">
<rating votes="18">6.68</rating>
<name>Sakura Mai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134403.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12266" picture="56026.jpg">Kanemoto Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50856" type="main character in" update="2013-03-29">
<rating votes="20">5.51</rating>
<name>Sanehara Hikari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134404.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="591" picture="226209.jpg">Mizuhashi Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50857" type="main character in" update="2013-03-29">
<rating votes="23">7.80</rating>
<name>Masaki Nonoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134405.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50858" type="main character in" update="2013-03-29">
<rating votes="20">5.62</rating>
<name>Yunoki Rina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134406.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2345" picture="22115.jpg">Oogame Asuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50859" type="main character in" update="2013-03-29">
<rating votes="15">5.18</rating>
<name>Misumi Tomoe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134407.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50860" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-29">
<rating votes="16">6.58</rating>
<name>Maeda Kanon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134408.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="101" picture="16709.jpg">Ise Mariya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50861" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-29">
<rating votes="8">6.01</rating>
<name>Ootani Momoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134409.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="424" picture="224027.jpg">Endou Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52936" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-29">
<rating votes="7">3.91</rating>
<name>Kurebayashi Katsumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134410.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1609" picture="19579.jpg">Mizuhara Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52937" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-29">
<rating votes="6">3.48</rating>
<name>Narita Ruu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134412.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4713" picture="186249.jpg">Hasegawa Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52938" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-29">
<rating votes="12">7.47</rating>
<name>Uchida Yuuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134413.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="411" picture="17475.jpg">Takagaki Ayahi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52939" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-29">
<rating votes="5">2.37</rating>
<name>Kudou Hiromichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134415.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52940" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-29">
<rating votes="4">2.39</rating>
<name>Nakagawa Itta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134416.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="434" picture="41082.jpg">Shiraishi Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52941" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-29">
<rating votes="6">1.72</rating>
<name>Azuma Takashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134417.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52942" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-05">
<rating votes="5">4.55</rating>
<name>Kitagawa Misa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kitagawa Misa is a teacher at class 2-B.</description>
<picture>134715.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="314" picture="10231.jpeg">Seto Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54961" type="appears in" update="2013-04-13">
<name>Photography Club</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Shady photography club that takes perverted shots of girls.</description>
</character>
<character id="54962" type="appears in" update="2013-04-13">
<name>Photo Club</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>School`s official photography club that takes the school`s official photos.</description>
</character>
<character id="55109" type="appears in" update="2013-04-20">
<name>Cooking Research Society</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Cooking club that has only one member but recognized because the Student Council President thought it was wonderful how recipes of students could be passed through the generations.</description>
</character>
<character id="57220" type="appears in" update="2013-06-15">
<rating votes="4">4.08</rating>
<name>Alice</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138592.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="411" picture="17475.jpg">Takagaki Ayahi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57559" type="appears in" update="2013-06-29">
<rating votes="3">4.27</rating>
<name>Maeda no Hahaoya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139273.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13796" picture="172018.jpg">Mizusawa Kei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57560" type="appears in" update="2013-06-29">
<rating votes="1">4.96</rating>
<name>Maeda no Chichioya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139272.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2016" picture="240331.jpg">Yanaka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="148781" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-04-26</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">これからの想い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Feelings Henceforth</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Nouvelles résolutions</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Korekara no Omoi</title>
<summary>Kazuya is taking full advantage of his blackmail material on Aki Muroto. If she wants certain pictures kept hidden, she has to do anything he says. But how will Kazuya respond when he gets thrown into a similar situation?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622137</identifier>
<identifier>photo-kano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148782" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-04-19</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">百花繚乱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Profusion of Flowers</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tapis de fleurs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hyakka Ryouran</title>
<summary>Kazuya is getting to know the girls around school. He learns of Aki’s surprising past and helps her “naughty” side blossom. When the Photography Club commences Operation: Haruka Niimi, he must put flirting aside to protect an old friend!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622135</identifier>
<identifier>photo-kano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148783" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-04-12</airdate>
<rating votes="8">3.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">学園天国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">School Paradise</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Paradis scolaire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gakuen Tengoku</title>
<summary>Now that Kazuya is a member of the Photography Club, he has been taking pictures right and left. One day, Haruka asks him to take some swimsuit pictures of her, but what if the Photography Club finds out?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622133</identifier>
<identifier>photo-kano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148784" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-04-05</airdate>
<rating votes="10">2.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">出会い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Encounter</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rencontre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Deai</title>
<summary>Kazuya’s father gave him a digital camera on the last day of summer vacation. He takes it to school with him, believing that it will change his life. During his very first day of taking pictures, he gets recruited into the Photograph Club!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622131</identifier>
<identifier>photo-kano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148877" update="2013-04-05">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-04-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148878" update="2013-04-05">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-04-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="149753" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-24</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">素顔を見つめて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gaze into Her True Face</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Vois mon vrai visage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sugao o Mitsumete</title>
<summary>As Kazuya blackmails Aki with his picture of her sneaking onto campus, he begins to catch snippets of her true self. She is the stern Student Body President, the young lady who loves to dive and an insecure girl...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622145</identifier>
<identifier>photo-kano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="149754" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-17</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">星の笑顔</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Star`s Smile</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sourire sous les étoiles</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hoshi no Egao</title>
<summary>Hikari Sanehara, who enjoys scenery shots in photo club and rarely cracks a smile is the next target in a stealth photo session that must go uninterrupted.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622143</identifier>
<identifier>photo-kano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="149755" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-10</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">想いはるかに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">These Feelings Are Vastly...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Toujours plus loin...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omoi Haruka ni</title>
<summary>Kazuya and Haruka are able to kiss and make up, but Kazuya isn’t in the clear yet. With the school festival coming up, the Photography Club’s Miss Photogenic Gallery is right around the corner! How will Haruka react to a gallery on her?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622141</identifier>
<identifier>photo-kano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="149756" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-03</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋の掛け違い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mismatched Romance</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Occasion manquée</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi no Kakechigai</title>
<summary>Kazuya and Haruka’s relationship seemed to be headed straight from childhood friends to boyfriend/girlfriend, at least for a while. But now with everyone insisting that Haruka can do better, maybe it’s time Kazuya let her go...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622139</identifier>
<identifier>photo-kano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="149826" update="2013-04-20">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Pv2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="149827" update="2013-04-20">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150532" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-21</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フォトグラフメモリー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Photograph Memory</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Photograph Memory</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Photograph Memory</title>
<summary>Tomoe is unhappy with herself and tries to remain aloof, but Kazuya won’t stand for that. He wants to make Tomoe realize that she isn’t plain and help her make friends. But what if there is a reason why she tries to remain invisible...?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622153</identifier>
<identifier>photo-kano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150533" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-14</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">学園のお嫁さん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The School Bride</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`épouse idéale</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gakuen no Oyome-san</title>
<summary>After trying one of Rina’s hamburgers, Kazuya promises to help recruit members for the Cooking Workshop. They need a total of four members before the school festival, but that’s only a month away! Will they get the people they need in time?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622151</identifier>
<identifier>photo-kano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150534" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-07</airdate>
<rating votes="7">2.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天使の舞い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Angel`s Dance</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La danse de l`ange</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenshi no Mai</title>
<summary>After finding those "dirty" magazines with Kazuya, Mai Sakura begins to blackmail him into doing her favors for her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622149</identifier>
<identifier>photo-kano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150535" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-31</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋の果たし状</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Letter of Challenge for Love</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Défi amoureux</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi no Hatashijou</title>
<summary>Nonoka has two goals at the moment. The first is the master the rise ball. The second, and quite possibly more difficult of the two, is to win Kazuya’s heart! Since she’s not really his type, it’s going to take quite a bit of work!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622147</identifier>
<identifier>photo-kano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151034" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-28</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">想い合い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mutual Feelings</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sentiments réciproques</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omoiai</title>
<summary>Kazuya has a big problem. While his parents are gone on a trip for Europe, he realizes that he might have the hots for his younger sister, Kanon. If he confesses his feelings, for better or worse, life at home may never be the same again!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>628013</identifier>
<identifier>photo-kano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151380" update="2013-06-29">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-06-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending - ep13</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151381" update="2013-06-29">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending - ep12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151382" update="2013-06-29">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-06-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending - ep11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151383" update="2013-06-29">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-06-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending - ep10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151384" update="2013-06-29">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-05-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending - ep9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151385" update="2013-06-29">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-05-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending - ep8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151386" update="2013-06-29">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-05-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending - ep7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151388" update="2013-06-29">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-05-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending - ep5,6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157603" update="2014-01-24">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">月の魔法姫 ムーンウィッチ プリティラビィ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Moon Witch Pretty Lovey Song</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
