<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9522" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2012-12-22</startdate>
<enddate>2013-03-16</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Boku no Imouto wa "Osaka Okan"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Boku no Imouto wa Osaka Okan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Osaka Okan</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">僕の妹は「大阪おかん」</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">나의 여동생은 "오사카 아줌마"</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">我的妹妹是「大阪大妈」</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.imouto-okan.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="29707" type="Music">Inoue Jun`ichi</name>
<name id="34753" type="Character Design">Pikomaro</name>
<name id="34754" type="Animation Work">Charaction</name>
<name id="34987" type="Original Work">Chuukei Shuppan</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch50888 [Kyousuke]`s younger sister http://anidb.net/ch50887 [Namika] has been living apart from him for ten years. One day, she returns and begins to live with him again, but she has turned into an energetic Osaka girl, an "Osaka Momma".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="581">2.88</permanent>
<temporary count="586">5.36</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>143769.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14906</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18419</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>16405</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>16936</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5273</identifier>
<identifier>tmvhhr</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.imouto-okan.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Boku-no-imoutowa"Osaka-okan"</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>僕の妹は「大阪おかん」</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2815</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>344493</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15999</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=a4yuf4YfyWA</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=PGoaNyibME8</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>boku-no-imoutowaosaka-okan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="50887" type="main character in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="10">6.59</rating>
<name>Ishihara Namika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129810.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50888" type="main character in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Ishihara Kyousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129811.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="208" picture="20458.jpg">Shiraishi Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50889" type="main character in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="4">5.30</rating>
<name>Kaede</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129812.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="146084" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2012-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ある朝, 大阪おかんの妹ができまして.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">One Morning, I Got an Osaka Momma for a Sister</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aru Asa, Osaka Okan no Imouto ga Dekimashite.</title>
<summary>Kyousuke is getting to learn the ways of his Osakan sister.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616619</identifier>
<identifier>boku-no-imoutowaosaka-okan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146529" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-01-05</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妹が大阪おかんなんですけど!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You See, My Sister Is an Osaka Momma!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Imouto ga Osaka Okan Nandesu kedo!</title>
<summary>Watching TV with an Osakan is an experience.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616621</identifier>
<identifier>boku-no-imoutowaosaka-okan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146729" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-01-12</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺の妹がこんなに大阪おかんなわけがない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Sister Can`t Be This Much of an Osaka Momma</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore no Imouto ga Konna ni Osaka Okan na Wake ga Nai</title>
<summary>An Osakan likes to shop for the deal and share the experience.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616623</identifier>
<identifier>boku-no-imoutowaosaka-okan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146854" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-01-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大阪おかんだけど愛さえあれば関係ないよねっ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">She`s an Osaka Momma, but What`s It Matter If We`ve Got Love?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Osaka Okan Dakedo Ai sae Areba Kankei Nai yo ne!</title>
<summary>An Osakan High school girl is a unique character, always there if you need a piece of candy.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616625</identifier>
<identifier>boku-no-imoutowaosaka-okan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146855" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-01-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大阪おかんホーム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Osaka Momma`s Home</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Osaka Okan Home</title>
<summary>If you say “We won” first thing in the morning, it’s always about the Tigers!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616627</identifier>
<identifier>boku-no-imoutowaosaka-okan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146992" update="2013-01-30">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2012-12-29</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">配信限定大阪おかん.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Webstream-only Osaka Momma.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haishin Gentei Osaka Okan.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147164" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-02-02</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最近, 妹のようすがちょっと大阪おかんなんだが.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Recently, My Sister Is a Bit Osaka Momma-ish</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikin, Imouto no Yousu ga Chotto Osaka Okan Nanda ga.</title>
<summary>Shopping is always about the haggling.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616629</identifier>
<identifier>boku-no-imoutowaosaka-okan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147316" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-02-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">この中に1人, 大阪おかんがいる!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">One of These People Is an Osaka Momma!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kono Naka ni Hitori, Osaka Okan ga Iru!</title>
<summary>An Osakan never admits a mistake.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616631</identifier>
<identifier>boku-no-imoutowaosaka-okan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147427" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-03-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">浪花はん@がんばらない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Namika-han@Unmotivated</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Namika-han Ganbaranai</title>
<summary>Nothing annoys an Osakan than a fake Osakan.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616641</identifier>
<identifier>boku-no-imoutowaosaka-okan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147428" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-03-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最近の大阪おかんブームはどうやら俺のおかげらしいですよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seems the Recent Osaka Momma Craze Is All Thanks to Me</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikin no Osaka Okan Boom wa Douyara Ore no Okage Rashii Desu yo</title>
<summary>Namika teaches her friend Kaede proper Osakan restaurant techniques.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616639</identifier>
<identifier>boku-no-imoutowaosaka-okan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147429" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-03-02</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妹は大阪おかんの女神ちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Sister Is the Osaka Momma Goddess</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Imouto wa Osaka Okan no Megami-chan</title>
<summary>Whether an Osakan is from the area, they will always give directions.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616637</identifier>
<identifier>boku-no-imoutowaosaka-okan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147430" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-02-23</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大阪おかんな妹と受難な俺</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Osaka Momma Sister and the Suffering Me</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Osaka Okan na Imouto to Junan na Ore</title>
<summary>An Osakan usage of words is very colorful and don’t waste a gag.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616635</identifier>
<identifier>boku-no-imoutowaosaka-okan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147431" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-02-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あるいは現在進行形の大阪おかん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Or It May Be a Present Progressive Osaka Momma</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arui wa Genzai Shinkoukei no Osaka Okan</title>
<summary>An Osakan wants to know who to root for early in a conversation.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>616633</identifier>
<identifier>boku-no-imoutowaosaka-okan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="149866" update="2013-04-21">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-04-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Blu-ray発売決定</title>
<title xml:lang="en">BD CM</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Blu-Ray Hatsubai Kettei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="149867" update="2013-04-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-12-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="149868" update="2013-04-21">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">PVムービー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV long</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">PV Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="153186" update="2013-08-31">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<rating votes="4">5.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">うちのお兄ちゃんは「東京ルール」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Brother`s "Tokyo Rules"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchi no Onii-chan wa "Tokyo Rules"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="153924" update="2013-09-07">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="153925" update="2013-09-07">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="153926" update="2013-09-07">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="153927" update="2013-09-07">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="153928" update="2013-09-07">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
