<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9546" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-01-04</startdate>
<enddate>2014-03-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Saikin, Imouto no Yousu ga Chotto Okashiinda ga.</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">최근 여동생의 상태가 조금 이상한 것 같다만</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">ImoCho</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">最近, 妹のようすがちょっとおかしいんだが.</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Recently, My Sister Is Unusual</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Recently, My Sister Is Unusual</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">最近, 妹妹的样子有点怪?</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="10350" type="Sequel">Saikin, Imouto no Yousu ga Chotto Okashiinda ga. Moa no Hatsukoi Memory? 16 Nenme no Happy Christmas</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9134" approval="4" total="9">Ore no Imouto ga Konna ni Kawaii Wake ga Nai.</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="409046">It was a lot better than i expected, better than the first episodes make it seem. However, the ending was awful.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="382805">not very good, but not very bad either</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="497205">Compared to Rom/Coms of recent creation this felt very refreshing. The levels of affection progressed at a nice (believable) pace, instead of lighting fast and slapstick. As far as the future of this series, I believe a Second season can gather a larger audience and better ratings if they continue at the pace they have been following. And Blu-Rays have a very promising sales figure if they properly uncensored everything and replace the "text scenes" with animated scenes</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://imocyo-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="35813" type="Animation Work">Project No.9</name>
<name id="20108" type="Character Design">Suzuki Futoshi</name>
<name id="1557" type="Series Composition">Kurata Hideyuki</name>
<name id="15782" type="Direction">Hata Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="20108" type="Chief Animation Direction">Suzuki Futoshi</name>
<name id="7900" type="Chief Animation Direction">Taniguchi Motohiro</name>
<name id="9448" type="Music">Nakanishi Ryousuke</name>
<name id="34691" type="Original Work">Matsuzawa Mari</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the manga by http://anidb.net/cr34691 [Matsuzawa Mari], serialised in http://anidb.net/cr12273 [Monthly Dragon Age].
http://anidb.net/ch51103 [Kanzaki Mitsuki] lives with her step-brother http://anidb.net/ch51102 [Yuuya] after her mother remarries. One day, Mitsuki is possessed by the self-proclaimed spirit of a young girl, http://anidb.net/ch51101 [Kotobuki Hiyori]. Hiyori (in Mitsuki`s body) must fall in love with Yuuya to move towards the Gates of Heaven.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1298">2.85</permanent>
<temporary count="1311">5.61</temporary>
<review count="1">4.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>146635.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14947</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17777</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://imocyo-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Saikin,_Imōto_no_Yōsu_ga_Chotto_Okaishiin_Da_Ga.</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>最近、妹のようすがちょっとおかしいんだが。</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3256</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>347807</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16758</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>recently-my-sister-is-unusual</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="28" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-16">
<name>baseball</name>
<description>Baseball is like a complicated version of Rounders. It involves hitting a ball with a stick, then running around several bases placed in the form of a diamond on a field. Big in the US, and also in Japan.</description>
<picurl>29801.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="997" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>association football</name>
<description>Football is a sport that involves kicking a ball in order to score a goal, while the other team tries to stop you by kicking the ball in the other direction to score a goal of their own. In the United States, this sport is known as soccer; the inappropriately titled "American" football (which in fact is played with the egg-shaped "ball" being carried around) is some kind of rugby for babies.</description>
<picurl>40031.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1049" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-03-06">
<name>cycling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1241" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-18">
<name>swimming</name>
<description>Swimming is an individual or team sport that involves using arms and legs to move the body through water. Typically, the sport takes place in pools or in open water. Competitive swimming is one of the most popular Olympic sports, with events in butterfly, backstroke, breaststroke, freestyle, and individual medley. In addition to these individual events, swimmers take part in relays.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>208479.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1645" parentid="2751" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-03">
<name>kendo</name>
<description>Kendo, or kendou in Japanese, is a popular sport from Japan. It consists of swordplay with one or two http://anidb.net/t1817 [shinai], a two-handed bamboo sword which may also be held with one hand only, while wearing armour.</description>
<picurl>163593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2535" parentid="1152" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-18">
<name>ghost</name>
<description>In traditional belief, a ghost is the soul or spirit of a deceased person or animal that can appear, in visible form or other manifestation, to the living. Descriptions of the apparition of ghosts vary widely: The mode of manifestation can range from an invisible presence to translucent or wispy shapes, to realistic, life-like visions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2578" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-12">
<name>vulgar</name>
<description>Talking (and acting) in a way that is considered uncultivated, bawdy, common, coarse or unrefined, or "taboo" according to existing cultural standards. Includes boorish manners and obtrusive display of carnal "assets".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2658" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>toilet humour</name>
<description>Everything leads back to poo.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2706" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>masturbation</name>
<description>Manual erotic stimulation of the genitals or other erogenous regions, often to orgasm, either by oneself or a partner.</description>
<picurl>210612.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2751" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-27">
<name>combat</name>
<description>Combat involves a violent conflict with the goal to establish dominance over an opponent.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2752" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tennis</name>
<description>Tennis is yet another sport involving hitting a ball. Were it not for the copious amounts of grass involved in certain varieties, it seems hard to imagine that people would pay it any attention at all.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2753" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>track and field</name>
<description>A collection of sports events that involve running, throwing, and jumping.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2816" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sexual fantasies</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime let their imaginations run wild thinking about another character.
Yes, they are thinking about sex, and in an ecchi anime these thoughts are often perverted, leading to a nosebleed. But it may also be romanticising simply being husband and wife, and everything that implies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2820" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>wardrobe malfunction</name>
<description>A euphemistic term for an embarrassing display of a body part when clothing droops, falls, or is torn. Wikipedia: "Super Bowl XXXVIII half-time show" for more details.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2822" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>skirt flipping</name>
<description>Naughty characters — usually boys — flip the skirts of female protagonists to ascertain what panties they are wearing (also see Pantsu category).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2828" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-26">
<name>borderline porn</name>
<description>Breaks the bounds of "excessive fanservice".
While the physical interactions and dialogue between characters may be extremely sexual, the most sexual situations do *not* have sex itself take place.
Specifically descriptive of containing all the plentiful features of (excessive) fanservice in addition to the interactions between characters being quite sexual — at most, sexual in NATURE only. This means physical touching such as groping, molesting, or bondage will focus primarily on the revealed (i.e. nude) upper portion of the body or through/over clothing on the lower half of the body. This is all WITHOUT actual sex acts (penetration, etc.) taking place.</description>
<picurl>214855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2894" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>female student</name>
<description>Pretty much exclusive to hentai shows only unless an ecchi show has implied sex and/or a strong indicator of nudity. A character is considered a student if she goes to school, doesn`t matter if it`s high school, college or homeschooling, but she should be of appropriate age for a student; a housewife going to college should not get this category.</description>
<picurl>210611.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3146" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-29">
<name>divorce</name>
<description>The parents depicted in this anime have divorced, usually upsetting the life of their children.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3504" parentid="2879" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>sake</name>
<description>Sake, generally referred to as a Japanese rice wine, is an alcoholic beverage made by fermenting rice.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>215208.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3663" parentid="6347" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-14">
<name>body takeover</name>
<description>A person`s body is taken over by some foreign intelligence. It`s not brainwashing, because they still have control of their own mind — but that`s all they have. Either they`ve been reduced to a spectator in their own body, or their soul has been booted out of their body entirely. Either way, the rest of the cast will soon find he`s not himself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4112" parentid="3842" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-14">
<name>excessive censoring</name>
<description>There are basically two cases to which this term can be applied to:
1) creative censorship
The TV station airing the anime does its best to remove most ecchi parts from the show, using various and original methods. Usually, an uncensored BD/DVD is released later. Apart from the publisher`s greed - sometimes the censorship is used intentionally to make a scene look more obscene than it actually is.
2) convenient censorship
Another case of it - more often known under the term of "convenient censoring/ship" - is a blatant substitute for mosaic/steam/etc. over nether regions. This applies both to normal shows with occasional nudity as a normal part of human life (or just occasional flash of fanservice), as well as to heavy ecchi / borderline hentai shows where /literally/ everything is a fair (and far more "obscene" no matter how to look at it) game, except that misinterpreted taboo nonsense coming from §175 of JPC.</description>
<picurl>169459.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4149" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>non-blood-related siblings -- DO NOT USE -- TO BE DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is set to be deleted. Please add char-char relations of the "is family of" type with the http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Content:Characters#is_family_of [appropriate relation comment] to the relevant characters and remove the tag from the corresponding anime. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4577" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-19">
<name>family values</name>
<description>Family values are traditional or cultural values, generally conservative in nature, that pertain to the family`s structure, function, roles, beliefs, attitudes, and ideals. They encompass a set of beliefs, the most common of which is the classical "traditional family" involving a middle-class family with a breadwinner father and a homemaker mother, raising their biological children.
According to Merriam-Webster, family values are "values especially of a traditional or conservative kind which are held to promote the sound functioning of the family and to strengthen the fabric of society."
Source: English Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5518" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-03">
<name>flat chest jokes</name>
<description>Jokes about the (supposedly or actually) flat chest of a character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5875" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>jealousy</name>
<description>A character is jealous of another character either due to love, or power, or wealth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5943" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-14">
<name>misunderstanding</name>
<description>Suggests that a large portion of storyline revolves around a rather large misunderstanding between two or more characters, usually forming long lasting situations of separation or hostility between all those involved.
A large portion of the story may be dedicated to gradually working all parties into a mutual understanding to true intentions or changes of heart.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6347" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>body and host</name>
<description>When a foreign entity like that of a symbiote, body snatcher, puppeteer parasite, or even a hacker (when regarding machines like robots and computers) enters/outright hijacks a body, the possessed subject becomes what is usually called: the host.
The basic purpose of the host varies on what the point was for it to have been hijacked in the first place. Sometimes it`s used as a disguise, other times it`s used as a decoy and destraction, even simply being used as a weapon and piece of armor that the possessor uses to cause sheer chaos and destruction, but sometimes... a host can be used for fetish fuel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7075" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-05-07">
<name>adapted into Japanese movie</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a Japanese movie.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="51101" type="main character in" update="2013-12-12">
<rating votes="25">4.69</rating>
<name>Kotobuki Hiyori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147021.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16794" picture="214757.jpg">Ogura Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51102" type="main character in" update="2013-12-12">
<rating votes="14">3.82</rating>
<name>Kanzaki Yuuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147020.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="400" picture="171989.jpg">Majima Junji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51103" type="main character in" update="2015-01-01">
<rating votes="20">4.08</rating>
<name>Kanzaki Mitsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147019.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38750" picture="145599.jpg">Hashimoto Chinami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61322" type="main character in" update="2013-12-11">
<rating votes="24">6.70</rating>
<name>Kiritani Yukina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147022.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12266" picture="56026.jpg">Kanemoto Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62230" type="appears in" update="2014-01-12">
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<name>Minami-sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148463.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4929" picture="41385.jpg">Kitta Izumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62232" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-01-06">
<rating votes="17">4.75</rating>
<name>Neko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148203.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21806" picture="186701.jpg">Sasaki Mikoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62233" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-01-12">
<rating votes="13">4.87</rating>
<name>Tachibana Ayaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148461.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27265" picture="134453.jpg">Tanaka Manami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62234" type="appears in" update="2014-01-06">
<rating votes="2">4.24</rating>
<name>Kanzaki Tetsuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148204.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="369" picture="223406.jpg">Aoyama Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62235" type="appears in" update="2014-01-06">
<rating votes="5">5.14</rating>
<name>Kanzaki Kaoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148201.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="229" picture="152363.jpg">Itou Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62236" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-01-06">
<rating votes="8">3.10</rating>
<name>Torii Shoutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148202.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10130" picture="151714.jpg">Takumi Yasuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62237" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-03">
<rating votes="17">6.04</rating>
<name>Torii Moa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149490.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25107" picture="76467.jpg">Aimi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62860" type="appears in" update="2014-01-06">
<name>Ishi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148206.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9164" picture="69944.jpg">Matsumoto Shinobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62861" type="appears in" update="2014-01-06">
<name>Kyoushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148205.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32216" picture="223331.jpg">Sasa Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63042" type="appears in" update="2014-01-12">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Start Kakari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148459.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25804" picture="71817.jpg">Yamamoto Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63043" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-03-25">
<rating votes="14">4.99</rating>
<name>Akesaka Nanami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148462.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="568" picture="65531.jpg">Sakuma Kumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63045" type="appears in" update="2014-01-12">
<rating votes="3">6.70</rating>
<name>Mei-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148460.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37282" picture="136945.jpg">Toyota Moe</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63254" type="appears in" update="2014-01-20">
<name>Suugaku no Sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148796.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18698" picture="49321.jpg">Nakane Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63393" type="appears in" update="2014-01-26">
<name>Ten`in</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149073.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33933" picture="205085.jpg">Iwasawa Toshiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="64040" type="appears in" update="2014-02-10">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Yuuya (Youshou)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149952.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34901" picture="130616.jpg">Lynn</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="64546" type="appears in" update="2014-02-19">
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<name>Soccer-bu Captain</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150441.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38903" picture="239362.jpg">Uchimura Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="64547" type="appears in" update="2014-02-19">
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<name>Tennis-bu Captain</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150440.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34901" picture="130616.jpg">Lynn</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="64548" type="appears in" update="2014-02-19">
<name>Jitensha-bu Buchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150439.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25812" picture="151726.jpg">Matsumoto Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65273" type="appears in" update="2014-02-27">
<rating votes="7">4.31</rating>
<name>Kanzaki Mitsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150871.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38750" picture="145599.jpg">Hashimoto Chinami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65399" type="appears in" update="2014-03-04">
<name>Matsuzaki Katsutoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151071.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36222" picture="133333.jpg">Matsuzaki Katsutoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65400" type="appears in" update="2014-03-04">
<name>Higa Moeru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151070.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2828" picture="22872.jpg">Higa Moeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66057" type="appears in" update="2014-03-26">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Mei no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152292.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21806" picture="186701.jpg">Sasaki Mikoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66059" type="appears in" update="2014-03-26">
<name>Ten`in</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152294.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36062" picture="132363.jpg">Ueda Harumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66060" type="appears in" update="2014-03-26">
<name>Nakai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152296.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39685" picture="152297.jpg">Komatsu Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="156953" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-01-04</airdate>
<rating votes="12">3.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">美月SOS</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mitsuki SOS</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ma sœur est devenue bizarre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mitsuki SOS</title>
<summary>"Kanzaki Mitsuki" has been troubling herself over her relationship with her new family and her new older brother now that her mother`s remarried. To top it off, her mother is following her new step-father to his post abroad, leaving her all along with her new step-brother, Yuuya, and only making her troubles worse...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648589</identifier>
<identifier>recently-my-sister-is-unusual</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="156981" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハートキャッチ日和ちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heartcatch Hiyori-san</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Hiyori joue à Cupidon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Heartcatch Hiyori-chan</title>
<summary>After declaring that Mitsuki was a failure as a little sister, she decides to set an example through action. She borrows Mitsuki`s body, fixes breakfast in an apron, and goes shopping together with her brother. Mitsuki watches how well they get along in her spirit form, feeling mixed feelings about it.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648595</identifier>
<identifier>recently-my-sister-is-unusual</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="156982" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-01-18</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">たわわな果実</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heavy-Hanging Fruit</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un arbre chargé de fruits</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tawawa na Kajitsu</title>
<summary>Mitsuki and Yuuya are both locked in the bathroom naked?! The one who saved them was Kiritani Yukina, aka "Yuki-nee", Yuuya`s childhood friend who moved back in next door. With the appearance of a powerful rival who`s an older woman, a childhood friend, and has big breasts unlike Mitsuki, Hiyori panics.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648593</identifier>
<identifier>recently-my-sister-is-unusual</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="156983" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-01-11</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">嵐の中で輝いて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shining Amidst the Storm</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Brille dans la tempête</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arashi no Naka de Kagayaite</title>
<summary>Thanks to the ghost girl Kotobuki Hiyori, Mitsuki is forced to wear an indencetly shaped chastity belt around her crotch. In order to get the device off, Mitsuki will have to satisfy Hiyori so she can pass on by using her own body to experience all the kinds of things lovers would with Yuuya.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648591</identifier>
<identifier>recently-my-sister-is-unusual</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157052" update="2014-08-16">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-01-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157053" update="2014-08-16">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-01-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157654" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-02-02</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いけないボディ・スナッチャー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Naughty Body Snatcher</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un méchant voleur de corps</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikenai Body Snatcher</title>
<summary>By coincidence, Mitsuki meets up with Yuuya, Yukina, and the others at a water park. But due to her worries about the chastity belt she covered with her pareo, she couldn`t go in the water, and she was left sulking by the poolside as she watched the others happily having fun.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648597</identifier>
<identifier>recently-my-sister-is-unusual</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157657" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-02-23</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二人きりの水族館</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Alone Together at the Aquarium</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">En tête-à-tête à l`aquarium</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futarikiri no Suizokukan</title>
<summary>Yuuya recieves tickets to the aquarium from Neko. The moment she sees them, Hiyori hijacks Mitsuki`s body, and decides that the two of them are going to the aquarium together.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648603</identifier>
<identifier>recently-my-sister-is-unusual</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157658" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-02-16</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">てさぐり?部活もの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fumbling Around? Club Activities</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tâtonnements ? La vie en club</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tesaguri? Bukatsumono</title>
<summary>Ayaka invites Mitsuki to join her in observing the various sports clubs, and Mitsuki agrees. When she borrows Hiyori`s ability, Mitsuki is able to display incredible physical prowess, but she never had any interest in such clubs.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648601</identifier>
<identifier>recently-my-sister-is-unusual</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157659" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-02-09</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おお! 幽霊人間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Oh! A Ghost!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Oh, une fille fantôme !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oo! Yuurei Ningen</title>
<summary>Yuuya is left confused by Mitsuki`s unstable attitude. He doesn`t really understand the girl with wings (Hiyori) that he keeps seeing from time to time either. Meanwhile, thanks to her chastity belt, Mitsuki was extremely depressed from the embarassment of getting caught in it.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648599</identifier>
<identifier>recently-my-sister-is-unusual</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158283" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-03-23</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さよなら日和ちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell, Hiyori-chan</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Au revoir, Hiyori</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sayonara Hiyori-chan</title>
<summary>Mitsuki`s his little sister, and Yukina is an older sister figure. To Yuuya, both of them are precious "family members". But on one morning of their stay at the hot-springs, Neko hypnotizes Yuuya to "be more honest", and he calls Mitsuki "really cute" and gropes Yukina`s breasts.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648611</identifier>
<identifier>recently-my-sister-is-unusual</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158284" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-03-16</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゴースト ~入浴の幻~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ghost ~Phantom in the Bath~</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ghost — La source de l’illusion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ghost: Nyuuyoku no Maboroshi</title>
<summary>Mitsuki won tickets to a hot spring at a lottery, so she ends up traveling together with Yuuya as well as Nanami, Yukina, Ayaka, Neko, Torii, and his little sister. Once they arrive, the girls head straight for the outdoor bath, but Mitsuki wasn`t feeling very happy.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648609</identifier>
<identifier>recently-my-sister-is-unusual</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158285" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-03-09</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神前美月は静かに暮らしたい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kanzaki Mitsuki Wants to Live in Peace</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Devant Dieu, Mitsuki veut vivre en paix</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanzaki Mitsuki wa Shizuka ni Kurashitai</title>
<summary>After fighting over a trivial matter, Hiyori throws a fit and leaves. Mitsuki even enjoys the chance to finally have some time alone to herself for the first time in a while. However, during her dinner with Yuuya, she notices her own heart aching at his little behaviors.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648607</identifier>
<identifier>recently-my-sister-is-unusual</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158286" update="2017-01-04">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-03-02</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バトルヒーター&amp;料理の鉄人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle Heater &amp; Iron Chef</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Battle Heater et accro aux légumes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Battle Heater &amp; Ryouri no Tetsujin</title>
<summary>Tomorrow there`s a math test, and that`s when Aunt Nanami finished moving in to the Kanzaki household and set out the kotatsu. Mitsuki decided to study under the warm kotatsu, but soon begins falling asleep instead.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648605</identifier>
<identifier>recently-my-sister-is-unusual</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162950" update="2014-09-29">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 05 (18 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162951" update="2014-09-29">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 04 (18 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162952" update="2014-09-29">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 03 (18 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162953" update="2014-09-29">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 02 (18 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162954" update="2014-09-29">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 01 (40 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162955" update="2014-09-29">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 01 (2 min 13 sec)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
