<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9553" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-07-09</startdate>
<enddate>2013-09-24</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kami nomi zo Shiru Sekai: Megami Hen</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The World God Only Knows - Goddesses Arc</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Одному лишь Богу ведомый мир III</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Kaminomi 3</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">twgok 3</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">神のみぞ知るセカイ 女神篇</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The World God Only Knows: Goddesses</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Que sa volonté soit faite saison 3</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">只有神知道的世界 女神篇</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9324" type="Prequel">Kami nomi zo Shiru Sekai: Tenri Hen</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="7">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="132520">recomended for those who wached the first and second tv series. still no need to watch the OVA`s (which seemd to be pretty bad). was good fun.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="87321">great continuation of the series with the same great comedy but with a more serious tone</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="605024">The standard for the Genre when it comes to great storytelling.
I watched  it at first thinking it was going to be bad,but TWGOK won me over through its writing.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="596844">First season was great, and second season was a really neat follow-up.
Third season not only adds a proper plot, but also depth to the story - If you`ve watched season 1 and 2, you shouldn`t miss out on season 3, it`s even better than the first two.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="311037">The first season was reasonably interesting with some LOL moments and some endearing ones as well. In the context of this genre I`d give it an 8/10. The second one dropped the ball for most of the time and regained some momentum back at points. Probably a 7/10 or 6.5.

And we come to S3... It`s a 10/10 for sure and not just in the context of the genre like the other two. It`s amazing but you would need to watch the first two seasons and the OVAs before you get here to fully appreciate it. Trust me though. It`s worth it! WORTH IT!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="590343">This show just keeps getting better. It is every bit as solid as the first two seasons, but it manages to be even funnier and more touching all while a fresh spin on its concept. 

Seriously funny, and it even has a heart. You feel for the characters. It`s different than the previous seasons, because love interests actually return instead of getting a one-off in a couple of episodes.

MUST WATCH. It`s that good. Do yourself a favor and pick this one up.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="463248">Though some girls were skipped, this season is just as (if not more) hilarious as the previous seasons. Definitely must watch!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/kaminomi3/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3328" type="Character Design">Kawamura Toshie</name>
<name id="986" type="Animation Work">Manglobe</name>
<name id="3529" type="Character Design">Watanabe Akio</name>
<name id="1557" type="Series Composition">Kurata Hideyuki</name>
<name id="18553" type="Original Work">Wakaki Tamiki</name>
<name id="12168" type="Direction">Oosedo Satoshi</name>
<name id="2529" type="Music">Matsuo Hayato</name>
<name id="2308" type="Work">Geneon Universal Entertainment Japan</name>
<name id="20833" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hirano Emi</name>
<name id="40242" type="Work">Hayashi Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="14037" type="Work">Oomura Makoto</name>
<name id="9314" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sakamoto Chiyoko</name>
<name id="3328" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kawamura Toshie</name>
<name id="51531" type="Work">Ishimoto Jun`ya</name>
</creators>
<description>After releasing fourteen girls from the grasps of runaway spirits by making them fall in love with him, http://anidb.net/ch18463 [Keima] has proven himself to be the Capturing God of both the 2D and 3D worlds. But a new challenge awaits as http://anidb.net/ch34022 [Diana], the goddess possessing Keima`s neighbor http://anidb.net/ch34021 [Tenri], tasks him to find her sisters, and his only clue to their whereabouts resides with past conquests who still retain their memories. Now Keima is on the hunt in hopes that these divine beings might finally release him from his contract with Hell. But with the shadowy organization known as Vintage out to kill these girls, it becomes a race against time to put a stop to their plans and restore these goddesses to their former power.
Source: Anime-Planet</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2332">7.89</permanent>
<temporary count="2349">7.87</temporary>
<review count="3">8.83</review>
</ratings>
<picture>138744.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15334</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16706</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/kaminomi3/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://kaminomi.jp/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>The_World_God_Only_Knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>神のみぞ知るセカイ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3027</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>346196</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16253</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1876" parentid="2794" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>musical band</name>
<description>A musical ensemble also known as a music(al) group or music(al) band is a group of people who perform instrumental or vocal music, typically known by a distinct name.</description>
<picurl>10249.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2438" parentid="2794" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-16">
<name>idol</name>
<description>In Japanese culture, idols (アイドル) are media personalities in their teens and early twenties who are considered particularly cute and cuddly and who will, for a period ranging from several months to a few years, regularly appear in the mass media, e.g. as singers for J-pop groups, bit-part actors, TV personalities, models in photo spreads published in magazines, advertisements, etc.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>63097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2568" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-06">
<name>deity</name>
<description>Some religions say that there is a supernatural being called God. Other religions say there is more than one god. A supernatural being is also sometimes called a deity. Many religions believe that a deity created everything that exists. In most religions, a god is believed to be immortal (cannot die), and to have powers to control nature far beyond the powers of humans.</description>
<picurl>32415.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2632" parentid="6563" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>hell</name>
<description>"Abandon hope all ye who enter here"
You been a sinner? Welcome to Hell, where you will suffer for all eternity for your sins. The devils with pitchforks will take good care of you there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3772" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-09-03">
<name>library</name>
<description>In a traditional sense, a library is a large collection of books, and can refer to the place in which the collection is housed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5824" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-23">
<name>god is a girl</name>
<description>In storylines where many or all gods are portrayed as goddesses (female gods), "The God of all Gods", or the Number-One-God so to speak, is also female.
In other instances, such may just refer to a girl with god-like powers.</description>
<picurl>215285.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6021" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>gender bender</name>
<description>Term used to refer to a person who takes on the role of their opposite gender. This often only reaches to the extent of cross-dressing (involving physical appearance and clothing only), but in rarer cases, involves a total gender swap (which seems to be more common in anime) - where the willing or unwilling victim receives a body opposite of their original gender (either permanently or temporarily), with all natural parts per their new body fully (or just all-out amply) included.
Example of cross-dressing gender bender: "Maria+Holic"
Examples of body-swap gender bender: "Kashimashi: Girl meets Girl", "Birdy the Mighty Decode"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6078" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-23">
<name>gotta catch them all</name>
<description>A typical plot or sub-plot for many shows. Either the cast or somebody else, that being often the main antagonist, embarks on a quest to collect things, shiny things. Things that are said to grant simple wishes or even do miracles like bringing people back to life, destroying the whole world, galaxy, universe and in rare cases turning the hero into the greatest Pokemon Master. Those things can be weapons, lost technology, magical artefacts, pieces of a giant magical artefact and in some cases even people or little critters.
The point is, there`s stuff to collect!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6563" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-23">
<name>spirit realm</name>
<description>A spirit realm is a place where inhabited by the spirits of the dead, deities, demons, and other such entities. Examples would be Heaven and Hell in Christianity, the Elysium in Greek mythology, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="18462" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="342">7.50</rating>
<name>Elysia de Lute Ima</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Elucia or Elsie as she is commonly known, is a demon who was assigned to capture evil spirits that have escaped from hell. Her feather cloth (the floating scarf she is always seen with) can change the appearance of an object, create disguises to aid the mission or it can hide people in plain sight. She is left-handed and is rarely seen without her broom, as it was from her original role as a cleaner for hell. To stay close to Keima, she tells Mari, Keima`s mother, that she is an illegitimate child of Keima`s father, and ends up living in the Katsuragi household as well as attending the same class in school. Elsie is often made fun of by the other demons because of the poor grades she had in the demon academy. However, after partnering with Keima, they were able to capture 9 escaped spirits within half a year`s time, which earned her the Section Chief`s Award.
Elsie is also a member of Chihiro`s band in which she plays a left handed bass. She has also developed an interest in fire trucks. She literally idolises Keima, often referring to him as "Kami-sama" or "Kami-nii-sama" in her role as his sister.</description>
<picture>55510.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18463" type="main character in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="620">8.23</rating>
<name>Katsuragi Keima</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Katsuragi Keima is the primary protagonist of the story, a 17-year-old high school student attending Maijima High School Academy. He is known as "The Capturing God (落とし神, Otoshi-gami)" in the gaming world for his legendary skills in "capturing" any girls in dating sims. But ironically, he is called otamegane (a derogatory portmanteau of the two words otaku and megane-"glasses"). At the start of the series, Keima becomes a collaborator for catching runaway spirits when he replies to an e-mail requesting his help to "capture" girls without knowing it was a contract from Hell, to which Elsee appeared and asked for his aid to "capture" girls in real-life. For each individual of the "Capture Targets"—a girl with the runaway spirit in her—Keima utilizes his analytical skills and experiences from dating sims to capture them. Whenever he isn`t capturing runaway spirits, he is almost always seen playing video games on his PFP (a parody of Sony`s PSP). Also, despite the fact he even plays video games in class, he is still at the top of class in every subject. As the story progresses, his perspective of the "real world" girls becomes different.</description>
<picture>55509.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20154" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="176">7.42</rating>
<name>Takahara Ayumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takahara Ayumi is an athletic, cheery girl in Keima`s homeroom at school; Ayumi is a member of the school`s track-and-field team. She is an exceptional runner and was chosen as the representative for the upcoming tournament. As a result however she was pressured by jealous third-year runners, causing her to fake an injury in order to back out of the tournament. Keima, who was able to see through the deception, consoled and encouraged her not to give up which lead to capturing the escaped spirit. Ayumi and Keima are often paired up for cleaning duty together. In an omake from Chapter 14, and much more obviously in the whole of Chapter 30, she has become more eager to be around him. She is also a member of Chihiro`s band. Responsible for the guitar (SG).
Her name comes from Takanohara Station (高の原駅, Takanohara-eki).</description>
<picture>55511.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20155" type="appears in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="71">5.54</rating>
<name>Aoyama Mio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aoyama Mio is an elitist daughter of Aoyama Central Industry`s president. She is imperious and disdainful, being from a wealthy family; however, not known to the public, she is no longer rich—a secret which Keima discovers after stalking her to a shabby apartment. Despite her financial situation Mio continues to think of herself as a rich woman and is unable to let go of her late father`s memory. In order to get closer to her Keima took on the role of her chauffeur and driving her to school in various rickshaws. He then confronts her at an evening party, convincing her to accept the past and move on. Keima encounter Mio several chapters later, while occupying Yui`s body and learns that instead of him meeting her at the party, she remembers her old chauffeur Morita.
The prototype version of Mio appeared in Tamiki Wakaki`s one-shot Koishite!? Kami-sama!!, with her surname being Tsumagawa.
Her name comes from Aoyamacho Station (青山町駅, Aoyamacho-eki).</description>
<picture>55512.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21505" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="220">7.02</rating>
<name>Nakagawa Kanon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nakagawa Kanon is currently the most popular "traditional idol" for her quaint style, beauty and singing talents. She is also in Keima`s homeroom but had not been attending frequently because of her idol occupation. Kanon hopes that her song would "resound in everyone`s hearts." She is constantly anxious and dependent about the acknowledgment of her existence by others. When she feels ignored the spirit possessing her causes her body to appear transparent to others. Her lack of confidence is so great that when Keima first met her and didn`t recognize her she buzzed him with a pair of stun guns that she carries. On the night of her premiere performance as an idol she was overcome with stage fright, (becoming nearly invisible) until Keima encouraged her to believe in herself, filling the gap in her heart. During the performance afterwards Kanon began to glow so brightly that it was hard to see her. Keima commented on this, saying that she was no longer and `idol` but a `star`. In Kanon`s 4-box comic strips, it shows that there are leftover feelings for Keima; it`s shown that she trips when saying `kiss`, and when she sees something or someone related to Keima`s name (Exa: the wig is called a katsura in japanese).
She debuted as side member of a trio unit "Citron", became center after took off her glasses and started solo after she cut her hair. She does not use the glasses when she performs as an idol, but wears it in school and private. Raises a turtle named Kintarou as a pet.
The cause of Kanon`s crevice in the heart was her doubt of her existance as an idol.
Her name comes from Ise-Nakagawa Station (伊勢中川駅, Ise-Nakagawa-eki).</description>
<picture>73489.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21506" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="181">8.16</rating>
<name>Shiomiya Shiori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shiomiya Shiori is a reticent girl who loves to read books. She is a member of the Library Committee, which acts as the governing body and librarian for the school library. Her official position is a secretary. She has always wanted to talk to others but finds that she cannot articulate as fast as her thought process, as a result by the time she has formulated a response to something, the conversation has already moved on. From the beginning, Keima immediately catches her attention and anger by saying that physical books are no longer necessary in a digital era. As Keima continues to vandalize the books in the library, she becomes more conversational each time. Near the end of her story arc, she learns that three thousand books are to be disposed of to accommodate an audio-visual booth. Protesting, she locks down the building and barricades herself in the library. After Keima literally descends into the library and gives her "courage", she finally overcomes her silence.
She starts to write a story based on her faint memories during Keima`s capture, though the parts including Keima are erased.
The cause of Shiori`s crevice in the heart was her will to speak out her mind, when she had doubts of a good reply.
Her name comes from Shionomiya Station (汐ノ宮駅, Shionomiya-eki).</description>
<picture>73490.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21742" type="appears in" update="2012-12-30">
<rating votes="18">6.54</rating>
<name>Dokurou Skull</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dokurou Skull is hell`s branch chief of "counter measures". She assigned Elsee to capture spirits in the human world and sent Katsuragi Keima the contract letter. She may be the only person from hell who doesn`t make fun of Elsea.</description>
<picture>58954.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3368" picture="132584.jpg">Kujira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23171" type="appears in" update="2020-04-13">
<rating votes="54">8.31</rating>
<name>Nikaidou Yuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nikaidou is Keima`s homeroom and national language teacher. She has been ignoring Keima ever since he told her that there are 5012 games that are more fun than her lessons. She is a sadist.
She is in reality a high ranked devil from hell but is not part of the runaway squad.</description>
<picture>246184.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="222" picture="19786.jpg">Tanaka Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23172" type="appears in" update="2020-04-13">
<rating votes="21">3.46</rating>
<name>Terada Miyako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Terada Miyako is asecond-year Maijima High School Academy student enrolled in Class 2-B. Miyako is a close friend of Ayumi and Chihiro. She has a long hair and freckles on her cheeks. Track-and-field club member. Her speciality are the 400m.
After the Chihiro Arc, she became a member of Chihiro`s band. Responsible for the keyboard (KORG X50).
Her name is derived from Terada Station (寺田駅, Terada-eki).</description>
<picture>246185.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22168" picture="186262.jpg">Chikamura Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23231" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="194">6.74</rating>
<name>Kosaka Chihiro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kosaka Chihiro is a classmate and close friend of Takahara Ayumi. Chihiro is an average girl who has no redeeming features whatsoever: she`s not pretty, her grades are so-so, and she doesn`t have an after-school activity—except for going home. She is described as a "reality girl among reality" by Keima`s visual novel argot, meaning she is void of defining characteristics. Keima therefore refuses at the greatest that he does not want to `capture` her. She has a habit of confessing to handsome, attractive boys without any serious consideration, which yields no success; all because she feels "luminous" as those she is in pursuit of, for that moment. When Keima is tricked into cleaning duty with Chihiro, she demands him to help her latest confession to succeed. Keima reliezes then that a gap does not need to be filled by his love but can be filled by another person` love. He agrees to help Chihiro in her confession. During this period however her feelings begin to shift towards Keima due to their similarities (they both share a sense of disappointment in the real world). After an argument between the two Chihiro ran off and Keima realized that Chihiro did have one defining parameter and vowed to capture the spirit himself, which he does by convincing Chihiro that as long as she truly wants it, nothing can stop her from no longer being generic. Aftrwards, like Ayumi, Chihiro`s attitude towards Keima improves somewhat, becoming one of his `friends`.
Chihiro is the founder of "2B Pencils", an all-female band composed of girls from Class B of Mai-High; its members besides herself are Ayumi Takahara, Elsie, Miyako Terada and Yui Goidou. Responsible for the guitar and vocals (Mustang).
The cause of Chihiro`s crevice in the heart was her disbelief of having a straight-forward path in life that will spark her interests.
Her name is derived from Kawachi-Kosaka Station (河内小阪駅, Kawachi-Kosaka-eki).</description>
<picture>73486.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23425" type="appears in" update="2020-04-13">
<rating votes="56">8.23</rating>
<name>Katsuragi Mari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Keima`s mother resembles a typical shoujo manga-style mother; optimistic, ditsy, and loving. However, when she is angry, Mari removes her glasses and lets her hair down and changes her personality completely. Keima claims that she used to be a part of a biker gang, and has shown violent tendencies that reflect this.</description>
<picture>246186.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25896" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="196">8.57</rating>
<name>Haqua d`rot Herminium</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haqua is a fellow demon and friend of Elsie. She graduated as an outstanding honour student and was promoted to the position of District Chief of District 32 in Nagumo city. However, until meeting Keima, she had never captured an escaped spirit. After hearing of Elsie`s successes in this regard, the gap within Haqua`s heart widened. This allowed a powerful spirit to take control of her. After Elsie calmed Haqua down, they joined forces and defeated the spirit. Even though her human partner is http://anidb.net/ch26096 [Marui Yukie], Keima has occasionally assisted Haqua in her quest to find and capture escaped spirits. She seems to have taken a liking to him.
Haqua`s first name is derived from "Cretaceous (白亜, Hakua)".</description>
<picture>73485.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26042" type="appears in" update="2013-08-13">
<rating votes="6">3.06</rating>
<name>Fujiidera</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fujiidera is the chairwoman of school library.</description>
<picture>76197.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="347" picture="41555.jpg">Nonaka Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26044" type="appears in" update="2011-10-18">
<rating votes="38">1.91</rating>
<name>Kodama-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70364.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3149" picture="132209.jpg">Nakao Ryuusei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26047" type="appears in" update="2018-11-25">
<rating votes="10">4.45</rating>
<name>Okada</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch21505 [Kanon]`s manager.</description>
<picture>227115.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="229" picture="152363.jpg">Itou Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26096" type="appears in" update="2011-11-02">
<rating votes="5">3.52</rating>
<name>Marui Yukie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yukie is a 54 year old saleswoman and is still currently single. However, she is also Haqua`s human partner in capturing escaped spirits. Yukie loves to practice Tai Chi Chuan in her spare time and she always likes to offer stuff to others. She spends her day walking to nearby towns, delivering and selling the drink Gokult to other people. Yukie is seen as useless by her partner Haqua because even though they managed to discover 15 escaped spirits, Yukie could not get a single one of them to come out in the past couple months, even when she`s visiting them daily. However that was proved to be wrong later on as Yukie was able to capture 4 spirits in one week.</description>
<picture>76330.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2228" picture="21776.jpg">Gibu Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29407" type="appears in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="52">8.66</rating>
<name>Kasuga Kusunoki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kasuga Kusunoki is an 18 year old tomboy, third-year Majima Academy student and head and only member of the Girl`s Karate Club. A practitioner of Kenpo, Kusunoki is the heir to her father`s dojo and their family`s martial arts called Koshikibujutsu Kasugaryuu Rashinkassatsujutsu (古式武術 春日流 羅新活殺術, Ancient Martial Arts, Kasuga-Style, Life And Death Technique). Keima and Elsie meet Kusunoki when she saved them from delinquents but also looks down on Keima`s weakness. Upon learning that she is his next target and investigating by becoming her disciple in the Karate club, Keima`s learns that Kusunoki is trying to be masculine in order to become her father`s successor by suppressing her feminine side. However, Kusunoki secretly likes cute things but tries to despise them and stay away from them as she sees her femininity as a weakness. As her personality continues to polarize, the spirit inside of her causes Kusunoki feminine side to manifest itself. In order to draw out her feminine personality, Keima convinces Kusunoki to do do a very girlish activity; go on a date with him. After drawing it out where both the masculine Kusunoki and her feminine side fight it out over which personality should be the dominant one, Keima manages to convince both personalities to accept each other which her feminine side agrees to merge with Kusunoki as long as the latter accepts her femininity. Before completely merging, Kusunoki`s feminine side takes over Kusunoki to kiss Keima to remember their date, which forces the spirit out.
Since then, Kusunoki has opened up to her femininity which includes liking cute things and adopting a pet cat. When Keima joins her family dojo in order to get to his next target, her older sister Hinoki, he learns she still remembers Keima during his time as her disciple but not during their date which she believes he ran away. He also learns that Kusunoki`s femininity problems before stems from her sister Hinoki, who she admired the most, left for America after having a disagreement with their father over inheriting the dojo, and in order to fill the void Hinoki left, she focuses herself in martial arts to become what she was when Keima first meet her. Yet, Kusunoki becomes a valuable help later when a powerful Weiss takes over her sister`s body where both she and Keima goes into Hinoki`s heart to fight a possessed Hinoki. As the sisters battle, the possessed Hinoki reveals her hatred for Kusunoki for forcing her to maintain the image of the perfect older sister and denying her right to be who she really wanted to be. Kusunoki at first is reluctant to hurt Hinoki but after some encouragement from Keima, Kusunoki is able to defeat the spirit possessing her sister and tells Hinoki she apologize for what she had go through as she never wanted a perfect sister, she just wanted the older sister she loved and would still admire Hinoki no matter what path she choose which finally calms Hinoki`s heart and forces the Weiss out. After Hinoki`s Weiss was captured, the supernatural events that both she and Hinoki experienced were erased from their memories, yet the relationship between the Kasuga sisters are repaired.
The cause of Kusunoki`s negative emotions was her conflicted feelings to become masculine or feminine.
Her given name is derived from Kusu Station (楠駅, Kusu-eki).</description>
<picture>73487.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="29408" type="appears in" update="2011-06-15">
<rating votes="61">8.23</rating>
<name>Nagase Jun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nagase Jun is a 21 year old university student from Narusawa Kyoiku University and a Maijima Academy graduate and Nikaido`s junior. Returning to Maijima Academy as a student teacher for Keima`s class, she is very passionate to help her students. Innocent and naive, she is a fan of the pro wrestler Jumbo Tsuruma. Concerned that Keima`s is a troubled child, she tries to help him to open up and give-up on video games. But Keima, learning she has a spirit inside of her and in an attempt to get rid of it, does his best to try and get her angry, such as playing more games in class but his plans backfire which only causes her to be more concerned about him instead, which infuriates him. Eventually, Keima does cares about her when he unintentionally upsets her, causing her to try to help the other students in his class. After Keima asks Nikaido about her past, she reveals that both she and Jun were on the high school basketball team with Jun as the Team Captain but Jun passionate desire to aim for the championship caused the rest of the team to quit because they felt she was just forcing her ideals onto them. After her over-zealousness leads to a disagreement with the students in class, Keima confronts her and reveals that the problem wasn`t because she was trying too hard but she was just giving up too eaisly and tells her to continue to follow her beliefs and not give up. Right afterwords, the whole class (thanks to Keima`s manipulations) reconciles with Jun. Before returning to Narusawa University after her time as a student teacher is over, she tells Keima that she will become a better teacher, make him give up video games and kisses him which expels the spirit.
During Keima and Haqua`s search for the Jupiter Sisters, they encounter Jun at her university who still remembers him. When he claims he has become a better student and Haqua is his girlfriend, Jun congratulates him without showing any signs of jealousy which Keima sees as proof that she doesn`t have a goddess inside her as her memories of falling in love with him are gone.
The cause of Jun`s negative emotions was her doubt of having her ideals coming true.
Her surname is derived from Nagase Station (長瀬駅, Nagase-eki).</description>
<picture>73488.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="32944" type="appears in" update="2011-05-31">
<rating votes="15">6.48</rating>
<name>Sugimoto Yotsuba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sugimoto Yotsuba, also known as Yokkyun, is Keima`s most favourite game girl. She is drawn in a parody style of the famed visual novel Kanon.</description>
<picture>72601.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="34014" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-12">
<rating votes="25">5.36</rating>
<name>Kujou Tsukiyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kujou Tsukiyo is a short, blond 17 year old Majima Academy student and the only member of the Astronomy Club. The daughter of designer Yoko Kujou, she rarely attends class and is frequently on the school rooftop in her private observatory to watch the moon with her doll Luna which she holds dearly. Her cold personality comes from watching her parents fighting and later divorcing when she was younger, which made Tsukiyo hate the real world and wish she could live on the moon, her ideal world with Luna, a metaphor for her desire to escape reality. Keima encounters her and finding out she has a spirit after they both get into an argument over what is "true beauty". Later that night while watching the moon, she wishes she was beautiful just like Luna which the spirit inside of her shrinks her to Luna`s size. Keima discovers her problem and with the help of Elsie, assists Tsukiyo with her situation. However, Tsukiyo begins to grow comfortable with her new life which Keima fears it will only widen the gap in her heart so he and Elsie make her new environment more bigger in order to frighten Tsukiyo by making her think she has become smaller but she later discovers the ruse and escapes to the roof. Keima confronts her there where he convince her despite what she believes, there is beauty within the real world. However, she accidentally falls but Keima jumps down to catch her and the two kiss and saved by Elsie`s magical raiment. In the aftermath, Tsukiyo still goes to her observatory with Luna but without the carpet that acted as a border between her ideal world and the real world and watches Keima through her telescope, blushing.
The cause of Tsukiyo`s negative emotions was her hatred of humanity and reality`s flaws.
Her surname is derived from Kujou Station (九条駅, Kujou-eki).</description>
<picture>139959.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34015" type="appears in" update="2011-11-08">
<rating votes="8">4.53</rating>
<name>Ikoma Minami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ikoma Minami is a 15 year old Majima Academy Middle School student who is a member of the Swim Club. A naive girl who loves swimming, she has messy hair that won`t straighten due to chlorine from swim practice which her younger brother makes fun of by calling her "Bird Nest". Her story is unique as it is mostly told by her own point of view. When she is first introduced, she learns that she has been selected as a third substitute for the school team despite wishing to be on the main team instead. As Minami laments on whether she should give up swimming just like her friends, Elsie detects a spirit inside of her and informs Keima. Then on one late night swimming practice, Minami meets Keima swimming at the school pool where she is captivated by his handsome looks and perfect swimming (thanks to Elsie help). At first, she believes Keima is a great senior within the Swim team, only to learn from her friends that Keima has an infamous reputation for being weird which leaves her very confused. Unknown to her, Keima is actually doing this to make Minami figure out the connection between the school`s impression that he is a weirdo and her impression that he is an amazing athlete. As she starts stalking Keima and rides on the bus with him, Minami starts to fall in love with him which Keima decides to ask her out at the Tanabata Festival. After having a good time at the festival, Minami wishes to stay with him forever as the festival ends but Keima comforts her, teaching her that moving on and accepting the past is a part of growing up and kisses her, which forces the spirit out. After the festival, Minami becomes mature thanks to Keima`s words (even though she has forgotten) and decides to stay and continue in the Swim Club. During Keima`s search for the goddesses, Keima meets Minami again and finds out she does not remember who he is which he confrims she doesn`t have a goddess. Before leaving, Keima asks Minami if she is still practicing swimming and wishes her luck.
The cause of Minami`s negative emotions was being unable to achieve her dreams.
Her name is derived from Minami-Ikoma Station (南生駒駅, Minami-Ikoma-eki).</description>
<picture>76855.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="34018" type="appears in" update="2011-11-08">
<rating votes="8">4.92</rating>
<name>Uemoto Sumire</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Uemoto Sumire is a 17 year old girl from Narusawa 3rd Public High School. Her a father is a chef and owner of a small Chinese restaurant called "Uemoto-ya" while her mother used to work there before she ran away which the only memento Sumire has of her mother is a cheongsam which she also wears while working at Uemoto-ya. Keima and Elsie first met Sumire during the last weeks of summer vacation while she goes out tasting every Ramen store`s ramen in the city. As they follow her to Uemoto-ya, they watch how both Sumire and her father have a thorny relationship which the latter doesn`t want her to work here. In order to figure out what is the cause of the gap in Sumire`s heart and the Uemoto`s family situation, Keima decides to work at Uemoto-ya much to Sumire`s suspicions. After gaining her trust, Sumire reveals she wants her father`s acceptance of her helping his ailing restaurant by researching the other Ramen stores and creating her own unique recipe of Ramen called "Sweet Ramen" with Keima as her food taster much to his displeasure as he dislike sweet food. After several failures and their relationship going smoothly, both Sumire and Keima finally make a Sweet Ramen that is delicious and edible. However, Sumire`s father refuses to eat it and tells her to just quit which Keima realizes the problem between father and daughter. In reality, both of them wants the other to be happy which Sumire wants to help her father`s restaurant and her father wants Sumire to give up the restaurant and have a better life. Eventually, Keima manages to have her father taste a ramen made by Sumire which taste exactly like his which Sumire explains that all that she wants is to help him succeed which will make her happy. Realizing his mistake, her father finally relents and passes the restaurant to Sumire. Before Keima leaves, Sumire thanks Keima and promises to make any ramen he wants if he visits and kisses him which expels the spirit in her.
After these events, the restaurant, now renamed "Sumire-ya" and under Sumire`s management becomes popular thanks to her Sweet Ramen which is a hit with the customers. While she still continues making new Ramen recipes and trying to lose weight from her research, Sumire remembers having a "boyfriend" but doesn`t remember who he was.
The cause of Sumire`s negative emotions was her disappointment that her father refuses her help.
Her surname is derived from Osaka Uehommachi Station (大阪上本町駅, Osaka Uehonmachi-eki).
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>76853.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="34021" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-10-12">
<rating votes="64">7.38</rating>
<name>Ayukawa Tenri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ayukawa Tenri is a shy 17 year old girl from Maijima Municipal Misato East High School. A reticent childhood friend of Keima`s, she was his neighbor before his family moved seven years ago. In the present, she and her mother visit the Katsuragi`s where Keima does not remember her well. Unknown to Keima at first, he believes Tenri has a spirit inside of her but in reality it is a Goddess name Diana. Ten years ago during a school trip, both Keima and Tenri got lost in an underground cave where they both witness the Weiss (what evil spirits where called before) escaping from Hell and were saved by Diana who agreed to take over Tenri`s body. In order to save Diana, who is being chased by Nora who believes Tenri has a spirit inside of her, Keima pretends to capture Tenri`s heart and kiss her and have Elsie release a weak spirit in order to fool Nora. After that incident, Tenri`s family soon moves next door to Keima home.
Tenri has been love with Keima since they were children as she admired his ability to remain calm and collected no matter the situation. Despite Diana suggesting that Tenri should do more to make Keima fall for her, Tenri is just fine with their current relationship of being friends. She also enjoys doing magic tricks and playing with bubble wrap.
As Diana`s host, whenever Diana takes over Tenri`s body, she is able to perform and do amazing feats that Tenri is unable to. While she usually does nothing when Diana takes over, Tenri will sometimes interfere if Diana does something she disapproves especially when it comes to Diana`s attempts to make her and Keima closer. While not taking over, Diana can communicate and see others via a reflective surface like glass or mirrors. Because of Diana`s knowledge about Heavens involvement with the New Hell regime, Keima usually meets Tenri to discuss with Diana about these topics. With recent events of Keima trying to find Diana`s other Goddesses sisters, Keima has warned Tenri to be careful as to not catch the attention of those targeting the Goddesses.
Tenri`s name is derived from Tenri Station (天理駅, Tenri-eki) and her character design is modeled after Diana Barry, from Anne of Green Gables.</description>
<picture>126782.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34022" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-09-03">
<rating votes="61">7.99</rating>
<name>Diana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Diana is the goddess of "the hunt and the moon", as well as the first goddess Keima encounters who resides in Tenri`s body. Keima first meets Diana when he assumes she is a Weiss, but Tenri manages to convince him otherwise after she tells Keima about how she first met Diana, who saved them both ten years ago from the Weiss. Because of her knowledge which Elsie and Haqua aren`t aware of, Keima visits her when he wants to know more about the relationship between Heaven and the Underworld. When Diana takes over Tenri`s body, she appears with slanted eyes in contrast to Tenri`s rounded eyes. Diana acts cold, selfish and thoughtless most of the time which tends to irk some people, yet she is very supportive of Tenri`s love for Keima. She wishes for Tenri and Keima to be a couple as it would restore her powers, despite being disgusted that Keima has managed to make other girls fall in love with him as well. Diana is also the one who originally requested that Keima should find her sisters, in exchange for helping him seal back the Weiss. Later on in the series, after Keima apologises to her for his indecisiveness, Diana regains more of her powers and now has the ability to use her angel wings.</description>
<picture>126783.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47891" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-12">
<rating votes="25">4.74</rating>
<name>Nola Florian Reolia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nola is a Spirit Hunter who is introduced during their biannual assembly; she is ten years older than Elsie and Haqua. She is arrogant and disdainful; she looks down on younger demons. Although she has a human partner, Asama Ryou, she sometimes tries to force Loose Spirits out without his help. Her preferred method of capturing Loose Spirits is to fulfill the target`s desire: (e.g. riches for those who want money, suitable partners for those who desire love, death to her enemies for those who desire revenge). Due to her impulsive nature, she sometimes assumes the target`s strong emotion to be hate instead of love, and attacks the target`s person of affection.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>139960.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48506" type="appears in" update="2012-12-26">
<rating votes="14">2.45</rating>
<name>Asama Ryou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129983.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="202" picture="25743.jpg">Terashima Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55888" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-12">
<rating votes="10">2.43</rating>
<name>Rune</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rune is an executive Vintage agent who has infiltrated the Spirit Hunters. She oversees other fellow Vintage agents.</description>
<picture>139957.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55889" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-12">
<rating votes="17">6.04</rating>
<name>Goidou Yui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139958.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="411" picture="17475.jpg">Takagaki Ayahi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57788" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-09-03">
<rating votes="12">5.75</rating>
<name>Apollo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139761.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57789" type="appears in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="3">4.89</rating>
<name>Hinaga Rieko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A ghost, who is Rieko`s spirit as a child. She changes her form to a teenager, and talks about how she misses her family and friends who have departed.</description>
<picture>139765.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="57790" type="appears in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="3">4.55</rating>
<name>Haibara Nanaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139766.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="57791" type="appears in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="4">5.64</rating>
<name>Kasuga Hinoki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kasuga Hinoki is 20 year old eccentric fashion designer and older sister of Kasuga Kusunoki.</description>
<picture>139767.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="57792" type="appears in" update="2013-07-09">
<rating votes="5">5.75</rating>
<name>Kurakawa Akari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kurakawa Akari is a petite girl from Majima Academy and a member of the Biology Club who is obsessed with the idea of creating the perfect human.</description>
<picture>139768.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="550" picture="151677.jpg">Shimizu Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58309" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-16">
<rating votes="10">5.30</rating>
<name>Vulcanus</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vulcanus is the self-proclaimed goddess of "love and justice". Named after the Roman god of fire, she is the first-born sister who resides in the body of http://anidb.net/ch34014 [Kujou Tsukiyo], though more often personified in the form of her doll, Luna. Unlike her sisters, Vulcanus has bad eyesight and hearing, and cannot walk, but can instead possess an object. When Vulcanus takes over Tsukiyo`s body, her hair becomes darker.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>140704.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58584" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-09-03">
<rating votes="9">5.83</rating>
<name>Mars</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mars is a goddess who resides inside Yui.</description>
<picture>141014.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="411" picture="17475.jpg">Takagaki Ayahi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58585" type="appears in" update="2013-08-06">
<rating votes="1">7.77</rating>
<name>Ryou-kun</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141013.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="195" picture="17009.jpg">Sakamaki Mitsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58586" type="appears in" update="2013-08-06">
<rating votes="3">4.67</rating>
<name>Katsuragi Keima</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Keima cross-dressed as a girl in order to re-capture Yui or rather to be captured by Yui.</description>
<picture>141015.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58887" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-09-03">
<rating votes="9">6.90</rating>
<name>Minerva</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141433.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59409" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-09-03">
<rating votes="8">5.90</rating>
<name>Mercurius</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142342.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59617" type="appears in" update="2014-04-06">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Gira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>142796.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1918" picture="225099.jpg">Sakurai Harumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59618" type="appears in" update="2013-09-10">
<rating votes="2">3.11</rating>
<name>Mobuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mobuko is a girl from Keima`s class. She sits near Elsie.</description>
<picture>142797.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2228" picture="21776.jpg">Gibu Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59894" type="appears in" update="2013-09-17">
<rating votes="2">4.56</rating>
<name>Ayumi no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143244.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1918" picture="225099.jpg">Sakurai Harumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59895" type="appears in" update="2013-09-17">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Ayumi no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143243.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="340" picture="17176.jpg">Yabe Masahito</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="151325" update="2013-06-26">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-06-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151654" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Doll Roll Hall</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Doll Roll Hall</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Doll Roll Hall</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Doll Roll Hall</title>
<summary>During the simultaneous walk-home-from-school events, Keima is attacked by a wave of flying books.  The books are being controlled by a small figure.  Meanwhile, section chief Nora drops by the Katsuragi residence to see Elsie.  It sounds like the Hell Bureau of Peace has issued an order to the loose soul team to search for residents of Heaven.  Kanon/Apollo is currently at the Katsuragi residence.  Is this a coincidence?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>642291</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151655" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">5 HOME</title>
<title xml:lang="en">5 Home</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">5 Home</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">5 Home</title>
<summary>A girl who hosts a goddess will remember everything that happened during her conquest.  In other words, she will remember falling in love with Keima.  Armed with that information, Keima attempts to walk home from school with all five potential hosts and increase their affection level.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>642289</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151656" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スクランブルフォーメーション</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scramble Formation</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Scramble Formation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Scramble Formation</title>
<summary>The goddess Apollo makes her appearance, but she is immediately stabbed by Lune, leader of Vintage, an organization which seeks to restore the Ancient Demons.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>641767</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151657" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">When the Sun Goes Down</title>
<title xml:lang="en">When the Sun Goes Down</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Quand le soleil se couche</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">When the Sun Goes Down</title>
<summary>Tenri, Keima`s childhood friend, has moved back next door to the Katsuragis.  She happens to be host to the goddess Diana, who tells Keima about she and the other 5 Jupiter Sisters once sealed away the Ancient Demons of Hell, the Weiss.  At the same time, the students of Maijima High School are excited because Kanon has made a rare appearance in the classroom for exams.  However, Kanon is preoccupied with the girl inside the mirror named Apollo, as well as the fact that she is being watched.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>641765</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151750" update="2013-07-09">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151959" update="2013-07-16">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152234" update="2013-07-31">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152237" update="2013-07-31">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152239" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">めがみみっくす</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goddess Mix</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mélange de déesses</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Megami Mix</title>
<summary>The Loose Souls team section chiefs are holding their regular meeting in Hell.  Haqua questions Bureau Chief Dokuro about the rumors she heard from Nora concerning goddesses and Vintage, but Dokuro rejects her claims.  Unsatisfied with the response, Haqua prepares to leave hell.  Back on Earth, four of the goddesses have assembled in an attempt to awaken Kanon and Apollo.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>642299</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152240" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="19">9.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Bad Medicine</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bad Medicine</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bad Medicine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bad Medicine</title>
<summary>The goddess search is going well, but the strain is too much for Keima and he falls ill.  However, this is an opportunity the God of Conquest to trigger the sick visit event.  Ayumi and Chihiro are the remaining candidates for the final goddess.  However, Keima doesn`t realize how difficult it is to conquer two friends at the same time.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>642297</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152241" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私について.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Story.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">À propos de moi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi ni Tsuite.</title>
<summary>Thanks to a convincing performance by Haqua, Keima successfully releases the fourth goddess, Mars.  However, Shiori was unfortunate enough to witness Keima during his conquest, and the shock leaves her unable to write a novel for the Mai High Festival.  Keima tries to help Shiori complete her story, but what will she write about?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>642295</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152242" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="12">8.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぱんちDEでーと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Punch and Date</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Punch de Date</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Punch de Date</title>
<summary>With help from Vulcanus, the third goddess, the Ancient Demon blade in Kanon has been removed.  However, she still remains unconscious.  Keima must search for the remaining goddesses and restore their power, but one of the potential hosts approaches him first.  Does Keima have a way to handle a heroine who doesn`t follow the dating sim model?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>642293</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152380" update="2013-08-06">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152488" update="2013-08-13">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152790" update="2016-10-21">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152791" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-09-24</airdate>
<rating votes="12">9.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">初めて恋をした記憶</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Memory of My First Love</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Souvenirs de mon premier amour</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete Koi o Shita Kioku</title>
<summary>The goddesses have been assembled and they take wing to Point Rock. Haqua and the Loose Souls team squares off against Vintage. And the climax of the Mai High Festival awaits.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>642307</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152792" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">SHOW ME</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Show Me</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Show Me</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Show Me</title>
<summary>Haqua returns from Hell after learning that Maijima Bay`s Point Rock is a gate between Earth and Old Hell. Vintage has imprisoned the goddesses in Point Rock. Soon, demons, goddesses, and humans will be engulfed in war. After Haqua helps to save Ayumi, Katsuragi is determined to conquer the final goddess, but he needs Chihiro`s help to get the job done.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>642305</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152793" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラビリンス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Labyrinth</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Labyrinthe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Labyrinth</title>
<summary>The last goddess is inside Ayumi, but only two days remain.  Keima has no choice but to drop Chihiro hard and switch over to Ayumi`s route.  However, Ayumi happens to be watching and she begins avoiding Keima, which disrupts his conquest. At the same time, Lune has come to the Mai High School with her Vintage underlings to hunt goddesses.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>642303</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152794" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Absent Lovers</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Absent Lovers</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Absent Lovers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Absent Lovers</title>
<summary>It`s the night before the Mai High Festival.  Keima and Chihiro are alone on the roof of the school.  Chihiro seems confused by Keima`s behavior, but he continues with his conquest.  But as Keima makes his move, Chihiro says something unexpected.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>642301</identifier>
<identifier>the-world-god-only-knows</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="153888" update="2016-10-21">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1f</title>
</episode>
<episode id="153941" update="2016-10-21">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154102" update="2016-10-21">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1g</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163489" update="2016-10-21">
<epno type="3">C13</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2013-09-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175911" update="2016-10-23">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-08-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7 Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175912" update="2016-10-23">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-07-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1 Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
