<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9564" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-07-13</startdate>
<enddate>2013-07-13</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gekijouban Pocket Monsters: Best Wishes! - Shinsoku no Genosect: Mewtwo Kakusei</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">ExtremeSpeed Genesect: Mewtwo Awakens</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pokemon: Movie 16</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pokémon the Movie: Genesect and the Legend Awakened</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">劇場版 ポケットモンスター ベストウイッシュ 神速のゲノセクト ミュウツー覚醒</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Pokemon the Movie: Genesect and the Legend Awakened</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Pokémon: Der Film - Genesect und die wiedererwachte Legende</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Pokémon o Filme: Genesect e a Lenda Revelada</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9926" type="Prequel">Mewtwo: Kakusei e no Prologue</anime>
<anime id="9216" type="Parent Story">Pocket Monsters: Best Wishes! Season 2</anime>
<anime id="9565" type="Other">Pikachu to Eievui Friends</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="376027">Not a bad movie.
Packed with action, big role for Mewtwo and his mega form, and a quick watch. 
Also for those that have only seen the first season of pokemon (it helps if you know who/what Mewtwo is).</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.pokemon-movie.jp/</url>
<description>A peaceful park amid the hustle and bustle seems like the perfect new home for a group of Mythical Pokémon: four Genosect and their red leader. These new neighbours quickly become a problem for the city`s residents, though - they don`t trust people, and they`ve found a dangerous ally in the Legendary Pokémon Mewtwo, whose origins also involve human tampering. But the red Genosect doesn`t want Mewtwo`s help, and their confrontation quickly rages out of control! Can http://anidb.net/ch6693 [Satoshi] and friends stop these two powerful Pokémon before they destroy the city?
Source: Amazon (edited)</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="173">3.59</permanent>
<temporary count="178">5.70</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221895.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14974</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16680</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.pokemon-movie.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Pokémon_the_Movie:_Genesect_and_the_Legend_Awakened</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>劇場版ポケットモンスター_ベストウイッシュ_神速のゲノセクト_ミュウツー覚醒</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3483</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>344658</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16223</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18015</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B01ASCOBS6</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2801" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>RPG</name>
<description>Any anime that is based on a role-playing game aka RPG. A role-playing video game is a video game which includes elements of non-electronic role-playing games. The player assumes control of one or several fictional characters (a party) who have joined forces in order to perform quests and overcome a great number of challenges and enemies, usually monsters inspired by fantasy, and, to a lesser extent, science fiction and classic mythology. During the course of the game the characters, or avatars, which are generally defined by quantized characteristics, evolve and improve in that their various attributes increase, as well as by gaining more powerful artefacts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5939" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-09">
<name>CAST MISSING</name>
<description>Important characters are missing, either in-part or entirely. This includes basic entry info (name, gender, picture), appear episode range, seiyuu and/or tags.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="74873" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-05-01">
<name>Yukino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>172817.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="74875" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-05-01">
<name>Natsuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>172819.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="74964" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-05-05">
<name>Erik</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>172996.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="145931" update="2013-10-26">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>70</length>
<airdate>2013-07-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="213396" update="2019-03-08">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Extended Trailer</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
