<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9568" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-04-12</startdate>
<enddate>2013-06-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kakumeiki Valvrave</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="synonym">والوراو ازادی بخش</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">valvrave</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">革命機ヴァルヴレイヴ Valvrave the Liberator</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Valvrave the Liberator</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Valvrave: the liberator</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">จักรปฏิวัติ วัลเวรฟ</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">革命機Valvrave</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">革命机Valvrave</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9949" type="Sequel">Kakumeiki Valvrave (2013)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8480" approval="40" total="55">Guilty Crown</anime>
<anime id="4521" approval="32" total="59">Code Geass: Hangyaku no Lelouch</anime>
<anime id="10445" approval="24" total="29">Aldnoah.Zero</anime>
<anime id="10291" approval="15" total="21">Buddy Complex</anime>
<anime id="5252" approval="10" total="18">Kidou Senshi Gundam 00</anime>
<anime id="192" approval="6" total="16">Mugen no Ryvius</anime>
<anime id="9989" approval="5" total="11">Neppuu Kairiku Bushi Road</anime>
<anime id="4178" approval="5" total="6">Zegapain</anime>
<anime id="7591" approval="4" total="17">Star Driver: Kagayaki no Takuto</anime>
<anime id="10813" approval="4" total="9">Owari no Seraph</anime>
<anime id="5415" approval="2" total="11">Macross Frontier</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="6">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="75448">This is Gundam, just different name, and little twist to mech design...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="471071">Might get what you want in the last episodes.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="520538">If you`re fan of battles scenes and pretty colors this series is for you. If you`re waiting for that "one" series to start up again, this will help pass the time.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="44864">If you`re trying to watch this with a straight face, forget it. There`s too much cheese, inconsistencies, absurd scenarios and situations that will make you roll your eyes to allow you any enjoyment. If you`re watching to have fun, there`s great animation, flashy battles, appealing character designs and catchy music for you to enjoy. 

There`s a reason why this isnt Gundam.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="558595">This is essentially Code Geass on speed, except the main character is not nearly as fabulous. Still very entertaining however.
If Geass was a trainwreck, Valvrave is a bullet-train wreck stuck on full throttle.
If you are a serious person, then don`t watch this. Otherwise prepare yourself for another magnificent Sunrise production!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="435866">This was quite good. Nice combination of different elements and somewhat unique. I don`t really care if it resembles Gundam or not , it`s a good show. It was too damn short and ended too abruptly. Waiting for the next season.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.valvrave.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="6762" type="Character Design">Suzuki Tatsuya</name>
<name id="1857" type="Series Composition">Ookouchi Ichirou</name>
<name id="1600" type="Direction">Matsuo Kou</name>
<name id="726" type="Animation Work">Sunrise</name>
<name id="2712" type="Music">Senju Akira</name>
<name id="6762" type="Chief Animation Direction">Suzuki Tatsuya</name>
</creators>
<description>Shinreki 71, 70% of all human beings have finally migrated to space due to the development of space cities. Between two organizations called the Dorushia Military Pact Federation and the Atlantic Ring United States (ARUS), there is a small neutral nation called Jiouru that has prospered economically. In the same year, http://anidb.net/ch51934 [Tokishima Haruto], a high school student living in Jiouru discovered a mysterious mecha called Valvrave during the Dorushia`s attack in the nation.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2033">4.96</permanent>
<temporary count="2044">6.67</temporary>
<review count="3">4.77</review>
</ratings>
<picture>133377.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14983</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16668</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.valvrave.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Valvrave_the_Liberator</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>革命機ヴァルヴレイヴ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2936</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>345248</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15878</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>valvrave</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>valvrave-the-liberator</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="428" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-12-25">
<name>contractor</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1393" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-03-08">
<name>drill</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1955" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-18">
<name>child soldier</name>
<description>Untrained and as yet immature, children are expediently thrust into the role of warriors to protect god, king, and country. Not having even finished school, they are inexplicably designated to elite status or roles, typically requiring months of training and years of experience. All the more so with "experimental" equipment or weapons of mass destruction.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3314" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-10">
<name>fate</name>
<description>Fate — The predestined path of all things. The outcome is inevitable and the consequences predetermined. Whether or not the protagonist ultimately decides to follow this path shall weigh heavily on their soul.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3741" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-25">
<name>bullying</name>
<description>Bullying is the use of force, threat, or coercion to abuse, intimidate, or aggressively dominate others. One who engages in bullying is known as a bully.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3755" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-19">
<name>unintentional comedy</name>
<description>This anime contains certain elements intended to be serious, dramatic, or sad. However, these elements wind up provoking laughter instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3836" parentid="3314" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-28">
<name>the chosen one!</name>
<description>One of the characters in the anime is the "chosen one", the one to bring about change, the only one to "set things right" in a "good" ending, or bring about complete destruction in a "bad" ending.</description>
<picurl>66957.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4081" parentid="2841" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space battles</name>
<description>There are space battles in this anime. Usually between Earth forces and some alien invader, but ship to ship skirmishes in deep space are just as common.</description>
<picurl>242377.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4113" parentid="6347" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-20">
<name>body exchange</name>
<description>Two or more characters swap bodies (or, equally, swap minds).
When this plot is done, usually the voices also switch as narrative cheat to help viewers keep track of who`s who. More subtly, it`s just the eyes. More serious/action-oriented shows might not do this. The Flip often involves characters of different ages, genders, races, or social classes. Another variation is a protagonist and antagonist switching, which usually involves each trying to undermine the other`s organization while simultaneously trying to switch back. If one or both of the characters have superpowers or other special abilities, they`ll have a lot of trouble figuring their new powers out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4116" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-13">
<name>eternal blush</name>
<description>It is no ordinary blush it is a blush that does not disappear.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4228" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-09">
<name>subtle OP ED sequence change</name>
<description>A (small) part of the opening or ending sequence changes after a certain episode, usually to reflect a plot milestone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5505" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-15">
<name>deus ex machina</name>
<description>When the story has been spun so wildly and the plot has been driven so deeply, when all resources are exhausted and the linear truth stands so proudly at the end of the road, ready to bring the never-ending adventure to its epic conclusion...
The writers kick you in the behind and say "Screw that!! Suddenly... UFOs!!! No, wait, Werewolf UFOs!!! Bet you didn`t see that coming!"
It`s the old-Greek form of solving your broken story because it was too much work to do it all over again, or you`ve already shown stuff that compromises what you wanted to do. It`s finding out about a better dragon on a whole different planet because you`ve already been revived 3 times and that`s the cap. It`s breaking a spaceship and "oh wait, there`s an exact copy built in secret by an unknown guy on the other side of the planet, and you can use it free of charge". It`s Doraemon`s pouch, on every single episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5585" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-29">
<name>curse</name>
<description>A "curse" in this manner depicts an adversity placed upon a person or object by a supernatural power often represented by unique designs and symbols found on the inflicted. While not all curses have negative effects, the majority are meant to remain forever hexing to the receiving victim`s soul.
A common portrayal is that which is conjured by an individual that has been caused great suffering and thereby extracts revenge against the accuser in the form of a curse. This abuser will then have their soul spirited away to hell to suffer endlessly for the rest of eternity. In some instances (such as in `Jigoku Shoujo`) the character who extracts revenge also condemns their own soul to Hell upon death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6072" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-25">
<name>just as planned</name>
<description>A term usually used to describe a situation, where a seemingly smart and cunning villain sets up a plan that seems grand and impressive, but is actually long winding, ridiculous, and convoluted. And all of that just to trick his opponent(s), like the hero or anybody else, into doing things exactly as he planned. Suffice to say that the villain could have reached his goal by much shorter and easier means, it just wouldn`t seem as awesome anymore.
The phrase is also known as the original Japanese "keikaku doori" where keikaku stands translated for "plan" or "schedule", and doori for "in accordance with ..." or "following ...".
The phrase is a reference to http://anidb.net/ch301 [Yagami Light] from http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], and his love for plans.</description>
<picurl>211219.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6347" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>body and host</name>
<description>When a foreign entity like that of a symbiote, body snatcher, puppeteer parasite, or even a hacker (when regarding machines like robots and computers) enters/outright hijacks a body, the possessed subject becomes what is usually called: the host.
The basic purpose of the host varies on what the point was for it to have been hijacked in the first place. Sometimes it`s used as a disguise, other times it`s used as a decoy and destraction, even simply being used as a weapon and piece of armor that the possessor uses to cause sheer chaos and destruction, but sometimes... a host can be used for fetish fuel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6614" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-03-12">
<name>Animeism</name>
<description>Animeism is a late-night Japanese programming block established in April 2012. It is devoted to anime and broadcast each Thursday night on MBS, in a fashion similar to Fuji TV`s http://anidb.net/t3865 [noitaminA] that also airs on Thursdays. Just like noitaminA, the block airs two series back to back. From April 2015 onwards, the block was moved to Friday nights.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>63625.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="51934" type="main character in" update="2013-08-09">
<rating votes="45">2.91</rating>
<name>Tokishima Haruto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haruto is a high school sophomore who is a kind young man who hates fighting and attends school at JIOR`s Sakimori Academy. He has an interest in http://anidb.net/ch51936 [Shouko], but can`t bring himself to tell her.
Source: aniplexusa.com</description>
<picture>131913.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29979" picture="223317.jpg">Oosaka Ryouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51935" type="main character in" update="2013-08-09">
<rating votes="45">7.83</rating>
<name>L-elf</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>L-elf is a 17 year old super agent who belongs to the Dorssian Military`s Secret Agency. He has a brilliant mind and excellent combat skills, and he`ll do whatever it takes to achieve his goal.
Source: aniplexusa.com</description>
<picture>131914.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2225" picture="192115.jpg">Kimura Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51936" type="main character in" update="2013-08-09">
<rating votes="41">3.81</rating>
<name>Sashinami Shouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shouko is a sophomore at Sakimori Academy. She`s a very bright girl and has lots of friends of both genders. http://anidb.net/ch51934 [Haruto] is her childhood friend. They fight constantly but also get along well.
Source: aniplexusa.com</description>
<picture>131916.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21733" picture="152476.jpg">Seto Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51937" type="main character in" update="2013-08-09">
<rating votes="77">6.82</rating>
<name>Rukino Saki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saki is a freshman at Sakimori Academy. She`s a popular idol but her career is on hold right now. Since she`s cold and hates dealing with other people, she`s isolated at school.
Source: aniplexusa.com</description>
<picture>131915.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52718" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-09">
<rating votes="14">6.78</rating>
<name>Inuzuka Kyuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kyuma is a high school senior and a very dependable upperclassman for http://anidb.net/ch51934 [Haruto] and his classmates. He is constantly thinking about ways to make money and hopes to become a very rich man in the future.
Source: aniplexusa.com</description>
<picture>131917.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3155" picture="24137.jpg">Ono Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52719" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-09">
<rating votes="8">4.53</rating>
<name>Sakurai Aina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aina is a very caring but an extremely shy freshman at Sakimori Academy. She is able to connect with http://anidb.net/ch51937 [Saki] who usually likes to isolate herself from all of the other students.
Source: aniplexusa.com</description>
<picture>131918.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52720" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-31">
<rating votes="20">5.52</rating>
<name>Nobi Marie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Marie is a sophomore and http://anidb.net/ch51936 [Shouko]`s best friend. Contrary to her childish appearance, Marie is very mature emotionally and is never afraid of letting others know her opinions.
Source: aniplexusa.com</description>
<picture>131919.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="304" picture="17139.jpg">Fukuen Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52721" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-09">
<rating votes="4">3.10</rating>
<name>Otamaya Yuusuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuusuke is a sophomore at Sakimori Academy and the leader of the Boys` Cultural Club. He is extremely knowledgeable about things involving machines. Some may even consider him a bit of a nerd.
Source: aniplexusa.com</description>
<picture>131920.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52722" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-09">
<rating votes="11">6.04</rating>
<name>Yamada Raizou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Raizou is a sophomore and better known as Thunder among the gang of misfits that he leads. He can be hot-blooded at times but he places importance on friendship.
Source: aniplexusa.com</description>
<picture>131921.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52723" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-09">
<rating votes="4">4.12</rating>
<name>Renboukouji Satomi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Satomi is a senior and the President of the Student Council at Sakimori Academy. He demonstrates an elite disposition, but is usually helpless in crisis situations.
Source: aniplexusa.com</description>
<picture>131922.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52724" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-09">
<rating votes="22">4.22</rating>
<name>Ninomiya Takahi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takahi is a senior and the leader of the Girls` Sports Club at Sakimori Academy. She is very proud of being named Miss Sakimori for the last 2 school years. She can be an overbearing rich-girl at times.
Source: aniplexusa.com</description>
<picture>131923.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1798" picture="20493.jpg">Kotobuki Minako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52725" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-09">
<rating votes="7">4.98</rating>
<name>Kibukawa Takumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takumi is a physics instructor at Sakimori Academy, but because of his aloof attitude toward everything and extremely casual tone, many find it difficult to see him as a member of the faculty.
Source: aniplexusa.com</description>
<picture>131925.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52726" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-09">
<rating votes="17">6.21</rating>
<name>Nanami Rion</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rion is a teacher-in-training at Sakimori Academy. She is bit of an air-head at times. Because of her sweet personality and attractive physical features, she is popular among the male students.
Source: aniplexusa.com</description>
<picture>131926.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52727" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-09">
<rating votes="34">6.98</rating>
<name>Renboukouji Akira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akira is a shy but skilled hacker that operates several computers concealed by cardboard boxes in a hidden area in the academy and is essentially a hikikomori. In the past she was bullied in middle school, for reasons unknown, leading to her current lifestyle and fearing the outside world.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>131924.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52728" type="appears in" update="2013-08-09">
<rating votes="6">8.22</rating>
<name>RM-011 Valvrave I</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>A humanoid weapon discovered in Module 77 of the JIOR Sphere. When its pilot was registered and authenticated, its white armor changed to black and it showed what the power concealed within it was capable of. The light given off by the unit has the unusual property of solidification (Solid Afterglow). Although the red-hued Unit 1 is equipped with the standard array of close-quarters / long-range / defensive armaments, this is a special standard that puts the power of humanoid weaponry on full display.
Source: aniplexusa.com</description>
<picture>131927.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="53601" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-09">
<rating votes="17">6.76</rating>
<name>Kriemhild</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lieutenant Kriemhild works directly under Colonel Cain. She is a very prideful woman who graduated the military academy with top scores.
Source: aniplexusa.com</description>
<picture>133371.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53602" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-09">
<rating votes="20">1.96</rating>
<name>Q-vier</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Q-vier enjoys being a prankster and tends to act before thinking. He can be a bit crazy at times and views war and death as a simple game.
Source: aniplexusa.com</description>
<picture>133373.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53603" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-09">
<rating votes="13">6.83</rating>
<name>X-eins</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>X-eins is a Dorssian agent. Even in the midst of a heated battle, X-eins is able to analyze his enemies` every weakness. He has a great level of respect for his former instructor and current supervisor Cain.
Source: aniplexusa.com</description>
<picture>133374.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3709" picture="84359.jpg">Hosoya Yoshimasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53604" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-09">
<rating votes="16">4.85</rating>
<name>H-neun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>H-neun is a Dorssian agent from the Carlstein Agency. He and X-eins were the only survivors among the trainees of their age. His light-hearted nature helps to keep his team members happy.
Source: aniplexusa.com</description>
<picture>133375.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="255" picture="40713.jpg">Miyano Mamoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53605" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-09">
<rating votes="22">4.93</rating>
<name>A-drei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A-drei is a Dorssian agent who has been trained at the Carlstein Agency alongside L-elf. Ever since they were trainees, A-drei saw L-elf as a formidable rival as well as a great friend.
Source: aniplexusa.com</description>
<picture>133376.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53606" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-09">
<rating votes="13">3.92</rating>
<name>Cain</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>At the Carlstein Agency, Colonel Cain used to be an instructor to L-elf and his fellow trainees. Cain is a perfect soldier and an admirable leader to all the Dorssian agents.
Source: aniplexusa.com</description>
<picture>133372.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54963" type="appears in" update="2013-08-09">
<name>Walkit-kyuu Uchuu Juujun`youkan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>Dorssian battleship.</description>
<picture>135209.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54964" type="appears in" update="2013-08-09">
<name>Splicer G</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The G-Type has broad multi-wings attached to the Main Core Block, and are suitable for bombing duties that center around physical munitions. Furthermore, both Splicer types are based in JIOR, and during the Dorssian invasion of Module 77, Z-Types were deployed and engaged their Waffe.
Source: aniplexusa.com</description>
<picture>135208.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54965" type="appears in" update="2013-08-09">
<name>Splicer Z</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>An all-environment fighter developed by the ARUS Army. Regardless of configuration, a Flexible Beam Gun which boasts a wide range of fire is housed in the primary wing. Splicers are designed around a system where multi-wings are attached to a universal Main Core Block, and this Z-Type is the high-maneuverability spec.
Source: aniplexusa.com</description>
<picture>135207.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54966" type="appears in" update="2013-08-09">
<name>Er114 Ideal-kyuu Kidou Senmetsu Ki</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Dorssian Army`s prized strategic weapons. Its maneuverability in both space and in the air belie its large size, and its combat capabilities surpass all existing weapons concepts. They are leaps and bounds ahead of any other country. Multiple variations exist, tailored to specific ace pilots or commanders.
Source: aniplexusa.com</description>
<picture>135206.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54967" type="appears in" update="2013-08-09">
<name>Nw507Un Waffe (Mujin Type)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>An unmanned Waffe type that acts based on remote control signals they receive from the manned type in their squad. Although they are inferior to the manned type in terms of specs, these easily-manufactured mechanized weapons with their high-level offensive and defensive capabilities are the vanguard of the Dorssian blitz.
Source: aniplexusa.com</description>
<picture>135205.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54968" type="appears in" update="2013-08-09">
<name>Nw507Be Waffe (Yuujin Type)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The Dorssian Army`s main-force, mass-produced units, equipped with large Eisen Geist shields and retractable Duquennoy Cannon beam weapon. Two types exist: the manned version, which brings to mind a burly, two-eyed beast; and a plane-type, unmanned version. They are usually employed in three-unit squads composed of one manned and two unmanned units. Their forearms are modular weapons units that can be swapped out to provide beam weaponry, projectile weaponry, close-quarters weaponry, etc.
Source: aniplexusa.com</description>
<picture>135204.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54969" type="appears in" update="2013-08-09">
<name>RM-069 Valvrave VI</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Indigo colored Unit-6. Believed to be used as a support unit, it has an air of mystery about it. Its weapon, Humming Bird, which appears as a mix between a staff and a hammer, has a special ability to hack into any system by tapping it to the target, which happens if the target then lets out a green circle, if not then the hacking failed. It is equipped with the Fan Talons for close combat. It is also studded with multiple Sense Nerves called Shinrabansho, which provide sensor functions for all humanoid weapons.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>135203.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54970" type="appears in" update="2013-08-09">
<name>RM-047 Valvrave IV</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Valvrave Unit 4, an assault type specialized for high mobility. In addition to the Spindle Knuckles, the special ability equipment on both its shoulders, we can also make out something that looks like a tailcoat in its green-hued silhouette...
Source: aniplexusa.com</description>
<picture>135201.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54971" type="appears in" update="2013-08-09">
<name>RM-031 Valvrave III</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>The yellow-hued Valvrave Unit 3. The Armstronger Cannon, the pair of giant arms that gives the instant impression of a powered-up version, is a type of special ability equipment developed especially for humanoid weapons.
Source: aniplexusa.com</description>
<picture>135200.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54972" type="appears in" update="2013-08-09">
<rating votes="2">9.17</rating>
<name>RM-056 Valvrave V</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Valvrave Unit 5, blue-hued and covered from head to toe in supplemental armor. The transparent material that comprises part of the oversized special ability equipment IMP is made up of Clear Fossils, whose hardness surpasses that of any armor material.
Source: aniplexusa.com</description>
<picture>135202.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54978" type="appears in" update="2013-04-13">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Taichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135231.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31810" picture="223818.jpg">Takanaka Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55489" type="appears in" update="2013-08-08">
<rating votes="2">2.26</rating>
<name>Figaro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141144.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55812" type="appears in" update="2013-08-08">
<rating votes="6">1.53</rating>
<name>ARUS Daitouryou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141140.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2339" picture="151715.jpg">Taketora</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55814" type="appears in" update="2013-08-08">
<rating votes="4">2.57</rating>
<name>Amadeus K Dorssia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141143.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56202" type="appears in" update="2013-05-26">
<rating votes="11">2.86</rating>
<name>Kitagawa Iori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>137135.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27357" picture="75009.jpg">Yasuno Kiyono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56203" type="appears in" update="2013-05-26">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Kishi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>137134.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2672" picture="188511.jpg">Endou Daichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56518" type="appears in" update="2013-06-01">
<rating votes="4">5.07</rating>
<name>Yamamoto Lily</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>137553.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33" picture="133462.jpg">Kimura Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56519" type="appears in" update="2013-06-01">
<rating votes="4">5.07</rating>
<name>Watari Eri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>137552.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="359" picture="65537.jpg">Sanada Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56520" type="appears in" update="2013-08-08">
<rating votes="9">6.31</rating>
<name>Lieselotte</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141142.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56811" type="appears in" update="2013-06-08">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Manninger</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>137973.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11054" picture="39865.jpg">Sakamoto Kunpei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56812" type="appears in" update="2013-06-08">
<rating votes="2">5.07</rating>
<name>Fukukan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>137974.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6012" picture="228332.jpg">Hirose Yuuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56893" type="appears in" update="2013-06-08">
<rating votes="1">2.36</rating>
<name>JIOR</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>138065.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="56894" type="appears in" update="2013-06-08">
<name>Kan Taiseiyou Gasshuukoku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>138066.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="56895" type="appears in" update="2013-06-08">
<name>Dorssia Gunji Meiyaku Renpou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>138067.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="57343" type="appears in" update="2013-06-22">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Derius</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138840.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57344" type="appears in" update="2013-06-22">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Sashinami Ryuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138841.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="371" picture="166173.jpg">Kuroda Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57345" type="appears in" update="2013-06-22">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Banshou Juuto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138843.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31810" picture="223818.jpg">Takanaka Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57549" type="appears in" update="2013-08-09">
<rating votes="12">6.75</rating>
<name>Pino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141187.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57550" type="appears in" update="2013-08-08">
<rating votes="4">4.76</rating>
<name>Prue</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141141.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="586" picture="171556.jpg">Yonaga Tsubasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58694" type="appears in" update="2013-08-09">
<rating votes="2">4.13</rating>
<name>Onai Youhei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60968.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="17705" picture="188509.jpg">Asari Ryouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58695" type="appears in" update="2013-08-09">
<rating votes="4">5.07</rating>
<name>Akashi Midori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60967.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="10759" picture="38748.jpg">Anzai Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58696" type="appears in" update="2013-08-09">
<rating votes="2">4.13</rating>
<name>Uesugi Seiya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60966.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="33630" picture="228524.jpg">Susaki Shigeyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58697" type="appears in" update="2013-08-09">
<rating votes="2">4.13</rating>
<name>Miyamachi Tooru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60965.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="33595" picture="223803.jpg">Masumoto Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="147563" update="2018-03-03">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 15s Type A</title>
</episode>
<episode id="149585" update="2018-10-27">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-04-12</airdate>
<rating votes="14">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">世界を曝く</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Revolutionary Transfer Student</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Des lycéens révolutionnaires</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sekai o Abaku</title>
<summary>True Calendar (T.C.) 71 - A new age where 70% of the human population lives in space. Haruto Tokishima lived an ordinary life as a high school student in the division known as “Module 77”—until the Dorssian military begins their sudden invasion!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622477</identifier>
<identifier>valvrave-the-liberator</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="149599" update="2014-05-11">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-04-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="149600" update="2018-10-27">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-03</airdate>
<rating votes="7">2.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人質はヴァルヴレイヴ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hostage Is Valvrave</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Valvrave prisonnier</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitojichi wa Valvrave</title>
<summary>L-elf tells Haruto to make a pact with him. ARUS kidnap Haruto and attempt to escape without saving the students of Sakimori. Shoko imparts the plans of ARUS to the student council. Not willing to depend on others, Sakimori students declare independence.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622483</identifier>
<identifier>valvrave-the-liberator</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="149601" update="2018-10-27">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-04-26</airdate>
<rating votes="8">2.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エルエルフの予言</title>
<title xml:lang="en">L-elf`s Prophesy</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La prédiction de L-elf</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">L-elf no Yogen</title>
<summary>L-elf is held in interrogation but he manages to escape. Haruto makes a triumphant return and is considered a hero by the masses for taking on the Dorssian military. Haruto has a meeting with Senator Figaro.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622481</identifier>
<identifier>valvrave-the-liberator</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="149602" update="2018-10-27">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-04-19</airdate>
<rating votes="9">4.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">666を超えて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beyond 666</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Au-delà de 666</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">666 o Koete</title>
<summary>Enraged by his loss, Haruto uses the Valvrave to seek vengenance against the Dorssian Military.  But an equally furious A-drie stands up against the attack and quickly overwhelms the inexperienced fighter.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622479</identifier>
<identifier>valvrave-the-liberator</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="149745" update="2015-07-29">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150064" update="2018-10-27">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-24</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">瓦礫の下のハルト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Haruto Under the Rubble</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Haruto sous les décombres</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gareki no Shita no Haruto</title>
<summary>L`elf hands Shoko papers which include a plan for the military development and territorial expansion of JIOR. A-drei, Q-vier and H-neun interfere and Rukino tries to stop them. Haruto possesses L`elf to use his Valvrave. Will he be able to help Rukino?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622489</identifier>
<identifier>valvrave-the-liberator</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150065" update="2018-10-27">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-17</airdate>
<rating votes="8">2.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サキ・カムバック</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Saki, Come Back!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le retour de Saki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saki Comeback</title>
<summary>Saki goes inside the Valvrave in hopes of becoming a famous singer. She bites Haruto on the neck and then pretends to be his little sister. Dorssia forces start an attack despite Shoko`s threat, while Saki pilots a female robot, which she named Carmilla.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622487</identifier>
<identifier>valvrave-the-liberator</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150066" update="2018-10-27">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-10</airdate>
<rating votes="8">1.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">歌う咲森学園</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Singing Sakimori Academy</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le lycée Sakimori chante</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Utau Sakimori Gakuen</title>
<summary>Since Shoko declared independence, the students of Sakimori have been leading a carefree lifestyle. All of a sudden, the power goes out. Finally, the students manage to turn the power back on, and they broadcast a video of themselves singing a song.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622485</identifier>
<identifier>valvrave-the-liberator</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150704" update="2018-10-27">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-21</airdate>
<rating votes="7">2.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">軍事法廷第54号</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Military Tribunal #54</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le tribunal militaire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gunji Houtei Dai 54-gou</title>
<summary>Module 77 is headed to the Moon while the students are appointed as cabinet ministers. Akira finally speaks to Shoko and it is revealed that she is Satomi`s sister. Module 77 is attacked by the Dorssians and Shoko`s father is held hostage by Wartenberg.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622497</identifier>
<identifier>valvrave-the-liberator</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150705" update="2018-10-27">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-14</airdate>
<rating votes="8">2.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋の選挙公約</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Campaign Promise of Love</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le programme électoral de l`amour</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi no Senkyo Kouyaku</title>
<summary>Not feeling fully qualified for her position, the student teacher Rion Nanami proposes that JIOR should hold an election for a Prime Minister. Shoko decides to run in the election. In the meantime, the interval between Haruto`s attacks is getting shorter.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622495</identifier>
<identifier>valvrave-the-liberator</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150706" update="2018-10-27">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-07</airdate>
<rating votes="9">1.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">犬と雷</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dogs and Thunder</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Chien et tonnerre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inu to Kaminari</title>
<summary>Module 77 is headed to the Moon and the students have begun military drills. Thunder has sworn revenge but he is put in solitary confinement. Thunder and Inuzuka decide to pilot their own Valvraves and help Haruto and Saki battle against the Dorssians.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622493</identifier>
<identifier>valvrave-the-liberator</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150707" update="2018-10-27">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-31</airdate>
<rating votes="8">3.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">光の王女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Princess of Light</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La princesse de lumière</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hikari no Oujo</title>
<summary>Students of Sakimori are mourning for Aina. L-elf is held prisoner by the students, and he recalls the time he first met Lieselotte. Sakimori is attacked by the Dorssians. Haruto and Saki go out to battle against them, trusting L-elf`s tactical advices.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622491</identifier>
<identifier>valvrave-the-liberator</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150724" update="2015-07-29">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-05-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150788" update="2015-07-28">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-05-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151124" update="2015-07-29">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-06-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151213" update="2015-07-29">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-06-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151214" update="2015-07-29">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-05-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151221" update="2018-10-27">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-28</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">起動する異端者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rise of the Heretic</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La montée de l`hérétique</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kidou Suru Itansha</title>
<summary>Haruto proposes to Saki, since he feels guilty about what happened between them. The school is under Dorssian attack. Haruto asks L-elf to drive the Dorrsians out. Shoko attempts to rescue Akira who refuses to go outside. Cain confronts L-elf.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622499</identifier>
<identifier>valvrave-the-liberator</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="151345" update="2015-07-29">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-06-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152808" update="2013-08-28">
<epno type="4">T11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 80s</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152809" update="2013-08-28">
<epno type="4">T10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 60s</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>644267</identifier>
<identifier>valvrave-the-liberator</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="152810" update="2013-08-28">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 40s Type B</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152811" update="2013-08-28">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 40s Type A</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152812" update="2013-08-28">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 15s Type B</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152813" update="2013-08-28">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 15s Type A</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152814" update="2013-08-28">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 30s Type B</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152815" update="2013-08-28">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 30s Type A</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152816" update="2013-08-28">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 15s Type C</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152817" update="2018-03-03">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 15s Type B</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170316" update="2015-07-29">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-06-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170317" update="2015-07-29">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-11-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1d</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
